<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dems blast Bezos space trip, demand he pay 'fair share' of taxes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/21/dems-blast-jeff-bezos-space-trip-demand-he-pay-more-taxes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin founder Jeff Bezos is being slammed for his “despicable” comments following his space flight Tuesday, in which he thanked Amazon employees and customers for financing his tr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol attack committee chair vows to investigate Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jul/21/capitol-attack-committee-chair-bennie-thompson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennie Thompson tells Guardian he will pursue wide-ranging inquiry to uncover root causes of January 6 attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jews behind pandemic' chanted at anti-vaccine protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/jews-are-behind-the-pandemic-chanted-at-anti-vaccine-protest-in-poland-674491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Every Pole can see today that behind the ‘plandemic’ are the Jews,' the crowd chanted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Ratings of Black-White Relations New Low...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/352457/ratings-black-white-relations-new-low.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. adults' positive ratings of relations between Black and White Americans are at their lowest point in more than two decades of measurement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France requires pass for Eiffel Tower, tourist venues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-europe-travel-france-89feee0a6be1e9962e989a6cc86c8169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Visitors now need a special COVID pass to ride up the Eiffel Tower or visit French museums or movie theaters, the first step in a new campaign against what the government calls a “stratospheric” rise in delta variant infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KODAK Deletes Post by Photographer Who Called Xinjiang 'Orwellian Dystopia'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/21/kodak-deletes-post-by-photographer-who-called-xinjiang-an-orwellian-dystopia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American company Eastman Kodak has deleted an Instagram post featuring images of Xinjiang, a western Chinese region where the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seemingly safe Republican incumbents under attack from right-wing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-religion-government-and-politics-el-paso-texas-mass-shooting-election-2020-4f3eaae4604492fea044435f8d8351ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Republican U.S. Sen. James Lankford would seem to have all the conservative credentials he'd need to coast to reelection in deep-red Oklahoma. A devout Baptist, Lankford was the director of the nation’s largest Christian youth camp for more than a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive man disguises self as wife in order to fly...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/indonesia-citilink-niqab-man-covid-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indonesian man is reportedly facing arrest after wearing a niqab in order to board a flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: World's best airlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/airline-ratings-worlds-best-airlines-2021/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AirlineRatings.com has revealed its annual round-up of the best airlines and last year's winner Air New Zealand is this year's No. 2. Find out which airline got the top spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Macron Independent Looking to Topple France's President...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/the-dark-horse-trying-to-put-france-s-macron-on-the-back-foot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dark Horse Trying to Put France’s Macron on the Back Foot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unscripted remarks start to haunt Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/564002-unscripted-remarks-start-to-haunt-president-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has been more freewheeling with his remarks in the last few weeks, leading to slip-ups the White House has had to clean up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia, under lockdown, sees jump in COVID-19 cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210721005252-1dhiy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Australia, under lockdown, sees jump in COVID-19 cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot Fitness Trend: Blood Flow Restriction...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/21/a-hot-fitness-trend-among-olympians-blood-flow-restriction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every four years, the Summer Olympics shows the world the latest training or recovery method the greatest athletes have taken</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ally Barrack jailed on charges of acting as agent of foreign govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/thomas-barrack-trump-s-inaugural-committee-chair-arrested-federal-charges-n1274533</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barrack, a longtime friend of Trump, is also charged with obstruction of justice and making multiple false statements to federal law enforcement agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More California areas urge masks indoors as Delta rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/56-25-of-californians-are-being-asked-to-wear-masks-indoors-again-as-delta-variant-rages/ar-AAMmRXE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six more California counties are urging masks in indoor public spaces amid upticks in coronavirus cases and circulation of the Delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough cases rattle Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/breakthrough-covid-19-cases-rattle-capitol-hill/article_750a5882-5341-5464-b63f-2e45761bbb00.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Democratic leaders aren’t ruling out reimposing mask requirements for the House now that the highly contagious delta variant has been detected in the Capitol complex and infection rates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Catholic Church official resigns over report linking him to gay bars, GRINDR...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-catholic-church-official-resigns-misconduct-claim-fed05d24-1e67-435c-bdcb-1bf729d6218b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Catholic outlet used phone data to track Monsignor Jeffrey Burrill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lambda found in Texas hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/lambda-covid-variant-texas-hospital-e2234821-3645-469f-af59-186ad8f8206d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the Texas hospital system's first known case of the "variant of interest."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden stuns USA in Olympic women's soccer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sweden-stuns-us-3-0-103707590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stina Blackstenius scored a pair of goals and Sweden once again stunned the United States at the Olympics with a 3-0 victory Wednesday in the women's soccer tournament. The Americans, ranked No. 1 in the world and the favorites to win gold in Tokyo, were riding a 44-match unbeaten streak heading into the match. The Swedes bounced the Americans from the 2016 Rio de Janeiro Games in the quarterfinals, the earliest U.S. Olympic exit ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor warns restrictions could return...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chicago-expands-travel-advisory-again-225700216.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot sounded the alarm on the continuing COVID-19 pandemic Tuesday, saying the city has to quash recent case increases or face the prospect of her reinstating public health restrictions to get the situation under control. “All across the United States there have been increases in COVID-19 cases, including in central and southern Illinois, and right here in Chicago,” ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On FOXNEWS, Vaccination Pleas Intensify, but Skepticism Persists...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/20/on-fox-news-vaccination-pleas-intensify-but-skepticism-persists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The morning anchor’s plea was urgent and framed in the starkest of terms: Get the Covid-19 vaccine, or you could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Trolls Trump, MAGA With White House Speech...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/07/20/tom-brady-cracks-election-joke-sleepy-tom-nickname-on-president-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady stepped to the podium at the South Lawn of the White House on Tuesday, and the reigning Super Bowl MVP brought some jokes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life expectancy biggest drop since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-coronavirus-pandemic-fac0863b8c252d21d6f6a22a2e3eab86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. life expectancy fell by a year and a half in 2020, the largest one-year decline since World War II, public health officials said Wednesday. The decrease for both Black Americans and Hispanic Americans was even worse: three years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies claim there's labor shortage. Their solution? Prisoners...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jul/20/companies-claim-theres-a-labor-shortage-their-solution-prisoners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worker advocates say prison labor programs exploit workers with few options</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modi accused of treason over India disclosures...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2021/jul/19/modi-accused-treason-opposition-india-spyware-disclosures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian prime minister under fire after phone numbers of political rivals appear in data leak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX moving into video games as growth slows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-technology-coronavirus-pandemic-games-video-games-2482bd5c5aa65b551da95f602d6311f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN RAMON, Calif. (AP) — Netflix reported its worst slowdown in subscriber growth in eight years as people emerged from their pandemic cocoons. But it has an answer to that: Video games. On Tuesday, the streaming giant announced plans to begin adding video games to its existing subscription plans at no extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm Bank Holds Contest to Find Out Who Has Best...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epnqga/china-sperm-bank-donation-contest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those with exceptional sperm will be invited to be donors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Mormon temple will open to public for first time in nearly 50 years...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/maryland/2021/07/dcs-mormon-temple-will-open-to-public-for-first-time-in-nearly-50-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in nearly 50 years, the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints is inviting the public to enter their D.C. temple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli lab: Existing drugs could stop Covid 100%...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israeli-lab-some-existing-drugs-could-stop-covid-at-almost-100-percent-674426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A research team found 18 drugs that they felt could be effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In propaganda video, China threatens to nuke Japan...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/in-propaganda-video-china-threatens-to-nuke-japan-after-japan-vows-to-defend-taiwan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (SBG) &amp;mdash; In a now-deleted propaganda video, China threatened to nuke Japan following comments made by Japanese leaders vowing to defend Taiwan from Chinese invasion. The nearly six-minute video, which was posted to the Chinese Communist Party-sanctioned channel Xigua, featured images and videos of Chinese war machines, such as tanks and fighter jets, edited into pictures of a devastated 1940s Japan following the World War II U. S. nuclear strikes on Hiroshima and Nagasaki.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys Leader Pleads Guilty To Burning BLM Banner...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/07/20/proud-boys-leader-pleads-guilty-burning-black-lives-matter-banne.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Henry Tarrio admitted to partaking in two crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Extradicted To LA; Faces 140 Years If Guilty On Rape Charges...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/harvey-weinstein-extradition-los-angeles-rape-charges-1234796616/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of delays, Harvey Weinstein is finally on his way to Los Angeles to face multiple rape charges. Facing up to a 140 years behind bars if found guilty in the California courts, the alrea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE foe named DOJ antitrust chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/20/biden-picks-doj-antitrust-chief-500310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The selection adds to the perils for tech industry giants like Google, Facebook and Amazon, as progressives clamor for aggressive enforcement of laws against anti-competitive abuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sees cases surge 224% in last 3 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9806537/US-sees-cases-surge-224-three-weeks-Delta-variant-makes-83-new-infections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. recorded 52,111 new COVID-19 cases on Monday with a seven-day rolling average of 34,682, representing a 224% increase from the 10,678 average recorded three weeks ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin hails Russia air power as new fighter goes on view...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-europe-business-russia-14f649c0a20dfca9136bdf07fddb253b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Alabama Freshman QB Already Offered 'Almost Seven Figure' Deals...</title>
      <link>https://247sports.com/Article/Alabama-Crimson-Tide-football-Nick-Saban-Bryce-Young-name-image-likeness-deal-seven-figures-168001730/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;247sports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ridiculed for 'Tone-Deaf' Victory Lap Thanking Workers, Shoppers...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jeff-bezos-ridiculed-for-tone-deaf-victory-lap-thanking-amazon-workers-and-shoppers-you-guys-paid-for-all-this/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos was bashed on social media in response to "tone-deaf" commentary that was made during a press conference Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phones of Macron, French ministers targeted in Pegasus affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210720-phones-of-macron-and-some-french-ministers-targeted-by-morocco-in-pegasus-affair-le-monde</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cell phones of French President Emmanuel Macron and 15 members of the French government may have been among potential targets in 2019 of surveillance by spyware made by the Israel-based NSO Group…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA agent arrested for participating in Jan. 6 Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/dea-agent-arrested-for-participating-in-jan-6-capitol-riot-by-trump-supporters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Drug Enforcement Administration agent has been arrested for allegedly participating in the Jan. 6 Capitol riot by supporters of then-President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfside collapse response dog now needs help...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/20/surfside-condos-response-dog-teddy-unable-to-walk-needs-help/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m scared of him not being able to walk again,” owner Sophia Barrett said of the 6-year-old dog, who may have a herniated disc and torn knee ligaments after three weeks of non-stop caregiving.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans cop sues, claims colleagues called him 'it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trans-officer-sues-port-authority-claims-colleague-called-him-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transgender police officer with the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey sued the agency over allegations he was referred to in a discriminatory way as "it" and "transvestite" by colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT OR FLIGHT:   Cabin crew being taught aggressive moves to take down unruly passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3316869/flight-attendant-fight-training-planes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLIGHT attendants are being taught fighting skills including ear slapping, eye poking and groin kicks to defend themselves against unruly passengers. Disruptive incidents on flights have risen in r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bride dislocates knee during first dance with groom...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wedding-nightmare-local-bride-dislocates-knee-during-first-dance-with-groom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania couple is sharing their story and laughing off a wedding nightmare after the bride seriously injured her knee as they danced at their wedding reception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-year-old robbed in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/brooklyn-man-arrested-for-stealing-scooter-from-7-year-old</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 59-year-old Brooklyn man faces robbery charges after allegedly stealing an electric scooter from a 7-year-old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House official, Pelosi aide test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/white-house-pelosi-covid-positive-41dd58f1-f4a3-4111-a6ae-492810f79703.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pelosi staffer helped usher a delegation of Texas Democrats around the Capitol last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Capsule Lands Back in TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3274747/jeff-bezos-space-flight-watch-live-blue-origin-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON founder Jeff Bezos has landed safely after blasting into space on board a rocket ship built by his company Blue Origin. Bezos and his brother lifted off at 9.10am ET (2.10pm UK time) on boar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRISON THREAT!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/fauci-rebukes-rand-paul-for-threatening-him-with-prison-in-fiery-clash-you-do-not-know-what-you-are-talking-about/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci faced off with Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) during a Tuesday Senate hearing that witnessed Paul threatening Fauci with imprisonment for "lying" to Congress — over Fauci's dismayed protestations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Businesses Requiring Proof Of Vax Upon Entry...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/07/19/some-sacramento-businesses-require-proof-of-vaccination-upon-entry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No proof of vaccine, no entry without a mask. It’s a new policy some Sacramento businesses are adopting for safety reasons as concern over the Delta variant increases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police officer calls for backup after 'being pursued by a drone'...</title>
      <link>https://notthebee.com/article/police-officer-calls-for-backup-after-being-pursued-by-drone-which-was-actually-just-jupiter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;notthebee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh man, this story can't be real!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Americans Growing Increasingly Desensitized To Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-risk-taking-desensitized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that despite the death toll continuing to increase, people are generally showing less concern about COVID-related news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul throwdown with Fauci...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/if-anybody-is-lying-here-senator-it-is-you-fauci-tells-sen-paul-in-heated-exchange-at-senate-hearing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Will Include 'Black National Anthem' During Pregame Ceremonies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/sports/2021/07/16/nfl-black-national-anthem-pregame-ceremonies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Lift Every Voice and Sing” will be performed before every game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein extradited to California; Faces more sex assault charges...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/20/harvey-weinstein-extradited-to-face-california-sex-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein was being extradited to California on Tuesday to face more sex-assault charges there, New York prison officials told The Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EGO TRIP'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/19/bezos-flight-is-an-ego-trip-but-it-sets-the-stage-for-much-more/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos is scheduled to take off for outer space Tuesday morning. Showing faith in his engineers, he will ride the first passenger flight of his space company Blue Origin’s New Shepard rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France broadens use of health pass...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210719183629-zlkr2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health pass will be required in venues including cinemas, bars, restaurants, hospitals and long-distance train and planes, a decision that led to protests at the weekend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA Strangest Encounters With Unidentified Aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41573/the-strangest-encounters-with-unidentified-aircraft-weve-found-in-the-faas-huge-database</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We found over 50 highly unusual incidents with our new FAA data mapping tool. And yes, there even are a few flying 'disks' and 'cylinders' in there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans model makes history: 'If don't like it, go somewhere else'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trans-model-makes-sports-illustrated-swimsuit-cover-history-e2-80-98if-you-don-e2-80-99t-like-it-you-can-go-somewhere-else-e2-80-99/ar-AAMlQaJ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This moment heals a lot of pain in the world. We deserve this moment,” Bloom said on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 'BLACK WIDOW' ticket buying suddenly drying up, growing questions for DISNEY about what did it in...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/with-black-widow-ticket-buying-suddenly-drying-up-growing-questions-for-disney-s-marvel-about-what-did-it-in/ar-AAMmdap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Marvel fans are tiring of the franchise, it would imperil the most lucrative movie universe of all time at precisely the post-pandemic moment movie theaters need it most and throw Marvel’s larger financial future into question along with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinzinger charts path from Illinois to new political battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/adam-kinzinger-charts-path-from-illinois-to-new-political-battlefield/article_60a99450-2aa3-53fa-99a5-d9ce8685ab23.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORRIS, Ill. — U.S. Rep. Adam Kinzinger, an Air Force veteran, is again on the frontlines. But it’s a different battlefield for the northern Illinois Republican. This one’s closer to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tiny little step' toward plan to build road to space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/jeff-bezos-says-this-is-a-tiny-little-step-toward-blue-origins-plan-to-build-a-road-to-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos said Blue Origin's space tourism venture is one step toward the company's mission of building a road to space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snakes look like monsters as fungal disease spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article252866068.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The snakes turn crusty with milky eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Brady, BUCS Honored At White House...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/07/20/tom-brady-in-attendance-as-buccaneers-make-white-house-visit-with-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Buccaneers made their trip to the White House on Tuesday. Tom Brady was in attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE to Postpone Return to Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/apple-reportedly-delay-employees-return-to-office-093544574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is reportedly delaying its return-to-office deadline by about a month due to a resurgence in COVID-19 cases..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems lay out vision for Civilian Climate Corps...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/equilibrium-sustainability/563848-dozens-of-democrats-lay-out-vision-for-civilian-climate-corps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of more than 80 House and Senate Democrats on Tuesday laid out their vision for a climate jobs program called the Civilian Climate Corps that is expected to be part of a sweeping $3.5 trillion budget reconci</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight just 11 mins. Reverberations will last much longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/07/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-successful-flight/619484/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flight was just 11 minutes. The reverberations for the world’s richest man will last much longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW MILESTONE</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/jeff-bezos-worlds-richest-man-set-inaugural-space-voyage-2021-07-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos, the world's richest man, and three crewmates soared high above the Texas desert aboard his space venture Blue Origin's New Shepard launch vehicle on Tuesday and returned safely to Earth, a historic suborbital flight that helps to inaugurate a new era of private commercial space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Capsule Lands in West Texas After Trip to Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/jeff-bezos-space-capsule-lands-in-west-texas-after-flight-to-space/ar-AAMmgC1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. founder Jeff Bezos and three others landed after Blue Origin’s first flight to space with passengers aboard, a key milestone in the company’s effort to make space tourism viable.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
