<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FAA fines passenger $27,500 for hitting flight attendant over mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/faa-seeks-27500-fine-from-passenger-for-hitting-flight-attendant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials are seeking a $27,500 civil penalty against an airline passenger who allegedly struck a flight attendant who asked the passenger and a companion to leave the plane after a dispute over wearing a face mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF GLOBAL DIGITAL TAX</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-drops-key-obstacle-global-173148199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen told her G20 colleagues Friday that Washington is dropping a push for a controversial provision in a global digital tax, opening the door to a likely agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For crematorium worker, mounting toll is measured in ashes and anguish...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crematorium-worker-covid-19s-mounting-153234671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never experiencing the relief of seeing COVID patients recover takes it toll on crematorium workers. One worries he'll develop a 'hard heart, a cold heart.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of social media: Warning for dog owners as thefts rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/feb/26/beware-social-media-warning-uk-dog-owners-thefts-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say people should be wary of posting pictures of pets online that could reveal their location</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overshadowed by ethics controversy, lack of diversity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/feb/26/golden-globes-ethics-controversy-criticism-lack-diversity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carey Mulligan and Chadwick Boseman are predicted to win big, but ceremony to air following damning investigation into voting membership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE investigators used private utility database covering millions to pursue violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/ICE-investigators-used-a-private-utility-database-15982865.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers have tapped a private database...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As USPS delays persist, bills, paychecks and medications are getting stuck in mail...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/As-USPS-delays-persist-bills-paychecks-and-15983524.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Mark Currie of Virginia had three checks snagged in postal delays in three...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE NATION Boss Predicts Music Festivals Could Be Back by Summer!</title>
      <link>https://www.spin.com/2021/02/live-nation-ceo-michael-rapino-says-largescale-u-s-concerts-could-start-in-midsummer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At almost full capacity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechs confined to their districts as infections soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/czech-republic-coronavirus-new-state-of-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vote will mean tougher restrictions as country battles sharp rise in coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid restrictions ease in Mexico's most popular tourist cities ahead of spring break season...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Coronavirus-restrictions-ease-in-some-of-Mexico-s-15982876.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican state of Quintana Roo is softening its coronavirus restrictions following a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says gave only few mins warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/26/russia-ally-syria-fumes-us-airstrike-against-milit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia, a key military ally of the government of Syrian President Bashar Assad, on Friday sharply condemned the U.S. airstrike targeting an Iran-allied Iraqi militia group operating in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Branson's Space Tourism Dream Crashing?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/02/virgin-galactic-crashing-uk-launch-partner-reject-space-tourism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic’s flight schedule is pushed back to 2022 due to a recent test failure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE PREPARES ORDER FOR AIRPORT EBOLA SCREENINGS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-white-house-preparing-order-for-enhanced-airport-screenings-for-ebola-203354978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is moving forward with plans to screen airline passengers from two African countries arriving in the U.S. for Ebola, which will involve sending them to one of about a half dozen designated airports, Yahoo News has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  GOLDEN GLOBES Aim To Go More Intimate Than Ever For Sunday's Star-Studded Show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globes-behind-the-scenes-tina-fey-amy-poehler-hfpa-dcp-sarah-paulson-sandra-oh-tracy-morgan-barry-adelman-1234702044/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: In this time of a global pandemic, the 78th annual Golden Globes intend to spotlight the foreign in Hollywood Foreign Press Association for Sunday’s Tina Fey and Amy Poehler bicoastal ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  Strikes in Syria sent warning to Iran...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-syria-airstrike-kills-1-34b4d7ac56fa8d0d2db8dc2ec8e921d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said Friday that Iran should view his decision to authorize U.S. airstrikes in Syria as a warning that it can expect consequences for its support of militia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Girl, 12, busted for selling stun guns to middle school classmates...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/k-12/stun-gun-salesgirl-389670</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 26--A 12-year-old Florida girl is facing criminal charges after she admitted to selling stun guns to classmates, police report. According to investigators, a staff member at Coleman Middle S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. diplomat rails against Jews...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/26/diplomat-online-activity-blood-and-faith-471755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fritz Berggren’s hundreds of blog posts, videos and podcasts date back several years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Suspends Advanced Learning Classes Citing Racial Inequities...</title>
      <link>https://www.wgbh.org/news/education/2021/02/26/citing-racial-inequities-boston-public-schools-suspend-advanced-learning-classes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wgbh.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An analysis of the program found that more than 70 percent of students enrolled in the program were white and Asian, even though nearly 80 percent of all Boston public school students are Hispanic and Black.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA panel endorses J&amp;J shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/26/fda-johnson-johnson-vaccine-advantages-471766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vaccine, which is given as a single dose and is easy to ship, appeals to officials struggling to vaccinate hard-to-reach or skeptical populations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police chief warns of threat during Biden speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/capitol-law-enforcement-heads-detail-intelligence-failures-leading-jan-6-n1258829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acting chief said members of militia groups want to "kill as many members as possible" in an attack during Biden's coming address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Yang rushes to aid of photographer during assault...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/26/andrew-yang-rushes-to-help-photographer-during-assault-on-si-ferry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayoral candidate Andrew Yang rushed to the aid of a news photographer who was attacked Friday on the Staten Island Ferry. Getty photojournalist Spencer Platt told The Post he was part of a small m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House and press at odds over plan to charge reporters for testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/White-House-and-press-are-at-odds-over-plan-to-15983010.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters who cover the White House may soon be paying what amounts to an admission fee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden doesn't penalize crown prince despite promise to punish...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/26/politics/biden-mohammed-bin-salman-jamal-khashoggi/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite promising to punish senior Saudi leaders while on the campaign trail, President Joe Biden declined to apply sanctions to the one the US intelligence community determined is responsible for the death of journalist Jamal Khashoggi: Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions About Legality, Precedent...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-02-26/pentagon-stands-by-syria-strikes-despite-questions-about-legality-precedent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘It was very much a defensive operation,’ Pentagon spokesman John Kirby said of the unilateral strike in Syria against pro-Iran targets in retaliation for deadly rocket attacks in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ man admits neo-Nazi group's 'Operation Kristallnacht' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/operation-kristallnacht-richard-tobin-synagogue-vandalism-rinaldo-nazarro-the-base-20210226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Tobin, of Brooklawn, also told FBI agents he recently sat in the parking lot of the Menlo Park Mall in Middlesex County with a machete willing himself to 'let loose' on Black shoppers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Stands By USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210226182856-v7d61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SYRIA/STRIKE-FRANCE (CORRECTED, URGENT):CORRECTED-France says stands by U.S. air strikes against Iran-backed militias in syria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bust of Queen beheaded in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/have-you-seen-her-majestys-head-bust-of-the-queen-desecrated-in-victoria-b-c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PET DETECTIVES STUMPED...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/why-lady-gaga-s-dognapping-has-stumped-pet-detectives/ar-BB1e3nca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamie Katz has seen a lot in her seven years as a pet detective. She had one case of a man who was walking his dog at 5 a.m. when “a car pulled up and just, like, four to five people got out and started beating the hell out of him.” The assailants kicked the dog during the attack, prompting it to run away. In another case, a client had their French Bulldog stolen from its crate in their home, along with $10,000 in cash. But even she was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia reserves 'right to retaliate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/02/26/us-airstrike-first-under-biden-kills-iran-backed-militiaman-militia-reserves-right-to-retaliate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Air Force F-15E aircraft launched seven precision guided munitions at facilities used by Iran-backed militias near Boukamal, on the Syrian side of the Iraq border, along the Euphrates River.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinyl sales beat CDs -- for first time since '86...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/vinyl-record-sales-increased-almost-30-in-2020-riaa-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Streaming expectedly continued to grow throughout the pandemic while downloads and CD sales continued to decline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Keeping Huge, Secretive DNA Database in Orange County...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4ade3g/why-are-prosecutors-keeping-a-huge-secretive-dna-database-in-orange-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The fact that you are giving up your DNA for a relatively smaller misdemeanor crime—forever—is pretty scary, when you think about it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 convicted in '93 World Trade Center bombing have had sentences cut...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bombings-619788d2b7b5806c34463e4dd6854774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Decades after going to prison, some of the men responsible for the World Trade Center bombing that killed six people 28 years ago Friday are still trying to whittle down their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ta-Nehisi Coates to write new 'SUPERMAN' film...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ta-nehisi-coates-write-new-superman-film-b4e8f60d4e4157d7d44c3e26967d89f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ta-Nehisi Coates, the acclaimed essayist and novelist who expanded the world of Wakanda for Marvel comics, will write the script for a new “Superman” film from Warner...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden preparing another tent facility to cope with border influx...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Biden-administration-preparing-another-tent-15982530.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - U.S. border officials are preparing to open another tent facility in Del...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.odni.gov/files/ODNI/documents/assessments/Assessment-Saudi-Gov-Role-in-JK-Death-20210226.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.odni.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  U.S. intel concludes MBS approved Khashoggi killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/26/us-intelligence-concludes-saudi-crown-prince-mohammed-bin-salman-approved-killing-of-journalist-jamal-khashoggi-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINE PASSPORTS BEGIN IN ISRAEL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-vaccination-passports-7a8ce11ce37c309d97969ab71df26e62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Violet light bathed the club stage as 300 people, masked and socially distanced, erupted in gentle applause. For the first time since the pandemic began, Israeli musician...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach moving away from palm trees to create more shade...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/due-to-climate-change-miami-beach-moving-away-from-palm-trees-to-create-more-shade/ar-BB1e2Cif?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Whether swaying in the background of a Super Bowl glamour shot or printed on Art Deco-themed postcards, palm trees are synonymous with the sun-and-fun allure of Miami Beach. In a city with nearly 50,000 trees, more than half have fronds. But because of rising temperatures, that’s about to change. To help address the consequences of climate change, city leaders will cut back on the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID cases, deaths starting to RISE again?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-cases-deaths-starting-124906554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two weeks, COVID-19 cases and deaths have dropped steadily from the alarmingly high peak of America's third wave of the pandemic. Vaccination rates are rising, new vaccines and millions more doses of approved ones are coming online soon, and deaths have dropped dramatically in places where significant numbers of people have been inoculated, especially nursing homes. But "this is not a time to relax," President Biden said Thursday as he celebrated the country's 50 million's vaccination. "We must keep washing our hands, stay socially distanced, and for God's sake — for God's sake — wear a mask." It turns out, a fourth wave of the pandemic already appears to be building. But the news is not all so encouraging. Most worrisome, the number of new cases has stopped declining over the past week. It's true in the U.S.: pic.twitter.com/CmOUFzLgDb — David Leonhardt (@DLeonhardt) February 25, 2021 Cases have leveled out worldwide, too. "The most likely explanation is the more contagious variants of the virus, like the B.1.1.7 variant, which was first detected in Britain," David Leonhardt writes at The New York Times. Business Insider's Jim Edwards points out that the uptick in cases and deaths could be statistical noise, but notes that worrisome new variants have also popped up in California and New York. Big question: Are the new fast-moving variants (UK, CA, and NY) moving faster than the vaccines? — Jim Edwards (@Jim_Edwards) February 26, 2021 "Taking into account the counterbalancing rises in both vaccinations and variants, along with the high likelihood that people will stop taking precautions, a fourth wave is highly likely this spring," Apoorva Mandavilli reports at the Times, citing a majority of 21 experts interviewed on the pandemic. "But they stressed that it is not an inevitable surge, if government officials and individuals maintain precautions for a few more weeks," and "COVID-19 deaths will most likely never rise quite as precipitously as in the past." "The good news," Mandavilli writes, is that "despite the uncertainties, the experts predict that the last surge will subside in the United States sometime in the early summer. If the Biden administration can keep its promise to immunize every American adult by the end of the summer, the variants should be no match for the vaccines. ... For now, every one of us can help by continuing to be careful for just a few more months, until the curve permanently flattens." More stories from theweek.comJournalist Tim O'Brien, who's seen Trump's taxes, thinks Trump's accountant will now flip in D.A. inquiryHusband of Hitler-quoting GOP congresswoman parked his militia-stickered truck outside Capitol Jan. 6Josh Hawley, Senator No</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee bill mandating school athletes align with their sex at birth heads to state's House...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/tennessee-final-votes-transgender-athlete-bill-birth-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tennessee bill that limits transgender participation in school sports is headed to the state's House after clearing an initial committee hurdle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Golden Calf' Wheeled Into Gathering...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2412084/donald-trump-cpac-gold-statue-comeback-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HUGE gold statue of Donald Trump holding a star wand delighted the CPAC crowds ahead of the former president’s comeback speech. The massive effigy was seen being rolled into the Conservativ…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERUPTING VOLCANO ATTRACTS RAINBOWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article249538423.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures above the lava lake are between 200 and 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK's News Blockade Shows How Tech Giants are Swallowing the Web...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/02/facebooks-news-blockade-australia-shows-how-tech-giants-are-swallowing-web/172292/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internet in 2021 is not the same open public sphere that Tim Berners-Lee envisioned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry blames 'toxic' British media for Royal split...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/prince-harry-says-toxic-british-media-drove-him-meghan-royal-n1258922</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with fellow Brit and TV host James Corden, Harry discussed what the future holds for his family after the couple finalized their royal exit last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elementary pupil put in closet to isolate after showing symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/symptomatic-south-carolina-elementary-student-who-visited-school-nurse-was-held-in-storage-closet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elementary school student who attends Myrtle Beach Elementary School in South Carolina visited the school nurse for COVID-19-like symptoms and was placed in a storage closet to isolate themselves from other students, district officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City Charges Woman More Than $100,000 for Parking on Own Property...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/25/a-city-charged-this-woman-more-than-100000-for-parking-on-her-own-property/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sandy Martinez says that fine, along with another $63,500 for driveway cracks and a downed fence, violates Florida's constitution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dawn of the solar car...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Solar-cars-Driving-on-sunshine-15982099.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dream began in 1955, with a tiny, toylike creation called the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizers Heckled For Pleading With Attendees to Put on Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/freedom-cpac-organizers-booed-and-heckled-for-pleading-with-attendees-to-put-on-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO — Freedom from coronavirus restrictions is a recurring theme at this year’s CPAC, held in Florida, a state with few. But Friday morning, moments after Ohio Republican Josh Mandel ended his speech by chanting “FREEDOM,” two CPAC organizers timidly walked out onto the stage with a plea. “Does the Bill of Rights matter?” asked […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Spooky' AI tool brings dead relatives' photos to life...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210226144936-jxdi4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deep Nostalgia a tool by genealogy firm MyHeritage turns still photos into lively videos, adding to global debate around deepfake technologies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombies everywhere in SKorea, feeding on fears and anxieties...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/zombies-are-everywhere-in-south-korea-feeding-on-fears-and-anxieties/article_99d7132b-a138-529e-b357-c921c03bb6cc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea — Kim Hyeong-seek knows what he would do in a zombie apocalypse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz colleagues mock Cancun trip in Senate gym locker room: 'Bienvenido de Nuevo, Ted!'</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/ted-cruz-locker-room-memes-cancun-trip-2021-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who turned up to the Senate gym Wednesday morning were welcomed by color printouts of Cruz's Cancun trip that read "Bienvenido de Nuevo, Ted!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIOLENCE SPURS QUESTIONS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/targeted-attack-violent-street-heist-130007062.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent Hollywood street heist of two French bulldogs attracted international intrigue Thursday after it was revealed the two purebreds belonged to global megastar Lady Gaga, leaving both fans and Los Angeles police to wonder whether the animals were targeted because of their doting owner's deep pockets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: American satisfaction more than doubles since January...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/330194/satisfaction-improved-recent-decline.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After three months of decline, the percentage of Americans who are satisfied with the way things are going in the U.S. has increased to 27%, largely because Democrats are more satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosion hits Israeli-owned ship in Mideast amid tension...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dubai-united-kingdom-united-arab-emirates-persian-gulf-tensions-oman-a63aec3ba34abb4cb0aa56a148cf45a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — An explosion struck an Israeli-owned cargo ship sailing out of the Middle East on Friday, an unexplained blast renewing concerns about ship security amid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Night Owls' Twice As Likely To Perform Poorly At Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/night-owls-perform-poorly-at-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Night owls sleep for shorter periods of time, more often suffer from insomnia, and have high levels of "social jet lag."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli cargo ship hit by explosion in Gulf of Oman...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-ship-explosion-gulf-of-oman-b1808127.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli cargo ship has been struck by an unexplained explosion while sailing in the Gulf of Oman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eilish Documentary Offers Intimate Glimpse Into Her Meteoric Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/billie-eilish-documentary-apple-tv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Directed by R.J. Cutler, “Billie Eilish: The World’s A Little Blurry” offers an intimate glimpse into how the 19-year-old singer has dealt with fame and touring, struggles with her mental and physical health, and just being a teen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media users desperate for likes 'have thinking patterns similar to lab RATS seeking food'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9303815/Social-media-Users-desperate-likes-similar-lab-RATS-seeking-food-study-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new findings may help experts uncover new ways to address problematic engagement with social media, the US and European team of researchers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real or fake? Forged docs add another headache to vaccine rollout...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/real-fake-forged-documents-add-140037083.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine eligibility requires proof. But as access expands officials have yet to establish what documents will be needed for verification, or a straightforward way to sort phony documents from real ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says gave only few mins warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-says-us-gave-only-a-few-minutes-e2-80-99-warning-before-strike-in-syria/ar-BB1e2YGL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The notice came too late to “deconflict” the situation, Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of covid bankruptcies has begun...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/the-wave-of-covid-bankruptcies-has-begun/ar-BB1e2NdQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts warn that because bankruptcies lag other signals of economic distress, a mountain of filings may be to come. New data show what industries might be most at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late for jab: 88-year-old caught going 119 mph...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210226-late-for-my-jab-88-year-old-caught-going-191-km-h-in-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late for my jab: 88-year-old caught going 191 km/h in France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With new podcast, sex work comes out of shadows...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210226133553-243ib/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The podcast, 'A Sex Worker's Guide to the Galaxy', offers guests in the industry a stage to share their experiences free of sanction and in their own words</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopper whips off THONG and wears as mask after supermarket refuses to serve her...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2411562/shopper-thong-wears-as-covid-facemask-supermarket/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a shopper whipped off her thong in the middle of a supermarket and donned it as a face covering after being refused service. The viral clip shows the female customer rem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID cases, deaths starting to RISE again...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/969094/covid19-cases-deaths-are-starting-rise-again-how-worried-should</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two weeks, COVID-19 cases and deaths have dropped steadily from the alarmingly high peak of America's third wave of the pandemic. Vaccination rates are rising, new vaccines and millions more doses of approved ones are coming online soon, and deaths have dropped dramatically in places where significant numbers of people have been inoculated, especially nursing homes. But 'this is not a time to relax,' President Biden said Thursday as he celebrated the country's 50 million's vaccination. 'We must keep washing our hands, stay socially distanced, and for God's sake — for God's sake — wear a mask.' It turns out, a fourth wave of the pandemic already appears to be building. But the news is not all so encouraging. Most worrisome, the number of new cases has stopped declining over the past week. It's true in the U.S.: pic.twitter.com/CmOUFzLgDb — David Leonhardt (@DLeonhardt) February 25, 2021 Cases have leveled out worldwide, too. 'The most likely explanation is the more contagious variants of the virus, like the B.1.1.7 variant, which was first detected in Britain,' David Leonhardt writes at The New York Times. Business Insider's Jim Edwards points out that the uptick in cases and deaths could be statistical noise, but notes that worrisome new variants have also popped up in California and New York.  Big question: Are the new fast-moving variants (UK, CA, and NY) moving faster than the vaccines? — Jim Edwards (@Jim_Edwards) February 26, 2021 'Taking into account the counterbalancing rises in both vaccinations and variants, along with the high likelihood that people will stop taking precautions, a fourth wave is highly likely this spring,' Apoorva Mandavilli reports at the Times, citing a majority of 21 experts interviewed on the pandemic. 'But they stressed that it is not an inevitable surge, if government officials and individuals maintain precautions for a few more weeks,' and 'COVID-19 deaths will most likely never rise quite as precipitously as in the past.' 'The good news,' Mandavilli writes, is that 'despite the uncertainties, the experts predict that the last surge will subside in the United States sometime in the early summer. If the Biden administration can keep its promise to immunize every American adult by the end of the summer, the variants should be no match for the vaccines. ... For now, every one of us can help by continuing to be careful for just a few more months, until the curve permanently flattens.' Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Lane Teases 'BIRDCAGE' Sequel...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/nathan-lane-teases-birdcage-sequel-095038732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getty ImagesIf fans of The Birdcage ever actually get a sequel, we will have Nathan Lane’s newfound love of podcasts to thank.With a lot of extra time on his hands staying at home over the past year, Lane decided to check out a 2018 episode of the podcast Beyond the Box Set in which the two British hosts pitch sequels that “nobody asked for” for films they love. It was titled “The Birdcage: Starina Rides Again.”“So, I’ve got nothing to do, I listened to it,” he says in this preview of next week’s 100th episode of The Last Laugh podcast. The first idea they threw out there was “not good” in his opinion, but as he listened to their second pitch he started thinking to himself, “Gee, this is really good, I’d like to see this movie.”With both director Mike Nichols and his co-star Robin Williams gone, Lane had always thought that “you can’t really revisit” the classic comedy film, which was released 25 years ago next week. “But what this guy came up with, I thought, wow, it’s a way to honor Robin and go off on another adventure with my character and [Hank Azaria’s] Agador Spartacus going to Guatemala,” he explains. “It’s a really smart, clever, funny pitch.”“So, I said to my manager, listen to this,” Lane continues. “He takes it to MGM. MGM likes it. So they’re optioning it and they’re going to try to team with a streamer and see if it can actually happen! And this is all because of a podcast.”Then, all of a sudden, he realized, “Maybe someone should mention this to Hank Azaria.” Lane called up the actor to see what he thought and Azaria told him something along the lines of, “I can’t possibly play the part again. People would go crazy. I have one word for you: Apu.’”Before Azaria’s breakthrough film performance as Agador Spartacus, he had already made a name for himself voicing several characters on The Simpsons, including Kwik-E-Mart owner Apu.After comedian Hari Kondabolu released his documentary The Problem With Apu in 2017, which highlighted the racist implications of having a white actor play that stereotypically Indian character, Azaria ultimately decided to stop playing the role. He recently told The New York Times, “Once I realized that that was the way this character was thought of, I just didn’t want to participate in it anymore. It just didn’t feel right.”Why MAGA-Mocking Comedian Blaire Erskine Makes Liberals So MadFor the actor to then step back into the role of a Guatemalan “house boy” in a sequel to The Birdcage would inevitably open him up to another round of justified criticism. According to Lane, Azaria said, “I loved playing it, I would love to do it again, but it’s just not appropriate now. And you should get a Latin actor.”“So then, again, I thought, ‘Oh well, maybe that’s the end of that,’” Lane says. “And then I thought, ‘Gee, this idea is so good, if you could find a great Latin actor or comedian, it could maybe still work.’ It’s now 25 years later, we’re all older looking. Maybe Agador looks a little different.”When I suggest that the story could center on Albert and Agador’s son somehow, Lane gets excited. “‘The Birdcage 2: Son of Agador!’” he imagines. Then he deflates again, adding, “Anyway look, I don’t know if it’ll ever happen.”Of course, this conversation about who is “allowed” to portray which parts also extends to the debate surrounding straight actors playing gay roles. That public conversation was recently reignited amid the release of the new film Supernova, starring straight actors Stanley Tucci and Colin Firth as an aging couple, and HBO Max’s It’s a Sin, in which all of the lead gay roles are played by gay performers.Lane was notably the only gay actor in the main cast of The Birdcage, even though he did not come out publicly until he started promoting it—more on that in our full interview next week—but he says he does not believe gay roles “have to be played” by gay actors.“Do I think maybe something special might come from it? Perhaps,” he says. “You have to take into consideration the world we’re living in right now. And on some level you can’t really fight it. Sometimes there’s a point and sometimes it seems ridiculous.”As someone who has been able to play plenty of straight roles over the past quarter-century, he thinks there has to be some room for actors to take on characters that are unlike themselves.“I certainly get it. But to say it has to be this—I mean, to a certain degree, it’s like, well, does this mean Meryl Streep is out of business because she can’t do another accent ever again?” Lane adds. He imagines the accusatory mob shouting, “She’s not Polish!”“What about acting?” he asks. “This is a part of acting, to take on different personalities, a totally different character than you. So, I don’t know. Obviously, I think it’s a healthy discussion, but I think it can be taken to an extreme and I get nostalgic for just being able to act.”Subscribe to The Last Laugh podcast now to hear our full conversation with Nathan Lane about the 25th anniversary of ‘The Birdcage,’ including stories about Mike Nichols, Robin Williams, Gene Hackman, Oprah Winfrey and a lot more when it drops next Tuesday, March 2nd.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Golden Calf' Wheeled Into Gathering...</title>
      <link>https://www.towleroad.com/2021/02/golden-calf-trump-statue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.towleroad.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of Trump's keynote speech at the CPAC conference this weekend, two staffers wheeled in a massive golden statue of the insurrectionist former president, and everyone was thinking about the idol created by Israelities when Moses went up to Mt. Sinai.Wrote one Twitter user with more following suit: 'Republicans wheel in the golden calf as they prepare to wander the electoral desert for 40 years.'https://twitter.com/WesClarkjr/status/1365170881039798274?s=20https://twitter.com/CKourouklis/status/1365163554958020613?s=20https://twitter.com/AynRandPaulRyan/status/1365158774952972291?s=20https://twitter.com/JoyAnnReid/status/1365166137718226944?s=20https://twitter.com/mmpadellan/status/1365180643446059008?s=20https://twitter.com/TheRaDR/status/1365142286854742016?s=20https://twitter.com/CaptNostradamus/status/1365166357071937537?s=20https://twitter.com/Goss30Goss/status/1365148754890883072?s=20https://twitter.com/DavMicRot/status/1365168538718248961?s=20https://twitter.com/JLCauvin/status/1365267970419793921?s=20</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Hazards Grow as Americans Churn Out More Garbage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/local-hazards-grow-as-americans-churn-out-more-garbage/ar-BB1e2nyI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasing waste, full landfills and shuttered recycling programs mean more cities are paying to send their trash out-of-state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians Escape NKorea on Hand-Pushed Railcar...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/26/russians-escape-north-korea-on-a-hand-pushed-railcar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW — North Korea sealed its borders more than a year ago because of the pandemic, grounding flights and shutting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte Gainsbourg says Serge would struggle with today's censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210226-charlotte-gainsbourg-says-serge-would-struggle-with-today-s-censorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlotte Gainsbourg says Serge would struggle with today's censorship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris eyes three-week Covid-19 lockdown in bid to then 'reopen everything'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210226-paris-eyes-three-week-covid-19-lockdown-in-bid-to-then-reopen-everything</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Paris is considering proposing a three-week lockdown in a bid to “reopen everything” in the City of Lights afterwards, the deputy mayor said Thursday, calling the current nighttime curfew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant kills zookeeper with blow from trunk...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spain-elephants-371f33e9420a25ef72c60d783dd5070f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Authorities in Spain’s northern Cantabria region are investigating how an elephant killed a worker at a local zoo. The Cantabrian regional government says 44-year-old Joaquín...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy warships in Mideast hit by outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bahrain-dubai-united-arab-emirates-persian-gulf-tensions-coronavirus-pandemic-706500afe1fe80156ca40eb481b02176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Two U.S. Navy warships operating in the Mideast have been struck by coronavirus outbreaks, authorities said Friday, with both returning to port in Bahrain....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
