<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Unpaid bills pile up in Trump rallies' wake...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/08/trump-rallies-unpaid-bills-039631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosenstein had  support of two cabinet colleagues for invoking 25th Amendment... MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7550157/FBI-lover-Lisa-Page-LIED-confronted-affair-Peter-Strzok.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI lawyer Lisa Page lied to Andrew McCabe about her relationship with agent Peter Strzok, new book Deep State: Trump, the FBI, and the Rule of Law claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil Peep's Mother Sues Managers Over His Death...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/lil-peeps-mother-sues-managers-over-death-1203363212/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lil Peep’s mother, Liza Womack, has sued the late rapper’s managers for negligence, breach of contract and wrongful death, according to court documents; the news was first reported by the New York …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JFK launches facial recognition boarding...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/08/jfk-airports-terminal-1-launches-facial-recognition-boarding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A biometric self-boarding gate has officially been launched at John F. Kennedy International Airport’s Terminal 1, officials said Tuesday. Lufthansa has deployed the paperless, high-tech boarding p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Loses Top Spot to Singapore in Competitiveness Rankings...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-dips-competitiveness-index-singapore-220222625.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is less competitive than it was a year ago and the global economy remains hobbled by low productivity despite a decade of cheap money from central banks, the World Economic Forum said Wednesday. In its latest assessment of the factors behind productivity and long-term economic growth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S.-China Relationship Swiftly Deteriorating by the Day...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-china-relationship-swiftly-deteriorating-220038212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- This was supposed to be the week U.S.-China trade talks got back on track and the two sides found a way to avoid sending more unsettling signals to financial markets and a global economy that looks increasingly fragile.But that didn’t take long to change. If the state of relations between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Return Ruling Could Open Door to Indictment...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tax-return-ruling-could-180002869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- A federal district judge in New York has held that the Manhattan district attorney may subpoena Donald Trump’s tax records as part of a criminal investigation.Apart from the obvious political implications, there’s something constitutionally significant about the decision by Judge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADMITS:  TWITTER misused phone numbers, email addresses for ad targeting... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Twitter-says-users-phone-numbers-provided-for-14502110.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter said Tuesday that it may have mishandled an unspecified number of users' email addresses and phone numbers, allowing that data to be used "inadvertently" for advertising purposes.  The incident marks the latest security mishap for the social-networking company, but one that could carry with it some legal headaches. Federal regulators penalized Facebook earlier this year for a similar situation.  In a blog post, Twitter explained that users share email addresses and phone numbers with the company for safety and login verification purposes, such as two-factor authentication, which allows people to receive a one-time code that they input along with their password in order to access their account.  The trouble, however, stems from the fact that advertisers can upload their own contact lists to match their customers with Twitter's users. In doing so, Twitter said it "may have matched people on Twitter" to a marketer's list "based on the email or phone number the Twitter account holder provided for safety and security purposes."  "We cannot say with certainty how many people were impacted by this, but in an effort to be transparent, we wanted to make everyone aware," Twitter said. "No personal data was ever shared externally with our partners or any other third parties."  The incident could invite trouble for Twitter in Washington, where regulators who investigated and penalized Facebook for a series of privacy scandals took issue with its handling of phone numbers. In that case, the Federal Trade Commission alleged Facebook deceived users because it "did not disclose, or did not adequately disclose" that phone numbers provided through its security tool for the purpose of two-factor authentication "also would be used by Facebook to target advertisements to those users."  Adding to Twitter's potential troubles, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida man pours beer into alligator's mouth, encourages it to bite him, officials say...</title>
      <link>https://www.news-press.com/story/news/crime/martin-county/2019/10/07/hobe-sound-man-accused-pouring-beer-into-alligators-mouth/3898854002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news-press.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man told his friends "watch this" as he enticed an alligator to bite his arm, according to FWC records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY 2020? 'DON'T TEMPT ME'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/dont-tempt-me-hillary-clinton-fires-back-at-trump-daring-her-to-run-with-eyebrow-raising-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh quid-pro-quo questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/08/trump-ukraine-missile-sale-040915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Admits Misusing Security Info For Ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/twitter-misused-security-information-for-advertising-purposes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might've given your phone number to Twitter for two-factor authentication. The company said that number could've been used for advertising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Al-Qaeda commander KILLED in Afghan raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7551345/Top-Al-Qaeda-commander-Asim-Omar-killed-joint-Afghan-raid-Taliban-Helmand-province.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAPHIC CONTENT WARNING: Asim Omar died alongside six of his fellow terrorists, including Omar's courier to the Al-Qaeda leader Ayman Al-Zawahiri in southern Helmand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Cop Suspended After Fake Arrest Video With Lingerie Models...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/miami-beach-police-officer-suspended-after-appearing-in-inappropriate-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH, FLA. (WSVN) - A Miami Beach Police officer has been relieved of duty after he appeared in uniform in a troubling video that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trey Gowdy declines to represent President...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/it-appears-trey-gowdy-wont-help-trump-fight-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN CLAMPS DOWN ON DISSENT...</title>
      <link>https://deadspin.com/internal-memo-espn-forbids-discussion-of-chinese-polit-1838881032</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadspin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you paid attention to ESPN channels yesterday, you saw the network repeatedly attempt to grapple with the story of Houston Rockets general manager Daryl Morey creating an international incident after tweeting and then deleting his support for pro-democracy protestors in Hong Kong. You heard talking head after talking head castigate Morey for sending the tweet, speculation over whether he’d keep his job, speculation about the sincerity of his convictions, discussions about what this meant for the Rockets’ bottom line, the observation that it’s unreasonable to expect for-profit companies like the NBA to act morally, and the non-take that cowing to China is simply the cost of doing business in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>76% Of Businesses Cyberattacked In Past Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/76-percent-of-us-businesses-have-experienced-a-cyberattack-in-the-past-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SMBs in the country are becoming a firm favorite as targets for cybercriminals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Warns Education Secretary DeVos He Could Send Her to Jail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/464874-judge-warns-devos-im-not-sending-anyone-to-jail-yet-but-its-an-option</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge in San Francisco rebuked Education Secretary Betsy DeVos for continuing to collect debt payments from students after she had been ordered to stop by a court order,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas could be new home to A's, MLB commissioner says...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/sports/aviators/las-vegas-could-be-home-to-as-mlb-commissioner-says-in-report-1865233/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oakland A’s could move to Las Vegas, MLB commissioner says in report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA puts visa restrictions on Chinese officials over abuses of Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/08/us-puts-visa-restrictions-on-chinese-officials-over-abuses-of-muslims-in-xinjiang.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration put visa restrictions on Chinese officials Tuesday amid ongoing abuses of Muslim minorities in the Xinjiang region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. says Brexit deal 'essentially impossible'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/brexit-news-british-government-says-brexit-deal-essentially-impossible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top EU official chides Boris Johnson for playing "stupid blame game" as British government says negotiations appear to have reached a standstill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy reduces size of parliament 'to save millions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49979103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling Five Star party says cutting the number of MPs and senators will save €1bn over 10 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex offenders say rehab 'made them worse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-49973318</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex offenders placed on a now discredited rehabilitation programme say it made them more likely to reoffend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside effort to contain Ukraine call fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/08/politics/donald-trump-ukraine-call-details-aftermath/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the time President Donald Trump's line with Volodymyr Zelensky went quiet, the scramble began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Baier to Maddow, News Anchors Carry More Weight in Late-Night...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/tv-news-anchors-late-night-tv-rachel-maddow-bret-baier-1203362830/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN’s Don Lemon recently delivered some amusing quips about bickering with his mother; his looming bachelor party; and his colleague Chris Cuomo’s diet (“Steroids,” joked Lemon). He wasn’t holding …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN COMING TO WASHINGTON?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a008ac28d704d5d8a0de26f70477571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A day after President Donald Trump threatened to "ruin the economy of Turkey" if it goes too far with a planned invasion of northern Syria, he announced on Tuesday that he's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STD rates hit record high...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-10-08/stds-hit-record-high-in-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS:  IMPEACHMENT SUPPORT GROWS</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/do-americans-support-impeaching-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking polls that ask whether respondents support impeaching President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madrid plans 'ethical slaughter' of city's parakeets...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/08/europe/madrid-parrot-cull-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madrid's city council is preparing a plan to clear the city of its pesky parrots -- which will include the "ethical slaughter" of the birds and and sterilization of eggs, authorities said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITNESS BLOCKED FROM  PROBE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/afe01764208b4eefabb2255fb6a45653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump intensified his fight with Congress Tuesday over the Democrats' impeachment investigation, as the administration blocked a U.S. diplomat from testifying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP 11,000 TWEETS!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trump-passes-11-000-tweets-but-just-one-third-of-americans-read-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has passed the 11,000 tweet mark since Inauguration Day, but there are indications that all but his base are growing bored with his Twitter commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's 2016 campaign was run on shoestring. His reelection machine is huge, armed with consultants... </title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/politics/nation/trump-reelection-presidential-campaign-democrats-20191008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's presidential campaign in 2015 had no pollster, rapid-response team or fundraiser. A bare-bones staff fueled by pizza and energy drinks toiled in a makeshift office at Trump Tower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China warns global brands...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2019/10/08/china-warns-brands-to-accept-communism-freedom-of-speech-ridiculous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese government newspaper Global Times warned "global brands" to "make their members speak cautiously" on Chinese political issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador moves govt out of capital as violent protests rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/08/ecuador-moves-government-out-of-capital-as-violent-protests-rage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters in Quito throw petrol bombs and ransack public buildings in fuel subsidy demonstrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK DIGS 'DEEP STATE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/james-b-stewart-the-truth-about-the-deep-state-donald-trump-and-jeffrey-epstein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalist James B. Stewart talks about reporting on Trump, the Clintons, Epstein, and why—as Steve Bannon tells him—Trump’s “deep state” conspiracy is for “nut cases.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey rejects Trump threats amid conflicting signals over Syria offensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Turkey-rejects-Trump-s-threats-amid-conflicting-14500616.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL - Turkey's vice president said Tuesday that his country would "not react to threats," as it prepared to mount a military offensive against U.S.-allied Kurdish fighters in Syria, a day after President Donald Trump warned that he would destroy Turkey's economy if the offensive did not meet with his approval.  "When it comes to the security of Turkey, as always, our president emphasized Turkey will determine its own path," the vice president, Fuat Oktay, said in a speech at a university in Ankara, the Turkish capital. He referred to President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, who has vowed to create a "safe zone" in a lengthy swath of Syrian territory along Turkey's border.  Erdogan and other Turkish officials have suggested for days that the military operation could begin at any moment. Turkish troop convoys have headed to the border, and local media outlets have published details of what they say is the battle plan. Turkey's Defense Ministry wrote Tuesday on Twitter that all its preparations for the operation were complete.  But there was no sign yet that Turkish troops were moving forward, as the United Nations and aid agencies warned of potentially catastrophic humanitarian consequences, and as the Trump administration delivered confusing signals about how it views Turkey's plans to attack a Syrian-Kurdish force that partnered with the U.S. military to fight the Islamic State militant group.  In a White House statement on Sunday and tweets on Monday, Trump suggested that U.S. troops would step aside as Turkey conducted its military operation.  "It is time for us to get out of these ridiculous Endless Wars, many of them tribal, and bring our soldiers home," Trump tweeted. Dozens of U.S. troops were withdrawn from the "safe zone" early Monday.  But after facing harsh criticism from some of his own allies that he was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge swath of Northern California could have power turned off as fire danger rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-08/california-utility-says-it-could-shutdown-power-to-nearly-30-counties-ahead-of-wildfire-friendly-weather</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the eve of the second anniversary of the wine country fires, Northern California’s biggest utility has warned customers across half the state to prepare for a possible blackout this week so their equipment doesn’t spark another repeat of those deadly blazes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Bets Big on GALACTIC Space Trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/08/boeing-20-million-stake-in-virgin-galactic-with-vision-of-hypersonic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two companies hope to mature the technologies needed to make hypersonic air travel a commercially-viable business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Young Americans More Likely to Resent Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.cato.org/blog/poll-young-americans-are-more-likely-resent-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cato.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young Americans are more likely to hold negative views towards the rich, support increasing taxes on the rich, and have favorable views of socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's 'Prosecutors Can't Touch Me' Spurs Question of Overreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-s-prosecutors-can-t-touch-me-spurs-question-of-overreach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trumpâ€™s â€˜Prosecutors Canâ€™t Touch Meâ€™ Spurs Question of Overreach</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 3 in 10 REPUBLICANS support impeachment push...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/870332/brutal-new-poll-shows-3-10-republicans-support-trump-impeachment-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 58 percent majority of Americans say House Democrats were right to begin an impeachment inquiry of President Trump, and a 49 percent plurality say the House should vote to remove him from office, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll released Tuesday morning. Support for impeachment has jumped significantly across the board since the White House released a transcript of Trump's July 25 call with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky in late September. There is a clear partisan split in the results, but 28 percent of Republicans said they support the House impeachment investigation â€” a 21-point jump from a Washington Post/ABC News poll in July â€” and 18 percent of Republicans want the House to "vote to remove Trump from office." Meanwhile, 86 percent of Democrats and 57 percent of independents support the impeachment investigation; 78 percent of Democrats and 49 percent of independents want the House to vote to evict Trump from the White House. There's also a generation gap â€” 40 percent of Republicans age 18-39 back the impeachment investigation versus 23 percent of those 40-64 and 13 percent of Republicans 65 and older. The Post and George Mason University's Schar School of Policy and Government conducted the poll by phone Oct. 1-6 among 1,007 U.S. adults, and the margin or sampling error for the entire survey is Â±3.5 percentage points. The results were nearly identical for U.S. adults and registered voters. On FiveThirtyEight's aggregate of impeachment polling, which did not include this new poll, 46.5 percent support the impeachment inquiry and 44.7 percent do not. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Senate Republicans turning on Trump?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/870188/are-senate-republicans-turning-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice GOP majority you've got behind you in the impeachment fight, Mr. President. It would be a shame if anything happened to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Security Guard Kills Armed Robbery Suspect At Dallas Store...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/10/08/apple-security-guard-shoots-kills-robbery-suspect-at-dallas-store/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An armed man who broke into an Apple store in Dallas was shot dead by a security guard early Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Yao Ming Mend Fences?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Sports/wireStory/yao-ming-mend-fences-nba-china-66132841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yao Ming could be the man in the middle if the NBA and China are going to mend fences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter Of Americans Have Never Eaten Vegetables!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/stunning-survey-reveals-1-in-4-adults-has-never-eaten-vegetables/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most popular vegetable in America is -- corn! That's according to a survey of 2,000 Americans who were asked which vegetables they liked and disliked the most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to make staff take polygraph tests?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/08/trump-obsession-polygraphs-leaks-038431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The legacy of 'NATURAL BORN KILLERS': Oliver Stone and Juliette Lewis on ultra-violence, media hysteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/movies/story/2019-10-08/natural-born-killers-anniversary-oliver-stone-juliette-lewis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of a 25th anniversary screening, filmmaker Oliver Stone and actress Juliette Lewis look back on their controversial tale of murder, mayhem and the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY: SYRIAN SHOUTING 'ALLAH' PLOUGHS TRUCK INTO TRAFFIC, 9 INJURED...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/germany-syrian-migrant-shouting-allah-ploughs-truck-into-traffic-9-injured/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incident being treated as terrorist attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice AI systems will be 'everywhere'; Phones will 'disappear in 10 years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/voice-ai-systems-everywhere-phones-20534590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entrepreneur Gary Vaynerchuk claims the AI system will connect us to the internet from anywhere and will enable humans to down their phones and merely speak to access any information or make any purchases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Farmers have most sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/farmers-have-most-sex-study-20536021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new study, farmers top the list of professions having the most sex</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends blocking witness before 'kangaroo court'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/464801-trump-defends-blocking-witness-before-kangaroo-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday defended his administration’s decision to block a key State Department witness from testifying before Congress as part of the House impeachment inquiry, claiming European Union Ambassador Gordon Sondland would have been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concerns about Assange health mounting...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/analysis/201910081076987752-we-received-a-message-in-morse-from-julian-assange---wikijustice-member/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detained in a high-security prison, WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange risks being extradited to the United States where he faces jail for disclosure of state secrets. Meanwhile, concerns about his health are mounting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE hides Taiwan flag emoji in Hong Kong, Macau...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1723334/apple-removes-taiwan-flag-emoji-in-hong-kong-macau-in-ios-13-1-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The keyboard has become a political battleground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new front-runner? Warren tops Biden in 3 out of 4 latest polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/a-new-front-runner-for-the-2020-democrats-warren-tops-biden-in-3-latest-polls-2019-10-07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential hopeful Elizabeth Warren has overtaken rival Joe Biden in three out of four recent polls, though she still is behind him in an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWNING DOG COULD HELP YOU LIVE LONGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/dog-owners-pet-live-longer-health-study-heart-disease-a9147081.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump considers making staff take LIE DETECTOR tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7550089/Trump-considers-making-staff-lie-detector-tests-president-grows-obsessed-leaks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has weighed making his staff take lie detector tests as he has become obsessed with leaks coming out of his White House, it was revealed on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding a way for lions and humans to share the savannah...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5313930d153744f29cb5bf8cb820738c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOIBOR SIRET, Tanzania (AP) — Saitoti Petro scans a dirt road in northern Tanzania for recent signs of the top predator on the African savannah. "If you see a lion," he warns, "stop and look it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to fight by stalling and attacking...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/22b5861e55084f39b7c7cf92cbbf3333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As House Democrats fire off more subpoenas, the White House is finalizing a high-stakes strategy to counter the impeachment threat to President Donald Trump: Stall. Obfuscate....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority in new poll supports impeachment inquiry; Half back removal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/464777-majority-in-new-poll-supports-impeachment-inquiry-almost-half-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of respondents in a new poll supports the impeachment inquiry into President Trump while almost half back his removal from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's odd dilemma: Low unemployment but pressure to do more...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/feds-odd-dilemma-low-unemployment-101119772.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the nation's unemployment rate at its lowest point since human beings first walked on the moon, you might expect the Federal Reserve to be raising interest rates to keep the economy from overheating and igniting inflation. Welcome to the strange world that Jerome Powell inhabits as chairman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five more Thai elephants died in waterfall plunge, drone footage shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-elephants/five-more-thai-elephants-died-in-waterfall-plunge-drone-footage-shows-idUSKBN1WN15A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five more wild elephants in Thailand died in a plunge from the top of a waterfal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 300 arrests as London 'climate-change' activists vow more protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-britain-protests/over-300-arrests-as-london-climate-change-activists-vow-more-protests-idUSKBN1WN113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London police have made more than 300 arrests as climate-change protesters, labe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China surveillance tech spreading globally, raising concerns about influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/08/china-is-exporting-surveillance-tech-like-facial-recognition-globally.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has built a huge surveillance state at home. It's now exporting that technology abroad, thanks to some of the country's largest firms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These men love their sex doll wives because they won't cheat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/07/these-men-love-their-sex-doll-wives-and-dont-care-who-knows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Silicone Soul” mates are more loyal, according to a new documentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany warns of repeat of 2015 migrant influx into EU...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191008103837-z9x3r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-MIGRANTS/MINISTERS (TV):Germany warns of repeat of 2015 migrant influx into EU</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOUTH PARK' creators offer mocking 'apology' over episode...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191008093328-wddz0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TELEVISION-SOUTH PARK/CHINA:'South Park' creators offer mocking 'apology' to China over episode</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSPENDS BROADCASTS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191008082619-6v5xu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-BASKETBALL/NBA-SILVER (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-China TV drops NBA exhibition games, escalating pressure amid tweet uproar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Time for LeBron to Speak Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/columnist/josh-peter/2019/10/07/lebron-james-china-hong-kong-controversy/3903187002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If LeBron James wants to preserve his reputation as an athlete willing to risk backlash while speaking out, he must support free speech and society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First meat grown in space lab 248 miles from Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/oct/07/wheres-the-beef-248-miles-up-as-first-meat-is-grown-in-a-space-lab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli company successfully cultures bovine cells on International Space Station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE SPEECH FURY</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/sport/basketball/article/3031997/cctv-pulls-nba-china-games-broadcast-response-adam-silvers-support</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Lakers and Brooklyn Nets to meet in Shanghai and Shenzhen this week but neither game to be screened</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate's secretly recorded film shows gruesome reality of life in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.roanoke.com/news/trending/an-florida-inmate-s-secretly-recorded-film-shows-the-gruesome/article_92501e97-4e55-5d2e-ac1c-d9a5c289c15b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.roanoke.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A convicted drug trafficker spent years filming daily life inside one of Florida's notoriously dangerous prisons. The result was a documentary he called "Behind Tha Barb Wire."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSPENDS BROADCASTS</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cacbc722f6834e64814f82b14752682c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — NBA Commissioner Adam Silver said the league is not apologizing for Houston Rockets general manager Daryl Morey's since-deleted tweet showing support for anti-government protesters in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA PUNISHES NBA</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/china-punishes-nba-crisis-over-democracy-tweet-deepens-091952657--nba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Tuesday scrapped plans to air NBA exhibition games as the league faced an escalating punishment campaign in the lucrative Chinese market ignited by an American basketball executive&amp;#39;s pro-democracy tweet. The National Basketball Association also faced a counter-attack in the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIFFANY removes advert over controversy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tiffany-removes-advert-over-hong-kong-controversy-093418861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiffany &amp; Co. have removed a tweet showing a woman covering one eye after Chinese consumers accused the jeweller of supporting the Hong Kong protesters. The photo posted on Monday showed Chinese model Sun Feifei wearing a Tiffany ring on her right hand as it covers her right eye. Angry Chinese buyers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion  -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-confounding-syria-moves-spur-policy-confusion-again/ar-AAIrbqT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDERAL DEFICIT HIGHEST IN 7 YEARS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/464764-federal-deficit-estimated-at-984b-highest-in-seven-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal budget deficit for 2019 is estimated at $984 billion, a hefty 4.7 percent of gross domestic product (GDP) and the highest since 2012, the Congressional Budget Office (CBO) said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans turn to alternative medicine amid shortages...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuelans-turn-alternative-medicine-amid-shortages-021232838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small waiting room at the home of self-styled healer "Brother Guayanes" in Caracas' rundown Petare district fills up quickly with patients -- business has never been better. With Venezuela's chronic medicine shortages and hyperinflation, more and more people are turning to alternative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCKLE UP!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191008033333-lmlnx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-TRUMP (PIX):'Buckle up': Abrupt Syria policy shift is sign of Trump unchained</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Institutions Keep Bowing To Communists...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/07/china-censorship-daryl-morey-american-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's institutions are catering to China. The NBA provided the latest example after Houston Rockets GM Daryl Morey tweeted support for Hong Kong protesters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens Turkey after greenlighting Syria invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-forces-start-syria-border-pullback-alarming-kurds-082650162.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump warned Turkey on Monday against going too far in Syria, one day after giving Ankara a green light to invade its southern neighbor and sparking panic among Washington&amp;#39;s Kurdish allies. The US pulled back 50 to 100 &amp;quot;special operators&amp;quot; from Syria&amp;#39;s northern frontier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Deepfakes Are Porn, and They're Multiplying Fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/most-deepfakes-porn-multiplying-fast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers worry that doctored videos may disrupt the 2020 election, but a new report finds that 96 percent of deepfakes are pornographic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR:  15,000 ISIS fighters will break out of prison camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10087333/fears-isis-will-use-turkish-invasion-to-break-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KURDISH fighters have warned that Turkey’s Syrian invasion may allow ISIS to attempt mass prison breaks as the US backs out of its occupied territories. More than 15,000 ISIS fanatics are cur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: League Choosing Money over Human Rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/daryl-morey-nba-hong-kong-houston-rockets-895706/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daryl Morey is now being forced to apologize because he… supports Democracy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETS owner, ALIBABA co-founder pens open letter defending China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-basketball-nba-tsai/brooklyn-nets-owner-alibaba-co-founder-tsai-decries-houston-rockets-gms-hong-kong-tweet-idUSKBN1WM0C8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph Tsai, owner of the Brooklyn Nets and co-founder of Chinese e-commerce gia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Struggles to Piece Together Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/08/caught-between-trump-turkey-and-kurds-pentagon-struggles-to-piece-together-syria-strategy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — For nine months, the Pentagon played down the presence of its 1,000 troops in Syria, hoping that President Trump would not focus on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former George W. Bush chief of staff endorses Trump impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/464763-former-george-w-bush-chief-of-staff-endorses-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Card, who served as White House chief of staff during the George W. Bush administration, on Monday expressed support for House Democrats’ impeachment inquiry of President Trump, saying that "clearly lines have been crossed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Using Trade Deals to Shield Tech Giants From Foreign Regulators... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/07/business/tech-shield-trade-deals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The push is the latest salvo in a global fight over who gets to set the rules for the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS fighters will break out of prison camps?</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/08/trumps-green-light-to-turkey-raises-fears-about-isis-detainees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — President Trump’s sudden blessing of a Turkish military operation in northern Syria and his announcement of an American troop withdrawal from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls begin to signal rising impeachment threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/07/polls-begin-to-signal-rising-impeachment-threat-to-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite last week's hailstorm of bad news, President Trump's job approval rating stood virtually unchanged. Yet surveys in recent days show public sentiment evolving more than Trump's steady topline would suggest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City Grinds to Halt as Cabs Block Airport to Protest UBER...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/mexico-city-taxi-drivers-block-191555656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of medallion taxi drivers parked their pink-and-white cabs to block major Mexico City thoroughfares for hours Monday in protest of ride-hailing apps such as Uber, causing long delays for motorists. Taxi drivers say they have to comply with requirements for licensing, tax, inspection and tests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  New York-based WBAI radio abruptly shuts down...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/07/new-york-based-wbai-radio-abruptly-shuts-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WBAI FM 99.5, a listener-supported radio station in New York City that has been on the air since 1955, abruptly announced on Monday it is shutting down. The station’s California-based nonprofit par…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
