<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Welcomes gun control; 'There will be no opposition'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/17/new-zealand-welcomes-jacinta-ardern-gun-control-af/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Zealand leader’s promise of tightened gun laws in the wake of the Christchurch mosque shootings has been widely welcomed by a stunned population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychiatrist found bludgeoned to death in trunk of Vegas car...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecalifornian.com/story/news/2019/03/16/salinas-doctor-found-trunk-car-murdered-las-vegas/3189401002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecalifornian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burchard died from blunt forceÂ to theÂ headÂ and his death was ruled a homicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic floods hit Nebraska after 'bomb cyclone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-weather-idUSKCN1QY00Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large parts of Nebraska and the U.S. Central Plains were underwater on Saturday ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In movies and TV, plus-size actresses finally assume lead roles...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190317-movies-tv-plus-size-actresses-finally-assume-leading-roles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In movies and TV, plus-size actresses finally assume leading roles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  DC Protesters Would Trade Trump for Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/16/hands-off-venezuela-protest-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's mind-boggling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born into al-Qaida: Hamza bin Laden's rise to prominence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a70a4562831e4ce0a8da88b0c888e16c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Years after the death of his father at the hands of a U.S. Navy SEAL raid in Pakistan, Hamza bin Laden now finds himself in the crosshairs of world...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO:  Being white male no disadvantage...</title>
      <link>http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2019/mar/16/beto-orourke-being-a-white-male-doesnt-put-me-at-d/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate Beto O’Rourke said Saturday that being a white man in a 2020 Democratic field that’s so deeply diverse won’t be a hindrance because his gender and race have given him inherent advantages for years. While he’d spoken before about his gender and race, O’Rourke had largely dodged campaign-trail questions about whether his party would go for a white man in a year when a historic number of women and minorities are running to deny President Trump a second term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive manhunt underway after West Bank shooting, stabbing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/17/west-bank-shooting-stabbing-spree-prompts-manhunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Palestinian killed an Israeli and seriously wounded two others in a West Bank shooting and stabbing spree Sunday before fleeing and setting off a massive manhunt, the Israeli military said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport closed after suspicious package...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12213645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source has told the Otago Daily Times the bomb squad has been called in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand digs graves as mosque massacre toll rises to 50...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/419df740e2464e47b416b2dcc6128cdb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHRISTCHURCH, New Zealand (AP) — Anguished relatives were anxiously waiting Sunday for authorities to release the remains of those who were killed in massacres at two mosques in the New Zealand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SXSW Shooting Sends Austin Into Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/shooting-at-sxsw-leaves-at-least-one-injured-1202577063/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The celebratory mood Saturday night at the South by Southwest festival in Austin, Texas ended in chaos, after a shooting erupted at the corner of 6th Street and San Jacinto, according to an eyewitn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest 'ultimatum' rally turns violent in France...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/yellow-vest-ultimatum-rally-turns-violent-paris-102144009.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After weeks of declining participation, France's "yellow vest" protest movement attempted to rebound on Saturday with a major rally in Paris which quickly turned violent. A large crowd gathered on the Champs-Elysees avenue for the 18th straight week of anti-government protests which initially</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREMATURE JOE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/joe-biden-almost-announces-running-president-004945084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president indicated he was "running" before correcting himself and saying, "I didn't mean it!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Young Americans Hilariously Explain Why Lowering Voting Age to 16 Is Terrible Idea...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-young-americans-hilariously-explain-why-lowering-voting-age</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'When I was 16, my friends and I bought a live lobster, put it on a leash, and walked it around the neighborhood at 2am'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popping Balloons Trigger Active Shooter Warning That Clears Michigan Campus...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/16/popping-balloons-active-shooter-michigan-campus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'No active shooter at U of M after all'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F**king Liars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/paris-jackson-calls-out-tmz-after-reports-of-attempted-suicide-f-ing-liars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"F-- you you f--ing liars," the model and actress tweeted at the publication just minutes after their story was published</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swung Up And Down Hundreds Of Feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-14/something-was-extraordinarily-wrong-doomed-boeing-swung-and-down-hundreds-feet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/author/peggy-noonan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read Peggy Noonan on The Wall Street Journal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census first-ever online headcount designed to reach Millennials...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/14/census-online-headcount-aimed-millennials-likely-m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Census Bureau plans to conduct its first-ever online headcount, which it predicts will generate 60 percent of the total responses for 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowy group trying to overthrow Kim raids NKorea embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/a-shadowy-group-trying-to-overthrow-kim-jong-un-raided-a-north-korean-embassy-in-broad-daylight/2019/03/15/ae4208a4-c451-4886-b608-f5ac1f182d3d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumors have swirled about the motivations behind the attack, which took place days before President Trump’s summit with Kim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA fan permanently banned after calling star 'boy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nba/2019/03/15/utah-jazz-ban-second-fan-separate-russell-westbrook-incident/3173929002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Utah Jazz have permanently banned another fan from their arena for an offensive and inappropriate interaction with Thunder starÂ Russell Westbrook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson Daughter Hospitalized After Attempted Suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/03/16/paris-jackson-hospitalized-attempted-suicide-leaving-neverland-michael/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris Jackson attempted suicide early Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eggs good or bad? New research rekindles debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/medical/article/Are-eggs-good-or-bad-for-you-New-research-13691872.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest U.S. research on eggs won't go over easy for those can't eat breakfast without them.  Study participants who ate about 1 ½ eggs daily had a slightly higher risk of heart disease than those who ate no eggs. The study showed the more eggs, the greater the risk. The chances of dying early were also higher.  The researchers say the culprit is cholesterol in egg yolks. Cholesterol is also found in other foods, but the study focused on eggs because they're a common source.  Dietary guidelines that eased limits on cholesterol have helped eggs make a comeback in U.S. diets. The new study has limitations and experts say eggs can still be part of a healthy diet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEAL IF MAY GOES?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8642613/brexiteers-tell-theresa-may-they-will-now-back-her-deal-if-she-quits-immediately/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREXITEERS have told Theresa May they can be swayed to back her deal – but only if she quits within weeks. Leave-backing MP Peter Bone said he was still a long way from getting behind the PM …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn age block triggers privacy fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2019/mar/16/uk-online-porn-age-verification-launch </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government to confirm launch date of nationwide age block on pornographic content</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Developing Prejudice -- On Own?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-robots-capable-developing-prejudice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embracing stereotypes or even forming a simple opinion about others may seem like a trait exclusive to humans, but a recent study shows that robots can develop prejudice and even discriminate in similar ways to people, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film uses unflattering wartime footage of Marines...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/film-uses-wartime-footage-of-marines-that-isn-t-necessarily-flattering-1.572698</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marine Corps, like other service branches, dispatches its media wing to curate its own version of war. But the THC-laced epiphany halfway through the documentary "Combat Obscura," directed by former Marine videographer Miles Lagoze, is something different.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farage leads march over betrayal...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-leave-march/arch-euroskeptic-farage-leads-march-over-brexit-betrayal-idUSKCN1QX0CA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nigel Farage, the politician who probably did more than anyone else to force Bri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busy week offers signs report coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/16/mueller-probe-report-1223959</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After many false alarms that the special counsel's work is winding down, the clues are mounting that it finally is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden will be big bust?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/15/trump-joe-biden-2020-1222398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has peppered aides for updates on Biden’s polling numbers, but his confidants are telling him the Democratic base won’t accept the former vice president’s centrism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie gets stitches after run-in with glass shower door...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/15/bernie-sanders-shower-door-1223545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the 2020 candidate was given a &amp;quot;clean bill of health&amp;quot; and will attend all of his previously scheduled campaign events over the next couple days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece Found at BOEING 737 Crash Site Shows Jet Was Set to Dive...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/piece-found-at-ethiopian-airlines-crash-site-shows-jet-was-set-to-dive-2008100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A screw-like device found in the wreckage of the Boeing 737 Max that crashed last Sunday in Ethiopia indicates the plane was configured to dive, a piece of evidence that helped convince U.S. regulators to ground the model, a person familiar with the investigation said late Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret feuds, heartbreak at center of first moon landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/secret-feuds-heartbreak-centre-historic-14139819</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neil Armstrong was the first man on the moon - but not everyone was happy about this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$12 Billion Defamation Suit Hits Major Media Outlets...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/failed-gop-candidate-don-blankenship-files-12-billion-defamation-lawsuit-against-major-media-outlets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans warn Beto could ramp up Dem turnout in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article227738534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAKE SHACK trying four-day workweek...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/even-shake-shack-is-trying-a-four-day-workweek-2019-03-15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The burger chain joins restaurants like Maaemo and Aloha Hospitality trying shorter workweeks to attract and retain employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California drought-free first time in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-rain-california-drought-conditions-20190314-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Thursday, 93% of the state was experiencing normal conditions and none of it was in drought, according to the latest report from the U.S. Drought Monitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot lived mysterious double life. Then plane crash exposed aliases, falsehoods, questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/pilot-lived-a-mysterious-double-life-then-a-plane-crash/article_b3ec55c1-bbfc-5393-a00e-97cf77e534ad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. — Jordan Aaron was the president of a Carson City sushi restaurant who once ran for justice of the peace in Arizona. Antonio Pastini was the brash ex-Chicago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looting, clashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190316-looting-clashes-mark-most-violent-day-yellow-vest-protests-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators looted stores on the Champs-Elysees avenue in Paris on Saturday, on the 18th week of “yellow vest” protests, characterised by an uptick in violence after dwindling participation in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy probes mystery death of Berlusconi sex trial witness...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190316-italy-probes-mystery-death-berlusconi-sex-trial-witness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy probes mystery death of Berlusconi sex trial witness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students around world hold 'climate change' walkout...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190315-students-around-world-begin-climate-change-walkout-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of students across the world skipped school on Friday to take to the streets in protest at their governments' failure to take sufficient action against global warming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU to slap GOOGLE with fresh fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190315-eu-slap-google-with-fresh-fine-sources</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU to slap Google with fresh fine: sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapists using VR to treat depression, anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/therapists-explore-virtual-reality-to-help-patients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Colorado Boulder are using immersive technology to help those who suffer from anxiety, depression, and irrational fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Wants to Test A SPACE-BASED WEAPON...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2019/03/pentagon-wants-test-space-based-weapon-2023/155581/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense officials have asked for $304 million to fund research into space-based lasers, particle beams, and other new forms of missile defense next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US warship quarantined for two months after rare virus outbreak infects crew...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/765915/uss-fort-mchenry-us-warship-quarantined-two-months-virus-outbreak-parotitis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border agency says ZERO new walls have gone up!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6811259/Trumps-border-agency-admits-built-ZERO-new-walls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The first new wall project, where no barrier currently exists, is anticipated to start in April,' a Customs and Border Protection spokesman said, identifying a Texas county as the project's location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Hollywood VIP sex club...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6804327/Inside-look-latest-VIP-sex-club-Hollywood-orgies-everywhere.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com got an exclusive look inside Kinky Rabbit Club, the latest VIP sex party in Hollywood where A-listers can fulfill their erotic fantasies in mansions during themed events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Man Who Used HIV As A Weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6812747/The-Man-Used-HIV-Weapon-Daryll-Rowes-victims-speak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lenny, an American man living in Brighton, discovered he was HIV positive in February 2016 after Daryll Rowe secretly ripped the condom they were using.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  U.S. charges Chinese intelligence officers for BOEING jet engine data hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.computerworld.com/article/2491302/chinese-man-indicted-over-theft-of-boeing-c-17-secrets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.computerworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese man has been indicted for allegedly directing two China-based hackers to infiltrate Boeing and other defense contractors to steal gigabytes of documents describing U.S. military aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was called 1,800 times: When robots collect bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/16/robocalls-about-your-bills-can-pour-in-every-day-all-day.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A quarter of consumers receive calls each month about a debt they owe. For some people, the calls are relentless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth smuggler busted as iPhone GPS mishap takes to border checkpoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickondetroit.com/news/man-trying-to-transport-meth-in-canada-busted-when-navigation-takes-him-to-port-huron-bridge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickondetroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who was allegedly attempting to transport meth from Montreal to Calgary was busted when his iPhone navigation took him to a border checkpoint - Port Huron's Blue Water Bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg very bad week of very bad year...</title>
      <link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/technology/zuckerberg-s-bad-week-gets-worse-with-fb-live-of-christchurch-shooting-119031600585_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.business-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negative sentiment toward Facebook, as measured in tweets on Twitter, rose to the highest in almost eight months on Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT DELAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f68cafee91a14ffd9e3485b656b3dd6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Theresa May worked Friday to pull off an against-the-odds rescue for her European Union divorce deal, after Parliament voted to postpone Brexit to avert a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon budget proposal in three words: 'China, China, China'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a6decfb9a37c4fe4936ecb5e252c86d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Chinese bombers. Chinese hypersonic missiles. Chinese cyberattacks. Chinese anti-satellite weapons. To a remarkable degree, the 2020 Pentagon budget proposal is shaped by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PARIS BURNING</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/73e7376d4ada4675bd31ea3ae4034c8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French yellow vest protesters set life-threatening fires, smashed up luxury stores in Paris and clashed with police Saturday in the 18th straight weekend of demonstrations against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left or center? Dems mull best options to beat Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1b04d2c8fa03483da8a54198b0116224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBUQUE, Iowa (AP) — As she waited to meet former Colorado Gov. John Hickenlooper at a recent house party in Dubuque, attorney Connie O'Connor was anxious about the liberal direction of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE' ACCUSED OF PLAGIARIZING SKETCHES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/saturday-night-live-accused-plagiarizing-1203163172/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Saturday Night Live” aired last October a sketch about a pumpkin patch where the employees, much to the consternation of the proprietor, engage in sexual intercourse with the product. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller says former Trump campaign aide STILL aiding investigation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/434213-former-trump-aide-still-cooperating-on-several-ongoing-probes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller and attorneys for former Trump campaign aide Richard Gates asked a federal judge to further delay his sentencing on account of his cooperation in “several ongoing investigations.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town holds funeral for crocodile...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/australian-town-holds-funeral-crocodile-104801379.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Elton John's "Crocodile Rock" playing in the background and a tribute from Steve Irwin's family, a small seaside town in north Queensland bade farewell to a beloved community member Saturday, a saltwater crocodile. Affectionately known as Bismarck, Fluffy or Gary, depending on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Mason's Todd Zywicki says the senator and presidential hopeful has inherited the ideas of Louis Brandeis without learning the lessons of overregulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Solomoon': Newlyweds Spend Honeymoon -- Away From Each Other!</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/03/15/solomoon-a-new-trend-where-newlyweds-spend-their-honeymoon-away-from-each-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Instagram, almost 1,500 posts display the reality of this new trend, where newlyweds decide to vacation alone or with friends after the wedding rather than with each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students rip Chelsea Clinton for 'stoking' hatred behind slaughter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/16/nyu-students-confront-chelsea-clinton-say-she-stoked-hatred-behind-new-zealand-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students blasted Chelsea Clinton at a vigil at New York University for the 49 worshipers massacred at two New Zealand mosques, claiming the former first daughter “stoked” the hatred tha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel launches dozens of Gaza strikes after rockets target Tel Aviv...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/two-rockets-fired-gaza-tel-aviv-area-army-211108796.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel said Friday its aircraft had struck dozens of Hamas targets in the Gaza Strip overnight in response to rockets from the Palestinian enclave, including rare fire toward its economic capital Tel Aviv. The escalation followed weeks of growing tensions and came at an especially sensitive time ahead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sins and spirits: Thais flock to tattoo fest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sins-spirits-thais-flock-tattoo-fest-002955976.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The possessed devotees appear to be on the verge of attack but are quickly restrained and coaxed back to normal. Every year, thousands of devotees gather at Wat Bang Phra for the annual festival, which celebrates the traditional Sak Yant tattoos. The symbols favoured by devotees vary from astrological</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan recovers after shot with 74 airgun pellets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/orangutan-recovers-shot-74-airgun-pellets-indonesia-091444900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An orangutan is slowly recovering after being shot with 74 airgun pellets in Indonesian, an official said Saturday. The 30-year-old female was found severely wounded in Aceh province last Sunday after officials received a tipoff from villagers. "The orangutans came to a villager's plantation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apprentice Meets Master as Bolsonaro Visits Washington...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apprentice-meets-master-bolsonaro-visits-110001016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Jair Bolsonaro, who revels in the “Trump of the Tropics’’ moniker, the trip offers him the opportunity to both drum up business for Brazil and to relaunch his image on the global stage after an underwhelming debut at the World Economic Forum in Davos. Few -- if any -- Latin American presidents have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who stood up to gunman probably saved lives...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ccf69233a36446c2b6c9e92f3e6cf417</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHRISTCHURCH, New Zealand (AP) — When the gunman advanced toward the mosque, killing those in his path, Abdul Aziz didn't hide. Instead, he picked up the first thing he could find, a credit card...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once sanctuaries, houses of worship struggle with security...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3c9532e4da55471f86bb37cf9c1ab255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — A rabbi who packs a gun. A church installing security cameras. A police car protecting a mosque. Houses of worship have traditionally been places of refuge where strangers are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News from The Associated Press, the definitive source for independent journalism from every corner of the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Showbiz, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheBlaze is your source for news and information, original reporting and insightful opinions about the stories that matter most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news, politics, culture, technology, health, and more, through its articles, podcasts, videos, and flagship magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL IN THE FAMILY: Barack Obama's brother asks if Michelle is 'Michael'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/all-in-the-family-barack-obamas-brother-asks-if-michelle-is-michael/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh boy! Barack Obama’s half brother, Malik, took to Twitter on Thursday to ask if Michelle is actually “Michael”. Is Michelle Michael? — Malik Obama (@ObamaMalik) March 14, 2019 “Is Michelle Michael?” Obama asked, referring to a conspiracy theory that the former First Lady is actually a man. In 2017, Alex Jones claimed to have …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rated the #1 political newsletter by political professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times opinion columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRAP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain — and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>http://www.jewishworldreview.com/0219/shapiro_archives.php3#.XG2A5KJKhhE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jewishworldreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELLO! brings you the latest celebrity &amp; royal news from the UK &amp; around the world, magazine exclusives, fashion, beauty, lifestyle news, celeb babies, weddings, pregnancies and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official Website of The Sean Hannity Show. Sean Hannity is a multimedia superstar, spending four hours a day every day reaching out to millions of Americans on radio, television and the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ city plans Universal Basic Income test...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/newark-universal-basic-income</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting a paycheck for doing nothing could be in the future for residents of New Jersey&amp;#39;s largest city. &amp;nbsp;Newark Mayor Ras Baraka says the city is going to study a pilot program to provide a universal basic income, or basically guaranteeing income for all residents whether they have a job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch CBSN the live news stream from CBS News and get the latest, breaking news headlines of the day for national news and world news today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hannity was the night's No. 1 cable news show, in both total viewers and the adults 25-54 demo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Magazine energizes people around shared interests, igniting important conversations on the news, politics, style, and culture that drive the world forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Watch detects irregular heart beat in large study...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190316134851-5cktc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-HEART/APPLE (PIX):Apple Watch detects irregular heart beat in large U.S. study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected white supremacist charged with murder after New Zealand mosque shootings...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190316053229-5x7ok</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWZEALAND-SHOOTOUT/ (UPDATE 4, TV, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 4-Suspected white supremacist charged with murder after New Zealand mosque shootings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple probes continue...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190315143150-hb2lr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA-GATES (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Mueller, in U.S. court filing, says multiple probes continue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke talks with USA suspended?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190315113112-81ujt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-North Korea may suspend nuclear talks with 'gangster-like' U.S. - diplomat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston news, sports, politics, opinion, entertainment, weather and obituaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
