<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CLIPPERS shocking moves shake up NBA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nba/columnist/jeff-zillgitt/2019/07/06/kawhi-leonard-paul-george-los-angeles-clippers/1663575001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Clippers instantly became a championship contender by acquiring Kawhi Leonard and Paul George.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Women's World Cup Make TV Ratings History?</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ianquillen/2019/07/06/will-womens-world-cup-gold-cup-finals-make-tv-ratings-history/#754341c92a5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether or not the single-game mark falls, a triple-header of finals in major competitions could make Sunday the most-watched day of soccer in American TV history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1200 for a POD? Renters in LA, San Fran opting for bunk beds in communal homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7218067/Renters-Los-Angeles-San-Francisco-paying-1200-month-bunk-bed-shared-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PodShare, founded in 2012, with locations in LA and San Francisco, has become a popular choice for Americans who can't afford rent, with each bed costing between $35 and $50 per night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democracies to lose economic dominance as 'authoritarian capitalism' rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/05/democracies-are-on-track-to-lose-their-global-economic-dominance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week's mini-drama over President Donald Trump's Fourth of July speech, with all its military accompaniment, shouldn't distract anyone from the far more significant story of global democratic decline on this 243rd anniversary of American Independence, Frederick Kempe writes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 Haitian Migrants Apprehended Since June 10 at Texas Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/07/06/1000-haitian-migrants-apprehended-since-june-10-at-texas-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Del Rio Sector Border Patrol agents apprehended more than 1,000 Haitian migrants who illegally crossed the border from Mexico since June 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Perks of Being a Psychopath...</title>
      <link>https://psychcentral.com/blog/the-perks-of-being-a-psychopath/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;psychcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Always treat everyone with respect. You never know who is secretly a psychopath." - Alex Wayne, Diagnosis How does one go about identifying a psychopath? It's not easy, but researchers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala tries to turbocharge campaign but faces lingering questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Kamala-Harris-tries-to-turbocharge-her-campaign-14075701.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa - When Sen. Kamala Harris arrived in Iowa for the first time since her attention-grabbing debate performance, she did so with a revamped stump speech and almost double her previous forces in Iowa and New Hampshire, all part of a retooled approach her campaign hopes will ensure her breakout moment fosters lasting momentum.  Harris' campaign team says many of these changes were planned far earlier. But they are coming at a pivotal moment - just after the first Democratic debate and as the candidates are separating into more-distinct tiers. Harris' push to sharpen her message and expand her operation is shifting the overall dynamic of the contest for the Democratic presidential nominee.  In returning to Iowa this week, Harris jettisoned a stump speech that centered on the vague notion of "speaking truth" and offered little clear reason for her candidacy. Instead, she is promoting the idea of a changing country - "our America" - in contrast with what she characterizes as President Donald Trump's effort to take the nation back into the past.  She has also begun embracing her controversial history as a prosecutor instead of shying away from it, telling voters that her record of taking on predators (she includes in that "big banks, big pharmaceutical companies, transnational gangs, and more") equips her to prosecute the "predator living in the White House."  And after months of criticism from Democrats in Iowa and New Hampshire who said they felt she had not made them a priority, Harris has hired 35 additional staffers in Iowa in recent days, raising her total in the state to about 65 - one of the largest teams on the ground here, according to people familiar with Iowa campaign operations. And she hired 25 additional staffers in New Hampshire.  "I think, early on, she didn't have much ground game in Iowa in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we living in simulated universe? Scientists believe possible...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/are-we-living-simulated-universe-here-s-what-scientists-say-ncna1026916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If we are living in a simulation, then the cosmos that we are observing is just a tiny piece of the totality of physical existence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Gavin-Newsom-State-of-Emergency-Kern-County512294532.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following the two latest earthquakes that rattled Southern California residents, Gov. Gavin Newsom issued a state of emergency in San Bernardino County Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN ANDREAS DANGER?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1149702/california-earthquake-will-big-one-erupt-san-andreas-fault-line-usgs-earthquake-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA was yesterday rocked by a magnitude 6.4 quake, with the earthquake’s epicentre close to Los Angeles. So, will the long-feared Big One erupt along the nearby San Andreas fault line?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS boots police officers because customer 'did not feel safe'...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/arizona-news/tempe-police-officers-claim-they-were-asked-to-leave-starbucks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Tempe Police officers were forced to take their coffee to go at Starbucks in the East Valley city, where officers claim an employee asked them to leave the store on July 4th. FOX 10&amp;#39;s Justin Lum reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump presses for contentious census citizenship question despite legal uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-census/trump-presses-for-contentious-census-citizenship-question-despite-legal-uncertainty-idUSKCN1U01LG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Friday refused to back down over its bid to put a co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGER STADIUM ROCKING DURING GAME...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/sports/dodgers/la-sp-dodger-stadium-earthquake-20190705-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dodger Stadium felt the 7.1 earthquake that shook Southern California on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW WARNING: Chance of another huge tremor in next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-huge-earthquake-forecast-southern-california-20190705-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is an earthquake sequence,” says seismologist Lucy Jones. “It will be ongoing. It is clearly a very energetic sequence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFTERSHOCK EVERY MINUTE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/06/us/ridgecrest-residents-earthquake-aftershock-trnd/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earth hasn't stopped moving under Southern California since Thursday, when a powerful 6.4-magnitude foreshock rattled Ridgecrest and its surrounding cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Threats to Theater Owners Screening Pro-Life Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/07/05/police-investigate-death-threats-to-movie-theater-owners-screening-pro-life-film-unplanned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have been called in to investigate death threats made to Canadian theater owners who scheduled to screen the pro-life movie Unplanned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of NSA leak lingers as stolen document case winds up...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f84c3f7f9cb54ef7aaab16acbbc6f61a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
STREISAND: HATE SOUND OF VOICE; DON'T SING UNLESS HAVE TO...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/barbra-streisands-heartbreaking-secret-battle-17479340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: One of the all-time greats hates the sound of her own voice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Human Rights Foundation Urges Minaj to Call Off Saudi Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/music/2019/07/human-rights-foundation-urges-nicki-minaj-to-call-off-saudi-arabia-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minaj faced a similar controversy back in 2015 when she agreed to perform for former president José Eduardo dos Santos and his family in Angola.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLITCH: Voters 'issued two ballots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-48890803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Conservative members received more than one paper to vote for the next PM, the BBC learns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS, VIDEOS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7218883/Magnitude-7-1-earthquake-rocks-Southern-California-middle-Los-Angeles-Dodgers-game.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquake hit about 11 miles from Ridgecrest, the town in Kern County which was very close to the epicenter of the magnitude 6.4 quake that was felt on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS ANCHORS TAKE COVER ON LIVE TV...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/news-anchors-take-shelter-on-live-tv-during-earthquake-watch-1203260443/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southern California was left rattled on Friday night for the second time in as many days after a 7.1 magnitude quake -centered, again, near the town of Ridgecrest – rocked the city of Los Ang…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Large-Earthquake-Shakes-for-Up-to-40-Seconds-512288562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after a powerful quake rattled Southern California, residents across Southern California were shaken by a 7.1 temblor that rattled for up to 40 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.1 MAG ROCKS CA</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/05/6-9-quake-rocks-southern-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The quake struck at 8:21 p.m. and was centered in the same location as Thursday's. 6.4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>125 MILES N OF LA</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/07/05/magnitude-5-0-earthquake-rattles-socal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news update:  After a swarm of more than 1,400 earthquakes hit the Searles Valley region over the past two days, a magnitude 7.1 temblor — the biggest yet — struck Friday evening.  The quake hit roughly 10 and a half miles from Ridgecrest at about 8:19 p.m., the U.S. Geological Survey reports. After previously downgrading it a 6.9 magnitude, seismologist pushed it back up to the preliminary figure of 7.1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS SET FOR LANDSLIDE IN BATTLE TO BECOME PM...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/boris-johnson-set-for-landslide-in-battle-to-reach-no-10-k8j3w3j03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson is on course to enter Downing Street with a resounding victory this month, according to a poll of Conservative Party members. Mr Johnson is backed by 74 per cent with Jeremy Hunt on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia readying S-400 missiles for Turkey amid warnings of U.S. sanctions on NATO ally...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Russia-confirms-plans-to-send-S-400-anti-aircraft-14073552.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - Russia will deliver its S-400 air-defense missile system to NATO-member Turkey in the coming days, a Kremlin spokesman said Friday, in a deal likely to trigger U.S. sanctions and test the bonds of the Western military alliance.  But the scope of the possible response from Washington remains clouded by apparent conflicting messages.  President Donald Trump has publicly shown sympathy for Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's position on the Russian missile purchase. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo, however, has warned of tough measures that could include canceling the sales of F-35 fighter jets to Turkey.  For the wider NATO alliance, the Turkish deal strikes at the heart of military coordination. NATO has expressed worry that the S-400 is incompatible with its possession of the U.S.-made F-35s, and would give Russia access to secrets of its stealth technology.  For more than a year, the United States has urged Erdogan not to procure the sophisticated Russian air-defense system - a move that would bring mandatory U.S. sanctions against Turkey under a 2017 law on cooperation with "adversaries."  The U.S. measures, if carried out, would cause an extraordinary breach in U.S.-Turkey relations and almost certainly complicate ongoing negotiations between the two countries over other issues, including military strategy in Syria.  But while U.S. officials have portrayed the sanctions against Turkey as a matter of certainty, Trump refrained from taking a hard line with Erdogan over the S-400s during talks last month at the Group of 20 summit in Japan.  Trump noted that Turkey help bring U.S. jobs by paying a "tremendous amount of money" on the F-35 fighters.  Trump, speaking to reporters at the summit, said Erdogan had first sought to buy Patriot missiles but had been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activist at center of landmark case allowing flag burning faces charges after melee in front of White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Activist-at-center-of-landmark-case-allowing-flag-14074645.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Prosecutors in Washington on Friday dropped the most serious criminal charge filed against a California man whose burning of two American flags outside the White House on the Fourth of July sparked a melee between ideologically opposed groups.  Gregory Lee "Joey" Johnson, 62, of San Francisco, had faced a felony charge of assault on a police officer after two officers said they were doused with an accelerant from the burning flag that made them ill and sent them to a hospital for treatment. That charge was not pursued on Friday.  Johnson still faces other charges of inciting violence, disorderly conduct and violating the fire code, all misdemeanors.  "It was a righteous thing to do in the face of a fascist regime," Johnson said Friday outside D.C. Superior Court after being freed until his next hearing Aug. 1. He was still wearing his group's black T-shirt with the slogan "Revolution - nothing less."  Johnson said he set two flags on fire Thursday afternoon as the city was busy with residents and tourists who had come to President Donald Trump's controversial "Salute to America" Fourth of July celebration. After the first was extinguished by opponents, another flag fire occurred moments later in front of a uniformed officer for the U.S. Secret Service.  "The flag is a symbol of empire and oppression," Johnson said.  Johnson is a member of the Revolutionary Communist Party, also espouses the slogan "imagine a world without America," and he has made burning flags an integral part of his protest. It was Johnson's burning of an American flag during a march against nuclear war in Dallas in 1984 that led to a landmark 1989 Supreme Court decision overturning his conviction for "desecration of a venerated object" and making flag burning a constitutionally protected...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Florida body found in mouth of alligator...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-alligators-surround-florida-body-20190705-7qwsqyhee5db3fpqwhqom5avhi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second time in a week, a Florida body has been found with alligators nearby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town on guard after black bear strolls through subdivision...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/environment/article232303077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Fined $100,000 for 'Anti-Vax' Social Media Posts...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/doctor-fined-100000-for-anti-vax-social-media-posts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chiropractor ordered to pay $10,000 per year for 10 years for committing thought crime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90&amp;#176;! </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be84a3d282d7435aaca91c151f056a33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegals fired from Trump clubs seek White House meeting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4534e483fbf94e008622024dd0fc138b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WARNS RIVALS: I COULD ROAST YOU!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/biden-warns-democratic-rivals-hes-got-all-this-information-about-other-peoples-pasts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden let slip that his campaign was collecting dirt on his rivals for the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.4 MAG WORSENED SEISMIC STRAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-did-california-earthquake-relieve-earthquake-stress-20190705-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some imagine that moderate or large earthquakes will put off the Big One. But it's not true. The 6.4 magnitude Ridgecrest quake is a warning of the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD LAST YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-aftershocks-ridgecrest-earthquake-20190705-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southern California should expect more aftershocks from Ridgecrest earthquake, even another shaker of magnitude 5 or greater at some point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 million bacteria, 10 million viruses in 1 drop of Lake Michigan water...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/environment/ct-lake-michigan-microbes-20190705-ihsj56fbs5d4ngvyljsjsg5ao4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of scientists is seeking to understand the hidden lives of some of the most prolific but least understood life forms in the Great Lakes: microorganisms that live deep beneath the surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosion reported at University of Nevada, Reno dorm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9290036e094548a991c9f917c9bfcdfe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulation Killed the Station Wagon -- and Created the Minivan...</title>
      <link>https://www.futureofcapitalism.com/2019/07/how-regulation-killed-the-station-wagon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.futureofcapitalism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a New York Times account of the career of auto executive Lee Iacocca — different from the Times obituary of him — comes this account of the role that government regulations played in changing the family car to a minivan from a station wagon:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family angry over HOA request to remove Virgin Mary statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/oakland/2019/07/05/novi-virgin-mary-discrimination/1643640001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Novi family says their homeowners association is discriminating against them because they're Catholic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA won't launch mission to hunt deadly asteroids...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1659566/nasa-nixes-hunt-for-deadly-asteroids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An infrared telescope to find threatening asteroids is stuck in budget limbo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA to update warning threshold...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/63dbb0812a9a4cfba4f0f14f2312590d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Drones Way Busier Than Thought Over Shadow Warzone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/us-drones-are-way-busier-than-we-thought-over-this-shadow-warzone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s unmanned air force is performing a host of mission over Yemen—which means the U.S. is more involved in that war than it cares to admit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in Yellowstone geyser activity...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/07/04/us/yellowstone-volcanic-activity-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's tallest active geyser is known to be unpredictable. But if there was ever a year to witness its spectacular surge of water, this might be it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swingers descend on village for Europe's biggest sex festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9442716/swingers-worcester-village-europes-biggest-sex-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNDREDS of swingers have descended on a sleepy Worcestershire village for Europe’s biggest sex festival. Festival-goers have splashed out up to £415 for a three-day pass to Swingfields, whic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala raises only $12M...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/nation-world/article232325102.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic caterpillars spark health scare across Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jul/05/toxic-caterpillars-spark-health-scare-across-germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People suffer rashes and breathing difficulties as warm weather brings infestation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coco Gauff Magic Continues at Wimbledon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7217641/Coco-Gauff-15-makes-debut-Wimbledons-main-court-bids-continue-fairytale-tournament.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 15-year-old, from Florida in the US, has been the talk of the tournament since she beat her idol Venus Williams, 39, in the first round. She takes on Solvenian Polona Hercog today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice signals it's still fighting for citizenship census question...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/justice-department-signals-to-court-its-still-fighting-for-citizenship-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge had ordered the DOJ to explain the president's tweet and administration's position</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump adds mystery to why Pence abruptly canceled trip...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/07/05/president-trump-adds-mystery-why-vice-president-pence-canceled-trip/1656674001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Friday extended the mystery of why Vice President Mike Pence abruptly canceled a trip to New Hampshire on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone charger fire triggered VIRGIN emergency landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/07/05/virgin-atlantic-london-flight-makes-emergency-landing-phone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An overnight Virgin Atlantic flight from New York to London was forced into making an emergency landing after a phone charger triggered a fire on-board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forensics firm hit by cyber attack pay ransom...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/07/05/forensics-firm-hit-cyber-attack-pay-ransom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leading forensic science firm, which is used by the UK police to help investigate major crimes, has paid a ransom to criminals after being targeted in a cyber attack, it is understood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tunisia bans face veils in public institutions after bombing...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2019/07/tunisia-bans-face-veils-public-institutions-bombing-190705132559010.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PM Chahed cites security reasons for the niqab ban following a double suicide bombing in Tunis last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed teachers practice responding to school shootings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f5968f1050d1493db8ed781b91120384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans wearing 'teledildonic suits' can now have sex with each other over internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/790087/sex-robot-brothels-androids-teledildonics-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
