<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Musk Plan to Build New Starship Every 72 Hours So Can Colonize Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a31248703/elon-musk-spacex-build-new-starship-every-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very doable!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Heathrow Baggage Handlers Test Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-03-06/london-heathrow-baggage-handlers-test-positive-for-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Williams, NYT's Gay criticized over math flub: 'Saddest clip in TV history'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/486288-brian-williams-nyts-gay-roasted-over-math-flub-saddest-clip-in-tv-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC's Brian Williams was mocked over math on social media after quoting a tweet claiming that former 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Michael Bloomberg "could have given each American $1 million and still have money left over"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic toll of outbreak deepens, duration remains unknown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b795767f74d690056cebadf80afeb770</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow over the past five days: up 1,293, down 786, up 1,173, down 967. The Dow tumbled 800 points at the opening bell Friday. The VIX, an index known as Wall Street's fear barometer, is hovering...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Life After Bernie'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/03/06/life-after-bernie-young-left-121534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Socialists are surprisingly sanguine about Bernie Sanders—because they’re building a movement that will outlast him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALM BEFORE STORM?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/economy/ahead-coronavirus-impact-economy-added-273-000-jobs-february-n1151376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data for the February jobs report was collected before the coronavirus epidemic hit the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: COSTCO CUSTOMERS SPRAYED WITH 'DISINFECTANT' AT DOOR...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/video-costco-customers-sprayed-with-disinfectant-at-door/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As people in London attempt to stock up they're subjected to 'cattle dip' by store staff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump CDC Visit Called Off After Infection Concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-coronavirus-cdc-visit-usa-cases-white-house-latest-a9381831.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: CANNOT promise million test kits...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8082939/Dr-Anthony-Fauci-says-promise-one-million-test-kits-fortnight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Anthony Fauci, a top official at the National Institutes of Health, says he's not happy about the shortage of coronavius testing kits but he can't promise 1 million will soon be available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus Motel Ignites Clash at Epicenter of Seattle Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/coronavirus-motel-ignites-clash-at-epicenter-of-seattle-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus Motel Ignites Clash at Epicenter of Seattle Outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIQUIDITY CONCERNS</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/credit-risk-concerns-build-key-124036016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A key gauge of banking-sector risk is indicating stress in dollar funding markets as equities around the world tank on growing virus concerns and traders bet on further central bank easing.The FRA/OIS spread, a U.S. money-market benchmark that measures the difference in rates between forward-rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marauding monkeys take over govt office block and force officials to flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/marauding-monkeys-take-over-government-21643512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Troops of monkeys have raided the offices of India's top cabinet ministers and taken over, leaving ministers too scared to make eye-contact with the animals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants claim they have been stripped and beaten by Greek police...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8082767/Migrants-claim-stripped-beaten-Greek-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State-owned Turkish channel TRT published photos of topless migrants warming themselves around a fire near the Greek border, with at least one person displaying a scar on his back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Americans asked to 'self-quarantine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/06/health/self-quarantine-explainer-procedures/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With US coronavirus cases topping 220 across 19 states and the death toll climbing to more than a dozen, state governments have asked thousands of residents to seclude themselves from the rest of the community to help contain the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEB JOBS SMASH EXPECTATIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/06/us-jobs-report-february-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Labor Department reported Friday that the U.S. economy added 273,000 new jobs during the month, while the unemployment rate was 3.5%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump postpones CDC visit...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/486265-trump-postpones-cdc-visit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's planned visit to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's (CDC) headquarters in Atlanta has been postponed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob Of Teens Stomp 15-Year-Old Girl On Brooklyn Sidewalk, Steal Sneakers, Phone...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/03/06/group-stomps-girl-on-brooklyn-sidewalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said the suspects chased the victim, jumped on top of her and then punched and kicked her several times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots fighting virus by disinfecting hospitals, taking temps, preparing meals...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/robots-fighting-coronavirus-china-disinfecting-130000493.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots are being used to spray disinfectant all over the city, but they've also been used to cook rice in hospitals and dispense hand sanitizer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ammunition Sales Soar...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ammunition-sales-soar-response-coronavirus-133400231.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Coronavirus (COVID-19) hits the US, it's not just hand sanitizer and flu medications that are flying off the shelves. While Walmart and Target are running out of emergency essentials and "currently unavailable" is popping up on various Amazon searches, the rush to be prepared has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders struggles to expand supporter base after Warren exit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d84e7134e893f67b2f3751a2a581a9a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It took Joe Biden's moderate rivals just hours to unite behind his presidential campaign after they left the race. Bernie Sanders hasn't been so fortunate. Elizabeth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lights, camera... no action? Hollywood rocked...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lights-camera-no-action-hollywood-rocked-coronavirus-114156882.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blockbuster productions shut down. Hollywood is being rocked by the unprecedented challenge of the new coronavirus, insiders told AFP this week. "I have never seen anything where this many films are going to be affected all at once," said Jeff Bock, senior analyst at Exhibitor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study predicts 15 million dead, $2.4 trillion hit to global GDP...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-spreads-one-study-predicts-101552222.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Australian researchers estimate that the coronavirus may have severe consequences on the global GDP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rationing and robbery: Outbreak sparks toilet roll panic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200306075622-yv4oo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TOILETPAPER (PIX):Rationing and robbery: Coronavirus outbreak sparks toilet roll panic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTEREST RATES HEAD TOWARD ZERO</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-rates-hurtle-toward-zero-103400835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Treasury yields plummeted to record lows Friday as concern about the global economic and financial impact of the coronavirus spurred demand for havens and traders amped up bets on further central bank easing this month.“What we are seeing is symptomatic of not enough positive yielding,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise passengers off California await virus test results...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/61a4efa966c02cbda9584f7266b99802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Coronavirus test results were expected Friday for some passengers and crew aboard a cruise ship held off the California coast. The Grand Princess lay at anchor near San...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Shuns Jamal Khashoggi Doc Over Fear of Saudi Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jamal-khashoggi-doc-dissident-hollywood-shuns-saudi-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bryan Fogel's "The Dissident," about the murdered journalist Jamal Khashoggi, is having trouble finding a distributor out of fear from the Saudis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfazed gamblers, worried showgirls: Vegas on edge as virus arrives...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2020-03-05/unfazed-gamblers-worried-showgirls-las-vegas-on-edge-as-coronavirus-spreads-nationwide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears of contracting the deadly virus has yet to penetrate the psyche of Las Vegas' tourists and gamblers, but the same cannot be said of those working in sin city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mecca deserted in chilling video...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mecca-deserted-chilling-video-coronavirus-21643018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has banned pilgrimages to the Great Mosque of Mecca as they battle the coronavirus outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican reports first case...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8082259/Vatican-City-reports-case-coronavirus-days-Pope-tested-negative.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery takes the epidemic to the city-state surrounded by Italy, which has confirmed more than 3,800 cases and 148 deaths due to the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE: America does NOT have enough test kits...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8080111/Mike-Pence-admits-America-does-NOT-testing-kits-meet-coronavirus-demand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Pence revealed Thursday that the administration will not be able to follow through on its promise to deliver 1 million coronavirus testing kits by the end of the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTEREST RATES HEAD TOWARD ZERO</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/bond-king-gundlach-says-fed-panicked-and-short-term-rates-are-headed-toward-zero.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When I say panicked, it doesn't mean it's not justified," DoubleLine Capital CEO Jeffrey Gundlach said about the Fed's surprise cut this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Cell Signal, No Wi-Fi, No Problem. Growing Up Inside America's 'Quiet Zone'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/06/no-cell-signal-no-wi-fi-no-problem-growing-up-inside-americas-quiet-zone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREEN BANK, W.Va. — Viral dance memes and dance challenges on TikTok largely bypass Green Bank, W.Va. So do viral</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN DROPS OUT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b475643fb3faf2ab543b68da8743308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Elizabeth Warren ended her once-promising presidential campaign on Thursday after failing to finish higher than third place in any of the 18 states that have voted so far. While...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Shuns Jamal Khashoggi Doc Over Fear of Saudi Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jamal-khashoggi-doc-dissident-hollywood-shuns-saudi-fears/ ?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bryan Fogel's "The Dissident," about the murdered journalist Jamal Khashoggi, is having trouble finding a distributor out of fear from the Saudis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major crimes surge in New York City...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-york-city-sees-surge-in-crimes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly released statistics show a big jump in crime last month compared to a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMIE DIMON EMERGENCY HEART SURGERY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/jpmorgan-says-ceo-jamie-dimon-is-recuperating-after-emergency-heart-surgery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JPMorgan said Thursday that CEO Jamie Dimon is recuperating after having emergency heart surgery,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST CEO warns plunging domestic travel has '9/11-like feel'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/900284/southwest-airlines-ceo-warns-dropoff-domestic-travel-over-coronavirus-911like-feel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mounting concern over the new coronavirus outbreak has caused school closures and movie premiere pushbacks, and now the crisis' effect on the aviation industry is drawing comparisons to 9/11. Southwest Airlines CEO Gary Kelly told CNBC on Thursday that the company has lost several hundred million dollars in a week's time thanks to a decline in bookings amid increasing fears over COVID-19. Kelly added that the drop-off was 'noticeable' and 'precipitous' and has continued declining on a daily basis. When prompted by CNBC's Phil LeBeau over whether the drop was reminiscent of former dips in demand spurred by the 2003 SARS outbreak or the events of Sept. 11, 2001, Kelly said the new coronavirus outbreak was more like the latter. 'It has a 9/11-like feel,' Kelly said. He explained that post-9/11 travel fallout was motivated by 'fear' rather than being economically driven, saying fear is 'really what's manifested this time' with the new coronavirus outbreak. Kelly told LeBeau he thought the dip in bookings was an 'overreaction' but that Southwest is financially prepared to handle the fallout. The outbreak's effect has been felt heavily in the U.S. stock market, which has rotated between sinking and soaring over the last week, and it has caused at least 11 U.S. deaths and four states to declare emergencies. Marianne Dodson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZILLOW co-founder trying to unload LA manse for $7 million over Zestimate...</title>
      <link>https://therealdeal.com/la/2020/03/05/zillow-co-founder-spencer-rascoff-lists-brentwood-park-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;therealdeal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spencer Rascoff, the co-founder and former CEO of Zillow, has put his Brentwood Park estate on the market for $24 million, according to Redfin. The asking price is $7 million over the "Zestimate," or Zillow's appraisal of what the home is worth.  Property records show that Rascoff paid $19.7 mill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banks ready disaster plans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-us-banks-ready-disaster-plans-sources-183300327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large US banks have begun testing crisis measures in case of a broader coronavirus outbreak that prevents staff from going to work, banking sources told AFP. JPMorgan Chase, Morgan Stanley, Goldman Sachs and Citigroup have asked hundreds of workers to work from home as part of emergency preparedness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First known human-to-animal transmission...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/a-dog-has-a-low-level-coronavirus-infection-in-first-known-human-to-animal-transmission/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pet dog in Hong Kong has a "low-level" infection of the coronavirus that causes COVID-19 in people, in what may be the first known human-to-animal transmission of the novel coronavirus that has sickened more than 90,000 people worldwide. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Sanders struggles to expand base...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/nation-world/story/2020-03-05/sanders-struggles-to-expand-supporter-base-after-warren-exit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took Joe Biden's moderate rivals just hours to unite behind him after they left the presidential race, but Bernie Sanders hasn't been so fortunate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodies 'pile up' in Iran morgue...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/05/middleeast/iran-coronavirus-morgues-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of bodies sheathed in black bags line the floor of an Iranian morgue, while workers in protective suits and masks busily walk among them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French politician in serious condition...</title>
      <link>https://translate.google.com/translate?sl=auto&amp;tl=en&amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.francebleu.fr%2Finfos%2Fsante-sciences%2Fun-depute-alsacien-hospitalise-pour-suspicion-de-coronavirus-1583440846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;translate.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER warns users...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/486220-tinder-warns-users-to-maintain-social-distance-amid-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dating app Tinder is warning users to take precautions amid the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced into runoff, Houston Dem investigates opponent he says may not exist...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Dutton-forced-into-rare-runoff-investigates-15108031.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. Harold Dutton said Thursday he has hired a private investigator to look into the candidacy of Natasha Ruiz, an opponent who forced him into a runoff despite never establishing a presence in the race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime FOXNEWS correspondent Wendell Goler dead at 70...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/wendell-goler-longtime-fox-news-white-house-correspondent-dead-at-70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Fox News White House correspondent Wendell Goler died this week at age 70.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venture firm SEQUOIA sounds alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/sequoia-capital-alerts-companies-about-coronavirus-economic-fallout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sequoia Capital sent out a memo to founders and CEOs of its portfolio companies about the worsening economic situation on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishing staff walks out over Woody Allen memoir...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/05/litlte-brown-staff-stages-walkout-in-support-of-ronan-and-dylan-farrow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staff at Little, Brown publishers have staged a walkout in support of Ronan Farrow and his sister Dylan Farrow, following its parent company’s plans to publish Woody Allen’s memoir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Such Elderly People Run America?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/03/why-are-these-people-so-freaking-old/607492/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanders is too old. So is Biden. Trump too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney could derail Republican subpoena targeting Bidens...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/05/hunter-biden-subpoena-mitt-romney-122207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Utah Republican is concerned the push appears intended to undermine a Trump rival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Agents Ignore Sanctuary Law, Make Arrest In Front Of San Fran Courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/05/ice-agents-ignore-sanctuary-law-san-francisco-courthouse-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local officials were irate Thursday over the arrest by federal Immigration and Customs Enforcement agents of an individual as he entered San Francisco courthouse for a hearing in violation of the city's sanctuary law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN plotting dream 'MONDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL' booth: Michaels, Manning...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/05/espn-plotting-dream-monday-night-football-booth-al-michaels-and-peyton-manning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thinking large and outside the box, ESPN plans to attempt to acquire Al Michaels from NBC Sports for “Monday Night Football,” The Post has learned. ESPN would like to team Michaels with…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's First Cloned Cat Passes Away At 18...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/03/04/worlds-first-cloned-cat-cc-lived-long-normal-happy-life-before-her-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first cloned cat named "Copy Cat" or "CC" for short, has passed away at the age of 18 after veterinarians diagnosed her with kidney failure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How blood plasma from recovered patients could help treat...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/03/05/how-blood-plasma-from-recovered-patients-could-help-treat-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The approach is based on the idea that antibodies developed by recovered patients might strengthen the immune system of new patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House sidelines health secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/05/white-house-alex-azar-coronavirus-122250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HHS Secretary Alex Azar has gone from the face of President Donald Trump's virus team to a supporting character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton blames Lewinsky affair on job pressures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8078733/Bill-Clinton-says-having-sex-Monica-Lewinsky-manage-anxieties.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former President makes the explosive claims in an interview featured in a new documentary series about his wife Hillary Clinton, called 'Hillary', out on Hulu Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans see Joe wins as setback...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/486042-republicans-rooting-for-sanders-see-biden-wins-as-setback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican lawmakers are surprised and disappointed by the results of Super Tuesday, which firmly re-established former Vice President Joe Biden as the front-runner for the Democratic presidential nomination and dealt Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to take questions at 1st TV town hall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c03cd0c8f2a41ad0300092fff48ee4f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump will field questions at his first TV town hall of the 2020 election cycle Thursday in the city that helped to shape a would-be rival, former Vice President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein being moved to Rikers despite bid to stay at hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/harvey-weinstein-being-moved-to-rikers-despite-bid-to-stay-at-bellevue-sources-say/2313943/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sources confirm Weinstein is being moved to the Rikers North Infirmary Unit from Bellevue. Those sources believe he will be put in protective custody in a “dorm cell” setting with round-the-clock supervision and medical supervision as needed. Weinstein’s team pushed hard to have him remain at Bellevue until sentencing, arguing he needed ongoing medical care connected to a hospital….</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASTER FEAR 2020...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c57bc457c0c1c02a910c1564d8f76715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BETHLEHEM, West Bank (AP) — Palestinian officials on Thursday closed the storied Church of the Nativity in the biblical city of Bethlehem indefinitely over fears of the new coronavirus, weeks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAVE TO THE APPLE:  Gadgets for tech giants made with coerced Uighur labor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f9a92b8dfd3cae379b57622dd801dd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NANCHANG, China (AP) — In a lively Muslim quarter of Nanchang city, a sprawling Chinese factory turns out computer screens, cameras and fingerprint scanners for a supplier to international tech...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea tests hundreds of thousands...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/south-korea-tests-hundreds-thousands-210000450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Highly contagious and manifesting in some with little or no symptoms, the coronavirus has the world struggling to keep up. But when it comes to containing the epidemic, one country may be cracking the code -- by doubling down on testing.South Korea is experiencing the largest virus epidemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS bans personal cups...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/starbucks-bans-personal-cups-over-coronavirus-161236531.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reusable cups are in vogue for reducing waste but are no longer welcome at Starbucks cafes over fears of the coronavirus, the coffee chain announced. "We are pausing the use of personal cups and 'for here' ware in our stores," Rossann Williams, an executive vice president, said in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore:  Lying about where you've been gets 6 months of jail... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/singapore-working-round-clock-coronavirus-153100020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The system relies on surveillance footage, police, and a dedicated team of contact tracers, who map out where patients went before they got COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi empties Islam's holiest site... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-empties-islams-holiest-sterilisation-161118787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia on Thursday emptied Islam's holiest site for sterilisation over fears of the new coronavirus, an unprecedented move after the kingdom suspended the year-round umrah pilgrimage. State television relayed stunning images of an empty white-tiled area surrounding the Kaaba -– a large black</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REGRET...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200305151143-v7hi5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/SCHUMER (URGENT):Democratic U.S. Senator Schumer expresses regret for Supreme Court comments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christ's birthplace in Bethlehem quarantined...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200305112530-ck0oy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PALESTINIANS-CHURCH (URGENT):Bethlehem's Church of the Nativity ordered closed over coronavirus fears</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
