<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Surrounded by controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/17/after-years-of-being-squeaky-clean-the-federal-reserve-is-surrounded-by-controversy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve has a big meeting on tap next week, one that will be held under the cloud of an ethical dilemma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centenarians Reveal Secrets To Living Past 100: Active, Social, Optimistic...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/09/16/what-is-the-key-to-a-long-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's something that used to be rare, but it’s becoming much more common. More people are living to 100, especially in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken deletes tweet saying US would 'stand with people of Hong Kong'...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/blinken-deletes-tweet-saying-us-070259808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Secretary of State Antony Blinken deleted a tweet that said the United States would “stand with the people of Hong Kong”, a post in which he accused Beijing of weakening the city’s long-term political stability. He posted the message after seven Hong Kong opposition district councillors were disqualified this week, with authorities declaring that the oaths taken by them were invalid. A spokesman for the Chinese foreign ministry’s Hong Kong office issued a statement on Friday strongly opposing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France recalls envoys...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-58604677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "exceptional decision" follows a pact between Australia, the US and UK, which scuppered a French deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER redirects 'Taiwan' search to 'China'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/twitter-cedes-taiwan-to-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has finally taken control of Taiwan, according to social networking giant Twitter, which redirects some searches for the word Taiwan to results for the word China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC restaurant host attacked over status request...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-texas-new-york-new-york-city-coronavirus-pandemic-355b61677d4996c42c11b1f12dd8106c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A host at a popular New York City restaurant was assaulted by three women from Texas after she asked for proof they had been vaccinated against COVID-19, police said. The three women punched the host at Carmine's on the Upper West Side repeatedly and broke her necklace Thursday afternoon after she asked for proof of vaccination, which is required to dine inside at a restaurant in New York City, police said in a news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan 'preparing for WAR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3682106/japan-preparing-for-war-military-drills-senkaku-islands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has claimed Japan is “preparing for war” as it stages its first major military exercised for nearly 30 years. The defence drills stoked already rising tensions between the neighbo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police chief drops request for armed National Guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/capitol-police-chief-dropped-request-for-armed-national-guard-to-be-on-standby-for-saturday-s-rally-after-pentagon-discussions/ar-AAOyIgl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Senate security official said the original request did not follow proper protocol. Chief J. Thomas Manger instead asked for troops who would be unarmed, other than batons, which was approved by the Department of Defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan lab created virus '10,000-times stronger than usual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3681845/wuhan-lab-coronavirus-10000-stronger-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WUHAN lab created coronavirus strains that were up to 10,000-times stronger than usual — amid fears a virus could have escaped when a technician was bitten by a mouse. Bombshell documents have em…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK leaders worry gotten too big to control...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/facebook-leaders-are-reportedly-worried-their-service-has-gotten-too-big-to-control-we-created-the-machine-and-can-t-control-the-machine/ar-AAOyi0R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With nearly 3 billion users around the world, Facebook leaders are reportedly worried about their inability to control the massive social network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Bans FOX Drone From Photographing...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/biden-admin-bans-drones-from-photographing-immigration-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration this week banned the media from using a drone to take pictures of the U.S.-Mexico border just as tens of thousands of immigrants poured across it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom signals more to come AFTER recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/California-vaccine-mandate-COVID-Newsom-recall-21-16464013.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democrats have speculated there's a 'silent majority' of those who would favor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence preps for potential '24 run amid rocky headlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/17/politics/pence-2024-run/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Pence is adding staffers for his brand-new office in downtown Washington -- inching closer to a possible White House run even as his standing worsens with former President Donald Trump and his base of supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 lions, 3 tigers at Smithsonian Zoo infected...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2021/09/6-lions-3-tigers-at-smithsonian-national-zoo-being-treated-for-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six African lions, two Amur tigers and a Sumatran tiger at the Smithsonian National Zoo are being treated for coronavirus, the zoo said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal sprays aim to block...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vaccine-nasal-sprays-aim-shut-160240077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could delivering Covid-19 immunity directly to the nose -- the area of the body via which it is most likely to be transmitted -- help conquer the pandemic?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENCY PUMPED UP APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestreet.com/investing/apple-verizon-bonds-and-others-are-bought-by-the-federal-reserve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple and Verizon bonds are among those bought by the Federal Reserve in the agency's effort to support the corporate-debt market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch are world's tallest people  --  but they're shrinking!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/sep/17/dutch-are-worlds-tallest-people-but-theyre-shrinking-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poorer diet may explain why the lofty lowlanders are at least 1cm shorter than the previous generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Growing Medicine-Filled Plants To Replace Injections...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/vaccines-salad-growing-plants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say if they're successful, the public could eat plant-based mRNA vaccines -- which could also survive at room temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Wealthiest Families Gained $312 Billion Over Past Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/world-s-wealthiest-families-gained-312-billion-over-past-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World’s Wealthiest Families Gained $312 Billion Over Past Year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Loomer Has 'Brutal' Case of Covid After Claiming No Worse Than Food Poisoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/laura-loomer-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right-wing activist Laura Loomer confirmed this week she has COVID-19 and the symptoms have been "brutal."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER CONGRESSMAN TO STEP ASIDE AFTER MAGA THREATS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/dark-omen-in-rep-anthony-gonzalezs-retirement/?amp#click=https://t.co/k5GmrYiZdw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A slap in the face for delusional Republicans who want to pretend the GOP is anything but a pro-insurrection Trump cult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Plays Down Concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/09/16/nbcs_kelly_odonnell_to_psaki_whats_up_with_president_bidens_coughing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC White House correspondent Kelly O'Donnell asked about President Biden appearing to have a mild cough or cold during his Thursday speech on his tax plan.  ""I don't think it's an issue of concern," White House press secretary Jen Psaki said.  KELLY O'DONNELL: We've seen [Biden] on many occasions where he has a repeated cough? What is the situation with that cough and is that a concern?...Is there an explanation for why he coughs so frequently in situations like that? I'm sure you saw it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 40%  want to sleep with sex robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/more-40-people-would-sleep-25009646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men were more likely to be up for a romp with a robot, with 48% saying they would. The survey also revealed anxieties about job losses to AI, with cashiers and drivers in the firing line</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands die each year and no one claims their bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Tens-of-thousands-die-each-year-in-the-United-16466973.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARICOPA COUNTY, Ariz. - Twenty miles outside Phoenix in a desolate cemetery, a funeral...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why some fish are 'junk,' others are protected. Study points to bias against native species...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-09-fish-junk-bias-native-species.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Rypel grew up fishing on Wisconsin's pristine lakes and rivers. With just a worm on his hook, he caught suckers, gar, sunfish and other native fish he never saw in his game fishing magazines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Passes 50,000 Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/09/17/grim-milestone-florida-50000-covid-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one-fourth of those COVID-19 deaths occurred this summer as the state battled a fierce surge in infections fueled by the Delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro to flout rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/sep/17/jair-bolsonaro-covid-vaccine-new-york-un-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil’s president claims he has not received a Covid-19 vaccine – but his immunization records have been locked away for 100 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies Getting Rid of Drug Tests Because Can't Find Enough Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3d7kx/companies-employers-drug-tests-labour-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global labour shortage is forcing companies like Amazon to stop punishing employees for recreational drug use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov orders 6 entry points along border shut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/16/politics/greg-abbott-six-points-of-entry-shut-down-mexico-border/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said Thursday he has directed the Texas Department of Public Safety and the Texas National Guard to shut down six points of entry along the US-Mexico border amid a surge in migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Illegal marijuana farms take West's scarce water...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-environment-and-nature-oregon-droughts-marijuana-333e813d352fd2343e3adfe4f954e61a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA PINE, Ore. (AP) — Jack Dwyer pursued a dream of getting back to the land by moving in 1972 to an idyllic, tree-studded parcel in Oregon with a creek running through it. “We were going to grow our own food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans encroaching on grizzly territory. Can we live together?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/sep/17/humans-encroaching-grizzly-bear-territory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’re more likely to be killed by lightning than a grizzly bear. But as humans encroach on bear territory, tensions rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we eating ourselves to extinction?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2021/sep/17/are-we-eating-ourselves-to-extinction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not just animals that are at risk of dying out, the world’s crops are in rapid decline. Here’s why it matters what is on your plate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: COVID Evolving Into More Transmissible Virus; 'Better At Traveling Through Air'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-evolving-airborne-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a positive note, study authors say certain face coverings usually cut the amount of exhaled viral particles in half.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin 'killed self' after separated from 'human lover'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3679902/dolphin-named-peter-killed-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PETER the dolphin fell in love with a human woman – but when the two separated he was so heartbroken he took his own life. The six-year-old bottlenose dolphin had a romance with 23-year-old r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO over Air Force base?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3679046/tic-tac-ufo-us-space-force/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “TIC-TAC” shaped UFO has been spotted flying and appearing to shapeshift near a US Space Force base, a skywatcher has claimed. Jason Suraci filmed several strange orbs and pill-like o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau rolled dice on snap election. Voters will decide whether gamble pays off...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trudeau-rolled-the-dice-on-a-snap-election-canadian-voters-will-decide-whether-his-gamble-pays-off/ar-AAOydoB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When he called the early vote, the prime minister bet voters would reward his handling of the pandemic with a majority. It's been a bumpier ride than he might have expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA advisers to meet on highly charged issue of boosters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fda-advisers-to-meet-on-highly-charged-issue-of-whether-to-recommend-coronavirus-vaccine-boosters/ar-AAOxOyX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has said it wants to begin offering boosters next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Behind 'French Fox News' Could Torment Macron...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/billionaire-behind-the-french-fox-news-could-torment-macron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Behind ‘the French Fox News’ Could Torment Macron</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Hostess At NYC Restaurant Attacked By Tourists After Asking For Proof Of Vax...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/09/17/carmines-hostess-attacked-indoor-dining-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is exactly what some restaurant owners feared when enforcement of the city's vaccine mandate took effect Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviews roundup: LIL NAS X new album impresses critics...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/montero-reviews-roundup-lil-nas-103503073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 15-track album has prompted many positive reactions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New disclosures show how General tried to check Trump. They could also further politicize military...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-disclosures-show-how-gen-mark-a-milley-tried-to-check-trump-they-could-also-further-politicize-the-military/ar-AAOy6s1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters say the country’s top officer sought to protect the Constitution, but some fear his actions could compound existing problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oath Keepers founder draws scrutiny from federal officials, followers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/oath-keepers-founder-draws-scrutiny-from-federal-officials-and-followers/ar-AAOxRIN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The private army that leader Stewart Rhodes boasts of is largely a myth. The real danger, extremism analysts say, is his ability to spread violent far-right propaganda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 10% of Kentucky deaths since June were under age 50, a fivefold increase...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/coronavirus/article254284698.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andy Beshear says the deadly virus is taking a toll on hospital staff and intensive care beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida county celebrated Hispanic Heritage Month with dancing Taco GIF. Outrage ensued...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Florida-county-celebrated-Hispanic-Heritage-Month-16466004.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The taco was supposed to be harmless, entertaining even.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St Influencers Making $500,000, Topping Bankers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-17/social-media-influencers-income-advertising-wall-street-products</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finance firms have long struggled to reach young and new customers — until now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 10,000 migrants await processing under bridge in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/572712-more-than-10000-haitian-migrants-await-processing-under-bridge-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 10,000 mostly Haitian migrants were crowded under a border bridge in South Texas awaiting processing Thursday, prompting U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ reviewing policies on trans inmates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-crime-prisons-minnesota-illinois-007d87693249a9831867a5289c09e612</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department is reviewing its policies on housing transgender inmates in the federal prison system after protections for transgender prisoners were rolled back in the Trump administration, The Associated Press has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILLEY DEFENDS CHINA CALLS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-china-joint-chiefs-of-staff-1b23ba339e50a7c17c43c1281a0b4e04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — The top U.S. military officer said Friday that calls he made to his Chinese counterpart in the final stormy months of Donald Trump's presidency were “perfectly within the duties and responsibilities” of his job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED AIRLINES experiencing system-wide outage... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3679975/united-airlines-down-outage-website-boarding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED Airlines is experiencing a huge outage causing issues for passengers boarding planes and using the website. Reports that the website was down started to arise at 7am EST on Friday morning. U…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Security forces under pressure to prevent repeat of Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/572687-security-forces-under-pressure-to-prevent-repeat-of-jan-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is bracing for Saturday's “Justice for J6” rally where demonstrators will be backing people who invaded the Capitol on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resorts Make Staying Put More Appealing...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/17/resorts-make-staying-put-more-appealing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Amanda Stephens, a doctor in North Florida, had two cruises canceled last year, she turned to the next-best thing:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clarence Thomas criticizes judges for veering into politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-courts-religion-judiciary-south-bend-746c700c52a7216b582dbd64b68d409f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas on Thursday criticized some in the judiciary for veering into the role of legislators and politicians, saying it is not the role of judges to make policy or to base decisions on their personal feelings or religious beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>660,000 white flags and climbing: Artist shows what America's death toll looks like...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/09/16/660000-white-flags-artist-covid-19-death-toll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around the Washington Monument 20 acres are being filled with flags representing the COVID-19 death toll in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marathon runners required to wear face masks in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/why-san-francisco-marathon-runners-will-need-to-wear-masks?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants in four races must wear masks on some portions of the course, race officials announced in updates to the race’s health protocols over the last two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger says voters were right to retain Newsom, calls Republican field 'disastrous'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/arnold-schwarzenegger-says-voters-were-212529529.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Arnold Schwarzenegger, who won office through a recall, says he's glad Newsom wasn't ousted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  1 in 3 patients suffer from long covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/1-3-covid-19-patients-170012968.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These long COVID patients reported at least one symptom of COVID-19 two months after first testing positive for the coronavirus, the CDC study says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Employees in China held hostage by angry investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/business/companies-markets/evergrandes-employees-held-hostage-as-worried-investors-demand-payments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail investors in China are taking drastic measures to get money back from embattled property developer.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find evidence of humans making clothes 120,000 years ago!</title>
      <link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/evidence-of-fur-and-leather-clothing-among-worlds-oldest-found-in-moroccan-cave-180978689/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smithsonianmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans likely sported clothes made of jackal, fox and wildcat skins some 120,000 years ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii told tourists to stay away. Did they listen?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/hawaii-told-tourists-to-stay-away-did-they-listen/ar-AAOwD8O?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ige told travelers to postpone trips last month as delta surged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As world leaders gather at UN, vaccine mandate creates confusion and dissent...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-york-wants-world-leaders-to-show-proof-of-vaccination-at-the-un-russia-says-that-is-e2-80-98discriminatory-e2-80-99/ar-AAOwlHm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate unfolding around the world over coronavirus vaccine mandates is playing out on a small scale at the United Nations headquarters ahead of a meeting of dozens of world leaders in New York next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New humanitarian emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-faces-new-border-emergency-in-texas-where-thousands-of-haitian-migrants-are-stuck-under-bridge-in-squalid-conditions/ar-AAOwoym?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Del Rio say more than 8,000 people have crossed in recent days, overwhelming Customs and Border Protection capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden leans into expansive, populist agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/at-an-economic-e2-80-98inflection-point-e2-80-99-biden-leans-into-expansive-populist-agenda/ar-AAOwr4y?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s pitch was part of a pivot away from the first chapter of his presidency, in which Washington and his administration were consumed by emergency funding measures to combat the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rikers Island spirals into chaos during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/rikers-island-jail-spirals-into-chaos-amid-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City’s Rikers Island jail complex has been troubled by years of neglect and now has spiraled into turmoil during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Removes Accounts Tied to German Anti-Lockdown Group...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/facebook-deletes-accounts-of-german-anti-lockdown-group/a-59206831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech giant says the Querdenken (Lateral Thinking) movement was causing "social harm" by promoting conspiracy theories against coronavirus restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New FTC bureau to police Big Tech?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Why-Democrats-are-rallying-around-creating-a-new-16465110.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Who in the federal government should police data abuses by tech companies -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 states threaten legal action over Biden's vaccine mandate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/572649-24-states-threaten-legal-action-over-bidens-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-four states threatened to sue the Biden administration on Thursday over the president's new rule to require employers with more than 100 employees to mandate vaccinations and frequent testing for their worker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police mine GOOGLE for your location, search history...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/sep/16/geofence-warrants-reverse-search-warrants-police-google</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geofence location and keyword warrants are new law enforcement tools that have privacy experts concerned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest cruise ship in world set to launch..</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/uncategorized/3673655/largest-cruise-ship-royal-caribbean-wonders-seas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE largest cruise ship in the world is launching next year – with new routes from Europe next summer. Royal Caribbean’s Wonder of the Seas, their fifth Oasis Class ship, will be able t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack of domain provider popular among conservatives leaks personal data...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/epik-hack-far-right-sites-anonymous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A breach of Epik exposed a massive trove of data, including the names of individuals behind some of the far-right's most notorious websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS TURN SOUR:   Slow motion deterioration with pockets of shares down 20% or more...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/the-stock-market-is-undergoing-a-slow-motion-deterioration-with-pockets-of-shares-down-20percent-or-more.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks are up against a range of obstacles, including seasonal weakness, uncertainty around the Covid delta variant and rising costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicki Minaj compares cancel culture in US to China...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cancel-culture-china-vaccine-blowback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rap artist Nicki Minaj slammed America’s cancel culture after she spoke out about her vaccine hesitancy and compared it to China's restrictions on residents and visitors from criticizing the country's leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS shutting last store in home state of Illinois...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/sears-is-shutting-its-last-store-in-illinois-its-home-state.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last Sears department store located in the retailer's home state of Illinois is getting ready to close its doors for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Cause Of Alzheimer's?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/likely-cause-of-alzheimers-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toxic protein deposits that form in people with Alzheimer’s likely leak into the brain from fat carrying particles called lipoproteins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Dempsey accused of 'terrorizing set' of 'GREY'S ANATOMY'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/patrick-dempsey-accused-terrorizing-set-192356028.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new book about the landmark series, one 'Grey's Anatomy' producer recalled 'HR issues' swirling around actor Patrick Dempsey before his departure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As workers age, robots take on more jobs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210916205718-xg26w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/ROBOTS (PIX):As workers age, robots take on more jobs -study</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
