<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Nobody can get to airport'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9907573/Afghanistan-evacuation-Chaos-continues-Kabul-airport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westerners and visa holders trying to flee Afghanistan cannot get into Kabul airport today because of 'huge crowds' of 'terrified locals' who are blocking the entrances, MailOnline has been told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groups call on APPLE to drop plans to scan children's messages...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/568517-policy-rights-groups-call-on-apple-to-drop-plans-to-scan-childrens-messages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coalition of 90 groups around the world are calling on Apple to drop its plans to scan its products to detect images of child sexual abuse stored in iCloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handcuffed by Trump deal in Doha?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-middle-east-taliban-doha-e6f48507848aef2ee849154604aa11be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — After President Donald Trump signed a peace deal with the Taliban in February 2020, he optimistically proclaimed that “we think we’ll be successful in the end.” His secretary of state, Mike Pompeo, asserted that the administration was “seizing the best opportunity for peace in a generation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booming Colo. town asks, 'Where will water come from?'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-census-2020-climate-change-a10d1a7ee50dd53ec6727a23ca6252e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREELEY, Colo. (AP) — "Go West, young man,'' Horace Greeley famously urged. The problem for the northern Colorado town that bears the 19th-century newspaper editor's name: Too many people have heeded his advice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bets war-weary America will reward for leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/joe-biden-bets-war-weary-america-will-reward-him-leaving-n1277104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's hard to see Republicans winning elections on a campaign promise to go back to war in Afghanistan in 2022 or 2024," says a Democratic consultant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden threatens legal action on masks in schools as feud with DeSantis intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article253591774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Wednesday said his administration is prepared to take possible legal action against governors who try to prevent local school officials from imposing universal mask mandates, throwing yet another wrench into Gov. Ron DeSantis’ plans to sanction Florida school districts that require students to wear masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorcyclist Struck By Hit-And-Run Driver, Robbed While Unconscious...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/08/18/motorcyclist-hit-and-run-robbery-minneapolis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Twin Cities motorcyclist involved in a hit-and-run needs help to find the other driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$500,000 in fines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/faa-calls-for-more-than-24500000-in-fines-against-dozens-of-disruptive-airline-passengers/ar-AANuVhl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration said it was proposing more than $500,000 in fines against 34 airline passengers accused of disrupting flights. The new fines bring the total the agency has sought to impose this year to more than $1 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK pushes VR for remote work but practicality, cost, nausea may stand in way...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Facebook-pushes-VR-for-remote-work-but-16397384.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook believes it has developed a tool for the future of work: a virtual reality app...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: 401(k) balances new all-time high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/19/401k-balances-hit-a-new-all-time-high-fidelity-says-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boosted by the market’s recent run-up, the number of 401(k) and IRA millionaires are at record highs, according to Fidelity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star salaries revealed; Daniel Craig tops at $100M!</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/biggest-movie-star-salaries-daniel-craig-dwayne-johnson-1235043305/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade ago, Hollywood stars knew their place on the A-list was secure when their film topped the box office. Today, success can be measured by views on Netflix or a vague press release touting a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter, trounced in 1980, gets fresh look from history...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-middle-east-jimmy-carter-18eab7024282910f6aab29026a1e04e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Jimmy Carter is sometimes called a better former president than he was president. Nodding to Carter's decades of work as a globe-trotting humanitarian but with a glaring reminder of his landslide defeat in 1980, the backhanded compliment rankles Carter allies and, they say, the former president himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Two-thirds Americans say war not worth fighting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-asia-pacific-afghanistan-only-on-ap-503a50cd8074ced7bc36d9c12e9fd2e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A significant majority of Americans doubt that the war in Afghanistan was worthwhile, even as the United States is more divided over President Joe Biden's handling of foreign policy and national security, according to a poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vow to ban heroin, but can they survive without it?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-taliban-vow-to-ban-heroin-but-can-they-survive-without-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban vow to ban heroin, but can they survive without it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped in no-man's land...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-desperate-afghans-trapped-in-kabul-airport-no-man-s-land</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desperate Afghans trapped in Kabul airport no-man's land</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit jailed in Singapore for not wearing mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-briton-handed-jail-term-in-singapore-for-not-wearing-mask</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Briton handed jail term in Singapore for not wearing mask</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling under intensifying scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/19/politics/joe-biden-presidency-under-scrutiny/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is struggling against an intensifying examination of his judgment, competence and even his empathy over the chaotic US exit from Afghanistan. And each attempt the administration makes to quell a furor that's tarnishing America's image only provokes more questions about its failures of planning and execution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Threats, Chaos in Sky Prompt Record FAA Enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-19/death-threats-chaos-in-the-sky-prompt-record-faa-enforcement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-Inclusive Magic Mushroom, Ayahuasca Retreats Are New Luxury Trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-19/all-inclusive-magic-mushroom-ayahuasca-retreats-are-new-luxury-trips</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resorts are starting to wake up to the appeal of mind expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Fewer Americans Drinking Alcohol...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/353858/alcohol-consumption-low-end-recent-readings.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have become slightly less likely to say they drink alcoholic beverages, and those who imbibe are drinking less, on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires Exhaust 10,000-Strong Army Fighting Them...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/another-california-town-ravaged-wildfire-125949027.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- There are over 10,000 firefighters battling unprecedented blazes in California, but that isn’t enough, and the state is having a hard time finding more as flames rage across the western U.S. and Canada. Twelve major wildfires now burn in the Golden State, forcing 31,000 people to flee their homes. Dry winds raking Northern California helped the Caldor Fire east of Sacramento jump from 6,500 acres to 62,586 by Wednesday night, seriously damaging the town of Grizzly Flats and hospit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says No One Being Killed?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3495132/joe-biden-afghanistan-interview-no-one-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden has sparked fury by saying that “no one is being killed in Afghanistan” despite stowaway deaths. It comes just one day after Afghan health officials said that one person was k…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Covid Plastic Barriers Make Things Worse?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/those-anti-covid-plastic-barriers-probably-dont-help-and-may-make-things-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid precautions have turned many parts of our world into a giant salad bar, with plastic barriers separating sales clerks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: Hypebeasts Hit Road With Next Level Car Customization...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/hypebeasts-hit-the-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is, by its owner’s description, a “zombie killer” dream machine — a 2021 Mercedes-Benz SUV G-Wagon/Brabus, Frankenstein-built using organs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Remote TX Town Became One of Fastest-Growing Cities...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/how-a-remote-town-in-texas-became-one-of-americas-fastest-growing-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;﻿NEW BRAUNFELS, Texas — In the not-too-distant past, motorists driving along a stretch of Interstate 35 just northeast of San</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian Butt Lifts Surge, Despite Risks...</title>
      <link>/https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/19/brazilian-butt-lifts-surge-despite-risks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petting, Cuddling Dog 'Significantly Enhances Well-Being'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/petting-a-dog-well-being/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our research tells us that interacting through touch is key to reducing student stress," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia sees worst day of pandemic amid delta outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/australia-sees-worst-day-of-covid-19-pandemic-amid-delta-outbreak-2513812</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia has suffered its worst day since the start of the Covid-19 pandemic, with total daily cases surpassing the previous record posted more than a year ago as a delta variant outbreak spreads as far as New Zealand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Are Shadowy Taliban Leaders Now Running Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/these-are-the-shadowy-taliban-leaders-now-running-afghanistan/ar-AANu7TS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades the Taliban’s leadership structure has been in the shadows: Even before the U.S. invasion in 2001, little was known about how the group operates beyond the names of a few top leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Chinese pressure on virus origins probe shocked WHO...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-chinese-pressure-on-coronavirus-origins-probe-shocked-the-who-e2-80-94-and-led-its-director-to-push-back/ar-AANtOpM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINES 'DECLINING EFFECTIVENESS' AGAINST INFECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccines-show-declining-effectiveness-against-infection-overall-but-strong-protection-against-hospitalization-amid-delta-variant/ar-AANsKR4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results were pivotal to the Biden administration's decision to recommend booster shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milley Denies Intel Predicted Rapid Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/gen-milley-says-there-was-nothing-that-i-or-anyone-else-saw-in-intel-indicating-afghanistan-would-collapse-in-11-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Mark Milley, Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, addressed questions about the intelligence assessments of Afghanistan prior to the Taliban takeover happening within several days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidman quarantine exemption sparks anger in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210819-kidman-quarantine-exemption-sparks-anger-in-hong-kong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kidman quarantine exemption sparks anger in Hong Kong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS TO MANDATE NURSING HOME SHOTS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/18/politics/nursing-homes-federal-funding/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden announced on Wednesday that he is directing all nursing homes to require their staff be vaccinated against Covid-19 in order to continue receiving Medicare and Medicaid funding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas faces tipping point...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/568484-texas-faces-tipping-point-as-covid-19-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is facing a tipping point in the state’s battle with COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions in US weaponry seized...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/568493-billions-in-us-weaponry-seized-by-taliban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billions of dollars of U.S. weapons are now in the hands of the Taliban following the quick collapse of Afghan security forces that were trained to use the military equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Shifts To Stark Tone As Seeks To Stay In Office: 'Life Or Death'...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/17/california-recall-newsom-shifts-to-stark-tone-as-he-seeks-to-stay-in-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom is using increasingly stark language as he campaigns in the final month of a tight recall election, calling it “a matter of life or death" that voters keep him in office and he is increasingly targeting a single Republican candidate: talk show host Larry Elder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  Larry David 'screamed' at Dershowitz in grocery store over Don ties...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/08/18/larry-david-screamed-at-alan-dershowitz-at-grocery-store-over-trump-ties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Larry is a knee-jerk radical,” Dershowitz told Page Six of the incident. “He takes his politics from Hollywood. He doesn’t read a lot. He doesn’t think a lot.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA County prosecutors bring Ron Jeremy sex assault case to grand jury...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-county-prosecutors-bring-ron-193512983.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors seek to indict porn star Ron Jeremy on multiple counts of sexual assault stemming from allegations made by 23 women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans face Taliban, airport chaos in scramble to evacuate Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/americans-faced-taliban-airport-chaos-012617139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden insisted late Wednesday that the U.S. was committed to getting all Americans out Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel eases restrictions on blood donations by gay men...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-health-israel-blood-donation-f81a405e03b93d57d8cb390f8e10cc64</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel has lifted restrictions on blood donations by gay men, saying the longstanding limitation was discriminatory and denigrating, Israel’s health minister said Thursday. Earlier this year the U.K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Grace makes landfall near Mexico's Tulum temples...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-travel-mexico-caribbean-hurricanes-ac7fbf17a36e7983b14645d909fa117e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULUM, Mexico (AP) — Hurricane Grace struck Mexico's Caribbean coast just south of the ancient Mayan temples of Tulum early Thursday, pushing a dangerous storm surge. Heavy rain and strong winds threatened to destroy flimsier homes and keep tourists off white sand beaches until it crosses the Yucatan Peninsula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants mark independence as challenges to rule rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-taliban-bd853cac9eee5e4f0cd4b76580f27b53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Afghan protesters defied the Taliban for a second day Thursday, waving their national flag in scattered demonstrations that were met with renewed violence by the militants who are facing growing challenges to their rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gulf Coast's beloved 'Redneck Riviera' now virus hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-c341a0e0ab5e9ecc3b3eedc855f33513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GULF SHORES, Ala. (AP) — Tourists and servers alike dance atop tables and in the aisles at one restaurant on the “Redneck Riviera,” a beloved stretch of towns along the northern Gulf Coast where beaches, bars and stores are packed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia was ready for win due to longtime contacts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-taliban-f25c1a8b030fb0721f9b8891f8d329e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — When the Taliban swept over Afghanistan, Russia was ready for the rapid developments after working methodically for years to lay the groundwork for relations with the group that it still officially considers a terrorist organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  No way to withdraw without 'chaos ensuing'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/biden-withdraw-afghanistan-chaos-ensuing/story?id=79507930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden in an exclusive interview with ABC News' George Stephanopoulos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Men Have Biological Clock Too, Fertility Drops After Age 50...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/men-biological-clock-fertility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say men should not wait too long to start a family - just like women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS mandates employees disclose status...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/18/media/fox-mandate-vaccine-status/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The right-wing channel Fox News, whose top personalities have for months assailed the concept of vaccine passports and argued that asking about vaccine status amounts to a major intrusion of privacy, told employees this week that they must disclose their vaccination status to the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>61% paid no income taxes in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/18/61percent-of-americans-paid-no-federal-income-taxes-in-2020-tax-policy-center-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the Tax Policy Center, 107 million households owed no income taxes in 2020, up from 76 million — or 44% of all taxpayers — in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Jew in Afghanistan refuses to give wife Jewish divorce...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/the-last-jew-in-afghanistan-is-staying-report-677002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghanistan's last remaining Jew, Zabulon Simantov, has decided to remain in the country despite the Taliban's takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's deepest swimming pool hides vast sunken city 200 feet underwater...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/in-dubai-worlds-deepest-swimming-pool-hides-sunken-city-200-feet-underwater/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We dive into Deep Dive Dubai with Jarrod Jablonski, director of the wild indoor diving facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does Covid affect brain? Troubling picture emerges...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/how-does-covid-19-affect-the-brain-a-troubling-picture-emerges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find that people who only suffered mild infections can be plagued with life-altering and sometimes debilitating cognitive deficits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Census hit by cyberattack, 'count unaffected'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-census-2020-89c02901178dfa088d7abdb35147ca3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Census Bureau computer servers were exploited last year during a cybersecurity attack, but it didn't involve the 2020 census, and hackers' attempts to keep access to the system were unsuccessful, according to a watchdog report released Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher on leave after sharing political opinions in class...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-education-coronavirus-pandemic-9a8cafb7f4b3f8360488009eb46f6c0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEHI, Utah (AP) — A Utah teacher has been fired after a video of her sharing political opinions in class began circulating online, school district officials said Wednesday. The teacher at Lehi High School was initially placed on administrative leave after the video surfaced, but Alpine School District officials confirmed she was let go following an investigation into the incident, Fox 13 reported .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba makes social media criticism of regime a crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuba-makes-social-media-criticism-of-regime-a-crime-in-effort-to-quash-growing-dissent/ar-AANsWjC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dissenting on social media is now a crime in communist Cuba after the government on Tuesday published sweeping legislation labeling those who criticize the government as cyberterrorists. The all-out attack on the freedom of expression of Cubans comes a month after social media helped fuel the largest anti-government protests on the island in several decades. They also seem designed to respond ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA cannot ensure safe passage to airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/afghanistan-taliban-us-news-08-18-21/h_b11fdb80790fc57e43797a33c0044895</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Taliban in control of Afghanistan, most countries are evacuating their citizens and shutting their embassies temporarily. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Kurson, who was pardoned, slapped with state charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-ken-kurson-state-charges-20210818-6jcocqxgkrgfba2rx5luksk5my-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A close friend of Jared Kushner was slapped with state harassment charges Wednesday — nearly eight months after he scored a last-minute pardon from President Donald Trump wiping away federal charges for the same alleged cyberstalking campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash erupts as NYC imposes biggest passport scheme in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9904797/Backlash-erupts-rollout-vaccine-passport-checks-gets-way-NYC-restaurants.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit was filed Tuesday, the same day Mayor de Blasio's 'Key to NYC' scheme went into effect, requiring staff and customers at dining, entertainment and fitness facilities to be vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed preparing for taper this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/18/fed-minutes-july.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve on Wednesday released the minutes from its July 27-28 meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist Publication Fires Staff for Doing Socialism...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7bmd7/socialist-publication-current-affairs-fires-staff-for-doing-socialism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We were fired by the editor-in-chief of a socialist magazine for trying to start a worker co-op," five fired staffers wrote in a letter posted on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS KILLED...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/middle-east/taliban-reportedly-shoot-dead-protesters-in-jalalabad-as-former-afghan-president-ashraf-ghani-resurfaces-in-uae/news-story/6af9ec57f28186a5811847309b220355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people were reportedly killed and more than a dozen injured after Taliban militants opened fire during protests against the group in the Afghan city of Jalalabad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's Double Agent...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3aqyz8/apples-double-agent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He spent years inside the iPhone leaks and jailbreak community. He was also spying for Apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why would anyone pay $500,000 for a painting by Hunter Biden?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/aug/17/why-would-anyone-pay-500000-for-a-painting-by-hunter-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s not an established artist – or critically acclaimed. Yet his works are apparently being sold for surprising amounts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOSTERS IN SEPT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/18/covid-booster-shots-us-to-begin-wide-distribution-of-third-vaccine-doses-next-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. agencies are preparing to offer booster shots to all eligible Americans beginning the week of Sept. 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grace reaches hurricane strength, set to slam Cancun as Cat 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/grace-to-threaten-two-landfalls-in-mexico-after-dousing-caribbean/1001514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After pummeling parts of the Caribbean, Grace strengthened into the second hurricane of the 2021 season in the Atlantic, and it will bring a host of hazards when it slams Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC to reveal new strategy in FACEBOOK antitrust fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/568302-ftc-expected-to-reveal-new-strategy-in-facebook-antitrust-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Trade Commission this week is expected to lay out its new legal strategy in an ongoing antitrust battle with Facebook that will also reveal how FTC chief Lina Khan plans to take on the market power of U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX School Includes Masks in Dress Code to Bypass Ban...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/568338-texas-school-officials-to-include-masks-in-dress-code-in-potential-loophole</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The board of trustees for a school district in Texas are amending their dress code for students to include masks in a bid to get around Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulance services make urgent plea...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/outside-hospital-inside-emergency-department-191918472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Ed Racht, Chief Medical Officer at Global Medical Response, joins Yahoo Finance to discuss the impacts of the pandemic on the EMS sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany:  'Greatest debacle NATO has seen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense/national-security/biden-stuns-allies-afghanistan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden’s chaotic exit from Afghanistan has sent a shiver of frustration and bewilderment through allies at home and abroad who regarded his inauguration as a break from former President Donald Trump’s oft-haphazard approach to foreign policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED airlines to crew: Don't duct tape passengers!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/don-t-duct-tape-unruly-passengers-united-airlines-says-memo-n1277065</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The memo was sent after recent incidents involving passengers on other carriers who were duct taped to their seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanity's 'DANGEROUS PATH': Movie Makes Dire Predictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/demonic-neill-blomkamp-in-the-earth-ben-wheatley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California builds 'Noah's Ark' to protect wildlife from extinction by fire and heat...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-08-18/california-builds-noahs-ark-as-extinction-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Earth warms and the drought deepens, a network of biologists and conservationists are racing to rescue California's most threatened species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studios Begin to Blink on Theatrical Releases...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/venom-release-studios-blink-amid-delta-1234998912/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As moviegoer comfort levels dive amid the spread of the COVID-19 variant, tentpoles like Sony’s 'Venom' sequel are once again on the move, but others (like MGM’s oft-delayed 'No Time to Die') may take the risk anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man brutally attacked with hatchet at Manhattan ATM...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bloody-hatchet-attack-at-manhattan-atm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD was questioning a person of interest in the brutal attack with a hatchet of an unsuspecting man inside an ATM in Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump exits Trump Tower to mix of cheers, boos and middle fingers...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/local/video-and-pics-donald-trump-exits-trump-tower</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump was spotted leaving Trump Tower’s 56th Street entrance Wednesday afternoon, and a sea of people greeted him – but not all of the salutations were warm and fuzzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Joins AMAZON in 'Top Secret' Cloud for Gov't...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/it-modernization/2021/08/what-top-secret-cloud-means-microsoft/184596/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A commercial platform announced last year is now generally available to government customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX School Includes Masks in Dress Code to Bypass Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/texas-paris-school-district-face-mask-loophole-covid-greg-abbott-1620430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Greg Abbott banned face mask mandates in the state, prompting criticism from several school districts amid the spread of the Delta variant of COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL county declares state of emergency amid hospital resource shortage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/568353-florida-county-declares-pandemic-state-of-emergency-amid-hospital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida county voted unanimously on Tuesday to declare a state of emergency as hospitals are becoming increasingly strained amid a surge in COVID-19 cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala touted role on policy. Now, she owns it too...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kamala-harris-touted-her-role-120034264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president says she was the last person in the room to advise President Biden when he decided earlier this year to pull out from Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Board Of Ed Votes To Punish Broward Over Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/17/broward-schools-punished-mask-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Education Commissioner Richard Corcoran said he's found probable cause, as he put it, that the Broward School District violated state law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hole Megastructures May Be Powering Alien Civilizations, Scientists Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epn7vn/black-hole-megastructures-may-be-powering-alien-civilizations-scientists-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dyson spheres encompassing around black holes could yield up to one million times more energy than those built around stars, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approval Falls Below 50%...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/biden-approval-falls-below-50-percent-for-first-time-in-polling-averages-amid-afghanistan-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's approval rating has fallen below 50 percent in two key polling averages for the first time in his presidency, as chaos in Afghanistan dominates news coverage. After many months of steady approval in the mid-50s, the president's approval rating has fallen to 49.8 percent in […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blob of human brain grows functioning eyes in lab dish...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/blob-human-brain-grows-functioning-24785482</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists were shocked when a batch of 'mini brains' they were researching developed working eye structures that are 'light sensitive' and harbour cell types similar to those in humans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data of more than 40 million exposed in T-MOBILE breach...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-f23cf2ea885f1089571ee45837c81382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The names, Social Security numbers and information from driver's licenses or other identification of just over 40 million former and prospective customers that applied for T-Mobile credit were exposed in a recent data breach, the company said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
