<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>High stakes and high stress, forecasting tornadoes can take psychological toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/high-stakes-and-high-stress-forecasting-tornadoes-can-take-psychological-toll/ar-AALjnSW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tornadoes can have profound impacts on the meteorologists who warn for them, especially when lives are lost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Troop Deployment Along Disputed Border Worries India...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/china-s-troop-deployment-along-disputed-border-worries-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Troop Deployment Along Disputed Border Worries India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising violent crime poses new challenge for White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/559467-rising-violent-crime-poses-new-challenge-for-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will detail his administration’s crime prevention strategy on Wednesday in a high profile address that comes as a series of major cities see spikes in crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Strawberry Moon to dazzle in last full moon of year...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3125408/strawberry-supermoon-june-full-moon-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE LAST Supermoon of the year will brighten up the night sky this week. June’s full Moon is called the Strawberry Moon and it will be at its fullest on Thursday June 24. The “Super Str…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican 'unprecedented' challenge to homophobia law...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210622-vatican-in-unprecedented-challenge-to-italy-homophobia-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vatican in 'unprecedented' challenge to Italy homophobia law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doge down 70% since Musk on SNL...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/currencies/news/dogecoin-price-elon-musk-snl-cryptocurrency-crash-china-bubble-2021-6-1030542208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Buyout Just the Start as Wealthy Flee Tax Hike...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/record-buyout-just-start-wealthy-120000843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For 110 years, four generations of Mills family members earned their money by expanding their great-grandfather’s Chicago apron business into a medical supplier that ranked among the nation’s largest private companies.But soon after Democrats turned their attention toward raising taxes for the wealthy this year, the family signed a deal to cash out billions.It was no coincidence, according to people close to the more-than $30 billion transaction, which sold part of Medline Industr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China crypto crackdown wipes $300 billion off market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/china-crypto-crackdown-wipes-nearly-300-billion-off-market-btc-slides.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Friday, China has stepped up its efforts to rein in the country's cryptocurrency industry from mining bans to warnings to financial institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin below key $30,000 level...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/bitcoin-falls-again-breaking-below-key-30000-level-that-traders-say-could-lead-to-more-losses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecocide: Fast-growing movement to put environmental destruction on par with war crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/how-a-growing-movement-plans-to-put-ecocide-on-a-par-with-war-crimes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecocide is an umbrella term for all forms of the mass damage of ecosystems, from industrial pollution to the release of micro plastics into the oceans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No one gonna steal election from me': Echoes of 2020 in NYC mayor race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/city-hall/story/2021/06/22/no-one-is-gonna-steal-the-election-from-me-echoes-of-2020-in-nyc-mayors-race-1386767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A racially-tinged battle has erupted over the process, with the leading candidate&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;leveling accusations of voter disenfranchisement&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;after two of his opponents formed a last-minute alliance to bolster their own campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mouse plague forces Oz prison evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mouse-plague-forces-australian-prison-evacuation/ar-AALi9Qu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mouse plague ravaging Australia's farmlands forced the evacuation of hundreds of inmates from a rural jail on Tuesday, as the rodents broke in and chewed through essential infrastructure. "The health, safety and wellbeing of staff and inmates is our number one priority, so it's important for us to act now to carry out the vital remediation work," said Peter Severin od Corrective Services NSW. Up to 420 inmates and 200 staff from the Wellington...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia struggles to quash persistent outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210622-australia-struggles-to-quash-persistent-coronavirus-outbreaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia struggles to quash persistent coronavirus outbreaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we be friends? Dating apps say sex isn't everything...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210622034933-9gsj0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOCIALMEDIA-DATING/ (GRAPHIC, PIX):FOCUS-Can we be friends? Dating apps say sex isn't everything in a post-pandemic world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fleet off Hawaii practices sinking aircraft carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9711403/Russian-fleet-35-miles-Hawaii-practices-sinking-aircraft-carrier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Monday announced that they had carried out an exercise simulating the sinking of an aircraft carrier, off the coast of Hawaii. The war games are the largest since the Cold War.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel tests digital shekel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/jpost-tech/israel-has-already-tested-a-digital-shekel-cryptocurrency-671639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept of issuing such a currency has been in discussion since 2017, but it decided to accelerate its research and preparation for the potential issuance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garland tries to untangle Trump legacy at Justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/garland-tries-to-untangle-the-trump-legacy-at-the-justice-department/ar-AALgBAO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC paid Mar-a-Lago $175K for spring donor retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/21/rnc-paid-trumps-mar-a-lago-over-175000-for-donor-retreat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump's private club was paid over $175,000 in May by the RNC to host its donor retreat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA BORED...</title>
      <link>https://w3-lab.com/instagram-reach-is-down-is-instagram-dying-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;w3-lab.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the Instagram trends for 2021? Why is Instagram`s reach and engagement rate declining? Is Instagram dying in 2021? Find out here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside dog 'factory farm' from hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/panicked-dogs-bred-factory-farms-24368423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING IMAGES: EXCLUSIVE: Footage shows beagles being piled onto overcrowded trolleys and whimpering before being force fed chemicals for 90 days in what comedian Ricky Gervais called 'terrible cruelty'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASSIB FIRST OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.instagram.com/p/CQZXu_8nyy_/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.instagram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;93.1k Likes, 8,563 Comments - Carl Nassib (@carlnassib) on Instagram: “For more information on the life-saving work and resources of The Trevor Project click the link in…”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAY IN NFL</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/31682318/carl-nassib-las-vegas-raiders-announces-gay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raiders DE Carl Nassib became the first active NFL player to come out as gay, announcing the news in an Instagram post Monday while pledging $100,000 to the Trevor Project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SUES NYC... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/trump-organization-sues-york-city-wrongful-termination-contracts/story?id=78408860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s company sued New York City Monday for allegedly wrongfully terminating contracts the Trump Organization had to operate city facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency services scramble to rescue drowning SEX DOLL...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3128026/emergency-services-rescue-drowning-woman-sea-discarded-sex-doll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMERGENCY services scrambled to save a drowning woman washed out to sea before discovering the damsel in distress was actually a discarded SEX DOLL. Crowds gathered to watch the dramatic rescue of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiCaprio's multi-million-dollar eco-friendly resort years behind schedule...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3091472/leonardo-dicaprio-eco-friendly-resort-belize-behind-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEONARDO DiCaprio’s plan to “change the world” by building the greenest luxury resort off the coast of Belize is running YEARS behind schedule after angry protests by fishermen an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIDER becomes NFL's only openly gay player...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/06/21/raiders-carl-nassib-comes-out-as-openly-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raiders defensive end Carl Nassib came out today, making him the NFL’s only openly gay player. “I just want to take a quick moment to say that I’m gay,” Nassib said in a video he posted on his verified Instagram account. “I’ve been meaning to do this for a while now but I finally feel [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS ARRESTED OUTSIDE TED CRUZ HOME...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article252262438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people were arrested outside Sen. Ted Cruz’s home, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITIZEN app told LA residents plane had crashed -- it was training drill...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/citizen-plane-crash-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh off sending a mob after the wrong person, Citizen accidentally misreported that a plane crashed in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Atlanta went from nearly defunding police -- to boosting funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/atlanta-news/atlanta-almost-withheld-73m-in-police-funding-last-year-whats-changed-since-then/FEZOTN3G7NFCDFAMAI5BBBTVYY/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discussions at City Hall over this year’s budget, which followed a citywide rise in violent crime, highlight how the discourse over policing has shifted in the last year, among elected officials and some members of the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte threatens those who refuse vaccine with jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/philippines-duterte-threatens-those-who-refuse-covid-19-vaccine-with-jail-2021-06-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Rodrigo Duterte threatened to jail people who refuse to be vaccinated against the coronavirus as the Philippines battles one of Asia's worst outbreaks, with over 1.3 million cases and more than 23,000 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado sweeps through suburban Chicago, causing damage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/suburbs-naperville-chicago-environment-and-nature-us-news-606ad68e325f0074102786a17a1bcbcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A tornado swept through communities in heavily populated suburban Chicago, damaging more than 100 homes, toppling trees, knocking out power and causing multiple injuries, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books Already 'Burning'...</title>
      <link>https://bariweiss.substack.com/p/the-books-are-already-burning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bariweiss.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The question is only: How long will decent people stand by quietly and watch it happen?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms used in health care nationwide rife with bias...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/21/algorithm-bias-playbook-hospitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report finds bias is pervasive in algorithms used by hospitals and insurers. It also offers a playbook on how to fix those flaws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5th presidential candidate detained in Nicaragua...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/21/americas/nicaragua-fifth-candidate-detained-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicaragua's National Police have detained a fifth presidential candidate, bringing the total number of opposition leaders so far detained to 15 ahead of the November general election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Woman who claims she gave birth to 10 babies admitted to psych ward...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/21/south-african-woman-who-says-she-birthed-10-babies-now-in-psych-ward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gosiame Thamara Sithole, who made headlines for the alleged record-breaking birth, was taken to the psychiatric ward last week at Tembisa Hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardline Iranian President Refuses Biden Meeting...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iranian-president-elect-rejects-biden-refuses-negotiations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s newly elected hardline president, Ebrahim Raisi, said in his first press conference on Monday that he will not allow negotiations to take place on the country’s contested missile program, which includes long-range ballistic missiles capable of carrying a nuclear warhead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCTV Company Paying Remote Workers in India to Yell at Armed Robbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avnnn/a-cctv-company-is-paying-remote-workers-in-india-to-yell-at-armed-robbers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clerks at 7-Eleven and other convenience stores are being constantly monitored by a voice of god that can intervene from thousands of miles away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad marriages kill? Men who bicker with wives at higher risk of dying young...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9709449/Men-think-relationship-failure-higher-risk-premature-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exploring extensive health data going back more than 30 years, a team from Tel Aviv University tracked the deaths and causes of death of more than 10,000 Israeli men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's only nuclear power plant mysteriously shut down...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3124659/iran-nuclear-power-plant-shut-israel-attacks-mass-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN’S sole nuclear power plant has been mysteriously shut down hours after Israel vowed to launch attacks on its “mass murdering hangmen”. Incoming President Ebrahim Raisi, 60, is a torturing kill…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis Wins Straw Poll...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2024/conservative-conference-2024-straw-poll-winner-donald-tr-no-wait-ron-desantis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the very conservative gathering of the Trump faithful in Denver, Florida's Ron DeSantis took the crown for most preferred 2024 candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked man breaks into Bel Air home, kills family pets...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/naked-man-breaks-into-bel-air-home-kills-family-pets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A naked intruder was arrested after breaking into a Bel Air home and killing the homeowner’s pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitehouse Defends All-White Club Membership...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/21/sheldon-whitehouse-under-fire-for-membership-at-all-white-club/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheldon Whitehouse was confronted by a GoLocal Providence reporter on Friday about the senator’s membership at Newport-based Bailey’s Beach Club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says Wuhan lab deserves Nobel Prize for Medicine!</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/the-morning-jolt/no-remorse-china-now-says-the-wuhan-lab-deserves-a-nobel-prize/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese Foreign Ministry argues that the Wuhan Institute of Virology deserves to win the Nobel Prize for Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel cites progress in laser that shoots down drones...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-business-technology-14d664c9738edc47a5888cecf8d86281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — The Israeli military said Monday it has successfully tested an airborne high-power laser that can shoot down drones, technology it hopes to deploy on a larger scale in the coming years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT CANADA KEEPS BORDER SHUT</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/canada-lift-border-restrictions-july-144552616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA (Reuters) -Canada said on Monday it would start cautiously lifting border restrictions for fully vaccinated citizens on July 5 but made clear it would be months before U.S. and other foreign travelers could enter the country. "This is the first phase of our precautionary approach ... at this time we are not opening up our borders any further," said Intergovernmental Affairs Minister Dominic LeBlanc. Ottawa first announced the plan on June 9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg Deal With NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/steven-spielberg-amblin-netflix-partnership-movies-the-trial-of-the-chicago-7-bradley-cooper-the-maestro-1234778665</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a difference two years and a global pandemic make. Steven Spielberg, who a couple of years ago was quoted — his camp maintains he never said it or anything he might have said was severel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian fired after refusing to provide fingerprints on religious grounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/christian-man-fired-after-refusing-to-provide-fingerprints</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities are suing a debt collection company after a Christian employee refused to be fingerprinted due to his religious beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress barrels toward debt cliff..</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/559218-congress-barrels-toward-debt-cliff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress is barreling toward a fight as soon as next month over raising the debt ceiling, creating a huge challenge for President Biden and Democratic leaders in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia's Richest Man Says No Option But to Make Businesses Green...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asia-richest-man-says-no-125500755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mukesh Ambani, Asia’s richest man, plans to transform each of the units under his refining-to-retail conglomerate to create a sustainable business model as Reliance Industries Ltd. chases a net carbon-zero goal by 2035.“We have no option as a society, as a business but to really adopt a sustainable business model,” Ambani told Bloomberg Television’s Haslinda Amin as part of the Qatar Economic Forum Monday. “I think that’s a prerequisite for every business to survive as we go forwa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The chaos, the conflicts.  Inside pandemic response...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-book-offers-fresh-details-about-chaos-conflicts-inside-trump-e2-80-99s-pandemic-response/ar-AALgO6w?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At one point, the president mused about repatriating infected Americans in Asia to Guantanamo Bay Naval Base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waitress kidnapped after confronting non-paying customers!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/waitress-abducted-assaulted-by-restaurant-goers-in-new-jersey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Gloucester County are looking for a group of people they say assaulted and kidnapped a waitress after they left the restaurant without paying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  JOE APPROVAL 52%...</title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Earth Has 'Pulse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/earth-heartbeat-geologic-pulse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major global geologic events have pretty much only occurred at 10 distinct points in time over the past 260 million years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adams holds on to lead in wide-open mayoral primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/559378-adams-holds-onto-lead-in-wide-open-nyc-mayoral-primary-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn Borough President Eric Adams is leading the field of Democrats vying to become New York City’s next mayor ahead of Tuesday’s primary, but ranked-choice voting means the race is far from decided.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
