<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Robots Fight Pandemic Loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/covid-19-robot-companions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's hard to replace human contact. But during a pandemic, robots can help patients fight off feelings of isolation and despair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High levels of cortisol associated with greater risk of death... </title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/high-levels-stress-hormone-cortisol-greater-risk-death-from-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research suggests that high levels of the stress hormone, cortisol, are associated with a greater risk of death in COVID-19 patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX testing fever-detecting cameras... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/LAX-is-testing-fever-detecting-cameras-as-15357205.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting Tuesday, some travelers at Los Angeles International Airport will be asked to undergo a new screening process long before they get to security checkpoints: walking past cameras that can flag travelers with a fever.  Officials on Monday planned to announce a pilot program to test the use of thermal imaging cameras at the departures entrance and the corridor for international arrivals in the airport's Tom Bradley International Terminal.  "We're trying to do everything we can to make sure that our airport terminals are a safe environment, and we're making sure that we're doing everything we can to make it healthy for people to come in," said Justin Erbacci, chief executive of Los Angeles World Airports.  Signs will direct travelers to walk through an area where cameras are stationed, which detect whether someone has a temperature of 100.4 or higher. Those who show an elevated temperature will be pulled aside for a secondary screening to confirm. Participation will be voluntary, and the airport will not stop anyone from continuing with their journey during the pilot - though workers will give advice handed down from county and federal health officials about traveling with an elevated temperature.  Airlines that are doing their own temperature screening can still prohibit travelers from flying if they have fevers.  "Through this pilot, we are not going to stop anybody from traveling," Erbacci said. "We want to test the accuracy of the technology and to understand if it is really able to capture accurate body temperatures of passengers en masse as they walk through this portal."  Similar technology has been used in airports in Asia since the SARS epidemic; during the coronavirus pandemic, workplaces, foreign airlines, resorts and others have invested in thermal imaging...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Office of Hate': Bot Army Target of Brazil's Top Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/In-hunt-for-office-of-hate-Brazil-s-Supreme-15356841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's known as the "office of hate." And like all good conspiracies, there's no hard proof it actually exists.  The alleged clandestine network of bots, businessmen and bloggers is said by some lawmakers and Brazil's biggest newspaper to rain vitriol on all who oppose President Jair Bolsonaro -- whether it be a super-star judge who jumps ship, a health minister who won't toe the line on the administration's covid strategy or a journalist who pens a critical article.  Now, the Supreme Court is trying to unmask pro-Bolsonaro social-media attack dogs after saying it found "serious evidence" pointing to the group's existence. The president blasts the effort as an affront to free speech and a political witch-hunt by a deep state cabal. The top court, which took the unusual step of launching its own investigation, alleges the "office of hate" may have weaponized fake news in a coordinated bid to topple opponents, institutions and perhaps even democracy itself.  There are "two or three campaigns every day in real time on every issue," said Marco Aurelio Ruediger, director of the Department of Public Policy Analysis at Getulio Vargas University, known as FGV, in Rio de Janeiro. "It's spontaneous, but also professional."  The Supreme Court investigation set in motion an interstate raid last month of properties linked to a far-right blogger, three high-profile businessmen and a dozen others. The case builds on two more probes already under way: One ordered by the nation's electoral watchdog and another by Congress.  Combined, the probes target the very way Bolsonaro communicates and energizes his base. Rulings against him could not only muzzle the social media machine that helped shoot him to power, but could also be grounds for impeachment.  "All these people were decisive in the construction of Bolsonaro, decisive in the creation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER SOLSTICE:  President's Shock at Rows of Empty Seats at Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-president-e2-80-99s-shock-at-the-rows-of-empty-seats-in-tulsa/ar-BB15O5Ht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSPITALIZATIONS GROW</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/22/coronavirus-hospitalizations-grow-in-arizona-and-texas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Sunday, the nation's seven-day average of new Covid-19 cases increased more than 24% compared with a week ago, according to a CNBC analysis of Johns Hopkins University data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Threatens 'Sensational Event' to End America...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/06/22/north-korea-threatens-sensational-event-to-end-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statement from North Korea's embassy in Moscow this weekend threatened a "sensational event" leading to the destruction of America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan supercomputer named fastest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/speed-japan-supercomputer-worlds-fastest-150435285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's Fugaku supercomputer, built with government backing and used in the fight against coronavirus, is now ranked as the world's fastest, its developers announced Monday. It snatched the top spot on the Top500, a site that has tracked the evolution of computer processing power for more than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Sales Fall to 9-1/2-year Low...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200622144752-zkcve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/ (WRAPUP 1):WRAPUP 1-U.S. home sales tumble to 9-1/2-year low; price growth slows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tearful Mexican cartel chief threatens government after mother's detention...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200621184831-yvaz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/ (PIX):Tearful Mexican cartel chief threatens government after mother's detention</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND:  104 shot, 14 fatally, over Father's Day weekend...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/crime/2020/6/20/21297470/chicago-fathers-day-weekend-shootings-homicide-gun-violence-june-19-22-104-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five children were among the 14 people killed, including a 3-year-old boy and 13-year-old girl killed in separate shootings in Austin on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVER 6 MILLION WATCH BOLTON INTERVIEW....</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/621639303687176192/martha-raddatzs-exclusive-interview-with-john</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News Chief Global Affairs Correspondent Martha Raddatz’s first exclusive interview with John Bolton stood as Sunday’s No. 1 program in Adults 18-49 (0.7/5) and Adults 25-54 (1.1/5).  In addition,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120,000 DEAD IN 4 MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/u-s-coronavirus-death-toll-surpasses-120-000-china-south-n1231663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus has infected nearly 8.8 million people as of Sunday and killed more than 464,000, according to Johns Hopkins University data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He has no philosophical grounding'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/21/trump-poses-danger-for-the-republic-if-re-elected-john-bolton-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump poses a “danger for the republic” and would be an even greater threat if he wins a second</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER SOLSTICE:  President's Shock at Rows of Empty Seats at Rally...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/21/the-presidents-shock-at-the-rows-of-empty-seats-in-tulsa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and several staff members stood backstage and gazed at the empty Bank of Oklahoma Center in horror. Mr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  38%  APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Bolton fears for the Republic if President re-elected...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bolton-hopes-trump-term-president-warns-country-imperiled/story?id=71320449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the many headlines from ABC News' interview with President Trump's former national security adviser John Bolton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-red House seat in Va. could turn blue...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Long-red-House-seat-in-Va-could-turn-blue-15356874.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats in central and Southside Virginia are choosing a nominee for an open congressional seat that the party thinks it could win for the first time in more than a decade.  Republicans last week ousted freshman Rep. Denver Riggleman in favor of Bob Good, who calls himself a "biblical conservative," to the delight of Democrats surveying their field of well-funded hopefuls competing in Tuesday's primary.  "I think everybody sort of breathed a sigh of relief and said, 'Bring it.' Bob Good really does not reflect the view of voters in this district," said Suzanne Long, chairwoman of the 5th District Democratic committee.  Four Democrats are on the ballot in the primary, which is being conducted mostly by mail because of the coronavirus pandemic but also has in-person voting from 6 a.m. to 7 p.m. Tuesday.  They are R.D. Huffstetler, a Marine veteran and former congressional chief of staff with Silicon Valley experience; John Lesinski, a retired Marine Corps colonel and former elected official in Rappahannock County who works in commercial real estate; Claire Russo, a former Marine intelligence officer and advocate for victims of military sexual assault; and Cameron Webb, a physician, former White House fellow and health policy researcher.  Applications for absentee ballots were due June 16, and in-person absentee voting was allowed through Saturday.  Huffstetler had the most cash on hand by the start of June, with $286,811, followed by Russo with $201,530, Webb with $139,661 and Lesinski with $36,078, reports show.  Good's campaign consultant, Chris Shores, declined to distinguish among the Democrats.  "No matter who they nominate, there is no doubt that they will adopt the radical agenda of the left - supporting restrictions on our gun rights, defunding police departments,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC Inks NASA Deal for Commercial Space Flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/virgin-galactic-inks-deal-with-nasa-for-private-trips-to-iss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It will act as a travel agency for trips to the space station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: What if Trump just gives up?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/921381/what-trump-just-gives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the president grapples with his growing unpopularity, will he lash out or lose interest?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: NJ Least Patriotic State...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/new-jersey-ranked-worst-patriotic-state-in-america-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study ranked New Jersey the worst patriotic state in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socially distanced orgies at NYC sex club...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/22/a-soho-sex-club-reopens-amid-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As NYC enters into Phase Two of reopening, Soho sex club NSFW is navigating how to get down and dirty while still staying squeaky clean and coronavirus-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe is no Hillary -- and that's problem for President...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-joe-biden-no-130040808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's best hope for reelection is dragging Biden down. That's harder when many voters like the guy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newest U.S. Attorney Faces Slate of Cases of Interest to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/newest-u-attorney-faces-slate-080000814.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Audrey Strauss takes over one of the most high-profile prosecutor jobs in America with a lot on her plate.The 72-year-old former deputy to Geoffrey Berman is taking the reins as acting U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York after an unusual shuffle -- her boss refused to leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO: At least 70 shot, including 4 children, in violent weekend...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/at-least-70-shot-10-fatally-including-4-children-in-violent-weekend/6259526/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten people were killed, including four children, and at least 60 others wounded in shootings across Chicago over the weekend, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police say deaths of black people by hanging are suicides. Many aren't so sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/Police-say-deaths-of-black-people-by-hanging-are-15356603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historical seasons have changed, and once again, America's trees are bearing a strange and bitter fruit - dead black bodies.  In less than one month, six black people have been found hanging from trees, in California, Georgia, New York, Oregon and Texas. Authorities say that all of these deaths appear to be suicides, with no signs of foul play. But family members of the deceased, protesters and activists, and some scholars of anti-black violence are intuitively suspicious about those conclusions. Rumors are also swirling on social media that these deaths are lynchings, with Twitter users saying things like: "With sound body and mind, I'm here to tell you right now, if my body is found hanging from a tree, I did NOT commit suicide, I was murdered."  These incidents are happening at a time of nationwide racial upheaval - when people are already on edge and suspicious about police accounts of their encounters with black people. Tree hangings evoke traumatic memories of America's grisly history of unpunished lynchings of thousands of black adults and children between 1880 and 1968.  Black people do commit suicide, of course, though the rate is 60% lower than for whites, according to data from the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. In black American culture, suicide is widely regarded as a shameful act; when it happens, it's generally private, and hanging is not a preferred method.  "It is very uncommon for young black men to commit suicide, let alone by hanging," says Raymond Winbush, a psychologist since 1976 who has treated hundreds of black men and boys and is the director of Morgan State University's Institute for Urban Research. The American Association of Suicidology reports that firearms are the predominant method of suicide among African Americans (as they are for the nation overall), regardless of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation dog may finally bark, investors bet...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-inflation-analysis/inflation-dog-may-finally-bark-investors-bet-idUSKBN23S09E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold, forests, property stocks, inflation-linked bonds - these are just some of the assets investors are pouring money into on the view that the recent explosion of government spending and central bank stimulus may finally rouse inflation from its decade-long slumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India, China commanders meet after border clash amid calls for boycott of Chinese goods...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200622124443-918dj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA-CHINA/ (WRAPUP 3, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 3-India, China commanders meet after border clash amid calls for boycott of Chinese goods</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From California to Texas, Triple-Digit Heat Set to Bake West...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-texas-100-degree-heat-113402336.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Temperatures forecast to hit 100 degrees Fahrenheit or more will bake the U.S. West, pushing up power demand and making going outside a misery from California to Texas over the next few days.Heat advisories and warnings have been issued from Oregon through California’s Central Valley east</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILVER: BIDEN LANDSLIDE POSSIBLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/nate-silver-a-biden-landslide-is-possible</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polling guru Nate Silver sees "a lot of issues" with President Trump's quest for reelection in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broken windows, Molotov cocktail: DOJ finds creative ways into local rioting cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/20/doj-local-rioting-cases-329735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While some of the cases are unquestionably grave, others have raised questions about whether the federal government is stretching its authority to satisfy President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Astonishing' neolithic circle found near Stonehenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/stonehenge-monument-neolithic-durrington-walls-archaeologists-a9578436.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Abnormally large dust cloud' making 5,000-mile trek across Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/abnormally-large-dust-cloud-making-5000-mile-trek-across-atlantic/761708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Upcoming Show 'CRACKA' Puts Blacks As Slave Owners, Whites As Slaves...</title>
      <link>https://allhiphop.com/news/upcoming-show-cracka-puts-blacks-as-slave-owners-and-whites-as-slaves-C3ANu-10YUqpINeVlN-kOw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;allhiphop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What history flipped the script on slavery and the Africans kept slaves? "Cracka" explores this alternative non-reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is This Lowest Point In Modern U.S. History?</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/is-this-the-lowest-point-in-modern-u-s-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things have certainly gotten really crazy here in 2020.  First we witnessed the eruption of the worst global pandemic in 100 years, then the U.S. economy started collapsing, and then we watched major U.S. cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear mounts FDA pressured to rush vaccine by election...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jun/22/trump-circle-pressure-fda-rush-covid-19-vaccine-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerns rises after White House attacked agency’s reversal on hydroxychloroquine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Much Strenuous Exercise Shortens Lifespan?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/take-it-easy-too-much-strenuous-exercise-may-shorten-your-lifespan-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surprising new study out of Japan concludes that daily strenuous exercise can actually shorten, not prolong, one's lifespan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The revolution is being streamed: Rappers DABABY and LIL BABY make protest music for the masses...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/music/story/2020-06-22/lil-baby-bigger-picture-da-baby-rockstar-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DaBaby and Lil Baby, who have the No. 1 song and album, respectively, in the country, have both released protest songs that have only added to their popularity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes of drive-in concert: 'Never been more grateful to be honked at'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Behind-the-scenes-of-a-drive-in-concert-I-ve-15356446.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Eli, lead singer of the Eli Young Band, strummed his guitar onstage and gazed into the crowd on a warm Texas evening in June. "How many of you out there are dreamers?" he asked.  He was answered by an explosion of car horns.  "Whatever it is that you dream about," he said, "keep on believing."  This was not exactly how the country band envisioned their 2020 touring experience. As they started singing their Grammy-nominated hit "Even If It Breaks Your Heart," a stirring anthem about following your dreams, they looked out on a parking lot filled with people sitting in their cars as they tuned into the show via an FM radio station, just like a drive-in movie.  Summer tour season is upon us, and Americans are starting to begrudgingly accept that, amid the covid-19 pandemic, large-scale concerts won't resume for a long time. The music industry has been forced to get creative - and besides artists hopping on Instagram for a live stream, the most popular choice for a musical performance might be drive-in concerts.  What was once an unimaginable concept makes a lot of sense in the era of social distancing. But how does it actually work? We talked to music executives, artists and fans at one show in Texas for a snapshot of what it's like to organize, perform and attend a concert in the year 2020.  As acts such as Keith Urban and Los Lobos embark on drive-in shows, each setup is different: Some are in fields, others are on farms. On June 27, Garth Brooks will perform a concert broadcast to 300 drive-in movie theater screens. The Eli Young Band show, part of the "Concert In Your Car" series (some of which we viewed via FaceTime from Washington, because that's how things work now) took place in a parking lot outside Globe Life Field in Arlington where the Texas Rangers play.  The idea started in March, as soon as Triple 8...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Former pope Benedict returns to Vatican...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6d673e690b9de6d31e55f134ec20bea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Emeritus Pope Benedict XVI left Germany on Monday to return to the Vatican after a four-day visit to his ailing elder brother.  Benedict, a Bavarian native, boarded an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Office of Hate': Bot Army Target of Brazil's Top Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/in-hunt-for-office-of-hate-brazil-s-supreme-court-closes-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Hunt for â€˜Office of Hate,â€™ Brazilâ€™s Supreme Court Closes In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left eyes huge night in NY, Kentucky primaries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/503620-left-eyes-huge-night-in-ny-kentucky-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expectations on the left are rising for what could be a huge night of victories Tuesday in separate primaries in Kentucky and New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Leaders Face Dilemma: Deal With Trump or Hang On...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-leaders-face-dilemma-deal-040001020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- America’s allies and rivals face a tough choice as Donald Trump trails in polls ahead of November’s presidential election: Wait to see if he loses to presumptive Democratic candidate Joe Biden, or cut deals now to avoid negotiating with an emboldened second-term Trump.The president addressed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I will be working with authorities to take legal action'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/06/22/justin-bieber-accused-of-rape-by-two-women-on-social-media-denies-and-refutes-i-will-be-working-with-twitter-and-authorities-to-take-legal-action</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two young women — going only by first names Danielle and Kadi– over the weekend accused Justin Bieber of rape. They say the assaults took place respectively in 2014 and 2015. In each ca…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT SHREDS... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/lincoln-project-mocks-trumps-size-in-new-ad-the-rally-theyre-talking-about-rally-size-probably/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest Lincoln Project ad is full of double entendres about size, mocking the president for low turnout at his rally in Tulsa on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMPAIGN MANAGER FACING CHOP?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/21/politics/jared-kushner-ivanka-trump-brad-parscale/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump and Jared Kushner are "pissed" at campaign manager Brad Parscale over his predictions of a much larger crowd than the one that turned out at the Tulsa rally Saturday night, according to a Trump campaign source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber denies sex assault allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1018107/justin-bieber-denies-sexual-assault-allegation-receipts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUSTIN Bieber has broken his silence to deny an allegation of sexual assault made against him. The singer, 26, took to Twitter to post a lengthy thread, vehemently refuting claims by an anonymous w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Dems' confidence comes with fear... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Biden-and-Democrats-confidence-comes-with-fear-15355742.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's campaign and his Democratic Party are feeling an emotion they have not sensed in quite some time, and one that prompts more than a little fear: confidence.  Poll after poll has placed the presumptive Democratic nominee ahead of President Donald Trump, with comfortable national leads that in some cases have swollen to double digits. He is ahead by narrower but consistent margins in battleground states, and Biden himself has grown increasingly bullish on the idea that Democrats will win back the Senate majority, a possibility not even dreamed of until recently. Once an anemic fundraiser, he is now routinely drawing multimillion-dollar hauls.  Trump is presiding over a Depression-style economy, a global pandemic and boiling social unrest. His administration has lost several high-profile Supreme Court cases, his former National Security adviser's new book has painted a damning portrait, and he is now in perhaps the weakest position of his presidency with less than five months before the general election. The images of a half-empty arena for Trump's much-hyped rally in Tulsa, Okla., on Saturday underscored the perception of a diminished incumbent, one who has long seen crowd size as a barometer of success.  But for Democrats, the very idea that they are doing well provokes an underlying skittishness. They worry about voting during the coronavirus crisis, amid restrictions that could make it harder to cast ballots. Some fear a coming misinformation campaign and say the party risks underestimating Trump's ability to turn the country against their nominee.  They also worry their party still does not fully understand what led voters to Trump in the first place, and they are terrified that overconfidence, like some of them had four years ago, will lead to complacency.  "It feels like 2016 all over," said Andrew...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane flies Confederate flag over NASCAR race...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/racing/nascar/story/_/id/29344050/nascar-sees-confederate-flags-fly-talladega-superspeedway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASCAR sees Confederate flags fly outside and above the track as the top circuit hits Talladega Superspeedway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How virus tore through Latin America's largest market...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-coronavirus-tore-through-Latin-America-s-15355707.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - Martín Mateo had a cold. Or so he thought: sore throat, body aches, runny nose. "He felt bad but kept working," said his son, Carlos. The 50-year-old father had labored for decades as a tomatero - a tomato man - at Latin America's biggest food market.  Coronavirus? He didn't believe in it.  Then Mateo started gasping for breath. Within days, he was dead.  By then, scores of his fellow tomateros also were infected. Workers hoisted yellow signs outside the market reading "High Contagion Zone." At least 10 tomato men died from mid-April to mid-May. They included Mateo's cousin Antonio, a bookkeeper at a neighboring stall named Guillermo, and a bald man everyone called El Peluche - loosely, "Fuzzy."  The tomato aisle at Mexico City's famed Central de Abasto market offers a glimpse into why the virus has hit the country so hard. It scythed its way through the sprawling complex, picking off workers made vulnerable by poverty-related problems: chronic illnesses, distrust of government, a need to keep earning money.  While there is no official data, vendors can name dozens of people in the vegetable aisles alone who lost their lives - green-bean sellers, chili vendors, potato men - in one of the most brutal outbreaks in the city.  "Here we didn't believe" the coronavirus was a threat, said 57-year-old Anastasio Ramón Alonso, a longtime tomato vendor. "But when people began to die and die and die, we lost our incredulity."  Officials have reported more than 20,000 coronavirus deaths in Mexico, undoubtedly an undercount. The virus appears to have entered the country with the upper class - people returning from business trips in Italy and skiing holidays in Colorado. But it spread quickly to low-income workers, who have been hit particularly hard.  As in the United...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arena less than third full at campaign kickoff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/503781-tulsa-fire-department-says-trump-rally-attendance-was-about-6200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer than 6,200 people attended President Trump's campaign rally at the BOK Center in Tulsa, Oklahoma, on Saturday night, well below the arena's capacity of roughly 19,000, according to the Tulsa Fire Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis star Dimitrov ill after playing in event... </title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/dimitrov-tests-positive-coronavirus-playing-djokovic-event-183427844--ten.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grigor Dimitrov said on Sunday he has tested positive for coronavirus after pulling out of an exhibition tournament which also featured world number one Novak Djokovic. &amp;quot;I want to reach out and let my fans and friends know that I tested positive back in Monaco for Covid-19,&amp;quot; world number 19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no flights, Argentine sails across Atlantic to see parents...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-flights-argentine-sails-across-atlantic-see-parents-215309502.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar del Plata (Argentina) (AFP) - "Mission accomplished!" That joyful declaration came from Juan Manuel Ballestero, an Argentine sailor who, unable to fly home from Portugal due to the pandemic, crossed the ocean alone in his modest sailboat to see his aging parents. After testing negative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH GETS BIGGER:  Secret pact between Trump and Zuckerberg?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/21/whats-facebooks-deal-with-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Nov. 20, NBC News broke the news that Mark Zuckerberg, Donald Trump and a Facebook board member, Peter Thiel,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights vulnerabilities heading into election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49b32796b5a9ab1884624d3173cf6283</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump's return to the campaign trail was designed to show strength and enthusiasm heading into the critical final months before an election that will decide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims he told officials to slow coronavirus testing to keep case numbers low..</title>
      <link>http://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-says-he-told-officials-to-slow-coronavirus-15355554.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid surging coronavirus infections nationwide, President Donald Trump said at his campaign rally in Tulsa Saturday night that he told officials to administer fewer coronavirus tests to keep case numbers down.  The comments drew a chorus of criticism from congressional Democrats, who said it validated fears that the president was more focused on saving face amid the pandemic than on protecting public health. A White House official told The Washington Post that Trump was joking, a common defense from Trump's aides when he says something controversial.  Eight states on Saturday reported their highest single-day case counts since the pandemic began, and daily new infections nationwide exceeded 30,000 on both Friday and Saturday. The country has not seen daily totals that high in more than seven weeks.  One of the country's leading public health experts said Sunday that he was worried that Trump's rally in Tulsa could become a "super-spreader" event resulting in many people being infected with the coronavirus.  "We have seen in the past few months around the world that indoor gatherings have been the source of most super-spreading events," Tom Inglesby, director of the Center for Health Security at Johns Hopkins University, told Fox News, responding to a question about possible contagion at the rally. "There's an opportunity for much more spread in a short period of time, so I am worried about that."  Attendance was reported to be significantly lower than expected, but Inglesby said the rally was still "concerning in terms of public health risks."  He noted that attendees were packed close together, shouting and shaking hands, and that many were not wearing masks. "All of those things will increase the risk of spread," he said.  Host Chris Wallace asked whether there was "some...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debacle in Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Analysis-What-empty-seats-in-Tulsa-tell-us-about-15355871.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. - The omens started early Saturday morning, before the gates to the "Great American Comeback" rally were opened. I got downtown later than I'd wanted to, making a detour to buy a poncho, after weather forecasts suggested a chance of rain. Shortly after 9 a.m., I started looking for parking, and two Tulsans who were charging $30 for a space politely said I might want to drive around before paying.  "I thought we'd be full by now," one of the sellers said, "based on the news."  One minute later, I found free street parking and began walking to the BOK Center. Eight hours later, President Donald Trump's campaign was dramatically downscaling its first rally since March, striking a stage at an overflow section as a few dozen supporters mingled in a space designed for thousands. The rain never came. Neither did the expected audience.  Saturday's rally in Tulsa was, on the campaign's own terms, a debacle - a meticulously organized and well-protected event that left thousands of seats unfilled in an arena once sold out by Nickelback. The president himself had predicted a "record-setting crowd," tweeting as the number of online ticket requests surged to Coachella proportions - 300,000, 600,000, 1 million.  "We've never had an empty seat, and we certainly won't in Oklahoma," Trump had said.  That hubris overshadowed what might have been landmark event, the first campaign rally of any kind since March and the start of the coronavirus pandemic. The audience was still larger than any Joe Biden had drawn before securing the Democratic nomination. And the hours of programming clarified how Trump would run against Biden - a message that partly relied on massive rallies.  "Would anybody sleep on the ground overnight waiting to see Joe Biden?" asked Lara Trump, a presidential daughter-in-law and key campaign surrogate, as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Tightens Controls...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/australia-fears-second-wave-as-state-tightens-virus-controls/ar-BB15NSUA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elgort says relationship 'brief, legal and entirely consensual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-8443923/Ansel-Elgort-denies-claims-sexually-assaulted-17-year-old-girl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ansel Elgort denied sexually assaulting a 17-year-old girl in 2014 in a message shared Saturday on Instagram. He said the two had a bad breakup and the relationship was 'legal and consensual.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theodore Roosevelt Statue to Be Removed From Museum of Natural History...</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/roosevelt-statue-to-be-removed-from-natural-history-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statue of former President Theodore Roosevelt that has stood in front of the American Museum of Natural History in Manhattan for 80 years will be removed amid ongoing protests for racial justice, officials said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on Roberts ahead of Supreme Court's abortion ruling... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/503645-all-eyes-on-roberts-ahead-of-supreme-courts-abortion-ruling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts is under the microscope as the Supreme Court prepares to issue its first major ruling on abortion rights in the Trump era, which will give the clearest indication yet of the court’s willingness to revisit protections tha</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WEST SIDE STORY' Star Accused of Rape...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/06/21/ansel-elgort-denies-sexual-assault-allegation-through-instagram-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I cannot claim to understand Gabby’s feelings but her description of events is simply not what happened,”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary's Largest News Website Sees Its Independence in Danger...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/hungarys-main-online-news-says-195524743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungary’s leading online news site said Sunday that its editorial staff and independence are at risk because of a reorganization attempt that could compromise its journalistic integrity. Index.hu moved its “ independence barometer,” set up in 2018 after an ownership change, to “in danger” from “independent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FURIOUS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/trump-furious-underwhelming-crowd-tulsa-rally-n1231674</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This was a major failure," one outside adviser said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin hints he could seek FIFTH term as president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-hints-he-could-seek-a-fifth-term-as-president-in-2024/ar-BB15N5vg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds to Week of Warning Signs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-tulsa-rally-adds-to-week-of-warning-signs-for-campaign/ar-BB15MD9J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeaching Attorney General 'a waste of time,' top judiciary Dem says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/impeaching-barr-e2-80-98a-waste-of-time-e2-80-99-judiciary-democrat-says/ar-BB15NhL8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parscale threatens to block reporters from future rallies... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-campaign-chief-goes-after-media-coverage-of-low-rally-turnout-suggests-they-may-revoke-credentials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's re-election campaign manager, Brad Parscale, threatened to block reporters from the president's future rallies following coverage on the lower turnout they saw in Tulsa on Sat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There Will Be Recriminations'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/axios-jonathan-swan-there-will-be-recriminations-for-half-empty-trump-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Axios White House reporter Jonathan Swan said "there will be recriminations" for the dramatically underwhelming rally President Donald Trump held in Tulsa, Oklahoma Saturday night. Earlier i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany struggles to enforce isolation rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200621171158-qic2t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY-MEAT (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Germany struggles to impose local coronavirus infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans regret lack of emergency savings during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/americans-regret-lack-of-emergency-savings-during-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adults in the United States are feeling economic pressure due to the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China bans some US chicken, shuts Pepsi plant to fight virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beijing-reports-22-virus-cases-millions-tested-055718774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China banned imports from a top US poultry producer and ordered a Beijing Pepsi factory to close Sunday as authorites clamped down on food production and distribution amid a new coronavirus cluster in the capital. Health officials also reported 22 new virus cases in Beijing, where they have tested more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd wave of virus cases? Experts say we're still in 1st...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f401d034122b820a89773432cbf51152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's all this talk about a “second wave” of U.S. coronavirus cases?  In The Wall Street Journal last week, Vice President Mike Pence wrote in a piece headlined “There Isn’t a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirated editions appear online...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d58c06b5dc22674bba6d43d4589421bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — John Bolton's memoir officially comes out Tuesday after surviving a security review and a legal challenge from the Justice Department. But over the weekend, it was available in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian DL Hughley tests positive after fainting onstage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cab1aa39b785468afb0eb19a42bdc3ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Comedian D.L. Hughley announced he tested positive for COVID-19 after collapsing onstage during a performance in Nashville, Tennessee.  The stand-up comedian,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New concerns in Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/894beaff53b7e7a30b7de989d960a198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — Will Boyd was at the funeral Saturday morning for a relative who had died after contracting the new coronavirus when he got the call with the news. His brother had also...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain declares deadly stabbing spree 'terrorism'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/18844d7216c6a25b4e85779806f31a56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;READING, England (AP) — A stabbing rampage that killed three people as they sat in a British park on a summer evening is being considered a terrorist attack, police said Sunday. A 25-year-old man...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Former pope Benedict to return to Vatican on Monday...</title>
      <link>http://www.naharnet.com/stories/en/272724</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.naharnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former pope Benedict XVI will return to the Vatican on Monday from Germany, where he is visiting his sick brother, the Regensburg bishopric said.  "Return trip is planned for Monday," said the bishopric in the Bavarian city on its website,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
