<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited food coming, but will shoppers buy?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/584754eadd0a43a1ab5bf93af54845af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The next generation of biotech food is headed for the grocery aisles, and first up may be salad dressings or granola bars made with soybean oil genetically tweaked to be good for your heart. By early next year, the first foods from plants or animals that had their DNA "edited" are expected to begin selling. It's a different technology than today's controversial "genetically modified" foods, more like faster breeding that promises to boost nutrition, spur crop growth, and make farm animals hardier and fruits and vegetables last longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns 'to gossip is to kill'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/064ffe09bc6e4fa9bf5a6c73692a9fe7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis is denouncing gossip as a form of "terrorism" and is warning the faithful against telling lies. Francis explored the Catholic commandment against "bearing false witness" during his Wednesday general audience. He warned the faithful in a chilly St. Peter's Square that "We all live by communicating, and we are continuously on the edge between truth and lies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Morale Takes Tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-morale-takes-a-tumble-along-with-stock-price-1542200400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An internal survey found just 52% of employees were optimistic about Facebook’s future, down from 84% the year earlier. The darkening mood comes amid a dropping share price, leadership turmoil and disclosures of privacy violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan migrants reach Tijuana, start climbing the border fence...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/caravan-migrants-reach-tijuana-start-climbing-the-border-fence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first wave of migrants from the Central American caravan began climbing border fences on Tuesday after arriving at the U.S. border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China builds artificial sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/china-built-artificial-sun-its-13588517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's artificial sun is designed to help develop cheap and clean energy on earth using nuclear fusion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Never Nancy': Dems ramp up efforts to sideline...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/nancy-democrats-ramp-efforts-sideline-pelosi-offering-alternative/story?id=59180391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A band of House Democrats determined to oppose House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi's speaker bid are planning to release a signed letter as soon as this week indicating that they have gathered enough support to deny her the 218 votes needed to win the gavel on the House floor in January, a move they...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazes on two fronts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/paradise-lost-california-fires-rage-155925886.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of firefighters battled blazes in northern and southern California on Tuesday as body recovery teams searched the remains of houses and charred cars for victims of the deadliest wildfire in the history of the US state. Most of the fatalities have been caused by the so-called "Camp Fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who battled flames to save his corner...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-battled-flames-save-corner-paradise-023856218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paradise (United States) (AFP) - By all accounts, retired carpenter Brad Weldon should have evacuated his home in Paradise as the flames approached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech stars see shares dim in eyes of investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181114-tech-stars-see-shares-dim-eyes-investors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Robocop' patrols summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/robocop-patrol-singapore-summit-094319844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi-tech Singapore has deployed an autonomous robot with a swivelling camera for a head and flashing lights to patrol a summit venue -- arresting the attention of amused passers-by who stopped to snap selfies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tech factory conditions fuel suicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/china-tech-factory-conditions-fuel-suicides-study-10929938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost city built by Trojan War captives found...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-lost-ancient-city-built-by-Trojan-War-captives-13390072.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mention the Trojan War and what may first come to mind is the oft-told tale of Helen, wife of Sparta's King Menelaus and possessor of a divinely bestowed beauty, falling in love with Paris of Troy. Their supposed affair and her subsequent abduction from Sparta sparked a 10-year Greek siege of Troy that would shape Greek civilization for centuries to come - at least according to Greek mythology. Now fast-forward about three millennia. For the past several years, archaeologist Elena Korka has been focused on a far less romantic but more concrete legacy of the Trojan War: A lost city named Tenea, reportedly settled by war prisoners brought over from Troy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida voting machines overheat, forcing another recount...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/floridas-palm-beach-county-voting-machines-overheat-forcing-another-recount-of-about-175k-early-votes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida’s Palm Beach County recount was delayed Tuesday night after its voting machines overheated, forcing it to restart the recount of about 175, 000 early votes, according to Susan Bucher, supervisor of Elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP to Pick Another Cheney to Help Party Find Winning Message...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/gop-to-pick-another-cheney-to-help-party-find-a-winning-message#gs.QddzCkY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP to Pick Another Cheney to Help Party Find a Winning Message</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel defense minister resigns over Gaza cease-fire; 'Surrendering to terror'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46207094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avigdor Lieberman denounced the cabinet's decision to accept a ceasefire as "surrendering to terror".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal justice reform faces a make-or-break moment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/416558-criminal-justice-reform-faces-a-make-or-break-moment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long-stalled criminal justice reform effort is facing a make-or-break moment: winning over President Trump’s support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink's husband threatens looters: 'Will be shot on site'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2018/11/13/pinks-husband-carey-hart-threatens-california-wildfire-looters-shot-site/1996302002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carey Hart posted a picture to Instagram Tuesday of a dozen gun-wielding men standing in front of a sign that reads,Â "Looters will be shot on site."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five days of fury...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ie/news/world/five-days-of-fury-inside-trump%E2%80%99s-paris-temper-election-woes-and-staff-upheaval/ar-BBPGZml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems eye Senate seat in Republican-led Mississippi...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2867f89dc1d347cdaab422902a320a55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — National Democrats are focusing on Mississippi's U.S. Senate runoff, a year after winning a longshot contest in another Deep South state dominated by Republicans. Democrat Doug Jones defeated Roy Moore in Alabama last December after Moore was hit by accusations of sexual misconduct. Now in Mississippi, Mike Espy is challenging Republican Sen. Cindy Hyde-Smith. She faces sharp criticism for a video that surfaced Sunday of her praising a supporter at a Nov. 2 campaign event in Tupelo by saying: "If he invited me to a public hanging, I'd be on the front row."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro Bashes President Again: 'Down With This Motherf*cker!'</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/scene/news/robert-de-niro-bashes-trump-again-down-with-this-motherf-er-1203027278/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert De Niro may have been the target of the Donald Trump-supporting pipe bomb mailer, but that isn’t stopping the Oscar winner from trashing the president. Just two days after playing Robert Mue…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC, CBS fighting for ratings dominance...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/nbc-cbs-fighting-television-ratings-dominance-59174251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Score one week for NBC in what's becoming an intriguing battle with CBS for dominance in the television ratings this season. NBC's victory in the most recent measurements provided by the Nielsen company means it has won bragging rights for three weeks so far this fall, with CBS also winning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES: Trump, stung by midterms and nervous about Mueller, retreats from traditional duties...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-trump-absent-20181113-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump, brooding over midterm losses and the Mueller probe, has cancelled a number of events that presidents normally attend, including a visit to Arlington National Cemetery. Behind the scenes, he has lashed out at aides, from low level press assistants to senior officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Virgin bride' sold to highest bidder on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7733272/virgin-bride-for-sale-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SICK family sold their 17-year-old daughter “virgin bride” on Facebook to the highest bidder for 500 cows, three cars and £7,500 in a “barbaric slave market”. The teen was married to businessman …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's most secretive lab: Bullets that never miss, weaponized insects, superhumans...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7726956/darpa-tech-us-government/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BULLETS that never miss, super soldiers with extreme strength and robot warriors capable of rising up against humans may sound like the stuff of science fiction… but the truth is that they have all…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clyburn claims critics using race to oppose leadership bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article221603770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Jim Clyburn, D-South Carolina, is accusing his detractors of launching a “dog whistle” whisper campaign to undermine his candidacy for House majority whip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: American military advantage has eroded; ChinaRussia threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-military-advantage-has-eroded-study-says-13390309.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The United States has lost its military edge to a dangerous degree and could potentially lose a war against China or Russia, according to a report released Wednesday by a bipartisan commission that Congress created to evaluate the Trump administration's defense strategy. The National Defense Strategy Commission, comprised of former top Republican and Democratic officials selected by Congress, evaluated the Trump administration's 2018 National Defense Strategy, which ordered a vast reshaping of the U.S. military to compete with Beijing and Moscow in an era of renewed great-power competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitting in embers, residents wonder: Can Paradise be rebuilt?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-paradise/sitting-in-the-embers-californians-wonder-can-paradise-be-rebuilt-idUSKCN1NI2UK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lovingly placed statues of a family of deer still mark the entrance to Mare Reas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jesus' face' uncovered at ancient church in Israeli desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/jesus-face-uncovered-at-ancient-church-in-the-israeli-desert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A previously-unknown 1,500-year-old painting of Christ’s face has been uncovered at a Byzantine church in Israel’s Negev desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNLUCKY IN LOVE?  IT'S ALL YOUR MOTHER'S FAULT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6385855/Your-mothers-love-life-determines-romantic-partners-have.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say the findings, based on data of mothers and children in the US since 1979, show mothers pass relationship skills to their kids, which influence how they interact with everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Lady's Office: White House Aide 'No Longer Deserves' to Serve...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-aide-ricardel-no-longer-deserves-serve-first-194655656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. first lady Melania Trump has asked that the White House sever ties with deputy national security adviser Mira Ricardel, a spokeswoman for the first lady's office said on Tuesday. "It is the position of the Office of the First Lady that she [Ricardel] no longer deserves the honor of serving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY'S BREXIT D-DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4179680916a64b08a3afa24ea50785a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Theresa May will try to persuade her divided Cabinet on Wednesday that they have a choice between backing a draft Brexit deal with the European Union or plunging the U.K. into political and economic uncertainty. May called a special Cabinet meeting after negotiators from Britain and the EU broke a months-long logjam and reached agreement on divorce terms, including a plan to keep the border between Ireland and Northern Ireland open after Brexit. May was meeting with ministers one-on-one Wednesday morning ahead of the Cabinet meeting at 2 p.m. (1400 GMT) in a bid to build agreement and stave off potential resignations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfire death toll rises as search for missing continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2144d7d18c2144d09ce31eec69515441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — A message board at a shelter for the many people who fled California's deadliest wildfire is filled with photos of the missing, as well as pleas for any information about relatives and friends. "I hope you are okay," reads one hand written note on the board filled with white and yellow sheets of notebook paper. Another had a picture of a missing man: "If seen, please have him call." Authorities on Tuesday reported six more fatalities from the Northern California blaze, bringing the total number of dead so far to 48. They haven't disclosed the total number still missing, but earlier in the week that figure was more than 200.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court hears case of cannibal who turned self in when 'tired of eating human'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timeslive.co.za/news/south-africa/2018-11-13-cop-recounts-grisly-find-in-cannibals-house-of-horrors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timeslive.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Estcourt policeman Constable Ryan Ntshalintshali got the shock of his life when traditional healer Nino Mbatha walked into the charge office in July 2017 and pulled a human hand out of a pink school bag he was carrying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU court rules taste of food cannot be trademarked...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/business/court-rules-taste-food-cannot-trademarked/cHNPIeJ7tkCEYlUpFlmOuM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union's highest court hasn't fallen under the spell of Dutch witches' cheese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shivering horse found waiting in pool...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-wildfires/article/Paradise-Camp-Fire-horse-found-pool-rescued-Hill-13388884.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A horse was found in the backyard pool of a Paradise, Calif. resident, after the animal apparently tried to find a safe space as the Camp Fire moved through town.  Paradise resident Jeff Hill shared photos of the horse Sunday on Facebook. The photos showed the horse in a pool, but entangled in the pool cover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Climate Change' Killing Sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/science/2018/11/13/climate-change-could-damage-sperm-and-thus-male-fertility/1990220002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We know that human sperm like to keep cool. And according to a new study,Â male fertility could decline asÂ temperatures soar due to global warming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCLAREN Moves More Production to UK; Brexit Trend Reverse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-14/mclaren-moves-more-production-to-u-k-in-reverse-of-brexit-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smart City of Surveillance' Faces New Resistance...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/11/13/google-quayside-toronto-smart-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local organizers in Toronto have united to push Google out of their government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Customer Chokes MCDONALD'S Manager Over Missing Ketchup...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2018/11/13/woman-upset-over-ketchup-beats-chokes-mcdonalds-employee-in-santa-ana-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was captured on video beating a McDonald's store manager in Santa Ana recently, and police released the footage Tuesday as they intensified their efforts to catch the assault suspect. The incident began around 11 p.m. on Oct. 27, after the woman went through the drive-thru of the McDonald's restaurant in the 1500 block of North Bristol Street, according to the Santa Ana Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient privacy concerns as GOOGLE absorbs health division... </title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/13/privacy-concerns-google-absorbs-deepminds-health-division/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Privacy advocates have raised concerns about patients&amp;rsquo; data after Google said it would take control of its subsidiary DeepMind&amp;rsquo;s healthcare division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American murdered in tourism hot spot, parents say Mexican authorities may be covering it up...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/american-tourist-murdered-in-mexico;-family-wants-fbi-to-investigate/4680803/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California family is looking for answers after learning their 27-year-old son was murdered while visiting Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal workers horrified after PYTHON slithers out of moving package...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/postal-workers-horrified-after-python-13584503</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pictures of the snake were posted online after being found by staff at Pos Laju in Malaysia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA: Humans on Mars in 25 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/3954/nasa-wants-people-mars-within-25-years-doc-1at6se1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer says Pena Nieto took bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-mexico-el-chapo/lawyer-calls-el-chapo-scapegoat-says-mexicos-pena-nieto-took-bribes-idUSKCN1NI18V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer for accused Mexican drug lord Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman told ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Thief faces armed robbery after dousing clerk with hot sauce...</title>
      <link>https://www.oanow.com/news/business/police-robbery-suspect-used-hot-sauce-in-attack-on-/article_644ec5f8-e75d-11e8-8767-0b941ecc71ae.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oanow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LaFayette man is accused of throwing hot sauce into the face of a 73-year-old store clerk and then struggling with her for money in a cash register before fleeing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gives in to threats of boycott...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/13/nfl-gives-in-to-threats-of-boycott-over-rams-chiefs-mexico-city-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most hyped game of the year — a potential electric Super Bowl preview — has a new, safer venue. Monday night’s Rams-Chiefs matchup, which was slated to take place in Mexico City, is being…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds drop probe against Bernie's wife, says aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.sevendaysvt.com/OffMessage/archives/2018/11/13/feds-drop-burlington-college-probe-according-to-sanders-aide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sevendaysvt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Updated at 3:07 p.m. A spokesperson for Jane O'Meara Sanders said Tuesday that federal authorities have concluded a long-running probe into her tenure as president...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL MOVES GAME OUT OF MEXICO; BACK TO LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/nfl-moves-chiefs-rams-game-from-mexico-city-to-los-angeles-due-to-poor-field-conditions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After concerns over the field in Mexico were raised, the NFL decided to move the game back to L.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY passholder displays pro-Trump signs at park, gets banned...</title>
      <link>https://www.wftv.com/news/local/back-at-it-disney-passholder-displays-pro-trump-signs-at-park-gets-banned-again/871736237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wftv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who was banned from Disney World several weeks ago for unfurling a giant Donald Trump banner in the Magic Kingdom has been banned again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities step up pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcentv.com/article/news/nation-now/cities-step-up-pressure-on-e-cigarette-industry-over-teen-vaping-epidemic/465-a0187dfb-376f-4228-9dbb-a98fae0e12a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcentv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cities increase pressure on e-cigarette industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-cig maker JUUL kills social media acounts in wake of govt scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/11/13/juul-stops-selling-e-cigarette-flavors-social-media-promotions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juul will stop selling its flavored pods at retail stores but will continue to sell them through its website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here come the hoverbikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/hoverbikes-are-finally-here-don-t-expect-fly-cheap-ncna935191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California firm's long-anticipated flying motorcycle will set you back $150,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploited contenders to learn secret infrastructure plans?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/11/13/amazon-headquarters-hq-2-search-process-giant-ruse/1986577002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Amazon dangled the prospect of 50,000 jobs and economic transformation, did the losers get played?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constitutional Right to Press Pass?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cnn-v-trump-is-there-a-constitutional-right-to-a-press-pass-1542142441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge could soon decide whether the Trump administration violated the U.S. Constitution when it stripped away the press credentials of CNN’s chief White House correspondent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AND Secret Service agent who took badge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/secret-service-agent-who-took-jim-acostas-press-pass-named-in-cnn-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN included a Secret Service agent as part of its lawsuit against the White House over the suspension of correspondent Jim Acosta's press credentials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kink robots on sale for less than $10...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7730548/sex-robot-harmony-ai-app-realbotix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VIRTUAL sex robot could be yours – if you’re willing to fork out $9.90 (about £7) for the app. Harmony AI lets randy gadget fans customise their sex robot’s appearance, voice and even…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN sues White House for banning Acosta...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6384825/CNN-sues-Trump-demanding-return-Acosta-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN filed a federal lawsuit against the Trump administration after the White House suspended correspondent Jim Acosta's 'hard pass' press credential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD: Media Emotionally 'Unhinged'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/416467-woodward-on-cnns-lawsuit-remedy-isnt-a-lawsuit-its-more-serious-reporting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watergate reporting icon Bob Woodward argued that the remedy to President Trump’s decision to revoke Jim Acosta’s White House press credentials isn’t a lawsuit, “it’s more serious reporting about what he’s doing.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court orders buoy Abrams in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/court-orders-buoy-abrams-georgia-counties-race-certify-results/ihrrRsVNW9mpJpcMODLWwJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The post-election drama in Georgia intensified Tuesday as protests rocked the state Capitol, dozens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran Declared Clinically Dead Miraculously Wakes Up...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/11/13/veteran-miraculously-wakes-up-after-being-clinically-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Wisconsin veteran was declared clinically dead. But then he woke up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi reveals why he's in crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/13/jerome-corsi-mueller-roger-stone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corsi says he will be indicted for perjury</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump could answer written questions this week...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-could-answer-written-russia-probe-questions-week-202713446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The questions from Special Counsel Robert Mueller that Trump is preparing to answer relate only to Moscow's involvement in the election, and not to whether Trump may have tried to obstruct the Russia investigation, the source told Reuters. Among the topics covered is a June 2016 meeting between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School under fire for patriotic speaker...</title>
      <link>http://www.toledoblade.com/local/education/2018/11/12/ottawa-hills-schools-under-fire-veterans-day-speaker-nick-adams/stories/20181112153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editor’s note: This story was updated Tuesday morning to include a statement from Nick Adams. Ottawa Hills school officials are facing backlash from ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Build Helipads...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/remysmidt/amazon-hq2-helipad-new-york-deal-jeff-bezos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Ah, so their top execs just can fly over the groveling masses squeezing themselves through the City’s overly clogged transportation arteries.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery after Cleveland reporter's trailer park murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/news/2018/11/clevelandcom-culture-reporter-nikki-delamotte-found-shot-to-death-in-wood-county.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nikki Delamotte, cleveland.com's culture reporter, was found dead early Monday in Wood County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May dramatically summons ministers to Downing Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6383371/May-gathers-Cabinet-amid-claims-Brexit-deal-touching-distance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Prime Minister is bracing for a showdown with her ministers after officials in Brussels reportedly firmed up a text overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA considered truth serum for terror suspects...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e4bc055b4fee4e0d9f47ab14adc2c173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Shortly after 9/11, the CIA considered using a drug it thought might work like a truth serum and force terror suspects to give up information about potential attacks. After months of research, the agency decided that a drug called Versed, a sedative often prescribed to reduce anxiety, was "possibly worth a try." But in the end, the CIA decided not to ask government lawyers to approve its use. The existence of the drug research program — dubbed "Project Medication" — is disclosed in a once-classified report that was provided to the American Civil Liberties Union under a judge's order and was being released by the organization Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY:  Obese kids less likely to flourish...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/obese-kids-less-often-demonstrate-coping-skills-academic-184333278.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We often think of childhood obesity as a problem of the future," the study's lead author told Reuters Health. "Now that we know childhood obesity is linked with poor coping skills and school performance, the time to act is now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Condo Frenzy; Selling Via Text Message...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/amazons-move-to-long-island-city-sparks-condo-frenzy-1542116117</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The retail giant’s interest in putting a headquarters in the Queens neighborhood has unleashed a gold rush that reminds some brokers of the boom preceding the last financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of all food wasted before reaches plate...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/11/13/obesity-pill-aims-kill-hunger-expanding-stomach/&gt;Pill to kill hunger by expanding in stomach...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TODAY' Ratings Climb After Megyn Kelly Departs...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/today-ratings-surge-megyn-kelly-departure-1203027190/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The departure of Megyn Kelly from NBC’s 9 a.m. “Today” timeslot marked a setback for the anchor as well as the network paying her millions of dollars to host. But the split appear…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More US kids get paralyzing illness; Cause still unknown...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/more-us-kids-paralyzing-illness-cause-still-unknown-180907054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — More children have been diagnosed with a mysterious paralyzing illness in recent weeks, and U.S. health officials said Tuesday that they still aren't sure what's causing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS Lay Offs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/starbucks-to-lay-off-5-of-corporate-workforce-1542130200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is planning to lay off approximately 5% of its global corporate workforce as the chain struggles to attract new and repeat customers to its U.S. coffee shops amid a highly competitive coffee market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic Materials Fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.vcstar.com/story/news/local/communities/simi-valley/2018/11/12/woolsey-fire-may-have-released-toxins-santa-susana-field-laboratory/1976845002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vcstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists concerned the flames at contaminated Santa Susana Field Lab may have released hazardous materials from site of 1959 partial nuke meltdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Injured After Car Crashes Into Social Security Office...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/11/13/car-crashes-into-social-security-building-in-egg-harbor-township/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crash happened at the building at 1350 Doughty Road, around 9:45 a.m. Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 1: Ocasio-Cortez protests at Pelosi's office...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-joins-climate-protest-in-pelosis-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY taxpayers to pay $48,000 per job at new AMAZON HQ...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/48k-per-amazon-hq-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York state is kicking in more than $1.5 billion in taxpayer-funded incentives for getting half of Amazon&amp;#39;s second headquarters located in a section of Queens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divisions between progressives and moderates threaten to complicate new majority...</title>
      <link>http://www.fltimes.com/tns/washington/divisions-between-progressives-and-moderates-threaten-to-complicate-democrats-new/article_3376bcc2-8ed9-51f6-8775-6e8d0e5bc8e3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON —House Democrats figured out how to win in districts that narrowly supported President Donald Trump in 2016. Now they have to figure out how to govern there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB TRAFFIC RACE:  FOXNEWS PASSES CNN; DRUDGE OVER NYT; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic Hollywood sites destroyed...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/historic-hollywood-sites-destroyed-as-woolsey-fire-burns-1160564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'M*A*S*H' TV set area, the Peter Strauss and Reagan ranches, and the Paramount Ranch all have been damaged by the wildfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA on track to set record trade deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenroberts/2018/11/13/this-year-ironically-first-u-s-deficit-record-in-12-years/#2a0d962b2550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. trade deficit will almost certainly set a record in 2018 for the first time in 12 years, U.S. Census Bureau data suggests for the first time. It's has been a remarkable run without a deficit. Prior to 2006, the last record-setting year, the U.S. had set a record 11 of the previous 12 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists predict 'dark matter hurricane' will collide with Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/scientists-predict-a-dark-matter-hurricane-will-collide-with-the-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, here's the story of the dark matter hurricane -- a cosmic event that may provide our first glimpse of the mysterious, invisible particle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trolled back by French army for missing memorial due to rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7726531/donald-trump-trolled-french-army-missing-ww1-ceremony-rain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE French army has mocked Donald Trump after the president pulled out of a Remembrance Day event due to the rain. Using the hashtag #MondayMotivation, they posted a picture of a soldier crawling u…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOCKS FRANCE FOR WAR LOSSES...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-renews-attack-on-macron-as-bromance-turns-sours#gs.rlI16s4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump implied that the French needed the U.S. to rescue them from the Germans in both world wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen gives 80 hours of testimony!</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/mr-cohen-comes-to-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's next prime minister?</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/152181/boris-johnson-britain-next-prime-minister</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the court jester of post-truth politics has positioned himself to seize power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman sues to stop algorithm from deciding election...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/11/13/poliquin-campaign-sues-in-federal-court-to-stop-ranked-choice-count/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Maine's Secretary of State continues the process to determine winner in the 2nd Congressional District, attorneys for the campaigns of Jared Golden and Bruce Poliquin head to court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEF ON THE CHOP!</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-planning-shakeup-eyeing-chief-staff-dhs-secretary/story?id=59159956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is considering yet another shakeup of his administration, preparing to remove Department of Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen and looking at possible replacements for Chief of Staff John Kelly, including Vice President Mike Pence's Chief of Staff Nick Ayers,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs and portable morgues...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/holding-out-slim-hope-as-crews-search-for-more-fire-dead/17990840/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities moved to set up a rapid DNA-analysis system and bring in cadaver dogs, mobile morgues and more search teams in an intensified effort to find and identify victims of the deadliest wildfire in California history, an inferno that killed at least 42 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising mentally fragile generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181113-smartphones-raising-mentally-fragile-generation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targets Stone in final push..</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/416372-mueller-targets-stone-in-final-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel seems to be have told his staff to go after the activist as the investigation closes in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Florida election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL RECORD SKID</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/13/oil-markets-opec-global-stock-markets-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices fell on Tuesday after U.S. President Donald Trump put pressure on OPEC not to cut supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Apprehensions Highest Since Trump Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/13/migrant-border-apprehensions-at-highest-level-since-trumps-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The apprehension of migrants between ports of entry in October hit its highest level since the election of President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ginsburg working from home after fall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/administration/416395-ginsburg-working-from-home-after-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, who is still recovering from a fall last week, missed a sitting of the court on Tuesday morning.The Supreme Court’s Public Information Office said Ginsburg, 85, was working from home Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel calls for creation of 'real, true' European army...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6384785/Angela-Merkel-calls-creation-real-true-European-army.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The German Chancellor put forward the idea in a speech to the European Parliament, echoing the words of Emmanuel Macron who called for the creation of a European army just days earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Perjury Trap'...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/right-wing-conspiracy-theorist-pal-of-roger-stone-reveals-he-will-be-indicted-for-perjury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN sues White House for banning reporter Acosta...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/13/cnn-sues-president-trump-and-white-house-for-banning-reporter-jim-acosta.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSNEWS:  INDICTMENTS AS EARLY AS TODAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/new-mueller-indictments-expected-as-soon-as-tuesday-cbs-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Mueller Indictments Expected as Soon as Tuesday, CBS Reports</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
