<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fed expects to keep rates near zero -- through 2023...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/16/federal-reserve-zero-interest-rate-416202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The central bank shed more light on its pledge not to raise interest rates until prices begin to rise more rapidly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American military employee facing German jail after 'going on bar crawl with COVID'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8739599/American-military-employee-26-facing-jail-Germany-going-bar-crawl-COVID.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Munich public prosecutor has opened an investigation after the woman, named only as Yasmin A., left, went out partying in bars, right, in Garmisch-Partenkirchen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake used as face mask on bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-manchester-54163293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger said she thought the man was wearing a "funky mask" until she spotted it slithering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS CORP closing printing plant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/16/news-corp-in-multiyear-deal-to-print-the-post-wsj-at-new-nyc-plant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Corp. on Wednesday announced plans to shift printing of the New York Post, the Wall Street Journal and Barron’s to a new press in New York City. Under a multiyear agreement unveiled Wedn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotels facing painful wave of permanent closures...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Hotels-permanently-closing-15569121.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large number of U.S. hotels temporarily closed their doors as bookings dried up last spring due to the coronavirus epidemic. And as fall approaches, it looks like a significant number of them might not be able to reopen as expected even if business starts to pick up to a healthy level again.  Although big banks and other lenders often allowed some flexibility for strapped hotels to make their mortgage payments during the pandemic, their patience is running low and foreclosure is looming for some major urban properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE WHITE HOUSE STAFFERS INFECTED...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/09/16/white-house-staff-members-reportedly-test-positive-for-covid-19-less-than-24-hours-after-president-donald-trump-visited-philadelphia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House staff members have reportedly tested positive for COVID-19 less than 24 hours after President Donald Trump visited Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCMASTER: Terror Threat In U.S. 'Far Greater' Today Than 9/11...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/09/16/scott-pelley-hr-mcmaster-60-minutes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Pelley previews the 53rd season of 60 Minutes, his interview this Sunday with former National Security Advisor H.R. McMaster and his conversation with legendary journalist Bob Woodward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: What happens if results are contested?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fa1f88c9ff0681bd78b147137c09b3d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Is it possible the election will be up in the air and we won't have a president on Inauguration Day: Jan. 20, 2021? Even if the election is messy and contested in court,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney says probe 'not legitimate role of government'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1de4ee7909548a132796767779ee56d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Utah Sen. Mitt Romney is sharply criticizing a Republican investigation into Democrat Joe Biden’s son, saying it's “not the legitimate role of government” to try and damage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posts Video of Himself Urinating on a Grammy Award Placed in Toilet... </title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/09/16/showstopper-kanye-posts-video-of-himself-urinating-on-a-grammy-award-placed-in-toilet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West has posted a video to Twitter in which he’s urinating on a Grammy Award placed in a toilet. It’s him, he’s wearing his ugly sneakers. Kanye has 21 Grammy Awards from 69…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS SPOKESMAN TAKES LEAVE AFTER MENTAL BREAKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/top-hhs-official-takes-leave-absence-after-facebook-rant-cdc-n1240051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came days after top HHS spokesman Michael Caputo warned of a CDC plot against the president and urged Trump supporters to "buy ammunition."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTFACEBOOK launch augmented reality reporting project...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/new-york-times-facebook-augmented-reality-0973fa9e-ffcc-4a68-91ec-ffb77d757745.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the first time that The Times has experimented with AR technology at scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director says masks might be better than vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/nation-world/us-outlines-sweeping-plan-to-provide-free-covid-19-vaccines/FFIOZFPD6BFM5P47GRLDG56HQI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDC Director Robert Redfield has told a Senate committee that face masks may offer more individual protection against COVID-19 than a potential coronavirus vaccine, according to reporter Max Burns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of NYC's top earners consider fleeing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/16/nearly-half-of-nycs-top-earners-considered-relocating-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of New York City residents earning six figures or more have considered fleeing the Big Apple during the coronavirus crisis over cost-of-living concerns, according to a new poll. Researc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC's Trump Town Hall Loses to 'AMERICA'S GOT TALENT' in Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/abc-trump-town-hall-draws-152953550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Stephanopoulos welcomed Donald Trump Tuesday to an ABC News town hall, when ABC welcomed in 3.8 million viewers. NBC’s “America’s Got Talent” roughed up the town hall’s audience in their shared 9 p.m. hour. NBC and CBS tied for first in ratings, both with a 0.6 rating/4 share in the advertiser-coveted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals Decapitate historic statue of Jesus in El Paso...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1482244/vandals-decapitated-statue-jesus-church-altar-elpaso/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING pictures show how vandals DECAPITATED a historic statue of Jesus on a church altar in Texas. The Diocese of El Paso shared pictures of the Sacred Heart of Jesus – a 90-year-old statue – th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD SECRETS:  Chateau Marmont Staff Allege Racial Discrimination, Sex Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/rot-at-hollywoods-playground-chateau-marmont-staff-allege-racial-discrimination-sexual-misconduct-and-neglectful-management</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Public Schools Spend $30K Per Student; 23% of 8th Graders Proficient in Reading...  </title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/dc-public-schools-spend-30k-student-only-23-8th-graders-proficient  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Cartel Gunmen Burn Rival's Face Off as He Begs for Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2020/09/16/graphic-exclusive-cartel-gunmen-burn-rivals-face-off-in-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunmen from a narco-terrorist cartel burned off the face of a rival and recorded the man’s agony as he begged for death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye asks campaign staff to avoid 'fornicating'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/516658-kanye-west-reportedly-asked-campaign-staff-to-avoid-fornicating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West reportedly requested that staffers working on his long-shot presidential bid abstain from sex outside marriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Tunnel Under Vegas for Self-Driving Cars Almost Complete...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/09/elon-musk-boring-company-tunnel-las-vegas-near-completion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Tunnels under cities with self-driving electric cars will feel like warp drive,” Musk tweeted on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  President Stuck at 42% Job Approval...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/320303/trump-stuck-42-job-approval.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval rating is proving rock steady this summer, but at a level that's not promising for reelection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey finds shocking lack of Holocaust knowledge among millennials...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/survey-finds-shocking-lack-holocaust-knowledge-among-millennials-gen-z-n1240031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty-three percent of those surveyed did not know 6 million Jews were murdered in the Holocaust. Over half of those thought the toll was under 2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe tops 50% for first time in Wisconsin... </title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/biden-tops-50-percent-in-wisconsin-polling-average/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s 6.7-point lead is almost identical to Hillary Clinton’s 6.5-point lead over Trump in the final RCP average of Wisconsin polls in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO Shops His Sprawling Aspen Estate as Rich Flee Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/goldman-ceo-shops-his-sprawling-aspen-estate-as-rich-flee-cities/ar-BB196uiI?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalio Warns of Threat to Dollar as Reserve Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/ray-dalio-warns-of-threat-to-dollar-as-reserve-currency/ar-BB194NhI?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One name is left on the hurricane list, and it's only September...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article245757115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy moving money to prepare for Biden presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/some-wealthy-americans-are-prepping-their-finances-for-a-possible-joe-biden-presidency-this-is-all-going-up-and-you-may-never-see-it-as-good-as-it-is-now-2020-09-16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One San Francisco accountant finishes every client conversation with a discussion about what a Biden administration could mean for portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockets fired at Israel after 'peace deal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/rocket-alert-sirens-sound-across-southern-israel-642391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamas: "The normalization agreements between the UAE and Bahrain with the Zionist entity are not worth the ink with which they were written."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS LAYOFFS</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/fox-news-hit-with-layoffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal documents show officials waved red flags before Tulsa rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/516605-exclusive-internal-documents-show-officials-waved-red-flags-before-trumps </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  Trump now says he 'up-played' virus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/516615-trump-says-he-up-played-virus-threat-despite-telling-woodward-he</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday claimed that he "up-played" the severity of the coronavirus pandemic, despite telling Bob Woodward in March that he "wanted to always play it down."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  '76% CHANCE' OF WINNING ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-election-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest forecast of the 2020 presidential election between President Donald Trump and Joe Biden by Nate Silver’s FiveThirtyEight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step Up Large Stock Sales...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/super-rich-step-large-stock-160806514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Some of the world’s wealthiest people have sold more than $3 billion of stakes in their major holdings since August, diversifying their fortunes as stock markets rebounded.Heinz Hermann Thiele offloaded about $1.2 billion in shares of Knorr-Bremse AG, the German brake manufacturer that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine Wedding Now Linked To 7 Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/09/16/millinocket-maine-wedding-coronavirus-deaths-covid-19-big-moose-inn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The August wedding reception at the Big Moose Inn in Millinocket is linked to more than 175 confirmed cases of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIC FLOODS TURN STREETS INTO RIVERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8427b1f1bb05f47ed74f7556c3f97bcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENSACOLA, Fla. (AP) — Hurricane Sally lumbered ashore near the Florida-Alabama line Wednesday with 105 mph (165) winds and rain measured in feet, not inches, swamping homes and trapping people in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea May Conduct Underwater-Launched Missile Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2020-09-16/seoul-n-korea-may-conduct-underwater-launched-missile-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fox-news-layoffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News Media laid off some of its workforce Wednesday while "realigning several functions and restructuring various divisions"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbados to remove Queen Elizabeth II as head of state...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200916-barbados-to-remove-queen-elizabeth-ii-as-head-of-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barbados to remove Queen Elizabeth II as head of state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO Shops His Sprawling Aspen Estate as Rich Flee Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/goldman-ceo-shops-his-sprawling-aspen-estate-as-rich-flee-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman CEO Shops His Sprawling Aspen Estate as Rich Flee Cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC creating wastewater surveillance system...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/937817/cdc-working-create-covid19-wastewater-surveillance-system-sewage-samples-prove-effective</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Testing wastewater for a deadly virus isn't new — it has been used to identify polio outbreaks — but the idea has gained traction as cities and universities look for ways to plod toward normalcy as the world awaits a safe and effective COVID-19 vaccine. Universities have had great success monitoring for COVID-19 flare-ups by testing wastewater, or 'all the dirty stuff from the toilets, showers, sinks, washing machines, dishwashers, you name it,' Politico reports. And now 'the CDC and HHS are working on a national wastewater surveillance system and data portal' for willing states and local governments. People shed the coronavirus in their waste days before they show signs of illness, so finding COVID-19 in wastewater can give authorities 'seven precious days for intervention,' said Ian Pepper at the University of Arizona. His team tested the wastewater outside dorms every morning, but monitoring samples of sewage in Baton Rouge predicted an outbreak two weeks after Louisiana's governor lifted restrictions — then tracked the sharp decline in infections after the governor started requiring people to wear masks. Setting up a nationwide wastewater surveillance system early in the pandemic would have helped alert officials before an outbreak took hold, says David Larsen, an epidemiologist and public health expert at Syracuse University, one of the schools that tests wastewater. 'My kids would be in school right now. Our economy would not have tanked the way that it has.' And testing every U.S. ZIP code twice a week would cost about $3 billion a year, Larsen estimates. 'It's really not much. The cost per person monitored is like $10, if that, a year.' The payoff, he said, is it 'would be huge to get us back to work' for the year before a vaccine becomes widely available. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With messaging on racism, sports joins the polarization of our lives...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/civil-rights/516593-with-messaging-on-racism-sports-joins-the-polarization-of-our-lives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Athletes have rights, but fans do too — and they may not want a lecture on systemic racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Ten reverses; Will play football...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaaf/bigten/2020/09/16/big-ten-football-announces-fall-season-start-october/5792689002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Ten presidents agreed to a plan Wednesday to move forward with an eight-game season starting Oct. 24 after postponing fall schedule in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London could introduce curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/london/london-curfew-coronavirus-a4548646.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Curfews could be imposed in the capital to fight a second Covid-19 wave, a public health chief signalled today as he appealed to Londoners to “pull together” to limit a feared surge in cases. With the epidemic expected to hit the city with far greater force in coming weeks, Professor Kevin Fenton, London director of Public Health England, made clear that more restrictions may be imposed, including some possibly across the capital, to avoid a more stringent lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't do it': Studies flash sub-zero rate warnings to central banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-markets-negative-analysis/dont-do-it-studies-flash-sub-zero-rate-warnings-to-central-banks-idUSKBN26724F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six years after the ECB cut interest rates below 0%, behavioural finance gurus have a message for other central banks thinking about taking the plunge: don't.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shares Fake Video of Joe Playing 'F*ck the Police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/trump-shares-manipulated-fake-video-of-biden-playing-fck-the-police-on-his-iphone-it-was-despacito/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump shared a fake video of Joe Biden playing the hit N.W.A. song "Fuck the Police" on his iPhone, a video which has earned a "Manipulated Media" warning from Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX ROLLOUT JANUARY?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-8739331/Feds-outline-sweeping-plan-provide-free-COVID-19-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration outlined a sweeping plan Wednesday to make vaccines for COVID-19 available for free to all Americans by providing shots from multiple companies in two doses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Denmark, forest the new classroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/In-Denmark-the-forest-is-the-new-classroom-15570973.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAMSO, Denmark - On a balmy Monday afternoon earlier this month, Sebastian Lukas, 27, watched from across a clearing as his third- and fourth-grade students whittled branches into spearheads with sharp knives.  His gaze turned to another group, who were supposed to be working on math problems. Two students, perched on a log, scrambled to produce their textbooks, just in time to look busy.  Lukas began the year teaching in a classroom like any other, in Samso Frie Skole, a school on the Danish island of Samso. But when the novel coronavirus pandemic struck, the school, like many across the country, embraced a new way to hold certain classes: almost entirely outdoors.  Instead of sitting at desks, Lukas's students wander through a rambling woodland, lush with trees and crisscrossed by dirt tracks.  As countries grapple with how and when to restore students to classrooms, a growing number of schools have embraced outdoor learning - especially in the highly regarded Nordic education systems, where the model had already begun to gain momentum.  When many Danish schools reopened in April, Prime Minister Mette Frederiksen urged teachers to allow for as much time outdoors as possible, as a precaution against the spread of the virus. In Norway, education and health officials also recommended that classes meet outside.  Out of nearly 200 Norwegian schools willing to respond to a recent survey by researchers Ulrich Dettweiler and Gabriele Lauterbach, the results of which have not yet been published, more than half said they had begun to provide more outdoor classes. Researchers in Denmark said they had observed a similar trend.  Some countries, including Germany, have a tradition of outdoor preschools and kindergartens, which have begun to catch on in the United States as well. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Senate seats most likely to flip...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/The-Senate-seats-most-likely-to-flip-in-November-15570881.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Republicans have a slim, three-seat majority in the Senate that they're trying to hold on to in November. And they are in for a battle to do it: There are 13 chances on this list for Democrats to flip Senate seats and just two for Republicans.  But Republican strategists say they're seeing evidence that Republican-leaning voters turned off by President Donald Trump's handling of the coronavirus are starting to come home to the party in the final stretch, and they think it might be enough for some of these vulnerable Republican senators to hang on and deny Democrats the majority.  Democrats' path to the majority is to net at least four Senate seats or net three and win the White House to get the majority, but that requires going through some Republican-leaning states.  For now, the most competitive races remain largely unchanged from our last rankings in August. We'll update these rankings again between now and November.  Because so many of the races could go either way - while others are more of a stretch - we divided them in three categories: More likely to flip than not, toss-ups, and could flip under the right conditions.  - More likely to flip than not: Alabama, Colorado and Arizona.  1. Alabama (Democrat-held): Democratic Sen. Doug Jones remains the most vulnerable senator in 2020. He's facing former Auburn University coach Tommy Tuberville, a first-time candidate that Democrats are modestly optimistic could stumble in the spotlight. But no one with a stake is arguing that a Senate race in one of the most pro-Trump states in the country is a toss-up.  2. Colorado (Republican-held): Republican Sen. Cory Gardner is trying to pull away from Trump in this purple-blue state by talking about an outdoors conservation bill he wrote, rather than how he voted to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe Covid Stars Scramble After Declaring Victory Too Fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/europe-virus-stars-scramble-after-declaring-victory-too-fast-2297277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's third aircraft carrier takes shape, with ambitions to challenge U.S. dominance...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/China-s-third-aircraft-carrier-takes-shape-with-15570885.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan - Shipbuilders in Shanghai have laid out the hull of China's first modern aircraft carrier, which could be launched into the water in the coming months as it enters the latter phases of construction, according to new satellite images and state media reports.  High-resolution photos recently obtained by the Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS), a non-partisan think tank in Washington, show for the first time sections of the carrier being assembled in the open at a dry dock at the sprawling Jiangnan shipyard. The vessel, which will be China's third carrier but the first to be equipped with modern technology, is likely to be larger than the previous two that were based on outdated Soviet designs. At the waterline, the new ship will be about 1,000 feet long and 130 feet wide, the photos show.  Matthew Funaiole, a researcher at the CSIS ChinaPower project, said it is not yet clear from the images whether the new carrier will have an electromagnetic catapult to efficiently sling fighter jets off its deck - the biggest question mark over current Chinese carrier technology. The USS Gerald R. Ford, commissioned in 2017, was the first carrier to include the cutting-edge feature.  Still, "the Chinese are showing tremendous capability of designing and fitting out vessels," Funaiole said. "It's moving along on pace. It's impressive the process they're going through to position themselves at the forefront of carrier technology."  The progress of China's third carrier has been of intense interest in rival capitals as well as inside China, where it is seen as a tangible symbol of the country's development into a global power boasting a modern, world-class military. China has commissioned two carriers in the past decade: the Liaoning was a retrofit of an old Soviet model and the second, the Shandong, was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem Al-Aqsa mosque compound to close over spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200916-jerusalem-al-aqsa-mosque-compound-to-close-over-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerusalem Al-Aqsa mosque compound to close over virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICUs nearing capacity in French city...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/16/europe/france-bordeaux-coronavirus-hospitals-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dealing with the first wave was like a sprint, the second will be more like a marathon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to Put 1,000 Warehouses in Suburban Neighborhoods...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-plans-put-1-000-090053785.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Amazon.com Inc. plans to open 1,000 small delivery hubs in cities and suburbs all over the U.S., according to people familiar with the plans. The facilities, which will eventually number about 1,500, will bring products closer to customers, making shopping online about as fast as a quick</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water shortages in West likelier than previously thought...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be04e1fa0008d0dbcd537148dd7f2ab0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARSON CITY, Nev. (AP) — There's a chance water levels in the two largest man-made reservoirs in the United States could dip to critically low levels by 2025, jeopardizing the steady flow of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic floods...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/86eaa637cd37f17323babec62fd43a4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the latest developments on tropical weather (all times local): The National Hurricane Center says Sally is still Category 2 Hurricane with top winds of 100 mph (155 kph) as it moves...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primate takes phone, then selfies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4c253ec1fb41d2ce6d234f4155908f8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia (AP) — A Malaysian student whose cellphone was stolen while he was sleeping has tracked down the culprit: a monkey who took photo and video selfies with the device before...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech ship launches on 400th Mayflower anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3ba9cb779caba78781a030a194bb57df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLYMOUTH, England (AP) — Dignitaries, seafarers and scientists were gathering in Plymouth, England, on Wednesday to mark the 400th anniversary of the departure of the Mayflower, the ship that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese warns against cinema becoming 'comfort food'...</title>
      <link>https://uk.movies.yahoo.com/martin-scorsese-warns-against-cinema-030935625.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In what appeared to be a dig at at-home viewing, the director said it was 'all the more important' to celebrate the medium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-rex skeleton could fetch record price at New York auction...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/t-rex-skeleton-could-fetch-091106895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The skeleton of a 40-foot (12-meter) dinosaur nicknamed &amp;quot;Stan&amp;quot;, one of the most complete Tyrannosaurus rex specimens ever found, will be auctioned in New York next month and could set a record for a sale of its kind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-Right Police Officers Suspended in Germany After Sharing Hitler Pictures...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/16/far-right-police-officers-suspended-in-germany-after-sharing-hitler-pictures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — Twenty-nine German police officers have been suspended from duty on suspicion of sharing images of Adolf Hitler and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space debris threatening to destroy ISS; Orbit 'too perilous for humans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8738593/1million-funding-tackle-space-debris-destroy-ISS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers are concerned that high-value craft in low-Earth orbit, such as the International Space Station (ISS), could be destroyed by a rogue piece of debris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Super-Rich Step Up Large Stock Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/super-rich-step-up-large-stock-sales-after-global-prices-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the world’s wealthiest people have sold more than $3 billion of stakes in their major holdings since August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politics creates economic illusion in Houdini hometown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/953f86e60c1420b2ebc7635c0823baaa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLETON, Wis. (AP) — Nothing can shake Scott Rice’s faith that President Donald Trump will save the U.S. economy — not seeing businesses close or friends furloughed, not even his own hellish bout...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T considers cellphone plans subsidized by ads!</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-at-t-ceo-interview-exclusive-idUSKBN2663HK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T Inc &lt;T.N&gt; is considering offering wireless phone plans partially subsidized by advertising as soon as a year from now, Chief Executive John Stankey said in an interview on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD:  'We are living in an Orwellian world'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/bob-woodward-calls-out-trump-now-claiming-he-up-played-covid-we-are-living-in-an-orwellian-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Woodward appeared on CNN Tuesday night shortly after the first preview of the president's ABC News town hall dropped, in which President Donald Trump actually claimed that he "up-played&amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of NYU students locked down in dorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-york-university-dorm-locked-down-due-to-coronavirus-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A residence hall at New York University was locked down after four freshmen tested positive for the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Audience Declines for Every Game Not Starring Tom Brady...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/football-audience-declines-for-every-game-not-starring-tom-brady/ar-BB194MbB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump less trusted than Putin and Xi!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-is-less-trusted-than-putin-and-xi-and-the-us-is-hitting-historic-lows-of-approval-from-its-closest-allies/ar-BB194Kdq?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Fish exposed to noise pollution die early...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/fish-exposed-to-noise-pollution-likely-to-die-early-study-01600211104?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fish stressed by noise are less able to fight off disease while prolonged exposure can lead to an early death, according to research published Tuesday, the latest outlining the consequences of man-made clamour on the natural world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuses Joe of taking performance-enhancing substance...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-accuses-biden-taking-performance-135853036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump, in his latest shredding of political niceties, suggested Tuesday that his Democratic opponent Joe Biden has taken drugs to improve his performance in debates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apatow Calls Out 'Chilling' Hollywood Censorship: 'China Has Bought Our Silence'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/judd-apatow-hollywood-censorship-international-china-saudi-arabia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Judd Apatow, Hollywood’s desire to bring home major box office wins in China and Saudi Arabia comes at the cost of meaningful and truthful content. The director, comedian and pro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9hnfX3M-aiw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Follow my Twitter for more f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Rockets Fired From Gaza During Ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-gulf-usa-gaza/palestinians-fire-rockets-into-israel-wounding-two-during-white-house-ceremony-idUSKBN2662YO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinian militants fired rockets from Gaza into Israel, wounding two people, on Tuesday at the same time as Israel and two Gulf Arab states signed normalisation agreements at the White House in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI:  Murders Soar In 2020 While Other Violent Crimes Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/murders-have-soared-while-other-violent-crime-declined-fbi-finds/ar-BB194iqZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York City Prepares for Second Wave Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/new-york-city-prepares-for-a-second-wave-with-a-chance-to-blunt-the-worst/ar-BB194NYO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL AND USA BATTLE OVER MASKS IN OVAL OFFICE?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/israel-uae-peace-accord-coronavirus-face-mask-b447338.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKE TRENDING:  PRO-TRUMP GROUP PAYS TEENS TO POST ONLINE</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pro-Trump-group-pays-teens-to-post-online-15569883.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - One tweet claimed coronavirus numbers were intentionally inflated, adding, "It's hard to know what to believe." Another warned, "Don't trust Dr. Fauci."  A Facebook comment argued that mail-in ballots "will lead to fraud for this election," while an Instagram comment amplified the erroneous claim that 28 million ballots went missing in the past four elections.  The messages have been emanating in recent months from the accounts of young people in Arizona seemingly expressing their own views - standing up for President Donald Trump in a battleground state and echoing talking points from his reelection campaign.  Far from representing a genuine social media groundswell, however, the posts are the product of a sprawling yet secretive campaign that experts say evades the guardrails put in place by social media companies to limit online disinformation of the sort used by Russia during the 2016 campaign.  Teenagers, some of them minors, are being paid to pump out the messages at the direction of Turning Point Action, an affiliate of Turning Point USA, a prominent conservative youth organization based in Phoenix, according to four people with independent knowledge of the effort. Their descriptions were confirmed by detailed notes from relatives of one of the teenagers who recorded conversations with him about the efforts.  The campaign draws on the spam-like behavior of bots and trolls, with the same or similar language posted repeatedly across social media. But it is carried out, at least in part, by humans paid to use their own accounts, though nowhere disclosing their relationship with Turning Point Action or the digital firm brought in to oversee the day-to-day activity. One user included a link to Turning Point USA's website in his Twitter profile until The Washington Post began asking questions about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP TO 30" OF RAIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/hurricane-sally-could-dump-30-inches-of-rain-on-parts-of-gulf-coast/811946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALLY CRAWLS TOWARD GULF COAST...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-09-15-hurricane-sally-forecast-louisiana-mississippi-alabama-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest on the dangerous storm surge and flooding rain threats Sally will bring to the Gulf Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Could Limit Virus Testing to Worst Cases as Labs Struggle...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-k-could-limit-virus-192833797.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.K. government warned that coronavirus tests could soon be further restricted as laboratories struggle to cope with rising demand, in a blow to businesses seeking to get more workers back to the office.Health Secretary Matt Hancock said on Tuesday he would “not shirk from decisions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dawn of new Middle East' as leaders sign peace deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7544b322a254ebea1693e387d83d9d8b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Israel on Tuesday signed historic diplomatic pacts with two Gulf Arab states at a White House ceremony that President Donald Trump declared will mark the “dawn of a new Middle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug sting busts alleged cocaine distribution network selling at 'pandemic prices'...</title>
      <link>https://www.silive.com/news/2020/09/drug-sting-busts-alleged-cocaine-distribution-network-selling-at-pandemic-prices-1-staten-islander-charged.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.silive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luis Rodriguez traveled off the Island to retrieve cocaine on multiple occasions, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dawn of new Middle East' as Israel, UAE, Bahrain leaders sign peace deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8733657/Trump-preside-historic-Arab-Israel-recognition-deals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump hailed the 'dawn of a new Middle East' when he presided over the signing of historic diplomatic deals between Israel, the United Arab Emirates and Bahrain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa bar owner arrested for flouting social-distancing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/15/iowa-bar-owner-arrested-for-flouting-social-distancing-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of an Iowa bar named the Pour Bastards Pub was busted for letting drinkers flout social-distancing rules — then ripping up the charge sheet when served at his bar, according to a re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting outside Phoenix court wounds federal officer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d0e12e28912fd08fdd7de74b9fb6f4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — A drive-by shooting wounded a federal security officer outside the U.S. courthouse in downtown Phoenix on Tuesday, and a person has been taken into custody, authorities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS chief overrode officials to ease testing rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/15/hhs-alex-azar-overrode-fda-testing-rules-415400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Azar took matters into his own hands, overriding objections from FDA chief Stephen Hahn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn, guns and racism: Virtual classrooms disrupted by hackers, pranksters...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/coronavirus/ct-covid-19-remote-learning-hacks-schools-20200915-fmfol6ew75a5djq3h2z75uvniq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Our students are being attacked for just coming to class and all the protection is falling on the educators,&amp;quot; one teacher said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alan Dershowitz Files $300 Million Lawsuit Against CNN...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/lawsuit/alan-dershowitz-files-300-million-lawsuit-against-cnn-for-portraying-him-as-an-intellectual-who-had-lost-his-mind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Morgue Brought In...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/oregon-wildfires-are-so-devastating-theyve-brought-in-a-mobile-morgue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once a painful fixture of the coronavirus pandemic, a mobile morgue is now scouring 900,000 acres of burned land in Oregon for human remains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: More Cats Likely Positive Than Assumed...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/more-cats-covid-positive-than-assumed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study out of COVID-19's epicenter, the Chinese city of Wuhan, has some troubling news for all the cat owners out there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna to Direct, Co-Write Her Own Biopic...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/madonna-to-co-write-direct-her-own-biopic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian to freeze FACEBOOK, INSTA accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/kim-kardashian-freezes-facebook-instagram-33b375c1-ec6a-41db-b1ec-697b63648a18.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She said the platforms were spreading "hate, propaganda and misinformation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC Cramer calls Pelosi 'Crazy Nancy' during interview...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/15/cnbc-host-jim-cramer-calls-pelosi-crazy-nancy-mid-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC host Jim Cramer called House Speaker Nancy Pelosi “Crazy Nancy” to her face during an interview on Tuesday morning — a taunt for the California liberal typically used by Pres…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Battling Memory Problems 6 Weeks After Leaving Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/09/14/covid-long-haulers-suffer-lingering-effects-of-virus-weeks-to-months-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The misery from people sick with COVID-19 may last longer than first thought. WCCO looked into the lingering symptoms leading to a new group of virus survivors known as "long-haulers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOUTH PARK' tackles virus with first hour-long special...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/tv/south-park-covid-pandemic-episode/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the trailer for South Park's upcoming 'pandemic special,' the show's first-ever hourlong episode.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
