<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ex-MSNBC, RT host Ed Schultz dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.wday.com/news/4468792-ed-schultz-former-fargo-radio-personality-has-died</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT LAKES, MINN. - Longtime broadcaster Ed Schultz has died.Sources tell WDAY-TV News in Fargo that Schultz died of natural causes at his lake home near Detroit Lakes. He was 64.Schultz started his broadcast career in TV and radio in Fargo in the early 1980s, including time as sports director at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make-or-Break Exams Bring Out Best and Brightest Cheaters...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/make-or-break-exams-bring-out-the-best-and-brightest-cheaters-1530806771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiny cameras, implanted microphones, sneaker transmitters—Iraqi students apply creativity and diligence to devising new ways to cheat on high-school tests, which carry huge weight in determining their futures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK DOC:  New movie examines mysterious skin lesions, Morgellons disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/arts/movies/2018/06/28/unflinching-look-the-pain-others/DtYApYQuHaBIFoagStn2AN/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film focuses on three women suffering from disease that feels like parasites under the skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump closes in on Supreme Court pick; 3 judges top list...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ap-source-pence-met-supreme-court-contenders-043447870--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is closing in on his next Supreme Court nominee, with three federal judges leading the competition to replace retiring Justice Anthony Kennedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. labor shortage is reaching critical point...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/05/the-us-labor-shortage-is-reaching-a-critical-point.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s labor shortage is approaching epidemic proportions, and it could be employers who end up paying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke Test Videos Released Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/over-250-declassified-nuke-test-videos-released-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers hunt down decaying footage from vaults across the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK DOC:  New movie exmains mysterious skin lesions, Morgellons disease...</title>
      <link>https://filmmakermagazine.com/105512-youtube-body-horror-penny-lane-on-her-morgellons-disease-doc-the-pain-of-others/#.Wz47ctJKjb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;filmmakermagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the era of fake news and alternative facts, and of people constructing their own custom-made versions of reality, Penny Lane’s The Pain of Others feels very timely, to say the least. Defying any expectations and preconceived notions, Lane’s perfectly titled “body-horror doc” acts as a challenging and thought-provoking sociological study of one unusual YouTube community (which, with Maxim Pozdorovkin’s Our New President also on the fest circuit this year, makes me think “YouTube behavioral psych” might soon become a thing).   The Pain of Others weaves together the video diaries of three women suffering from Morgellons disease, a term given to a scientifically unrecognized series of symptoms that seem straight out of a Cronenberg flick (crawling sensations and thread-like fibers emerging from the skin!), and it leaves the viewer with conflicting emotions and more questions than answers. Indeed, watching the film before its Rotterdam premiere I went from laughing and rolling my eyes to getting angry at these “con artists” to feeling ashamed that I was being dismissive of mental illness to wondering if one woman was a psychologically disturbed fraudster, another just lonely and mentally ill, and on and on. In other words, these psychically distressed ladies defy any easy categorization -- much like Lane’s entire body of work.   Prior to the film’s June 28th NYC premiere at BAMcinemaFest, Filmmaker was fortunate enough to catch up with the very busy director who also has two shorts, Nellie Bly Makes the News and Normal Appearances (debuting in NYC as part of the Rooftop Films shorts program on July 14th), currently making the festival rounds. The Pain of Others will be released exclusively on Fandor July 1st.    Filmmaker: So what made you want to make a film about this obscure subject in the first place? Was it the online community of sufferers (all of whom are white, middle-aged women)? Their use of the YouTube medium? The idea of -- what seems to me at least -- an Internet-based, crowd-sourced disease?   Lane: I first came across the subject of Morgellons in a 2013 essay by Leslie Jamison called</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Marijuana Market Still Thrives in Los Angeles...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/california/articles/2018-07-05/illegal-marijuana-market-still-thrives-in-los-angeles?int=undefined-rec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE CENTER WATCHES DEPRESSION...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/refresh/AL022018_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/144424_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSTON FLOODS AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/houston-texas/article/Flash-flood-warnings-in-place-as-soggy-4th-of-13049229.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Unfortunately the weather situation did not go as predicted," said Susan Christian, the city's director of special events. "We've taken on a lot rain on the site, so much so that it's compromised the site. And while we were prepared to do one heck of a show unfortunately we will cancel all but the fireworks."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom's secret recording catches kindergarten teacher calling 5-year-old 'loser'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/education/article214204009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida mother suspected a kindergarten teacher at Banyan Elementary School of bullying her son and placed a recording device in his backpack. She heard the teacher call him a loser. The Miami-Dade school district is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother accused of selling children...</title>
      <link>http://www.kristv.com/story/38570236/mugshot-of-mother-accused-of-selling-children-released</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kristv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jail officials over at the Nueces County Jail have released the mugshot of a mother accused of selling her children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP meeting with FBI raises ethical questions...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/4/ap-meeting-with-fbi-raises-ethical-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Associated Press reporters asked the FBI and Justice Department for a meeting in April 2017, hoping to find out whether their reporting on President Trump’s former campaign chairman was on the right track.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK flags Declaration of Independence as hate speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/4/facebook-flags-declaration-independence-hate-speec/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the week of America’s Independence Day, the algorithms of Facebook decided that the Declaration of Independence was hate speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  FACEBOOK Marketplace is black market for knock-off designer goods...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6701037/facebook-marketplace-fake-counterfeit-replica-gucci-louboutin-cheap-football-shirts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK’s official Marketplace store has turned into a black market for counterfeit goods, The Sun can reveal. Rogue traders are using the eBay-style feature to flog knock-off items, includi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Host Declares 'NATIONAL EMERGENCY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/l-brent-bozell-iii/cnn-host-proclaims-national-emergency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can count on CNN "Reliable Sources" host Brian Stelter to stay true to the trash-Trump parade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-powered robot mimics ANY action after watching person do it just once...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-5920747/New-AI-powered-robot-mimic-action-watching-just-once.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at the University of California, Berkeley, developed a clawed machine that can learn several tasks – such as dropping a ball into a bowl or picking up a cup – by watching a person do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC spokesperson warns Dems will impeach Trump if they win House...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/395568-rnc-spokesperson-warns-dems-will-impeach-trump-if-they-win-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican National Committee spokeswoman Kayleigh McEnany on Thursday warned that Democrats in the House will move to impeach President Trump if they win back the lower chamber in the midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebratory gunfire wounds BUSCH GARDENS guest, damages car and apartment...</title>
      <link>http://www.tampabay.com/news/publicsafety/Police-Celebratory-gunfire-wounds-Busch-Gardens-guest-damages-car-and-apartment_169748565</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA — A guest at the Busch Gardens Tampa Bay amusement park was wounded by a stray bullet while watching the Fourth of July firework show Wednesday night.Tampa Police believe Scott Deel, 36, was st</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Cities Americans abandoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/economy/2018/07/05/cities-americans-abandoning-population-migration/35801453/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 50 cities where the most people are moving away from can primarily be found in the Northeast, Midwest, and West Coast, particularly in states like Illinois, Michigan, Ohio, and New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Companies Win Reprieve as EU Parliament Delays Copyright Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tech-companies-win-reprieve-as-eu-parliament-delays-copyright-law-1530787465 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU lawmakers rejected new copyright rules, instead opting for more debate, a victory for tech firms that are facing a broader European effort to rein them in on topics ranging from privacy to taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London mayor Khan approves baby Trump blimp to fly over city during visit...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/trump-angry-baby-blimp-gets-green-light-to-fly-over-london-during-presidents-visit-11426665</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The six-metre balloon depicting Mr Trump as a nappy-clad orange baby will take flight from Parliament Square Gardens on 13 July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BLOOD RAIN' pours down in freak weather event prompting 'biblical plague' panic...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/984303/blood-red-rain-Russia-freak-weather-viral-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLOOD-COLOURED rain poured down in a remote Siberian city, creating an eerie scene that witnesses compared to a biblical plague or the apocalypse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest performs mass exorcism on hundreds of people...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5920293/The-Exorcist-Priest-performs-mass-exorcism-hundreds-people-Ethiopian-ceremony.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 150 people had been queuing up at a church outside the Ethiopian capital Addis Ababa in order to meet a local healer whom they believe would be able to free them from 'demons'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA testing being done on separated children and parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/05/politics/dna-testing-migrant-family-separation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DNA testing is being conducted as part of the process to reunite children who were separated from their parents at the border, a federal official with knowledge of the reunifications told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTHQUAKE HITS ENGLAND: 3.0 MAG SHAKES HOMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/984289/earthquake-surrey-sussex-crawley-cranleigh-guildford-gatwick-airport-uk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN earthquake has hit England with residents across Surrey and Sussex feeling the 3.0 magnitude tremor. The epicentre has been placed in Cranleigh, a small village a few miles west of Crawley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEEN ATTACKED FOR WEARING MAGA HAT</title>
      <link>https://news4sanantonio.com/news/local/viral-video-shows-teen-attacked-for-wearing-make-american-great-again-hat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news4sanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating after a teen says he was verbally attacked and assaulted at a Whataburger for wearing a Make America Great Again hat. In the video, you can see a man throw a drink in 16-year-old Hunter Richard's face before leaving the restaurant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin soon worth nothing?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/04/why-bitcoin-may-be-soon-worth-nothing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I thought we’d finally get rid of bitcoin. But the fake “currency,” which I like to call bitcon, just won’t fade away. Bitcoin’s price rallied to over $6,600 yesterday, but it had been well under $…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poachers eaten by lions after breaking into game reserve to slaughter rhinos...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/gang-poachers-eaten-lions-after-12857347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A head and other body parts were found after the three illegal hunters were devoured by six starving predators</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to Roll Out Buses of Peacekeepers After Violence in Communities...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-city-to-roll-out-buses-of-peacekeepers-after-violence-in-communities-1530788400 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will spend $1.8 million this year to roll out “mobile trauma units,” or buses filled with counselors and peacekeepers, to crime scenes throughout the city in an effort to ease tensions in communities after acts of gun violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, IRAN TRADE WARNINGS</title>
      <link>https://www.rferl.org/a/iran-pentagon-trade-warnings-over-us-effort-block-iranian-oil-exports/29339873.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rferl.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and Iran have traded warnings over U.S. efforts to block Iran's oil exports, with Tehran suggesting that it could retaliate by blocking oil tankers from leaving the Persian Gulf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China rejects 'blackmail' on eve of US tariff hike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec5e533fd2f04331a0758718a245402e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China rejected "threats and blackmail" ahead of a threatened U.S. tariff hike, striking a defiant stance Thursday in a dispute companies worry could flare into a fu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanctioned Russian oligarch linked to Cohen has vast US ties...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e533f93afae4a4fa5c2f7fe80ad72ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Long before Viktor Vekselberg was tied to a scandal over the president and a porn star, the Russian oligarch had been positioning himself to extend his influence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Amazon tribe 'at risk of being decimated by measles outbreak'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/remote-amazon-tribe-apos-risk-053000278.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An isolated Amazon tribe on the Venezuela-Brazil border has been hit by a measles epidemic that could kill hundreds of indigenous people if emergency action is not taken, NGOs have warned. The Yanomami people, who live in communities on both sides of the border, have reported up to 100 cases of measles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Parliament to vote on controversial copyright law...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/eu-parliament-vote-controversial-copyright-law-doc-1765531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHC: Two tropical depressions likely in Atlantic by end of week...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-storm-atlantic-nhc/two-tropical-depressions-likely-in-atlantic-by-end-of-week-nhc-idUSKBN1JV0E9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two low pressure systems in the Atlantic ocean could form into tropical depressions by the end of the week, the U.S. National Hurricane Center (NHC) said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Taps More Prosecutors to Help With Growing Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/05/mueller-said-to-tap-more-career-prosecutors-as-trump-probe-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller is tapping additional Justice Department resources for help with new legal battles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Shutter Show That Cast White Singers as Black Slaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/protests-shutter-a-show-that-cast-white-singers-as-black-slaves/17675852/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTREAL — It was, the critics roared, an insulting and insensitive performance: White women playing black slaves picking cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Smart TVs in Millions of Homes Track More Than What's on Tonight...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/how-smart-tvs-in-millions-of-u-s-homes-track-more-than-what-s-on-tonight/17675939/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing concern over online data and user privacy has been focused on tech giants like Facebook and devices like smartphones. But people’s data is also increasingly being vacuumed right out of their living rooms via their televisions, sometimes without their knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The 21st Century has not been the American Century'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-21st-century-has-not-been-the-american-century-2018-07-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How did we descend from the country that cured polio, built the interstate highway system and put a man on the moon, asks Paul Brandus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard fighting to keep its secretive admissions process under wraps...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/harvard-university-is-fighting-to-keep-its-secretive-admissions-process-under-wraps-2018-06-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The school says releasing the information could put it at a competitive disadvantage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record highs leave world baking...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/heatwave-2018-think-it-s-hot-here-record-highs-leave-world-baking-nn0rd8cq9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperature records are being broken in a heatwave enveloping the northern hemisphere that has put Britain on course for its longest spell of hot weather for 42 years. The world’s highest sustained...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas border town becomes center of immigration fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Texas-border-town-becomes-center-of-immigration-13049850.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MCALLEN, Texas - Maria's Restaurant offers Pollo en Mole for $8.25 and patriotic red, white and blue peanut M&amp;Ms for a quarter in a gumball machine near the front door. The menu in this family restaurant, about seven miles from the U.S.-Mexico border, is a reflection of the blended community it has served for 41 years. But now this town built on immigration has become ground zero for the nation's nastiest political battle in the angry summer of 2018. "This is a border culture, so these people are not monsters to us," said Carolina Garza, 31, a third-generation Mexican-American whose family runs Maria's. She was talking about the masses of Central American immigrants flowing across the southern U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEFACEBOOK disagree on how to curb fake news for midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/03/facebook-and-apple-disagree-on-how-to-curb-fake-news-for-u-s-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple News launched a human-curated elections section, sparking a debate about tech companies and automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Guards threatens to block oil shipments in Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oil-iran-irgc-threat/irans-guards-threatens-to-block-oil-shipments-in-gulf-yjc-ews-website-idUSKBN1JU2MW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iranian Revolutionary Guards commander said on Wednesday that Tehran will block oil shipments through the Strait of Hormuz in the Gulf if the United States bans Iranian oil sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uganda leader says social media used for 'lying', defends tax for access...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/uganda-leader-says-social-media-used-lying-defends-191424087--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Elias Biryabarema KAMPALA (Reuters) - Uganda's President Yoweri Museveni has defended the country's new social media tax, saying Ugandans were using such platforms for "lying", and squandering the nation's hard currency on fees to foreign-owned telecoms firms. In May Uganda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump praises military for keeping USA 'safe, strong, proud'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e4040e9398ea401d83b54d68a2596516/Trump-praises-military-for-keeping-US-'safe,-strong,-proud'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Wednesday praised the U.S. military for keeping America "safe, strong, proud, mighty and free" and used the Independence Day holiday to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian missiles killed ISIS leader's son...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/iraqis-russian-missiles-killed-leaders-son-185515596.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian forces killed the son of Islamic State group leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi in a missile attack on a Syrian cave in which he was hiding, Iraqi intelligence said Wednesday. IS's propaganda outlet Amaq said Hudhayfah al-Badri was killed in an "operation against the Nussayriyyah and the Russians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.Z. court rejects Kim Dotcom US extradition appeal...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/n-z-court-rejects-kim-dotcom-us-extradition-234826993.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand's Court of Appeal ruled Kim Dotcom was eligible for extradition to the United States Thursday in a major setback for the Internet mogul who is accused of online piracy. Dotcom had asked the court to overturn two previous rulings that the Megaupload founder and his three co-accused be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Trolls Trump with Mysterious July 4th Message...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sacha-baron-cohen-trolls-trump-july-fourth-message-1125002 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial comedian teased a new project involving Trump after posting a video of the president criticizing Cohen for being a "third grade character" who needs to "learn about being funny."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Logs 16,000 Feces Complaints in Week...</title>
      <link>https://newswars.com/san-francisco-logs-over-16000-feces-complaints-in-one-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newswars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaultier lights up fashion week with provocative ode to smoking... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180704180704-jam8v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FASHION-PARIS/HAUTECOUTURE-GAULTIER (PIX, TV):Gaultier lights up fashion week with provocative ode to smoking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson faces casting backlash for playing trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2018/07/04/scarlett-johansson-faces-backlash-again-role-transgender-man/757746002/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a controversial decision, Scarlett Johansson has been cast in "Rub &amp; Tug," the true story of Dante "Tex" Gill, a transgender massage parlor owner. She faced a similar flap for last year's "Ghost in the Shell," which cast her as a Japanese manga character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test tube rhino embryos could bring extinct species back from dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/jul/04/first-test-tube-rhino-embryos-could-bring-extinct-species-back-from-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The northern white rhino is essentially extinct – just two females remain – but new research paves the way for its resurrection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY accidentally releases entire film instead of trailer...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/07/04/sony-pictures-make-huge-faux-pas-release-entire-film-instead-trailer-7683088/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it has already received bad reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns of worldwide financial crisis....</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/merkel-warns-of-worldwide-financial-crisis/article_2dff7b52-12a8-5a67-86b0-e4b9324607aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN –– German Chancellor Angela Merkel raised the specter of a new global financial crisis as she warned of the potential fallout from a trade war with the U.S., saying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestor Climbs Statue of Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/watch-live-protester-climbs-statue-of-liberty-liberty-island-evacuated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
