<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Italian parties strike deal for new govt in blow to Salvini...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/italian-parties-strike-deal-for-new-government-in-blow-to-salvini/ar-AAGsv10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market fears 'disaster scenario'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/28/bond-yields-still-heading-lower-as-market-fears-disaster-scenario.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bond yields are heading south, and there appears to be no stopping them for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mnuchin Endorses Longer-Term Bonds...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-yield-curve-steepens-as-mnuchin-endorses-longer-term-bonds-1.1308282</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-end of the U.S. yield curve steepened after Treasury Secretary Steve Mnuchin said the government is seriously considering a plan to issue debt well beyond the current 30-year maximum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov declares state of emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article234471052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland dog park divides rich and powerful...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Maryland-dog-park-divides-the-rich-and-powerful-14383917.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows there's a problem with Chubbs. Dirt is smeared across his face. His tongue is rolling out of his mouth. He's surrounded by signs that say "NO EXCESSIVE BARKING." But the 5-month-old golden retriever does not know how to read. At a dog park in one of Maryland's wealthiest suburbs, he spends this sunny August morning rolling on his back. He opens his mouth, and then, he does it. He woofs. Twice. "CHUBBS!" four humans around him yell, trying to stop him from doing what dogs do - just not in Chevy Chase Village this summer. Here in this community of the rich and powerful, where the average household income is $460,000, barking is the subject of a ferocious (fur-ocious?) debate - one that has divided the two-legged one-percenters for nearly a year. The drama began last fall when the village spent $134,000 to turn a muddy triangle of land into a park where pups could run off-leash in a fenced refuge. Chase tennis balls. Sniff one another's butts. But after about a month, signs decrying the barking of those dogs began appearing around the park. The village police started receiving almost daily calls about the noise, mostly from one particular neighbor whose house backs up to the park. By spring, the tension had escalated so much that the Chevy Chase Village Board of Managers called a public hearing. Then another in June. And another in July. At the center of it all is Elissa Leonard, chair of the village board and wife to Jerome Powell, chairman of the Federal Reserve. In recent months, her husband has been under attack from President Donald Trump, who appointed him but blames him for the tanking stock market. "My only question is, who is our bigger enemy, Jay Powell or Chairman Xi?" the president tweeted Friday. Leonard, meanwhile, is on the receiving end of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS bars Dems from visiting border facilities after 'rude', 'disruptive' behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dhs-bars-house-oversight-dems-from-visiting-cbp-facilities-at-border-after-rude-and-disruptive-behavior</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security has barred Democratic staffers from the House Oversight Committee from visiting Customs and Border Protection (CBP) facilities at the U.S.-Mexico border as part of a planned trip this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US airmen prep for fog of war...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/smr/a-modern-nato/2019/08/28/denied-hot-meals-and-indoor-toilets-us-airmen-prepare-for-the-fog-of-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force is embracing the suck as it considers how it might fight in a war against near-peer adversaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Largest mass child sacrifice' found in Peru...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-49495167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find 227 child victims of human sacrifice, believed to have been killed over 500 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHARK TANK' star Kevin O'Leary's boat involved in fatal crash...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/28/shark-tank-star-kevin-olearys-boat-involved-in-fatal-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I am fully cooperating with authorities,” the reality show judge said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense chief urges Tehran to hold talks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-defense-chief-urges-iran-hold-talks-us-205923005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Defense Secretary Mark Esper urged Iran Wednesday to enter discussions with the United States in order to ease tensions in the Gulf region. "We are not seeking conflict with Iran. "The president said once again he is willing to meet with Iran's leaders," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When You Don't Pay a Hospital Bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/08/medical-bill-debt-collection/596914/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Americans sink under medical expenses, debt collectors go to great—and sometimes strange—lengths to collect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atheists can be barred from giving invocation at Penn. statehouse, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/atheists-can-be-barred-giving-invocation-pennsylvania-statehouse-federal-court-n1047201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans United for Separation of Church and State said the ruling is indicative of a "troubling trend" that allows "special privileges to people because they believe in a god."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DALIO:  Central Banks Losing Ability to Reverse Downturns...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-28/dalio-says-central-banks-are-losing-ability-to-reverse-downturns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children of US troops born overseas will no longer get automatic American citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/military-children-born-abroad-citizenship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children born to U.S. service members and government employees overseas will no longer be automatically considered citizens of the United States, according to policy alert issued by U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services (USCIS) on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face of oldest direct human ancestor?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9816294/face-oldest-human-ancestor-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is our oldest direct ancestor to be finally given a face — 3.8million years on. It can be shown for the first time after a near complete skull of Australopithecus anamensis was found in Ethiop…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRENGTHENS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/281510.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARM WATERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/northern-bahamas-and-southeast-atlantic-coast-bracing-for-hurricane-force-winds-tropical-rainfall-from-dorian-on-labor-day-weekend/70009190</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH:  COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDFE6R4XoAIa_-5?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Game changing', 3.8 million year old skull...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/game-changing-skull-of-38-million-year-old-human-ancestor-discovered-11796214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery is said to challenge previous assumptions of a linear transition between two early human ancestor species..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: APPLE admits retaining Siri audio recordings...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2019/08/28/apple-apologizes-retaining-siri-audio-your-conversations/2140989001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple concedes that it hasn't "been fully living up to our high ideals" and will end the practice of retaining Siri audio recordings by default.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The conversation that may lead to a Netanyahu conviction...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/The-conversation-that-may-lead-to-a-Netanyahu-conviction-Analysis-600008</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu can note that Walla! still published many negative stories about him, or argue that Elovitch wanted to please Netanyahu for his own reasons unrelated to Bezeq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV personality, driver dies trying to break land speed record in jet car...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/tv-personality-professional-driver-jessi-combs-dead-at-39/5498617/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jessi Combs died in a crash trying to break a land speed record in a jet car, according to local authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI, IRS raid UAW president's home...</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/fbi-irs-raiding-uaw-presidents-home-in-canton-township</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A raid was conducted at a home in Canton Township Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROY COHN GETS TWO DOCS!</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/08/28/donald-trump-mentor-roy-cohn-gets-2-documentaries-this-fall-one-from-granddaughter-of-convicted-spies-he-sent-to-electric-chair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I told you last week that I’d seen the new documentary, “Where’s My Roy Cohn?” Matt Tyrnauer’s incendiary film, which debuted at Sundance, lays out the evil path taken…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video from 2005 raid on Epstein estate shows images of underage girls...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7400871/Resurfaced-video-shows-inside-Jeffrey-Epsteins-Palm-Beach-home-raided-2005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage shows police officers combing Epstein's now-infamous $16.4million mansion in Palm Beach in October 2005 during an investigation into claims that he hired underage girls to massage him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Host Forced to Walk Back 'Bombshell' Trump-Russia Report...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/nbc-news-cant-confirm-odonnells-bombshell-trump-russia-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence O' Donnell issued a clarification after making claims about President Donald Trump's ties to Russian oligarchs that had not been vetted by NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Having 'Mental Episode' Drives Mobility Scooter Wrong Way On Busy Freeway...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/08/27/police-woman-on-shopping-scooter-pulled-over-on-going-wrong-way-on-interstate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman driving a grocery store scooter the wrong way on a busy Kentucky freeway was pulled over by police officers Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP SHRINK: BIDEN 'NO SO PERFECT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/psychiatrist-who-called-trump-dangerous-warns-about-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The psychiatrist who authored a book calling President Trump’s mental health “dangerous” isn’t so sure about leading 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans feel dread and doubts about race...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2019/08/28/2020-biden-leads-democrats-voters-dread-election/2120726001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in the USA TODAY/Suffolk Poll said fundamental values are at stake in 2020. Four in ten have little confidence the election will be fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces Off With De Niro...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/joaquin-phoenixs-joker-gets-his-name-in-final-trailer-with-robert-de-niro-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Superhero origin story makes its world premiere at the Venice Film Festival this week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS AIRPORT TO TEST FACE SCANS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/08/tsa-launches-facial-recognition-pilot-las-vegas-airport/159479/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency will assess how the tech verifies travelers’ live facial images against pictures taken from travelers’ identity documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Trailer Drops...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/new-joker-trailer-unveiled-watch-video-1235081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film premieres at Venice Saturday ahead of its Oct. 4 release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital fitness trend NOT making us healthier...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/28/peloton-ipo-shows-company-serving-wealthy-not-making-us-healthy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peloton says in a filing ahead of its IPO that it's riding a consumer trend for fitness and wellness solutions. But it's not reaching those most in need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie hit self in face with punching bag...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/08/28/watch-speed-bag-hits-bernie-sanders-face-during-boxing-session/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socialist Senator Bernie Sanders was widely ridiculed on Tuesday for a video showing him taking a swing at a boxing speed bag, only to have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGERS star says woman kicker would get stampeded in NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/08/28/chargers-keenan-allen-says-carli-lloyd-would-get-stampeded-if-she-kicked-in-an-nfl-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Chargers wide receiver Keenan Allen believes that Carli Lloyd would get stampeded, if she ever became an NFL place kicker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger Shuttle 'Busjacked' From San Francisco Airport...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/08/27/shuttle-bus-stolen-from-san-francisco-international-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man stole a 16-passenger shuttle bus from a driver at San Francisco International Airport Tuesday afternoon, according to the president of the shuttle company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video from 2005 raid on Epstein estate shows images of underage girls...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/28/video-from-2005-raid-on-jeffrey-epsteins-estate-shows-images-of-underage-girls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly surfaced video from a 2005 police raid on Jeffrey Epstein’s sprawling Palm Beach estate offers a disturbing glimpse into the late pedophile’s tastes — including photographs of scantily …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  Man Attacked With Large Stone While Jogging In Brooklyn Park...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/28/man-attacked-with-stone-in-possible-anti-semitic-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abraham Gopin, a beloved father and grandfather, was going for a jog inside Lincoln Terrace Park around 7:30 a.m. Tuesday when he was attacked by a man yelling an anti-Semitic slur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES Launches Facial Recognition To Board Passengers At DFW... </title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/08/27/american-airlines-launches-facial-recognition-board-passengers-dfw-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines calls the facial recognition a more secure verification system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos indicate NKorea building sub capable of launching nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/photos-indicate-north-korea-may-be-building-submarine-capable-launching-n1047066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Korean submarine capable of launching nuclear missiles would bolster the threat posed by the regime and make it more difficult for U.S. forces to counter the danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 'JOKER' stakes are life and death -- comic book movies may never be same...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/movies/story/2019-08-27/joker-todd-phillips-joaquin-phoenix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 'Joker,' director Todd Phillips gives the comic book movie a dark new Scorsese-esque spin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man drops 113 pounds to enlist in Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/las-vegas-man-loses-weight-enlist-army</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young man in Las Vegas has lost over 100 pounds since the beginning of the year in order to join the U.S. Army – but he has gained so much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARM WATERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/all-eyes-on-dorian-as-tropical-storm-barrels-toward-puerto-rico/70009177</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senator From Georgia To Resign...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/459104-gop-sen-johnny-isakson-to-resign-at-end-of-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP Sen. Johnny Isakson (Ga.) announced Wednesday that he will step down from the Senate at the end of the year, citing health issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  Every major 2020 Dem beats Trump by at least 9 points...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/national/release-detail?ReleaseID=3638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Top Dems Beat Trump As Voters' Economic Outlook Dims Quinnipiac University Poll Finds; Dem Primary Stays Stable With Biden Holding The Lead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH:  COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDENbNBXoAIDVO-?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Films vying for Golden Lion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/films-vying-venices-golden-lion-122007186.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-one films are competing for the prestigious Golden Lion award at the Venice film festival, which kicks off Wednesday and runs until September 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag shows and hipster parties: Jerusalem underground nightlife...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190828140914-429qk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-JERUSALEM/NIGHTLIFE (PIX):Drag shows and hipster parties: Jerusalem has an underground nightlife</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 25 killed in 'horrendous' arson attack on bar in Mexico...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190828134610-z3xj2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-FIRE/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-At least 25 killed in 'horrendous' arson attack on bar in Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fasting boosts healthy weight loss; Mimics 'caveman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/08/27/fasting-every-day-boosts-healthy-weight-loss-mimics-hunter-gatherer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fasting every other day could be the secret to losing weight while staying healthy because it mimics humans&amp;rsquo; caveman diet, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: America...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7396975/Is-social-credit-coming-Report-claims-systems-like-Chinas-used-Silicon-Valley.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State  Department of Financial Services allows life insurance companies to base their rates on one's social media posts. Dangerous activities mean higher premiums.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Will Replace Iger -- And How?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/08/disney-stock-bob-iger-ceo-replacement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at the major front runners and the criteria Disney may be using to guide its search for a new CEO after Bob Iger steps down in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'JOKER' Trailer Set To Drop...</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/dc/2019/08/27/joker-movie-trailer-teaser-instagram/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As hard is it might be to believe, DC's most iconic villain is getting his own live-action feature [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans googling DOW -- could spell trouble...</title>
      <link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/americans-are-googling-dow-jones-and-that-could-spell-trouble-for-the-stock-market-2019-08-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Main Street is paying attention to stock market volatility — and that might not be a good sign, says one analyst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, Iran Prepare For Final War?</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/the-fighting-dramatically-escalates-as-both-sides-prepare-for-the-final-war-between-israel-and-iran</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are we about to see World War 3 erupt in the Middle East?  Over the past several days, Israel has attempted to prevent attacks by Iranian forces and their allies by striking targets in Syria, Gaza, Lebanon and Iraq.  As you will see below, political leaders in both Lebanon and Iraq are now accusing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC silent on vaping THC as injuries mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/08/28/critics-cdc-silent-vaping-thc-injuries-mount/2121523001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDC, the FDA and state health agencies say they are completing the painstaking work of tracing common factors that may have triggered the lung issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American spies recuited through LINKEDIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/united-states-canada/article/2162287/china-using-linkedin-recruit-american-spies-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The foreign ministry in Beijing described the accusation as ‘complete nonsense’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top destinations for out-of-state movers...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/fleeing-to-florida-top-3-destinations-for-out-of-state-movers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York saw the largest outflow of residents to Florida last year, as people look to lower tax obligations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great White Sharks Vanish From Cape Town -- No One Knows Why...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/great-white-sharks-abandon-cape-town-with-no-explanation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Great White Sharks Vanish From Cape Town, and No One Knows Why Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families In Fear Over 5G Towers In Neighborhood; 'Living In Microwave'...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/28/davis-researcher-no-health-hazard-5g-cell-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacramento Mayor Darrell Steinberg is trying to position the city as a demonstration hub for new technology, but with anything new comes questions about public safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
RICH STOP SPENDING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/28/the-rich-arent-spending-signaling-a-possible-recession-ahead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From real estate and retail stores to classic cars and art, the weakest segment of the American economy right now is the very top.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Savers Take Another Hit in Denmark as Negative Rates Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/rich-savers-take-another-hit-in-denmark-as-negative-rates-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Savers Take Another Hit in Denmark</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star-studded Venice opens under cloud of controversy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/star-studded-venice-opens-under-cloud-controversy-022112052.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rows about filmmakers Roman Polanski and Nate Parker threaten to take some of the sheen off a selection featuring a dazzling array of major stars including Brad Pitt, Johnny Depp, Kristen Stewart, Meryl Streep and Scarlett Johansson at the festival -- a launchpad for the Oscars. After the festival was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLLAR RISE BAD OMEN?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dollar-rising-possible-u-recession-204221745.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The dollar has been ascendant in 2019 and forecasts for a U.S. recession are growing louder. If the greenback’s strength keeps up and the economy does shrink, some experts are worried this combination will make it harder for the economy to claw back out.A Federal Reserve Bank of New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortgage Defaults Rise First Time Since Financial Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-08-27/mortgage-defaults-rise-first-time-financial-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-rich illegally buying cheetahs as pets; Leading to extinction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/28/africa/somaliland-cheetahs-gulf-intl/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of cheetahs are smuggled from the Horn of Africa to Gulf countries each year, where they're sold to the ultra-rich as pets. At the current rates of trafficking, the cheetah population in the region could soon be wiped out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-YEAR RATE UNDER 2%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/28/us-bonds-key-yield-curve-inverts-further-as-30-year-hits-record-low.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key part of the U.S. yield curve inverted even further Wednesday morning, exacerbating fears of an impending recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News anchor apologizes for saying black co-anchor looked like a gorilla...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/oklahoma-city-news-anchor-apologizes-saying-black-co-anchor-looked-n1046911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I want you all to know from the bottom of my heart, I apologize for what I said. I know it was wrong and I am so sorry," she said tearfully on air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump got under the media's thin skin... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/how-trump-got-under-the-medias-thin-skin/ar-AAGqKbn?li=AAEz3n1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Falls Short in Big Screen Debut of 'IRISHMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/netflix-forgoes-wide-release-martin-scorseses-irishman-1234382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streamer and theater owners have been unable to reach a compromise that would allow the star-studded drama to play on thousands of screens across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES calling travelers to apologize for travel disruptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/27/american-airlines-apologizes-for-summer-travel-disruptions-with-miles.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines is calling travelers affected by hundreds of flight disruptions this summer and is offering frequent flyer miles to retain customer loyalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman abandons six kids at WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/crime/article234442637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLBOARD:  Most-anticipated thing about music this fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/columns/pop/8527901/lana-del-rey-billboard-cover-story-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With her new album, 'Norman Fucking Rockwell,' the singer makes her most adventurous and candid music yet -- and leads Billboard’s list of the 38 most-anticipated things about music this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey having moment...</title>
      <link>https://uproxx.com/pop/lana-del-rey-norman-fucking-rockwell-singles/2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uproxx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As ’Norman F*cking Rockwell’ approaches its release, Lana Del Rey appears ready for the biggest moment of her career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Racism in USA institutional, 'white man's problem'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/88bd58010e75449eb5748499724df2f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Racism in America is an institutional "white man's problem visited on people of color," Vice President Joe Biden said Tuesday, arguing that the way to attack the issue is to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gJFgRuMvCGM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: http://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts do NOT r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson Stands Strong Amid Controversy..</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tucker-carlson-holds-firm-in-august-ratings-amid-blowback-to-white-supremacy-comments-second-behind-hannity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson is still continuing to dominate in the ratings in the midst of controversy over his recent comments about white supremacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-YEAR RATE UNDER 2%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/27/us-treasurys-investors-monitor-trade-developments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-term Treasury rates added to their August slide, exacerbating an inversion of the yield curve and adding credence to recession fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto ejects reporter from event -- after campaigning on free press...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/08/27/beto-orourke-ejects-breitbart-news-reporter-from-event-at-historically-black-college/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ironically, Beto O'Rourke told an MSNBC town hall last year that press freedom was necessary to "hold people like me accountable."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDBLA_tX4AYAruq?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Rises; MSNBC Remains At Trump-Era Low...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/fox-news-ratings-wins-cable-hannity-rachel-maddow-cnn-msnbc-politics-1202705396/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In science, an experiment usually must be conducted three times with the same result to be considered a success. By that measure and metaphor, the latest monthly cable ratings results make Fox News…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive inferno engulfs 115-year-old Philadelphia church...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/live-fire-erupts-at-church-in-parkside-section-of-philadelphia/5496379/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters have brought under control a blaze that engulfed a west Philadelphia church, causing portions of the building to collapse and sending one person to a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMAs Hit All-Time Ratings Low for 3rd Straight Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/vmas-hit-all-time-ratings-low-3rd-straight-year-1234937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The on-air numbers weren't down quite as sharply as in recent years, and MTV is touting big increases in social and online engagement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Bon Jovi album has presidential title...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/bon-jovi-2020-album-title-1203316056/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rock and Roll Hall of Famer Jon Bon Jovi revealed the title of his band’s new album on Tuesday night on board the Runaway to Paradise Mediterranean Cruise. Speaking to fans in the Norwegian P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man's Pickup Truck Stolen -- While He Robbed Store Across Street...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/08/27/watch-mans-pickup-truck-stolen-while-he-allegedly-robbed-store-across-street/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man's pickup truck was stolen while he was busy stealing items from a business across the street, police in Kennewick, Washington said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
