<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SECOND COMING OF THE ROBOT PET...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-second-coming-of-the-robot-pet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man's best friend isn't a dog—it's a dog-like robot, designed to perform tricks and tug at your heartstrings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Inevitability of Biden over'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/01/joe-biden-democrats-2020-1390739</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a new top tier — and a sense among the campaigns that the Democratic primary has broken wide open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot lectures global conference in first android live chat...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/788614/international-congress-love-sex-robots-brussels-said-levy-harmony-sexbot-real-doll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duty free owners wield quiet influence in right-wing Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/87e58e1f3779432fb353bb786794c6b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half contenders in danger of being cut from debates...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/11be2611cecc4be4bc7a59bebfae9829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Ukrainians sexiest people on planet...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/photo/201907011076112155-poll-sexy-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sexy, Sexier, the Sexiest: Top Nations 2019 Poll Finds to Be Hot. For more great photos, visit the Sputnik International website</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insect apocalypse: Bug watchers sound alarm...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-07-insect-apocalypse-german-bug-watchers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For almost 30 years they passed as quirky eccentrics, diligently setting up their insect traps in the Rhine countryside to collect tens of millions of bugs and creepy crawlers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake FACEBOOK Warlord Used to Spread Malware, Researchers Say...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fake-facebook-warlord-used-spread-081310761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In one of the largest malware campaigns to exploit Facebook Inc., a suspected Libyan hacker lured tens of thousands of people into exposing personal information and granting access to personal devices, Israeli cyber security company Check Point Software Technologies Ltd. said.A Facebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds issue 'domestic' terror warning for July 4...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/domestic-terrorists-target-july-holiday-events-federal-authorities/story?id=64038406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heading into the July 4 holiday, the FBI, Department of Homeland Security and National Counterterrorism Center urged law enforcement to look out for suspicious activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh blow to troubled Bond film as Grace Jones quits after arriving on set...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/9406675/james-bond-grace-jones-quits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE troubled James Bond film has suffered another blow after Grace Jones quit her much-hyped role moments after arriving on set. The diva, 70, who played iconic villain May Day in 1985’s A View To …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran exceeds enriched uranium limit under nuke pact...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Irans-exceeds-300-kg-limit-of-enriched-uranium-594251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the deal, Iran was prohibited from accumulating more than 300 kilograms of enriched uranium to the 3.67% level and from enriching uranium beyond that level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete raises $24.8 million in quarter!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/01/pete-buttigieg-second-quarter-fundraising.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's among three 2020 candidates for president, including former Vice President Joe Biden and California Sen. Kamala Harris, who has received the support of top financiers across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalism Job Cuts Haven't Been This Bad Since Recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/journalism-job-cuts-haven-t-been-this-bad-since-the-recession-1.1280981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests escalate as Hong Kong marks handover to China...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/19414449e01c441284d8ba7eab58ef3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freak hail storm strikes Guadalajara...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/freak-hail-storm-strikes-mexican-city-guadalajara-000911507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freak hail storm on Sunday struck Guadalajara, one of Mexico's most populous cities, shocking residents and trapping vehicles in a deluge of ice pellets up to two meters (yards) deep. "I've never seen such scenes in Guadalajara," said the state governor, Enrique Alfaro. Guadalajara</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Truce a Relief -- For Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/nasdaq-bulls-are-king-for-a-day-as-futures-rally-on-trade-truce-1.1280836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Old Town Road' rapper comes out... </title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/c/lil-nas-x-comes-out-gay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper said he thought he "made it obvious."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Tensions between trans women and gay men boil over at Stonewall anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tensions-between-trans-women-gay-192236862.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A black transgender woman wanted to be heard, but the white men wanted to celebrate. The scene at New York City's Stonewall Inn on Saturday, as reported by multiple witnesses on social media, showed how long-simmering tensions between transgender women of color and white gay men have boiled over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan says 'some people' paying 'serious money' to bury Khashoggi issue...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190630224122-bokdu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-KHASHOGGI/TURKEY (URGENT):Turkey's Erdogan says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Marchers protest New York's 'commercialized' Pride parade...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190630201737-703d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alternative Queer Liberation March in downtown Manhattan was designed to be a return to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-corporate dissidents...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190630173056-x1suy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAY-PRIDE/ (PIX, TV):World Pride parade preempted by anti-corporate dissidents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump fever takes threatening turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-anti-trump-fever-takes-threatening-turn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The toxicity of the resistance to President Trump has risen in recent days, with the nation's most respected newspapers publishing rationalizations for denying Trump supporters public accommodation and for doxxing career federal employees, while a journalist found himself under physical attack from…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT:  Broadway 'Liberace' Musical...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/06/29/broadway-liberace-musical-based-on-hbo-movie-behind-the-candelabra-finally-on-the-way-producers-want-bradley-cooper</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberace and his glittering pianos are finally on track for Broadway. For the last couple of years, movie producer David Permut–who just produced the all-star Mueller Report reading– ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka plays prominent role in Asia trip...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ivanka-Trump-plays-prominent-role-in-Asia-trip-14062628.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few Americans alive today have set foot inside North Korea, the isolated, nuclear-armed dictatorship sometimes called the Hermit Kingdom.  On Sunday, Ivanka Trump became one of them, capping a consequential three-day Asian trip in which the president's eldest daughter played a very public role that blended family ties with diplomatic work that is usually performed by diplomats.  She pronounced the short walk to the other side of one of the world's most fortified borders "surreal."  Previously, at the Group of 20 economic summit in Japan, Ivanka Trump was everywhere - at her father's side at times when other leaders' spouses were present (first lady Melania Trump skipped the trip), in meetings during which her presence puzzled other participants, and even giving an awkward video "readout" of Trump's meeting with Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi.  A video of Ivanka Trump talking with British Prime Minister Theresa May, French President Emmanuel Macron, Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and International Monetary Fund chief Christine Lagarde at the G-20 also went viral over the weekend. Lagarde's impatient side-eye as Ivanka Trump interjects in what appears to have been a back-and-forth between Macron and May suggested irritation at finding herself standing alongside the daughter of the U.S. president - rather than the president himself.  "As soon as you charge them with that economic aspect of it, a lot of people start listening who otherwise wouldn't listen," May can be heard saying, as Lagarde nods in agreement.  "And the same with the defense side of it, in terms of the whole business that's been, sort of, male-dominated," Ivanka Trump then says, as a startled-looking Lagarde turns toward her, then purses her lips.  The first daughter's prominence in Japan and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court term found Trump's justices forming unpredictable alliances...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-term-found-trump-s-justices-others-forming-unpredictable-n1024916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high court divided along the typical ideological lines only seven times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim has conceded nothing on nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-s-dmz-summit-shows-how-little-kim-has-conceded-on-nukes/ar-AADDHbG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 people dead after airplane crashes into hangar in Addison, Texas... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/addison/2019/06/30/crews-battle-blaze-addison-airport-after-plane-crashes-hangar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten people were reported to have died after a small plane crash set a hangar on fire Sunday morning at Addison Airport, authorities say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide rates at highest level since World War II...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mental-health-depression-suicide-epidemic-51ed2696-4153-49a9-8fba-e3f6958259c9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were 1.4 million suicide attempts in 2017 and 47,000 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift 'Sad and Grossed Out' by Scooter Braun's Acquisition of Her Catalog...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/taylor-swift-slams-scooter-brauns-acquisition-of-big-machine-as-my-worst-case-scenario-1203256624/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift has described herself as “sad and grossed out” by Scooter Braun’s acquisition of Big Machine Records, which holds the rights to her entire catalog up through 2017’s “Reputa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump helps bring shunned authoritarians back in from the cold...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-helps-bring-shunned-authoritarians-123000871.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It was a good few days to be an authoritarian leader.At the Group of 20 gathering in Japan, leaders who can find themselves shunned at such multilateral summits were the focus of U.S. President Donald Trump’s attention, humor and respect across Friday and Saturday.Turkey’s leader was a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8-months-pregnant woman stabbed to death in London; baby delivered at scene...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/pregnant-woman-fatally-stabbed-in-croydon-south-london-11751577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman was understood to be eight months pregnant and her baby was delivered at the scene and taken to hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History or just photo-op?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4823bd17c1c94869826d8bf2a2825896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First US leader to enter NKorean territory; 'Great friendship'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0697162d26414f5fb06649a1fcb1844e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen scalded BURGER KING worker with coffee after drive-thru dispute...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/florida/customer-scalds-burger-king-worker-830561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 30--Following a dispute in the drive-thru lane of a Burger King, a Florida teenager yesterday walked into the restaurant and threw a cup of scalding coffee on a fast food&amp;nbsp;worker who suffere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spies desperate for Merkel's medical records to find shaking fit cause...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9404979/worlds-spy-agencies-desperately-want-angela-merkels-medical-records-to-find-out-whats-really-causing-shaking-fits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL spy agencies are trying to uncover medical records of German leader Angela Merkel after recent shaking episodes, it’s reported. The 64-year-old has insisted she is well but world leaders are…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Schultz's cautionary tale -- but the populist center's surprising promise...</title>
      <link>https://www.roanoke.com/news/trending/is-centrism-doomed-the-cautionary-tale-of-howard-schultz-and/article_62455516-48db-5c6f-bed9-994e9830bbfa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.roanoke.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schultz personifies why the political middle gets a bad rap: It's seen as wishy-washy, corporate, elitist. But what if there's an alternative?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Taxes to Rise in 5 States Monday...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/personal-finance/states-gas-taxes-to-rise-july</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national average for fuel prices as of Friday was $2.70 per gallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON:  Moscow outgunning USA in race for global influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/30/pentagon-russia-influence-putin-trump-1535243</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A divided America is failing to counter Moscow's efforts to undermine democracy and cast doubt on U.S. alliances, says the report, which warns of a surge in “political warfare.“</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All Out Brawl'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7197451/White-House-Press-Sec-getting-scuffle-North-Koreans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Grisham, 42, was in an 'all out brawl' with North Koreans during the meeting between President Trump and Kim Jong Un.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80% of market now on autopilot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/28/80percent-of-the-stock-market-is-now-on-autopilot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;80% of investing on Wall Street is tied to passive or quantitative funds, JP Morgan estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 steps into history...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-am-254c6413-f5de-496a-a572-ae7349350bff.html?chunk=2#story2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegals hiring smugglers off CRAIGSLIST...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1655419/man-arrested-for-smuggling-immigrants-after-answering-craiglist-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver says he was suspicious when the pickup location turned out to be the side of a highway, but decided to forge ahead anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient palace emerges from drought-hit reservoir...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/iraq-palace-drought-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 3,400-year-old palace has emerged from a reservoir in the Kurdistan region of Iraq after water levels dropped because of drought. The discovery should yield more light on the mysterious Mittani Empire.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
