<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FEDS EYE ZUCK IN PRIVACY PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/04/19/federal-investigation-facebook-could-hold-mark-zuckerberg-accountable-privacy-sources-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal regulators investigating Facebook for mishandling its users’ personal information have set their sights on the company’s chief executive, Mark Zuckerberg, exploring his past statements on privacy and weighing whether to seek new, heightened oversight of his leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DC War: Subpoenas, payback...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mueller-report-sparks-new-dc-war-over-russia-probe-subpoenas-payback-and-more</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public release of Special Counsel Robert Mueller's report on Thursday marked the dramatic final note of a lengthy and contentious investigation, but also sparked a tinderbox of new calls for subpoenas, congressional testimony, resignations, and even impeachment proceedings -- all despite the probe's central finding that no evidence showed collusion between President Trump's team and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>855 SEPARATE REDACTIONS</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/donald-trump/mueller-redactions-738952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The version of the Mueller Report released this morning contains 855 separate redactions, the bulk of which appear in the section devoted to the Russian government’s actions to influence the 2016 el</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA Memers Unionizing: 'Exploited for too long'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/04/instagram-memers-are-unionizing/587308/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re hoping to solve some of the new economy’s problems with an old tactic: collective bargaining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castro luxurious Havana mansion for rent on AIRBNB...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6936503/Cuban-leaders-granddaughter-rents-mansion-Havana-650-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vilma Rodríguez, the granddaughter of Cuban leader Raul Castro, is renting a four-bedroom mansion with a Jacuzzi on Airbnb for $650 a night in Havana, Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' Considers Classifying Fetanyl as WMD...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/dhs-fentanyl-wmd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security is considering classifying the painkiller drug fentanyl as a weapon of mass destruction "when certain criteria are met," according to an internal memo obtained by Task &amp; Purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell says raising age to buy tobacco to 21 'top priority'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/18/mcconnell-tobacco-age-21-1280950</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate majority leader’s move comes one day after he announced his reelection campaign and shows the changing politics of tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Panic Over Political Bias Leaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/04/18/exclusive-google-leftists-panic-about-leaks-threaten-employment-of-colleagues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Left-wing employees at Google are threatening the employment of their colleagues amid a panic about frequent leaks revealing political bias in the company’s products and working atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfers rush to beat bobcat with clubs after pouncing on player...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/breaking-news/hc-br-sprague-bobcat-golf-course-injury-20190418-bzr2qobin5aavcp7owqm6muc6a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bobcat injured someone on a casino golf course Thursday morning, according to 911 center administrator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCARTHY: Mueller blithely reversed burden of proof...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/18/mueller-completely-dropped-the-ball-with-obstruction-punt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most remarkable thing about special counsel Robert Mueller’s 448-page report is how blithely the prosecutor reversed the burden of proof on the issue of obstruction. To be sure, President Trump…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First 'seasteaders' in hiding after Thai navy swoops in...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/the-first-seasteaders-in-rough-waters-after-thai-navy-swoops-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The couple, part of a movement aimed at creating communities in international waters, face the possibility of life in prison or death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves earn $10,000-per-night stealing used cooking grease...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/public-safety/you-can-make-10000-in-a-night-thieves-target-used-cooking-grease/2019/04/18/bab6d938-613f-11e9-9ff2-abc984dc9eec_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six incidents have been reported in Fairfax County in the past year, including one this month in Annandale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV used to cure 'bubble boy' disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-47969367</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All eight infants now have fully functioning immune systems after undergoing treatment, say experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Kraft Naked Spa Video Shopped to Media as Judge Halts...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/robert-kraft-naked-spa-video-shopped-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburban Colorado community changes 'Swastika Acres' name...</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/2019/04/16/cherry-hills-village-residents-change-name-of-swastika-acres-subdivision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHERRY HILLS VILLAGE, Colo. — A neighborhood in the Denver suburb of Cherry Hills Village will no longer be called Swastika Acres. The Cherry Hills Village City Council voted Tuesday to approve a name change, hoping to prevent future controversy. That vote was unanimous. The subdivision was named Swastika Acres decades before the symbol was adopted by the Nazis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eastwood to Direct Film About 1996 Atlanta Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/clint-eastwood-the-ballad-of-richard-jewell-movie-disney-fox-1202598528/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Clint Eastwood is circling to next direct The Ballad Of Richard Jewell, and has been in discussions with Disney/Fox drama based on the life of a security guard whose life was turned upsi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon confirms NK test launch, says not ballistic missile...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/332110cbca26491fa82bf6bd29b1b19f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Acting Defense Secretary Patrick Shanahan is confirming that North Korea conducted a test launch on Wednesday, but he declined to provide any details. He is the first U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Surcharge Among Taxes, Fees Added To Gas In California...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/04/18/mystery-surcharge-taxes-fees-gasoline-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A University of California, Berkeley professor is drawing attention to a gasoline “mystery surcharge" in the state - unexplained price increases in gasoline which have cost drivers $20 billion since 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Scare At GOOGLE HQ...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/04/17/san-mateo-county-resident-exposed-google-employees-measles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials in San Mateo and Santa Clara counties confirmed that a person diagnosed with measles recently visited Google's headquarters in Mountain View, exposing employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Text of Q&amp;A...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98f22511be924ced895ce5c0bfedfe37</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Robert Mueller's 448-page investigative report into allegations of Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election includes 23 unredacted pages of Mueller's written...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROADMAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/18/muellers-roadmap-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller said one reason he didn’t recommend bringing charges against President Trump is that it could have foreclosed Congress’ ability to impeach him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eco-warriors plot to shut down HEATHROW...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8891580/extinction-rebellion-protest-london-shut-heathrow-easter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXTINCTION Rebellion eco-warriors are plotting to shut down Heathrow Airport tomorrow as millions get ready for their Easter holidays. Activists – who have already caused chaos across the cap…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex bots -- featuring FEET with built-in privates...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/tech/4140041/sex-robot-pervs-can-now-buy-fake-silicone-feet-with-built-in-privates-to-simulate-foot-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RANDY sex-bot fans can now buy pairs of silicone feet to “simulate foot sex”. Even more bizarrely, some pairs of fake feet have built-in privates – and sell for up to £315 a pair. The s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal tickled by tiny tremors every 3 minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/state/california/article229424659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster than fighter jet: $2.5M electric hypercar debuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/18/the-2point5-million-pininfarina-battista-electric-hypercar-debuts-in-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company's new all-electric Battista hypercar produces a whopping 1,900 horsepower and reaches 60 miles per hour in under two seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD FREAKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/04/18/hollywood-mueller-report-meltdown-complete-whitewash-trump-is-guilty-as-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood joined Democrats and the establishment media in going into full meltdown mode Thursday following Attorney General William Barr releasing the full Mueller report to the public. Celebrities accused President Donald Trump of being "guilty" and called the report a cover-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER sold for $100 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/business/article-national-enquirer-reportedly-bought-by-ceo-of-hudson-news-for-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supermarket tabloid, along with two sister publications, will be purchased by James Cohen, the head of the travel retailer known for its airport newsstands, the Washington Post reported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires pledged money to rebuild. Then came backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Billionaires-raced-to-pledge-money-to-rebuild-13777806.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS - The eventual reconstruction of Notre Dame is now a foregone conclusion. Within hours of the fire that destroyed much of the cathedral on Monday, donors pledged more than $1 billionto restore the Parisian icon to its former glory.  Even before the smoke had cleared, Luxury goods magnate Francois-Henri Pinault announced his family would donate 100 million euros ($112 million) to the effort. Not to remain on the sideline, his rival Bernard Arnault - the chief executive of LVMH and the richest man in Europe - pledged twice that amount on Tuesday morning. The Bettencourt Meyers family, which controls L'Oreal, quickly matched that pledge. And Patrick Pouyanne, chief of excutive of French oil giant Total, offered another $112 million.  Officials are still assessing the extent of the damage, so the cost of Notre Dame's reconstruction remains unknown, but these and the many other donations coming in should pretty well cover it.  In the meantime, the cascade of cash that materialized overnight to save the cathedral has raised eyebrows in France, still in the throes of a crippling protest over rising social inequality and whose leader is regularly decried as the "president of the rich."  "Of course, I find it nice, this solidarity," said Ingrid Levavasseur, a leader of the yellow vest movement that has protested inequality in a series of often violent Saturday demonstrations since mid-November. The stream of donations essentially confirmed the movement's broader social critique, Levavasseur said.  "If they can give tens of millions to rebuild Notre-Dame, then they should stop telling us there is no money to help with the social emergency," Philippe Martinez, head of the CGT trade union, said on Wednesday.  The cash flow has also furrowed brows abroad, with critics emphasizing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bee-wildering! Hives in miraculous survival...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190418-bee-wildering-hives-notre-dame-miraculous-survival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bee-wildering! Hives of Notre-Dame in miraculous survival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Rejecting Rep. Omar Money...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/dan-mccready-ilhan-omar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan McCready (D., N.C.), the sole remaining Democratic candidate from the 2018 midterm cycle, has returned a $2,000 campaign donation from Rep. Ilhan Omar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COP: Short-circuit likely caused Notre Dame fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7e795958c894ef491201aa9ef835638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Paris police investigators think an electrical short-circuit most likely caused the fire at Notre Dame Cathedral, a police official said Thursday as France paid a daylong tribute to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Florida cities among fastest growing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/25fe6d1f5afd4024a8f3c1239bab63d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — When it came to population growth last year, cities in central Florida grew by stadiums. Metro Orlando grew by 60,000 residents last year, almost as large as the number...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishers hurry to cash in...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f7ce8b6ee244567a6a663db51007ca6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — With the Mueller Report finally out, at least in redacted form, publishers are hurrying to release book editions. Two Mueller Report books already are in the top 100 on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House lawyer refused order to fire Special Counsel...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-trump-russia-firing/white-house-counsel-refused-trumps-order-to-fire-mueller-report-idUSKCN1RU1YE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House counsel Don McGahn refused to carry out President Donald Trump'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Dylan rips fans for taking photos after nearly falling over at gig...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/music/bob-dylan-calls-fan-taking-photos-live-show-2478420</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage has emerged of Bob Dylan calling out fans for taking photos at a recent live show. See it below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA MELTDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/issues-events-groups/Mueller-Report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not 'conscious wrongdoing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/mueller-s-report-trump-sections-blacked-out-released-public-n990191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The document revealed the president launched an "f-bomb" when he found out a special counsel had been named to investigate him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana sewer project unearths trove of mastodon bones...</title>
      <link>http://www.tribtown.com/2019/04/16/gigantic-discovery-mastodon-remains-found-during-city-project/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tribtown.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes, you find something you're not even looking for. That was the case for workers with Atlas Excavating, who recently discovered the remains of a mastodon at a farm in Seymour. The workers were digging on property owned by Joe Schepman and his family on the city's east side, installing sewer lines as part of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/mueller-report-russia-investigation-findings/2019/04/18/b07f4310-56f9-11e9-814f-e2f46684196e_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of Post reporters is reading the redacted Mueller report, which was just made public. This page will update frequently with key findings as we go through the document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Live Analysis... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/18/us/politics/live-mueller-report-analysis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Times reporters are reading and analyzing the redacted Mueller report, released on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows man left to die in South Carolina prison yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/the-prison-system/video-shows-man-left-die-south-carolina-prison-yard-n995461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of South Carolina’s prisons, Bryan Stirling, concedes the system failed Allen Capers. "We should’ve done more to help," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Demon with fangs' arrested after woman found dead with 'bite marks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/demon-fangs-arrested-after-woman-14397965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrey Gorbatyuk is suspected of visiting Tatyana Podvashetskaya before she was found with stab wounds in her apartment in Ternopil, Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead' family dog digs out of his grave and returns to owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/family-dog-found-dead-digs-14396237  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dik, 18, was buried by his heartbroken owners who assumed he was dead - but he clawed himself out of his grave and returned home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Bottled water made by WHOLE FOODS and DR. PEPPER has unsafe amounts of arsenic...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90336849/report-bottled-water-made-by-whole-foods-and-dr-pepper-have-unsafe-amounts-of-arsenic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus, here’s the bottled water that’s safe to drink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER CHANNEL hit with 'malicious' software attack, knocked off air...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/439511-weather-channel-hit-with-malicious-software-attack-briefly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Weather Channel’s broadcast was briefly interrupted Thursday after what it said was a “malicious software attack on the network.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Mysteriously Bursts Into Flames -- Burns For 4 HOURS...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/04/17/monroeville-tesla-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tesla vehicle was on fire for hours Wednesday night in Monroeville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXELROD: 'Inviting Impeachment Probe'...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/axelrod-mueller-report-virtually-inviting-an-impeachment-probe-from-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico blindsides with $39M utility bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d9396a5f9b9d4b5fa6383fbdd68f37cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — A powerful New Mexico regulatory authority is requiring the state's largest utility to bill Facebook $39 million for a new transmission line construction. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER CALLED TO TESTIFY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a99d0b66de82494bb29ca16ec8443643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on special counsel Robert Mueller's report on Russia and President Donald Trump (all times local): 11:45 a.m. The Mueller report appears to be most heavily...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New APPLE lab uses robots to rip apart devices for recycling materials...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-environment/new-apple-lab-uses-robots-to-rip-apart-devices-for-recycling-materials-idUSKCN1RU1DW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc is notorious for keeping what happens in its laboratories a closely gu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER:  I COULD VOTE FOR BERNIE... IF!</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/04/18/coulter_i_could_vote_for_bernie_sanders_if_he_returned_to_original_immigration_position.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative columnist Ann Coulter said she could support Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-VT) for president if he returned to this old stance on immigration. In an interview with PBS 'Firing Line' host Margaret Hoover, Coulter said she doesn't care about "the rest of the socialist stuff" if Sanders went back to his original "pro-blue-collar position." MARGARET HOOVER, 'FIRING LINE' HOST: What do you think about Bernie Sanders? If Bernie Sanders is for getting rid of low-skilled workers to ensure higher wages for [Americans]. ANN COULTER: And protecting the border. If he went back to his original position, which is the pro-blue-collar position, I mean, it totally makes sense with him. If he went back to that position, I'd vote for him. I might work for him. I don't care about the rest of the socialist stuff, just can we do something for ordinary Americans?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READ, READ</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/read-text-full-mueller-report-n994551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The full Mueller report, with some redactions, was released on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail spending rebounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190418-us-retail-spending-rebounds-february-driven-autos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US retail spending rebounds in February, driven by autos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bans UK far-right groups...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190418-facebook-bans-uk-far-right-groups</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook bans UK far-right groups</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER EDITS</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/media/mueller-report-released-barr-releases-full-400-page-report-redactions-today-live-updates-2019-04-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barr held a press conference Thursday morning to discuss the report's release</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1800 Migrants Illegally Enter El Paso Sector in One Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/04/18/1800-migrants-illegally-enter-el-paso-sector-in-one-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Paso Sector Border Patrol agents apprehended more than 1,800 migrants who illegally crossed the border Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detailed scenes of Trump raging...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mueller-report-witness-expectations-white-house-9258dd00-56cd-412f-986d-00b0b13ff921.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They think former White House counsel Don McGahn will play a starring role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>448 PAGES</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mueller-report-released-trump-russia-collusion-obstruction-8bb646b5-69d6-4210-b17f-1e78758882c3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the public's first look at the long-awaited document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump legal team visited DOJ twice to review the report...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/barr-committed-greatest-degree-transparency-consistent-law/story?id=62466298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Bill Barr held a press conference on the day of the expected release of special counsel Bob Mueller's report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/attorney-general-plans-news-conference-to-discuss-mueller-report/2019/04/17/f5ca1cc6-6138-11e9-9ff2-abc984dc9eec_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr is planning to provide an overview of the report at a news conference and later give the document to lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No material redacted based on executive privilege...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/barr-no-material-in-mueller-report-was-redacted-based-on-executive-privilege</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr on Thursday said no redactions in special counsel Robert Mueller’s report on his Russia investigation were made based on claims of executive privilege by the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicious beast...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-mammal-idUSKCN1RU18A </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Ohio University integrative biologist Nancy Stevens peered into a drawer in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priests in Philippines crucify selves in penance ahead of Easter...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/773107/catholic-priests-crucify-themselves-philippines-pampanga-easter-jesus-christ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER EDITS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6936383/Attorney-General-Bill-Barr-reveals-redacted-Mueller-report.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Bill Barr has used a press conference to announce the findings of the Mueller report - to the fury of Democrats who say he is spinning it in favor of Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr considered Trump frustration with media when deciding on evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/18/mueller-report-recounts-10-episodes-involving-trump-and-questions-of-obstruction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Mueller's report on his Russia investigation recounts ten episodes involving President Donald Trump and questions of obstruction of justice, Attorney General William Barr said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President declares 'Game Over'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/439496-trump-declares-game-over-on-mueller-investigation-with-game-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump took a “Game of Thrones”-themed victory lap after Attorney General William Barr’s press conference on special counsel Robert Mueller’s report on his Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Of Teens Run Through Chicago, Fighting And Disobeying Police...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/04/17/hundreds-of-teens-run-through-downtown-chicago-fighting-and-disobeying-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police were dealing with hundreds of teens running through downtown Chicago Wednesday night, yelling, stopping traffic and running in the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Claims Tumble To Fresh 50 Year Lows...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-04-18/initial-jobless-claims-tumble-fresh-50-year-lows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers discover ancient giant 'lion' in Kenya...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190418-researchers-discover-ancient-giant-lion-kenya-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers discover ancient giant 'lion' in Kenya</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Population Dips First Time in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-citys-population-dips-for-first-time-in-over-a-decade-11555560060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s largest city is losing population for the first time in more than a decade, new federal estimates show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies, foes united in skepticism on redactions...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/US-allies-foes-may-have-different-takes-on-13777089.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - Like much of the United States, governments abroad will watch closely Thursday as special counsel Robert Mueller's report is released in a redacted version. U.S. allies and foes may have very different hopes for that report, which is also expected to shed more light on the extent to which Russia was able to disrupt the 2016 U.S. elections.  But even though their interests in the Mueller report may be different, they will be united on at least one aspect: skepticism of the redactions by Attorney General William Barr.  The attorney general has said he plans to restrict only lightly access to information that would violate privacy rights, affect ongoing inquiries, provide insights into sensitive intelligence details or include grand jury material. Key members of Congress are expected to have access to a more complete version of the report.  And yet, the one thing that is almost certain is that there will be a battle over the things that won't be included. Democrats are likely to argue that Barr may have deliberately left out crucial details that would cast President Donald Trump in a negative light. Republicans will side with Barr, arguing that redactions are standard practice and necessary to protect other investigations and the integrity of the process.  But watching from afar, many Europeans are likely to share the Democrats' concerns: Often, in the past, their own concerns over redactions have proved to be justified.  That is especially true for countries where memories of the abuse of such techniques are still vivid. In what was once East Germany, authorities regularly opened letters sent to or from democratic West Germany and redacted passages deemed a threat to socialism, until the fall of the Berlin Wall in 1989. What became known as the "postal war" has deeply ingrained an inherent skepticism of redactions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Still Losing People...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/news/chicago-still-losing-population</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR LIVE 9:30AM ET...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?459919-1/attorney-general-barr-holds-news-conference-muller-report-release</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild bee species critical to pollination on decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f768748b36c648e49c14b0366fdec7e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, N.H. (AP) — More than a dozen wild bee species critical to pollinizing everything from blueberries to apples in New England are on the decline, according to a new study. Researchers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a99d0b66de82494bb29ca16ec8443643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on special counsel Robert Mueller's report on Russia and President Donald Trump (all times local): 8:10 a.m. President Donald Trump is blasting the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kakapow! Rare world's fattest parrot has record breeding season...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kakapow-rare-worlds-fattest-parrot-record-breeding-season-065032899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's fattest parrot, the critically endangered kakapo, has enjoyed a record breaking breeding season, New Zealand scientists said Thursday, with climate change possibly aiding the species' unique mating spree. Less than 50 years after the flightless nocturnal bird was thought to have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Church Membership Plummets...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/248837/church-membership-down-sharply-past-two-decades.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The percentage of U.S. adults who belong to a church or other religious institution has fallen 20 percentage points within the past two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA, intel agencies have become bastions of liberals...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/u-s-intelligence-institutionally-politicized-toward-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CIA and other U.S. intelligence agencies have become bastions of political liberals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrants Propel Population Growth in 10% of U.S. Counties...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/immigrants-propel-population-growth-in-10-of-u-s-counties-11555560061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About one in 10 U.S. counties grew in the fiscal year that ended last June primarily because of immigration—a significant increase from 2011—showing how new arrivals are shaping the nation as the population ages and the birthrate slows, new census figures show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROVE: Bernie Could Win This Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/bernie-sanders-could-win-this-time-11555541440 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He showed on Fox that he knows how to soften socialism’s rough edges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK uploaded email contacts of 1.5 million users without consent...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/18/facebook-uploaded-email-contacts-of-15m-users-without-consent </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company says it has stopped using password verification feature that collected data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S NOT OVER: Pelosi, Schumer call on Mueller to testify...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/439450-pelosi-schumer-call-on-mueller-to-testify-after-barrs-regrettably</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top Democratic congressional leaders are calling on special counsel Robert Mueller to testify on Capitol Hill as soon as possible following what they describe as Attorney General William Barr's "partisan" handling of the release of t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Nazi camp guard, 92, charged as accessory to thousands of murders...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418101135-pj0x9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-NAZI/TRIAL (PIX):German Nazi camp guard, 92, charged as accessory to thousands of murders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online activists silencing us, scientists say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418094429-rl1l2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-SOCIAL MEDIA/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Online activists are silencing us, scientists say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-lapse shots of Notre-Dame spire may offer clues on blaze...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418092525-nnw8y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NOTREDAME/ (PIX, TV):Time-lapse shots of Notre-Dame spire may offer clues on blaze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release of long-awaited report on Russia watershed moment for Trump...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418044628-va37q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA (PIX, TV):Release of long-awaited Mueller report on Russia a watershed moment for Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hatred of journalists turning to violence, watchdog warns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hatred-journalists-turning-violence-watchdog-warns-040627489.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hatred of journalists whipped up by populist and authoritarian leaders is degenerating into violence across the world, media watchdog Reporters Without Borders (RSF) warned Thursday. Political leaders' hostility towards the media "has incited increasingly frequent acts of violence that have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Unveils Secret Data Centers for Classified Gov't Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/04/microsoft-unveils-two-secret-data-centers-built-classified-government-data/156376/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft is building data centers and expanding security capabilities to compete with Amazon to host sensitive government data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech-Funded 'Privacy' Think Tanks -- Fight Privacy Protections...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/04/16/consumer-privacy-laws-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silicon Valley-funded privacy think tanks’ positions on a federal online privacy bill mirror the tech industry’s lobbying priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACK THE KNIFE FALLS ON SWORD; RULES OUT 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ap-sources-ex-virginia-gov-mcauliffe-rule-2020-230656357--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Former Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe won't run for president in 2020, according to two people familiar with calls he made Wednesday to allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAUNTS WEST...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/2ff1e53cfc9d42a7821c7f4e6a740642/north-korea-test-fires-new-tactical-guided-weapon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Thursday that it had test-fired a new type of "tactical guided weapon," in what may be an attempt to register displeasure with a deadlock in nuclear talks with the United States without causing those coveted negotiations to collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA TEST FIRES NEW WEAPON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ff1e53cfc9d42a7821c7f4e6a740642</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Thursday that it had test-fired a new type of "tactical guided weapon," in what may be an attempt to register displeasure with a deadlock in nuclear...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
