<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CELINE DION DRAMA BRINGS FEST TO TEARS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/celine-dion-aline-cannes-premiere-titanic-valerie-lemercier-1235019031/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celine Dion did not make the trip to 74th Cannes Film Festival for the premiere of “Aline,” a French musical drama inspired by the life of the Quebecois superstar. But if she’d attended the premier…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Industry That Unmasks People At Scale...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epnmvz/industry-unmasks-at-scale-maid-to-pii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unique IDs linked to phones are supposed to be anonymous. But there’s an entire industry that links them to real people and their address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fighter jets intercept American spy plane again...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3237665/russian-fighter-jets-intercept-us-spy-plane-black-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US spy plane was dramatically intercepted by Russian fighter jets over the Black Sea on Tuesday as experts fear violent escalation amid rising tensions between the US and Russia.  The ground crew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In looted SAfrican mall, man lies dead as poor pick over scraps...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210714-in-a-looted-s-african-mall-a-man-lies-dead-as-the-poor-pick-over-scraps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a looted S. African mall, a man lies dead as the poor pick over scraps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARVILLE WARNS ON 'WOKENESS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jul/14/james-carville-warns-democratic-party-letting-woke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Democratic strategist James Carville said Tuesday that Democrats need to do a better job at not allowing the “noisy” left wing define the party if they want to continue winning elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Shep Smith Crash on CNBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/inside-shepard-smith-post-fox-085839959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos CNBCWhether it’s a poor time slot, behind-the-scenes squabbles, an outdated news format, a slower post-Trump news cycle, or just a once-popular anchor taking his frustrations out on staffers, CNBC insiders have a lot of reasons for why Shepard Smith’s show has failed to capture major ratings. But one thing many agree on is that it has not met the bosses’ expectations.In the nine months since he went on the air for NBCUniversal’s financial news netwo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT Predicted in '72 Society Will Collapse This Century. Research Shows on Schedule...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xw3x/new-research-vindicates-1972-mit-prediction-that-society-will-collapse-soon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 1972 MIT study predicted that rapid economic growth would lead to societal collapse in the mid 21st century. A new paper shows we're unfortunately right on schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of Dogs With Severe Behavior Problems Has Trainers Alarmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx5485/a-wave-of-dogs-with-severe-behavior-problems-has-trainers-seriously-alarmed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shunning of Weisselberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/07/donald-trump-allen-weisselberg-removed-from-subsidiaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen Weisselberg has been removed as an officer from dozens of Trump Organization subsidiaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Detained Live On-Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/dina-stars-cuba-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dina Stars, an independent journalist and YouTube star who has been covering the protests in Cuba, was rounded up by police during a TV hit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunglass Company at War With Far-Right Extremists...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sunglass-company-war-far-extremists-085656827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photo GettyWith an out-there look that wouldn’t look out of place in a 1980s wrestling ring, Pit Viper sunglasses have become a go-to choice for anyone looking to bring some attitude to the pregame. But Pit Viper has a problem: their reflective glasses are also a hit with far-right extremists.On the latest episode of The Daily Beast’s Fever Dreams podcast, hosts Asawin Suebsaeng and Will Sommer discuss Pit Viper’s attempts—so far unsuccessful—to distance t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAD OF RUSSIAN SPACE PROGRAM CRITICIZES 'BILLIONAIRE OLIGARCHS'...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/head-russian-space-program-criticizes-billionaire-oligarchs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jealous much?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation shows scale of big food dominance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/ng-interactive/2021/jul/14/food-monopoly-meals-profits-data-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigation shows scale of big food corporations’ market dominance and political power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for loneliest whale in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/jul/13/loneliest-whale-in-the-world-search</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When people learned he vocalized at a much higher pitch than other whales, they wondered: could other whales hear him? Was he plaintively calling, never hearing a reply? Was he lonely?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bush slams Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/14/bush-bidens-afghanistan-withdrawal-499598</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president’s criticism comes amid warnings from western officials that the Taliban could soon topple the U.S.-backed government in Kabul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns chaos if mix shots...</title>
      <link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/warns-chaos-people-freedom-choose-104847950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization (WHO) has warned there will be “chaos” if people start mixing different types of Covid-19 vaccine. The organisation’s chief scientist Soumya Swaminathan insists public health authorities must use the available data to decide how vaccines are administered, claiming individuals shouldn't take it upon themselves to mix and match jabs from different manufacturers, or decide when to have them. Some countries are planning to roll out a third vaccine, or a booster shot, to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA SURGE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/delta-variant-now-accounts-58-covid-19-cases/story?id=78834579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The so-called delta variant is estimated to account for about 58% of all COVID-19 cases in the United States, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Buck cast as deadly predator as overdose trial opens...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ed-buck-is-cast-as-deadly-predator-as-overdose-trial-opens/ar-AAM7WSA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Hollywood Democratic donor Ed Buck goes on federal trial over fatal "party and play" sexual encounters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 1.8 million turned down jobs due to unemployment benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/high-unemployment-insurance-people-reject-jobs-9e426791-65b6-453b-9803-81aa3d0ca7e7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. businesses have been wrestling with labor supply shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Iconic MERCEDES for modern era...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/an-iconic-mercedes-for-the-modern-era-e94277c7-9e84-4d69-aa42-ac228ddde168.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An iconic sports car is remade for the digital age</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The incredible shrinking dollar...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/13/inflation-surges-as-prices-see-biggest-jump-since-2008/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation continued to surge in June, with consumer prices accelerating at the fastest pace in almost 13 years as the economy emerges from the pandemic, the feds said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just another low-paying job' say overtaxed firefighters...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210714093414-wpkb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As climate change drives worsening U.S. wildfires, federal firefighters say they are underpaid - and some are leaving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney bid for freedom goes back to court...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210714084809-0rxwi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-BRITNEY SPEARS/ (PIX, TV):Beset by squabbles, Britney Spears' bid for freedom goes back to court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Dems dig in after exodus; Republicans threaten arrest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/texas-democrats-voting-bills-0e475d25bc7c0a8c4019e51619cd5244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas Democrats who hurriedly took off to Washington to block sweeping new election laws urged Congress on Tuesday to quickly pass legislation protecting voting rights, while Republican Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti seeks 5 fugitives as president killing probe deepens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-caribbean-coronavirus-pandemic-haiti-fugitives-24ed959aaf1018a7246c31f53680feac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — A former Haitian senator, a fired government official and an informant for the U.S. government are the latest suspects identified as part of a sweeping investigation into the killing of President Jovenel Moïse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic athletes to put on own medals at Tokyo ceremonies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/euro-2020-2020-tokyo-olympics-tokyo-coronavirus-pandemic-soccer-06686aa23eccd467616a150ffd556457</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Athletes at the Tokyo Olympics will put their medals around their own necks to protect against spreading the coronavirus. The “very significant change” to traditional medal ceremonies in the 339 events was revealed Wednesday by International Olympic Committee president Thomas Bach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Massive flight delays, cancellations prompt finger-pointing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/562879-massive-flight-delays-cancellations-prompt-finger-pointing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines are racking up an unprecedented number of delays and flight cancellations just months after Congress gave the industry $54 billion so that carriers could retain their employees and facilitate a seamless return to air travel as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden team scrambles to address Latin American crises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/562875-biden-foreign-policy-team-scrambles-latin-american-crises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s foreign policy is being upended by a series of cascading crises in the Western Hemisphere and posing significant challenges for a State Department that still doesn’t have its full regional team in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer Set to Propose Decriminalization of Pot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/14/in-a-milestone-schumer-will-propose-federal-decriminalization-of-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Senator Chuck Schumer of New York plans to propose legislation on Wednesday to decriminalize marijuana at the federal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Walking Can Build Up Brain...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/14/how-walking-can-build-up-the-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise can freshen and renovate the white matter in our brains, potentially improving our ability to think and remember as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China begins military flights from disputed South Sea bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jul/13/china-begins-military-flights-disputed-south-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s military recently deployed electronic warning and surveillance aircraft and helicopters on two disputed islands in the South China Sea in what analysts say is a sign the People’s Liberation Army has begun routine air operations from the bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syphilis cases rising around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/15581026/outbreak-syphilis-pandemic-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYPHILIS cases around the world have risen as countries open up again and romances are struck up once more. Currently Ireland is having an outbreak, with “urgent action” required to tac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge tosses Roy Moore defamation suit against Sacha Baron Cohen...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/13/roy-moore-lawsuit-baron-cohen-499505</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Alabama chief justice alleged the comedian defamed him in a trick interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border agent was supposed to guard checkpoint. He took $400 bribes to smuggle migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-border-patrol-agent-was-supposed-to-guard-a-us-mexico-checkpoint-he-took-24400-bribes-to-smuggle-migrants/ar-AAM8LJN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case highlights a problem that U.S. Customs and Border Protection has faced for years: corruption among its agents guarding the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI beefs up veggie burgers as market booms...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-07-ai-beefs-veggie-burgers-booms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a beef with beef? A burgeoning veggie burger industry is using artificial intelligence to propose alternatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian intelligence agents plotted brazen abduction of Brooklyn dissident journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/iranian-intelligence-agents-plotted-brazen-abduction-of-brooklyn-dissident-journalist-us-prosecutors-say/ar-AAM8vgp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several exiled Iranian dissidents have recently disappeared in mysterious circumstances, though an abduction on U.S. soil would have been especially brazen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations rising again as delta variant spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/13/hospitalizations-rising-again-as-delta-variant-spreads-among-the-unvaccinated-doctors-say-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases are rising in unvaccinated pockets of the U.S., deaths and hospitalizations may soon follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER PRICES RISE 5.4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/13/consumer-price-index-increases-5point4percent-in-june-vs-5percent-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consumer price index was expected to increase 5% year over year in June, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban Dissidents Emboldened Despite Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/13/theres-no-turning-back-cuban-dissidents-feel-emboldened-despite-crackdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guillermo Fariñas, a veteran Cuban dissident known for long stints in prison and frequent hunker strikes, said he couldn’t believe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORWEGIAN CRUISE LINE sues over DeSantis ban on vax passports...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/norwegian-cruise-lines-sues-state-florida-vaccine-passport/story?id=78827331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norwegian Cruise Lines is suing Florida after the state banned vaccine passports, saying it cannot safely resume sailings without ensuring people are vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUBAN PROTESTERS SHUT MIAMI FREEWAY</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/ron-desantis-anti-blm-protests-law-backfires-cuban-american-protests-1609456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protestors were gathered on the freeway to demonstrate unity toward the civil unrest that's currently taking place in Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US covid cases rising again, doubling in weeks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-us-cases-rising-03150d6404004711b80e9bd6ff0d410d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 curve in the U.S. is rising again after months of decline, with the number of new cases per day doubling over the past three weeks, driven by the fast-spreading delta variant, lagging vaccination rates and Fourth of July gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Lobbying Behemoth in Disarray...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/12/internet-association-powerhouse-recedes-499212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Internet Association once brokered deals on tech legislation. But its role has shrunk amid the industry's divides and changes under a new CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Ken Starr helped Jeffrey Epstein with 'scorched-earth' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jul/13/ken-starr-jeffrey-epstein-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Book by Miami Herald journalist details extraordinary efforts by special prosecutor who hounded Bill Clinton to aid sex trafficker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron James' Firm Selling for Up to $750 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.theinformation.com/articles/lebron-james-entertainment-firm-explores-sale-at-valuation-of-up-to-750-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theinformation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBA superstar LeBron James’ entertainment firm, SpringHill Company, is exploring a possible sale at a valuation that could reach $750 million, according to people familiar with the situation. Among the companies said to be considering an offer is Nike, the people said. The sale discussions ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archivist Sneezes on Priceless Document. Then What?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-archivist-sneezes-on-a-priceless-document-then-what/ar-AAM7knM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What, exactly, does history lose when an archive-worthy text is destroyed?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17-Million-Gallon Sewage Spill Into Ocean Prompts Closure Of LA Beaches...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/13/sewage-spill-beaches-closed-el-segundo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beaches from El Segundo to the southern end of Playa del Rey were closed to swimmers Monday due to a 17-million-gallon sewage spill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN abandons vaccine outreach to minors -- not just for Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/health/2021/07/13/tennessee-halts-all-vaccine-outreach-minors-not-just-covid-19/7928701002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennessee is halting COVID-19 vaccine outreach to minors amid pressure from Republican lawmakers. The state also fired its top vaccine official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom sending out stimulus checks near recall election...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-politics/article/California-stimulus-check-do-I-qualify-when-600-16311420.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Californians who qualify for the stimulus don’t need to do anything to receive the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen sues cannabis dispensary over 'BORAT' billboard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/sacha-baron-cohen-sues-massachusetts-cannabis-dispensary-over-borat-billboard-n1273852</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Mr. Baron Cohen never has used cannabis in his life. He never would participate in an advertising campaign for cannabis, for any amount of money,” the lawsuit says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA trial paused after attorney vomits in juror box...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9784395/Tesla-trial-pauses-attorney-plaintiffs-VOMITED-juror-box.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proceedings on Tuesday in Wilmington, Delaware were briefly interrupted when a lawyer vomited in the jury box, which is being used by court officers during the bench trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw sewage killing South China Sea coral reefs...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/week-asia/politics/article/3140992/raw-sewage-chinese-fishing-vessels-killing-south-china-sea-coral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discharged effluent can be seen from space, claims US firm Simularity, which has been monitoring more than 200 Chinese fishing vessels anchored near the Spratly Islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  ATLANTIC future uncertain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/media/atlantic-thrived-trump-pandemic-future-harder-rcna1398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic's challenges cast a shadow over what had been an otherwise sunny media story about a recent digital success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA testing for miscarriages, stillbirths, birth defects...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9784519/Moderna-launches-clinical-trial-testing-COVID-vaccine-safe-pregnant-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna will soon begin trials to find whether their vaccine is safe for pregnant women. Currently, the CDC does not have advice for pregnant women and the vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probe launched into strip club, gifts given to AMTRAK staff...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/13/probe-launched-into-strip-club-entertainment-gifts-to-amtrak-staff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A criminal investigation has been launched in connection to gifts accepted by two Amtrak employees from a construction contractor who had a $58 million contract with the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top TN Bureaucrat Says She Was Fired Over Shots for Teens...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/top-tennessee-vaccine-official-says-she-was-fired-over-shots-for-teens/ar-AAM73td</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE — Across the country, public health officials have left their jobs, strained by a pandemic unlike anything they had confronted before, then tested further as the coronavirus and vaccines became entangled in politics and disinformation. In Tennessee, the state’s top immunization official, Michelle Fiscus, said this week that she was forced from her job after writing a memo describing a 34-year-old legal doctrine that suggested that some...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver Stone reheats conspiracies at Cannes: 'Obama feared assassination'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210713-obama-feared-assassination-oliver-stone-reheats-conspiracies-at-cannes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Obama feared assassination': Oliver Stone reheats conspiracies at Cannes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most aggressive ransomware group suddenly offline...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/13/multiple-revil-ransomware-sites-are-down-on-the-darkweb-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dark web sites linked to the REvil ransomware gang were not operating Tuesday. The gang, aka Sodinokibi, took credit for the July 2 international attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the dawn of demisexuals tell us?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/commentisfree/2021/jul/13/what-does-the-dawn-of-demisexuals-tell-us-how-sex-drenched-society-has-become</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop culture has become more and more sexualised, as sex is sold to us willy-nilly. But young people are turning away from it in droves, writes the Guardian columnist Arwa Mahdawi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wellness Resorts Eye Long Covid Treatments as New Moneymaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/wellness-resorts-eye-long-covid-treatments-as-new-moneymaker/ar-AAM5Lfk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From colonic cleanses to brain modulation to nutrient-rich IV drips, spas are coming up with all sorts of (costly) ways to treat symptoms of long Covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POOP POLICE:  Tel Aviv dog owners must now register DNA with municipality...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/dog-owners-in-tel-aviv-must-now-register-their-dogs-dna-with-municipality-673693</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The municipality calculated that an estimated 500 kilos of dog feces are not picked up from the street every month, and hope that this new law will work to decrease the amount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,000-year-old 'Freedom to Zion' coins found in Binyamin...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/2000-year-old-freedom-to-zion-coins-found-in-binyamin-region-673677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coins, dated to around the Second Temple and Bar Kochba revolt periods, document the Jewish revolt against the Romans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excerpt from 'FINAL YEAR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/I-Alone-Can-Fix-It-book-excerpt-Inside-Trump-s-16311355.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOTE: This is an excerpt from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO edges out NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hbo-beats-back-netflix-to-lead-emmy-nominations-thanks-to-hbo-max</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pay cable network rolled up its count with streaming service to come out ahead by a single nod with 130</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU gets involved in Britney battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/britney-spears-aclu-conservatorship-amicus-brief</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ACLU on Tuesday filed an amicus brief in support of Britney Spears as the pop star seeks to choose her own attorney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snubs for Kidman, Corden, Myers, Fallon... MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/13/emmy-nominations-shock-snubs-for-nicole-kidman-and-the-undoing-genius-aretha</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Emmys will be held on September 19th on CBS, hosted by one of their stars, Cedric the Entertainer. The presenters for the Emmy noms were father and daughter Emmy winners Ron Cephas and Jasmine …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Hospital puts new kidney in wrong patient...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wrong-patient-gets-kidney-at-ohio-hospital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio hospital has acknowledged that a patient received a new kidney meant for someone else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMMYS:  Rodriguez First Trans Woman Nominated in Lead Acting...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2021/07/13/mj-rodriguez-emmy-nomination-pose-history-lead-actress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The category is… one for the record books. Pose star Mj Rodriguez received an Emmy nomination on Tuesday for Lead Actress in a Drama Series</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulder, CO Named Best Place to Live in USA...</title>
      <link>https://realestate.usnews.com/real-estate/articles/what-makes-boulder-the-best-place-to-live-in-the-us-in-2021-22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realestate.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado metro area's relative job stability and high marks for quality of life make it No. 1 for the second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://realestate.usnews.com/real-estate/articles/us-news-ranks-the-best-places-to-live-in-the-us-in-2021-2022 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realestate.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Best Places to Live rankings help consumers weigh key factors in deciding where they should live next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Man Burned With Unknown Liquid In Random Attack In Midtown Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/07/13/midtown-unprovoked-liquid-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video shows a 57-year-old man walking on the sidewalk, when a shirtless man runs up behind him and throws an unknown liquid on his back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC restaurant: $200 french fries!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/entertainment/the-scene/serendipity3-sets-guinness-world-record-for-worlds-most-expensive-french-fries/3152081/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are a foodie with quite a bit of change to spare, an iconic restaurant may have just the thing for you to celebrate #NationalFrenchFryDay. Serendipity3, the iconic Upper East Side restaurant, set a Guinness World Records title for making the “Most Expensive French Fries” — just in time to celebrate National French Fry Day Tuesday! Serendipity3’s Creative Director…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don unloads on 'Disgraced' Kavanaugh...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-kavanaugh-supreme-court-michael-wolff-fd429590-57ab-4a7f-a648-9a3fd50d25f3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There were so many others I could have appointed, and everyone wanted me to."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
