<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Chinese tennis star's sex allegation against former top leader prompts online blackout...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/china-peng-shuai-zhang-gaoli-metoo/2021/11/03/79c0f308-3c4f-11ec-bd6f-da376f47304e_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Censors have scrubbed mentions of the accusations by Peng Shuai against former vice premier Zhang Gaoli.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Marines force American troops into humiliating surrender just days into training exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10159949/Royal-Marines-commandos-force-troops-humiliating-surrender-training-exercise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American combatants asked for a 'reset' halfway through a five-day simulated war exercise against Royal Marines in southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diana Ross teases first music video in decade...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211103110006-2f0ak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSIC-DIANA ROSS/ (TV, PIX):Singer Diana Ross teases first music video in over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says it thwarts U.S. attempt to 'steal' oil in Sea of Oman...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/iranian-state-tv-says-iran-thwarts-us-attempt-steal-oil-sea-oman-2021-11-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards foiled an attempt by the United States to "steal" the Islamic Republic's oil in the Sea of Oman, Iranian state TV reported on Wednesday, saying the incident took place recently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to hear biggest gun rights case in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-hear-biggest-gun-rights-case-more-decade-n1282583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both sides hope the court will clarify how much protection the Second Amendment provides for carrying a gun outside the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Newman Will Tell Own Story, 14 Years After His Death...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/03/paul-newman-will-tell-his-own-story-14-years-after-his-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades ago, the actor and philanthropist Paul Newman, frustrated by all the unauthorized biographies and coverage of his life, recorded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta's Braves Win World Series...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/32522726/world-series-2021-atlanta-baby-braves-all-grown-now-mlb-champions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Baby Braves are all grown up! Here's how Atlanta's young core helped bring home the team's first championship since 1995.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bragg Elected Manhattan's First Black DA, Will Take Over Probe Into Trump...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/02/voters-to-elect-new-manhattan-da-will-be-just-the-4th-person-to-hold-the-office-in-80-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bragg, a civil rights lawyer and former federal prosecutor, defeated Republican Thomas Kenniff to join a growing wave of progressive, reform-minded prosecutors across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both parties win in special election for OH House seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2021-special-elections/ohio-house-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Governor Race CLOSER than expecteed... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2021-elections/new-jersey-governor-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER STOCK DOWN FOR YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TWTR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get Twitter Inc (TWTR:NYSE) real-time stock quotes, news, price and financial information from CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Middle School Teacher's Wild Political Rant Recorded By Student; Goes Off On  Biden, Sex, Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/01/exclusive-middle-school-teacher-draws-criticism-for-comments-on-hunter-biden-presidential-election-and-vaccines-in-classroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident occurred two weeks ago and was recorded by an eighth grader in the teacher's classroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Average Child Now Spends 8 Hours Day Looking At Screens!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/childrens-screen-time-doubled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results show adolescents are, on average, looking at screens for recreation for 7.7 hours a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Boosts Quarterly Borrowing Estimate to $1 Trillion...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-treasury-boosts-quarterly-borrowing-190000895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. Treasury increased its estimate of federal borrowing needs for the three months through December after it ran down its stockpile of cash more than it previously anticipated.Most Read from BloombergInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’Can a New Mayor Fix Seattle’s Downtown?In Minneapolis Election, the Future of Policing I</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM DOWN IN VA</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-day-2021-mcauliffe-youngkin-biden-trump-a84bf1d7f2113c77197bca103fd0e81b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Polls were closing Tuesday night in the nation’s most closely watched off-year election as Virginia voters chose between Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin in a campaign that became partly a referendum on President Joe Biden’s first year in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2021-elections/virginia-governor-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayoral candidate caught illegally parking, driving on sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nyc-mayoral-candidate-eric-adams-caught-illegally-parking-driving-on-a-sidewalk-and-actually-entering-his-brooklyn-apartment-in-wild-stakeout-by-new-york-magazine-reporters/ar-AAQfnaz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reporter saw Adams "climb into the car from the passenger side, shimmy into the driver's seat, then drive the car up onto the sidewalk."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jellyfish Keep Attacking Nuke Power Plants...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epx4mj/jellyfish-keep-attacking-nuclear-power-plants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jellyfish are continuing to clog the cooling pipes of nuclear power plants around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Maskless Voters Turned Away...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2021/11/02/virginia-poll-workers-requiring-masks-to-vote-in-violation-of-election-rules-rep-n2598436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE:Following reporting from Townhall and others that Virginia voters were being required to wear a mask in order to cast a ballot on Tuesday, Virginia Department of Elections Commissioner Chris</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX defends shot, rebukes reporter's 'false claims'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/579696-newsmax-defends-vaccines-in-rebuke-of-its-own-reporters-false-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative news network Newsmax issued a pair of statements Tuesday distancing itself from "false claims" about coronavirus vaccines made by one of its correspondents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Radio 'Money Doctor' Sentenced For Bilking Listeners In Ponzi Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/11/01/william-neil-doc-gallagher-sentenced-life-terms-ripping-off-texans-ponzi-scheme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2020, he pleaded guilty to similar charges in Dallas County and was sentenced to 25 years in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON Followers Gather in Dallas for Arrival of JFK Jr, Who Died in '99...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/weird/qanon-followers-gather-in-dallas-for-the-arrival-of-jfk-jr-who-died-in-1999/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember QAnon? Well, apparently there are still people who believe these conspiracies, one of which involves... John F. Kennedy Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers release Israeli LGBTQ dating site details...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211102-hackers-release-israeli-lgbtq-dating-site-details</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's justice ministry said Tuesday Google had blocked sites of a hacking group that leaked user details of an Israeli LGBTQ dating site, an attack some security experts blamed on Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Not Worried About Armed Conflict With China...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211102193046-snxhy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-UN/USA-CHINA (URGENT):Biden says he is not worried about armed conflict occurring with China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Monkey Jizz' Crypto Turns Out to Be Scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7nw4k/unbelievable-monkey-jizz-cryptocurrency-turns-out-to-be-a-scam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team behind Monkey Jizz was able to make off with nearly $300,000 worth of Binance Coin on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man in Halloween costume randomly attacks pedestrian with ax in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/02/masked-man-randomly-attacks-pedestrian-with-ax-in-nyc-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 51-year-old victim was on Broadway near West 61st Street just after 10 p.m. Monday when the suspect threatened to kill him and struck his arm with the ax without provocation, cops said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage: 'Stupidest Thing I've Ever Heard'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-11-02/how-the-military-is-handling-troops-who-refuse-coronavirus-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday marked the military’s first deadline for all Air Force and Space Force troops to receive the coronavirus vaccine. Following months of patience, the punishments now begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worship and elderly visits on ballots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-texas-voting-rights-constitutions-5c839f590064ffc1a530d83992e464b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pandemic policies were being put to the test Tuesday in several states where ballot measures sought to rebuke or affirm actions taken by officials trying to fight COVID-19. The virus-related measures were among two dozen ballot proposals in six states that also include new constitutional rights for residents to grow their own food or enjoy clean air and water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL STAR INVOLVED IN FATAL CAR ACCIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/11/02/las-vegas-raiders-henry-ruggs-involved-in-serious-car-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raiders wide receiver Henry Ruggs III was involved in a serious car accident in Las Vegas early Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighter jet pilots at greater cancer risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/11/02/fighter-jet-pilots-at-greater-risk-of-certain-cancers-study-concludes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers recommend that fighter aviators who served during the 35-year span in question talk with their doctor or flight surgeon about the report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College costs up 169%. Pay up only 19%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/02/the-gap-in-college-costs-and-earnings-for-young-workers-since-1980.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is far better to be born rich and white than smart and poor in America," reads a recent report from Georgetown University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK, Citing Societal Concerns, to Shut Facial Recognition System...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/02/facebook-will-shut-down-program-that-automatically-recognizes-people-in-photos-and-videos-delete-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meta, the company formerly known as Facebook, on Tuesday announced that it will be putting an end to its face recognition system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds file antitrust suit to stop major book publisher merger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-business-united-states-publishing-book-publishing-6cc11dea867b63b1edad1cc2c9a353b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is suing to block a $2.2 billion book publishing deal  that would have reshaped the industry, saying consolidation would hurt authors and, ultimately, readers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-DAY IN VA</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10156741/Virginia-voters-head-polls-GOPer-Glenn-Youngkin-Dem-Terry-McAuliffe-neck-neck.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Monday's polling average, Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin had a .9% gap, with the GOP candidate pulling ahead in the days leading up to the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW STREAMING:  'JUDY JUSTICE' Debuts With Significant Changes...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/01/judge-judy-sheindlin-judy-justice-streaming-prime-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a decade and a half, "Judge Judy" has been 4 p.m. appointment television here on CBS2. While she remains a staple before our broadcast, she is now venturing into streaming entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Schools grapple with growing shortage of teachers and substitutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-e2-80-98serious-problem-e2-80-99-schools-grapple-with-growing-shortage-of-teachers-and-substitutes/ar-AAQbxBW?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Florida’s schools are suffering under a pandemic double-whammy: Not enough teachers, and not enough substitutes to fill in for them. For substitutes, the stressful working conditions aren’t worth $15 an hour when they can make more at places like Walmart or Starbucks and also secure health care. Burnt-out teachers say the passion that keeps them coming back year after year is no longer ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECONSTRUCT:  The day Alec Baldwin shot Halyna Hutchins and Joel Souza...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/the-day-alec-baldwin-shot-halyna-hutchins-and-joel-souza/ar-AAQ9wif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interviews with multiple members of the "Rust" crew paint an hour- by-hour picture of a cascade of bad decisions that created a chaotic set on which a led bullet was put into a prop gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims 'Israel literally owned Congress'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jta.org/2021/11/01/politics/trump-until-recently-israel-literally-owned-congress-and-that-was-a-good-thing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jta.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump uses a trope that has gotten other politicians into trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says TESLA has not signed contract with HERTZ. HERTZ says deliveries already started...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/02/hertz-says-teslas-already-started-delivering-cars-despite-musk-tweet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hertz declined to discuss details of the agreement but said the company remains "on plan" with its announcement to offer 100,000 Teslas by the end of 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden has resettled fewest refugees in history of program...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-has-resettled-the-fewest-refugees-in-the-history-of-the-us-program-what-could-change-that/ar-AAQdYsL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over time, refugees bring communities a net financial gain, research finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court looks to medieval England in gun rights case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/supreme-court-looks-to-medieval-england-in-gun-rights-case/ar-AAQdZyY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court's originalists look to history to determine the meaning of the 2nd Amendment and the right to 'keep and bear arms.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension Grows in East Ukraine With Report of Russia Army Buildup...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/tension-grows-in-east-ukraine-with-report-of-russia-army-buildup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tension Grows in East Ukraine With Report of Russia Army Buildup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools grapple with growing shortage of teachers...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/schools-grapple-growing-shortage-teachers-100000410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — South Florida’s schools are suffering under a pandemic double-whammy: Not enough teachers, and not enough substitutes to fill in for them. For substitutes, the stressful working conditions aren’t worth $15 an hour when they can make more at places like Walmart or Starbucks and also secure health care. Burnt-out teachers say the passion that keeps them coming back year ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERs swamped with seriously ill patients, although many don't have virus...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/hospital-emergency-rooms-swamped-seriously-ill-non-covid-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Certain patients who couldn’t get in to see a doctor earlier in the pandemic, or were avoiding the covid risks inside hospitals, have become too sick to stay away. Many ERs now struggle to co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring Wheat Prices Raising Bread Costs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/soaring-wheat-prices-raising-bread-124125570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wheat prices are surging from the U.S. to Russia, hitting a record in Europe and raising bread costs all over the world. And there may not be much relief soon.Most Read from BloombergSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’The Best New Restaurants in Washington, Chosen by Top ChefsBallot Initiatives to Watch, From Policing to the En</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile Construction Progress...</title>
      <link>https://fas.org/blogs/security/2021/11/a-closer-look-at-chinas-missile-silo-construction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fas.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the discovery during the summer of what appears to be at least three vast missile silo fields under construction near Yumen, Hami, and Ordos in north-central China, new commercial satellite images show significant progress at the three sites as well as at the People’s Liberation Army Rocket Fo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Having Kids Make Happy?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/11/does-having-kids-make-you-happy/620576/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research has found that having children is terrible for quality of life—but the truth about what parenthood means for happiness is a lot more complicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX 'Jetpack Man' Just Balloon?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/lax-jet-pack-man-latest-new-video-may-finally-solve-viral-mystery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New videos and photos released by LAPD may have finally revealed the true story behind the LAX “Jet Pack Man.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia official: Call to 'find' votes was threat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-arts-and-entertainment-elections-georgia-2b27f4c92919556bf6548117648693b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Donald Trump was threatening Georgia Secretary of State Brad Raffensperger when he asked him to help “find” enough votes to overturn his loss in Georgia to Democratic President Joe Biden, Raffensperger writes in a new book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping Naked Doubles Chances For Good Night's Rest?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sleeping-naked-good-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who prefer a warm room also reported better sleep than those who like sleeping in a cold room, survey results show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino to offer seven uncut scenes from 'PULP FICTION' as NFTs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/02/quentin-tarantino-to-offer-seven-uncut-scenes-from-pulp-fiction-as-nfts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The collectibles also include original handwritten scripts from the film and exclusive audio commentary from Tarantino himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster-spreading Delta variant spotted in 8 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-delta-plus-variant-ay-4-2-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New data from the U.K. suggests vaccines remain effective against the coronavirus variant sometimes called "Delta plus."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laughing or crying, Biden wears heart on sleeve...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/laughing-crying-biden-wears-heart-104258287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He laughs, he cries, he says sorry. For the most powerful man in the world, President Joe Biden sure shows his soft side a lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Pearl Harbor Coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/chinas-satellite-crusher-space-pearl-harbor-coming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race may hinge on debates about schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Virginia-s-governor-s-race-may-hinge-on-debates-16584416.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Republican business executive Glenn Youngkin prevails over former Democratic governor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman convinced husband he had Alzheimer's. Police say she stole $600,000 from him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-woman-convinced-her-husband-that-he-had-alzheimer-e2-80-99s-police-say-she-stole-24600000-from-him-over-time/ar-AAQdEJv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To cover her tracks, she convinced the now-73-year-old man he had Alzheimer’s, according to police reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Hawley says attacks on manhood driving men to porn, video games...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Sen-Josh-Hawley-says-liberals-attacks-on-16584505.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missouri Republican Sen. Josh Hawley on Sunday night told fellow conservatives they must...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will broken supply chains stop Santa?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/579513-will-broken-supply-chains-stop-santa-claus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’re speaking not just of stocking stuffers — but the success of U.S. technical industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulators Sound Alarm on Stablecoins...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/02/regulators-sound-the-alarm-on-stablecoins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seeking stability Financial regulators have urged lawmakers to act fast on legislation to address the rising risk of stablecoins. This</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YAHOO pulls out of China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/yahoo-inc-leaving-china-f3b589754224bc663d5e83ec385eb49a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Yahoo Inc. said Tuesday it has pulled out of China, citing an “increasingly challenging business and legal environment.” Chinese authorities maintain a firm grip on internet censorship in the country and require companies operating in China to censor content and keywords deemed politically sensitive or inappropriate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govs and more: What to watch in elections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-day-2021-what-to-watch-230b722f8fdf1f229ae043d1c1475a73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be an odd-numbered year but Tuesday's elections aren't sleepy, local contests. Voters in Virginia are weighing in on a governor's race that could rattle President Joe Biden and Democrats in Washington .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis voters weigh fate of police...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/death-of-george-floyd-police-minnesota-minneapolis-police-reform-cc108d1707d9cb8cbaa6135bb60e7fbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Voters in Minneapolis were deciding Tuesday whether to replace the city’s police department with a new Department of Public Safety, more than a year after George Floyd’s death under the knee of a white police officer launched a movement to defund or abolish police across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mainers to decide on 'right to food' amendment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-maine-constitutions-referendums-605019e60df5b3e32bc70c86dcf957b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Maine voters will decide Tuesday whether to pass the nation’s first “right to food” constitutional amendment. A statewide referendum asked voters if they favored an amendment to the Maine Constitution “to declare that all individuals have a natural, inherent and unalienable right to grow, raise, harvest, produce and consume the food of their own choosing for their own nourishment, sustenance, bodily health and well-being.” It's an experiment not tried before by any state.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
