<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Won't bow...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/taiwan-won-t-bow-to-china-and-will-fortify-its-defenses-says-president-as-military-tensions-mount/ar-AAPkRmT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Taiwan's national day, President Taiwan Tsai Ing-wen stated that the country will reject all efforts from China to 're-unify' the two states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandora Papers reveal new details about Miami businessman who out-trumped Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/pandora-papers-reveal-new-details-about-how-a-miami-businessman-out-trumped-trump/ar-AAPhXFP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orestes Fintiklis thrust himself into the public eye with an audacious acquisition of a Panamanian luxury hotel that sported the surname of the 45th U.S. president, Donald J. Trump. The Cypriot, who resides in Miami, wowed local media in Panama and Florida less than a year later in March 2018 when workers crowbarred Trump’s name from hotel signs, one letter at a time. The Trump Organization’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington, Beijing Enter Dangerous Territory...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/09/starting-a-fire-u-s-and-china-enter-dangerous-territory-over-taiwan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 25 Chinese fighter jets, bombers and other warplanes flew in menacing formations off the southern end of Taiwan, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST flight woes continue; 1,000 Sunday cancellations, and counting...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/airline-news/2021/10/10/southwest-airlines-flight-issues-cancellations/6080308001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest has canceled 28% of its Sunday flights after canceling 24% on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop shot dead first day on job...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3828008/cop-shot-dead-first-day-job-manhunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GEORGIA cop was shot dead during his first day on the job sparking a manhunt to find his killer. Dylan Harrison, 26, was killed Saturday, leaving behind a wife and a six-month-old baby. Georgia B…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  100-year-old Nazis accused of concentration camp horrors...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3827929/nazi-pensioners-ww2-concentration-camp-murder-prisoners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE accused look frail and harmless – like they couldn’t hurt a fly.  But they are accused of aiding and abetting some of the worst war crimes in recent history as part of the Nazi Third…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With NASA partnership, Orlando begins planning for air taxis, flying cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/with-nasa-partnership-orlando-begins-planning-for-air-taxis-flying-cars/ar-AAPluJo?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Orlando is preparing for when flying cars are an option for those who want to soar over congested highways or between nearby cities. And they may arrive far sooner than 2062, as "The Jetsons" predicted. The city has signed onto a partnership with NASA to develop strategies for welcoming electric oversized drones, which take off vertically from landing pads called vertiports. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandora Papers reveal new details about how a Miami businessman out-trumped Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/pandora-papers-reveal-new-details-about-how-a-miami-businessman-out-trumped-trump/ar-AAPhXFP?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orestes Fintiklis thrust himself into the public eye with an audacious acquisition of a Panamanian luxury hotel that sported the surname of the 45th U.S. president, Donald J. Trump. The Cypriot, who resides in Miami, wowed local media in Panama and Florida less than a year later in March 2018 when workers crowbarred Trump’s name from hotel signs, one letter at a time. The Trump Organization’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK willing to open algorithms to regulators...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-willing-open-algorithms-regulators-144628180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook’s chief spokesman said the company is willing to subject itself to greater oversight to ensure its algorithms are performing as intended and aren’t harming users.Most Read from BloombergNYC's Waldorf Gets Plush Renovation, Becomes Icon of China's OverreachBefore Interstates, America Got Around on InterurbansHow Singapore's $50 Billion Financial District Will Change After Covid-19Tycoon Behind a Crisis-Era Property Crash Now Sits on a $9 Billion Debt MountainHow France Tur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Media Mogul 'Degrading' Boss From Hell, Her Staffers Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/hollywood-media-mogul-sharon-waxman-is-a-degrading-boss-from-hell-thewrap-staffers-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheWrap’s founder, CEO, and editor has created a toxic workplace culture, said 20 current and former staffers. Sharon Waxman is “very sorry” to hear this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon plunged into total darkness...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3824729/lebanon-blackout-no-power-light/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON has finally got the lights back on some 24 hours after the country was plunged into total darkness by fuel shortages. The Mediterranean country is battling one of the planet’s worst e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BOND' SOFT IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/10/james-bond-no-time-to-die-earns-a-disappointing-56-mil-plus-open-billie-eilish-theme-song-has-no-revival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror moment actor killed on stage by falling prop as 'audience think it's stunt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/horrified-bolshoi-theatre-performers-raise-25181992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yevgeny Kulesh, 37, is thought to have been hit by a ramp on Saturday night at Moscow's famous Bolshoi Theatre as audience members thought it was part of the opera Sadko</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETTER GLOBAL...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/no-time-to-die-weekend-box-office-1234852700/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday AM: When it comes to Bond and the box office, the world is enough, and the bigger exclamation, as we first told you earlier this week, was going to be in No Time to Die’s global figure…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUT:  Kurz to quit as Austrian chancellor amid corruption probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-austria-3eb18d26c4e3ddfde86c104200be933d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Austrian Chancellor Sebastian Kurz said Saturday that he will step down in a bid to defuse a government crisis triggered by prosecutors' announcement that he is a target of a corruption investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WENDY'S manager douses drive-thru patron with hot oil...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/wendys-hot-oil-assault-108573</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 8--A drive-thru dispute at a Wendy’s in Tennessee turned felonious when a restaurant manager doused a customer with hot oil, leaving the victim with burns and extensive blistering, police all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shootout in busy St. Paul bar leaves 1 dead, 14 injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/shootout-busy-st-paul-bar-leaves-1-dead-14-injured-n1281180</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“In an instant, they found themselves caught in a hellish situation,” St. Paul Police Chief Todd Axtell said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SEVERAL SHOOTERS'...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/10/10/st-paul-bar-mass-shooting-1-dead-14-injured/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person has died and more than a dozen others are hurt after a shooting inside a bar on the 200 block of West Seventh Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>126 mainly Haitian migrants abandoned in locked shipping container...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/126-mainly-haitian-migrants-attempting-to-get-to-the-us-were-abandoned-in-a-locked-shipping-container/ar-AAPl753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Locals alerted the Guatemala police after hearing screams and shouts coming from the trapped migrants, the majority of whom were from Haiti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traditional blue, pink gadgets banned...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10076771/California-law-requires-gender-neutral-area-stores.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large department stores must now display products like toys and toothbrushes in gender-neutral ways. The law is a win for LGBT advocates who say pink and blue hues pressure children to conform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF TROOPS DEFY VAX MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Hundreds-of-thousands-of-U-S-troops-have-not-yet-16522715.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of thousands of U.S. service members remain unvaccinated or only partially...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allen West Infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/allen-west-texas-gop-gubernatorial-candidate-has-covid-c7092b3f-f628-4287-8177-01b9107503bb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He has not been vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Driver Pulled From Truck, Beaten To Death...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/10/09/driver-killed-after-attack-by-crowd-in-hawthorne/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities were investigating the death of a man killed in Hawthorne early Saturday morning, who was allegedly pulled from a truck and beaten to death after nearly striking several people on the sidewalk in front of a business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurse Dies After Being Knocked To Ground By Mugger In Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/10/10/maria-ambrocio-times-square-mugging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little more than 24 hours after oncology nurse Maria Ambrocio was assaulted in Times Square, she was taken off life support and died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lava blocks size of buildings falling from La Palma volcano...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211010102603-r5zvs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPAIN-VOLCANO/ (TV,PIX):Lava blocks the size of buildings falling from La Palma volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing toddler found alive, survived days in woods alone...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/10/texas-3-christopher-ramirez-found-alive-in-woods-missing-for-three-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Ramirez had last been seen by his family on Wednesday when he chased a neighbor’s dog into the woods around 2 p.m. while his parents were unpacking their food truck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won't 'bow', will fortify defense; Tensions mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/taiwan-won-t-bow-to-china-and-will-fortify-its-defenses-says-president-as-military-tensions-mount/ar-AAPkRmT?ocid=Peregrine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Taiwan's national day, President Taiwan Tsai Ing-wen stated that the country will reject all efforts from China to 're-unify' the two states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos at LaGuardia: Passenger pinned to tarmac after 'threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10076181/American-Airlines-confirms-potential-security-issue-onboard-flight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flight AA4817 made an emergency landing at LaGuardia and deplaned passengers after a 'security issue' but the pilot reportedly landed because of a 'suspicious passenger and luggage on board'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan rejects China's 'path' amid show of military force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-lifestyle-taiwan-taipei-music-03340a5f14db94c49b5a2a349a2ee3b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Taiwan's president on Sunday vowed to defend the island from China's rising pressure for reunification, after a week of unprecedented tensions with Beijing. Speaking at the island's National Day celebrations, a rare show of Taiwanese defense capabilities in the annual parade underlined Tsai Ing-wen's promise to resist Chinese military threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi takeover leaves conflicted fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.football365.com/news/opinion-newcastle-takeover-saudi-taste-conflicted-fans-staveley-bin-salman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.football365.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Newcastle fans have turned a blind eye to the takeover. There is real inner conflict for most as expectation on supporters is heightened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle could fire 40% of already depleted police force over mandate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/09/seattle-could-fire-40-of-police-force-over-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city is poised to fire as many as 403 officers, about 40 percent of the 1,000-person force, for failing to take the COVID-19 jab by an Oct. 18 deadline, according to local reports.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
