<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GLASSER:  A Race in Which Everything Happens and Nothing Matters...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/letter-from-trumps-washington/the-2020-election-a-race-in-which-everything-happens-and-nothing-matters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a pandemic that has killed nearly two hundred thousand Americans can’t significantly hurt Trump’s support, can anything?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars line up for chance to play with Brady's BUCS...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox13memphis.com/sports/stars-line-up-chance/FUCFXREHIBJAHPOF7WLTKM442U/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox13memphis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Signing Tom Brady was just a start for the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, who continue to assemble a star-studded cast around the six-time Super Bowl champion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 OFFICERS SUSPENDED</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/daniel-prude-rochester-ny-video-seven-officers-involved-in-death-suspended/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Mr. Daniel Prude was failed by our police department, our mental health care system, our society, and he was failed by me," the city's mayor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland protests set up clash between journalists, police...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/40e2712cdfe132b6ee4e950fa42a6653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — The beam of a police officer’s flashlight swept across a group of 15 people standing on the sidewalk in downtown Portland, Oregon, recording and taking photos of the nightly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER slaps warning labels on tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/03/twitter-slaps-warning-labels-on-trump-tweets-that-suggest-voting-twice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter on Thursday slapped warning labels on several of President Donald Trump's posts, suggesting the messages violated a policy against advocating illegal election activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman glues up own vagina in attempt to frame ex-boyfriend for crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/woman-glued-up-vagina-attempt-22621636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vanesa Gesto accused former boyfriend Ivan Rico of kidnapping her outside her home and later abandoning her while semi-naked in the town of Bembimbre, near Leon in Spain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Thirst-trap' posts on TIKTOK raise questions about military social media policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2020/09/02/thirst-trap-posts-on-tiktok-raise-questions-about-military-social-media-policies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military TikTok has a whole host of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Florida's 18th district is fraught with history of sex scandals...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8671861/How-Floridas-18th-district-fraught-history-sex-scandals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's 18th District has been the playground of politicians involved in illicit sex scandals for two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moment cops shoot dead 18-year-old black man after he pulled gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8695029/DC-Police-release-bodycam-footage-Deon-Kay-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington D.C. police have released bodycam footage showing the moment officers shot dead an 18-year-old black man after he allegedly brandished a gun during a police chase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gonorrhoea cases in England hit record high...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/newsbeat-54011133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Numbers in 2019 were highest ever, but a drop is expected this year due to coronavirus and lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor admits she lied about being black: 'I cancel myself'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/03/african-historian-jessica-krug-admits-shes-lied-about-being-black/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I have lived this lie, fully, completely, with no exit plan or strategy,” the George Washington University historian said in a life-shattering post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bahrain Set to Normalize Relations With Israel...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/bahrain-set-to-normalize-relations-with-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bahrain is set to be the next Gulf country to normalize relations with Israel, a senior Israeli official told Israel's Kan 11 News Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Month on, signal in rubble raises hope for survivor...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/world/a-month-on-signal-in-beirut-rubble-raises-hope-for-survivor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — A pulsing signal was detected Thursday from under the rubble of a Beirut building that collapsed during the horrific port explosion in the Lebanese capital last month, raising hopes there may be a survivor still buried there....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do-Over: Coppola to Re-Edit, Re-Release GODFATHER: PART III...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/godfather-do-over-coppola-to-release-re-edited-godfather-part-iii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Francis Ford Coppola will release a re-edited version of his often-maligned The Godfather: Part III that will include a new beginning, new ending, and new title: The Godfather, Coda: The Death of Michael Corleone. Coppola said the film will better reflect his intentions for the third film in the series, released in 1990, to mark its […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football doc: 30% of positive Big Ten athletes had myocarditis...</title>
      <link>https://www.centredaily.com/sports/college/penn-state-university/psu-football/article245448050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.centredaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty theaters, shuttered dreams: Images tell of lost season...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/life/arts-culture/empty-theaters-shuttered-dreams-images-tell-of-a-lost-season/NC5YHEVFJVCUPHH3JNTZV5NQ74/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo project documents the empty theaters in Atlanta and North Georgia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanese army finds 4 tons of ammonium nitrate in Beirut...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1744e807bfc465c4220fafff2395b558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — A pulsing signal was detected Thursday from under the rubble of a Beirut building that collapsed during the horrific port explosion in the Lebanese capital last month, raising hopes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will flag any effort to declare premature victory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/sep/03/facebook-flag-trump-campaign-effort-premature-victory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Network, which has been condemned for failing to police propaganda, to also ban political ads in final week of 2020 race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Riskiest places where you could catch...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1414035/opening-post-work-bar-how-risk-catching-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEELING anxious about the kids going back to school, visiting a bar or restaurant or heading back to the office? As life starts to return to a “new normal” as coronavirus lockdown is li…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 in 5 want to flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wrong-direction-survey-shows-dismal-outlook-for-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of New York City residents found that they are split in how they feel the city is headed as it continues to fight the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA three-day loss of 18%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/03/tesla-is-dropping-again-bringing-three-day-loss-to-percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla shares came under pressure again on Thursday, following two days of heavy selling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batman Hit By COVID; Superhero Movie Shuts Down In UK...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/batman-uk-production-halts-covid-19-1234569959/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With filming on Matt Reeves’ The Batman having only resumed three days ago after pausing 5 1/2 months ago, the UK production at Warner Bros. Leavesden has stopped again after one of the peopl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Act of Heresy, NRA Former No. 2 Calls for Gun Control...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/nra-insider-speaks-gun-owners-horrified/story?id=72797290</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former high-ranking official within the National Rifle Association is breaking ranks with the powerful gun lobby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZHefkY4cFo8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FULL STORY HERE: https://www.the-sun.com/news/1412523/black-man-died-asphyxiation-cops-hood-face-down/ PROTESTS erupted in upstate New York after shocking vi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TENET' Debut Leaves Forecasters Stumped on Definition of Hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/e2-80-98tenet-e2-80-99-debut-leaves-forecasters-stumped-on-definition-of-a-hit/ar-BB18FpY8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE WORST DAY SINCE MARCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/02/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell sharply on Thursday as investors paused in the wake of a recent rally to all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK!</title>
      <link>https://okmagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;okmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrity News | Entertainment Gossip</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci warns seven Midwest states to be on alert over Labor Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsindiatimes.com/fauci-warns-seven-midwest-states-to-be-on-alert-over-labor-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsindiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO MONTHS UNTIL ELECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-holds-lead-over-trump-as-conventions-fail-to-reshape-polls/ar-BB18Fb45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philip Seymour Hoffman Son Cooper Cast as Lead in Paul Thomas Anderson Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cooper-hoffman-son-of-phillip-seymour-hoffman-leads-paul-thomas-anderson-70s-drama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr suggests law enforcement could be sent to polling places...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/514931-barr-suggests-law-enforcement-could-be-sent-to-polling-places-if</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr said late Wednesday that President Trump's pledge to send federal law enforcement to polling locations on Election Day would be legal if the president were responding to a "particular criminal threat."&amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of depression triple...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/signs-depression-tripled-u-since-130007743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prevalence of depression symptoms in the U.S. has more than tripled in the COVID-19 era compared to the period before the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Economic recovery stalls as consumers signal caution...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/68a7f0edb88460c0e3fbadb6356a6ef0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The U.S. economy's economic engine may be running out of fuel. Consumer spending accounts for about 70% of the U.S. gross domestic product, making it the single most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EX-MICHIGAN GOP GOV: TRUMP IS BULLY</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2020/09/03/rick-snyder-why-im-voting-joe-biden-even-republican-column/5696508002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is a bully who lacks a moral compass. Joe Biden would bring back civility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network of news sites must register as political committee due to Dem links, complaint alleges...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Network-of-news-sites-must-register-as-a-15539836.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A new complaint filed Thursday with the Federal Election Commission alleges that a national network of local media websites must register as a political committee because of its ties to a Democratic-aligned group.  Courier Newsroom, which includes seven news sites concentrated in presidential swing states,is backed by ACRONYM, a politically active nonprofit run by Democratic strategist Tara McGowan.  Federal election laws and regulations do not apply to media outlets unless they are "owned or controlled by" a political party, committee or candidate and are acting as a media outlet rather than a political one.  But the complaint, filed by Americans for Public Trust, a watchdog group affiliated with former Nevada attorney general Adam Laxalt, a Republican, alleges that Courier Newsroom is not eligible for that exemption and that the media group failed to register as a political group and report its donors and expenses as is required of political groups under federal law.  The complaint points to a June 2019 ACRONYM internal memo, in which McGowan wrote that the group was launching a "for-profit digital media company building out online news properties in seven 2020 battleground states" of Wisconsin, Michigan, Pennsylvania, Virginia, North Carolina, Florida and Arizona.  In the memo, McGowan warned that Democrats are "losing the media war" online to the Republican Party and to President Donald Trump's campaign, and laid out her plan for Courier Newsroom to counter that GOP advantage.  "Building this media content network - majority owned by ACRONYM - will: Enable Democrats to compete with Republican echo chambers online; Build nimble communications infrastructure for Dems in critical states; Reach voters with strategic narratives + information year-round; Make cyclical investments in paid advertising more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WRANGLER goes electric...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wrangler-introduces-jeeps-first-electric-204031169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiat Chrysler&amp;#39;s Jeep brand is starting to offer gas-electric hybrid and eventually full electric powertrains across its lineup. The main reason driving the new offerings likely is FCA&amp;#39;s obligation to meet fuel economy and pollution regulations in Europe, China, and the U.S. or face stiff fines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade deficit surges to highest in 12 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd93ecd3cafc5df88a8f9f4a61693b07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. trade deficit surged in July to $63.6 billion, the highest level in 12 years, as imports jumped by a record amount. The Commerce Department reported that the July...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Pours Massive Fundraising Haul Into Battleground Ad Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/09/joe-biden-pours-massive-fundraising-haul-into-new-battleground-tv-ad-blitz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raising $364 million in a single month lets a presidential candidate do a lot of things—including release a volley of ads aimed at voters impacted by the coronavirus. Here’s a first look at the three new spots premiering Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cargo ship carrying 43 crew and thousands of cattle sinks off Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/sep/03/typhoon-maysak-ship-with-43-crew-and-nearly-6000-cattle-missing-off-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strong winds and rain from Typhoon Maysak hamper rescue of crew from Philippines, New Zealand and Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Common Medications Linked To Thinking, Memory Problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/common-drugs-linked-to-memory-problems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metoprolol, atenolol, loratadine, and bupropion are among the most common medications in the anticholinergic drug class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says people in NCarolina should vote twice...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-trump-vote/trump-says-people-in-north-carolina-should-vote-twice-idUSKBN25U0KK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump suggested on Wednesday that people in the state of North Carolina should vote twice in the November election, once in person and once by mail, although doing so is a crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and dread haunt COVID-19 'long-haulers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-long-fear-feature/fear-and-dread-haunt-covid-19-long-haulers-idUSKBN25U0ET</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Until March 19 this year, Felicity Callard, a 49 year-old British university professor and lecturer, was fit, active and strong. Now, she says, she's exhausted, frail and scared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets facing potential 'Minsky moment' collapse, strategist says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/03/markets-are-facing-a-potential-minsky-moment-collapse-strategist-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asset prices could be on the cusp of a sharp collapse known as a "Minsky moment," and may retest lows last seen in March, according to Ron William, market strategist and founder of RW Advisory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TENET' Debut Leaves Forecasters Stumped on Definition of Hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/-tenet-debut-leaves-forecasters-stumped-on-definition-of-a-hit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€˜Tenetâ€™ Debut Leaves Forecasters Stumped on Definition of a Hit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 14 Policy Scenarios Might Change...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/14-u-s-policies-that-could-change-after-the-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How 14 Policy Scenarios Might Change After the U.S. Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have Republicans Lost Suburbs? Arizona County Suggests So...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2020-09-03/u-s-election-have-the-republicans-lost-the-suburbs-arizona-county-suggests-so</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts: Cohen may profit from criminal exploits in tell-all...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fbd241da120af910ca7e2e35dd181428</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — When Michael Cohen testified before Congress last year, Republican lawmakers worried aloud that President Donald Trump's former fixer would parlay the spectacle — and his criminal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: 50 Million Americans Fighting Hunger By End Of Year?</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/it-is-being-projected-that-more-than-50-million-americans-will-be-fighting-hunger-by-the-end-of-this-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Has there ever been a time in your life when you haven't had enough food to make it through the week?  If you have never experienced this, you are extremely fortunate.  Even during the best</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NO TIME TO DIE' Gets New Trailer as 007 Marketing Engine Roars Back to Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/no-time-to-die-gets-new-trailer-as-007-marketing-engine-roars-back-to-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Faces Pressure to Drop Russian Pipeline to Hit Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/merkel-faces-pressure-to-drop-russian-gas-pipeline-after-navalny-s-poisoning/story-cb4jKpOMpZf5hEYZVR7ibI.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norbert Roettgen, head of the German parliament’s foreign affairs committee and a candidate to head Merkel’s Christian Democratic party, said the Nord Stream 2 pipeline needs to be stopped because completing it would reward rather than punish Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would military intervene in election results?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/514789-would-the-united-states-military-intervene-in-the-election-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is notable that we even have to ask this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO: Trump better have army to protect him if comes to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/02/cuomo-trump-better-have-an-army-to-protect-him-if-he-comes-to-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo on Wednesday all but threatened President Trump’s safety if he returns to New York City in a rant responding to an exclusive story by The Post that Trump is looking…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pull Out of Kentucky Derby? Pressure on Black Owner Mounts...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/03/pull-out-of-the-kentucky-derby-pressure-on-a-black-owner-mounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In any other year, Greg Harbut would be enjoying the achievement of a lifetime. On Saturday, he will watch his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Burning Man Internet's Ultimate Test?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/03/is-virtual-burning-man-the-internets-ultimate-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What makes Burning Man so special to those who attend — the cliché among the faithful is “life-changing” — is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Act of Heresy, NRA Former No. 2 Calls for Gun Control...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/03/in-act-of-heresy-n-r-a-s-former-no-2-calls-for-gun-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association’s former second-in-command is breaking with the group’s orthodoxy and calling for universal background checks and so-called</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increased risk of civil unrest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/45d5266e50df78175141544a136242d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just two months left until the U.S. presidential election, Facebook says it is taking more steps to encourage voting, minimize misinformation and reduce the likelihood of post-election “civil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Kenosha, Biden to test his promise to unify nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2373c9517d2781ab11b92e1ee0dd5273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Joe Biden faces the most intense test yet of his pledge to be a calming, unifying leader for a divided nation when he travels Thursday to Kenosha, Wisconsin, a city now at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEESE: Can you tell me woke joke?</title>
      <link>http://www.irishnews.com/magazine/entertainment/2020/09/03/news/john-cleese-can-you-tell-me-a-woke-joke--2055272/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran comedian warned that organising ‘a society around the sensibilities of the most easily upset people' leads to a ‘very neurotic society'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA DEBATE RAGES</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Debate-rages-over-whether-FDA-should-use-15538911.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A fierce debate has erupted over whether the Food and Drug Administration should use its emergency authority to clear a coronavirus vaccine before it is formally approved - a move opponents warn could pose safety dangers and inflame anti-vaccination sentiment but others say could save thousands of lives by speeding protection from the virus.  With concerns growing about the politicization of the FDA amid a botched White House rollout of the agency's emergency authorization of convalescent plasma and sharply criticized comments by FDA Commissioner Stephen Hahn, some scientists and bioethicists are demanding the agency forgo use of its emergency authority for a vaccine. They worry its very flexibility, which gives FDA officials broad latitude, could it make it easier for the White House to pressure the agency into clearing an unproven vaccine before Election Day, Nov. 3.  President Donald Trump's repeated promise to deliver a safe and effective vaccine this year, "or maybe even sooner," has become central to his reelection campaign and has sparked concerns in the scientific community in particular that the White House could pressure regulators to cut corners.  Those concerns come against the backdrop of an accelerating race to develop a coronavirus vaccine as three vaccine makers - pharmaceutical giant Pfizer, biotechnology firm Moderna and drugmaker AstraZeneca - conduct Phase 3 clinical trials, the last before seeking a green light from regulators.  A recent report by Morgan Stanley said the most likely timing for data from one or more of the trials is November. But others say it's possible some results might be available in October if the vaccines prove spectacularly effective and there are enough viral infections in the community to prove the shots are protecting patients who receive them.  The CDC has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden garners more Republican endorsements, this time from ex-govs...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden-republicans-exclus-idUSKBN25U1AK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 100 Republican and independent leaders will endorse Democrat Joe Biden for president on Thursday, including one-time 2020 Republican presidential candidate Bill Weld and the former Republican governors of Michigan and New Jersey, people involved in the effort told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBD/TIPP POLL:  BIDEN +8...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/politics/joe-biden-holds-solid-lead-over-president-donald-trump-no-convention-bump-ibd-tipp-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rochester erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8692307/Disturbing-new-video-shows-black-man-41-suffocating-death-New-York-police-custody.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Prude was left brain dead after the incident and later died on March 30 after he was taken off of life support - seven days after the encounter with police in Rochester, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP VACCINE BY NOV 1</title>
      <link>https://www.centredaily.com/news/coronavirus/article245406245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.centredaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
THE ROCK reveals COVID battle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rock-reveals-family-coronavirus-battle-012121233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dwayne &amp;quot;The Rock&amp;quot; Johnson and his entire family tested positive for coronavirus but have made a full recovery, the professional wrestler turned Hollywood A-lister said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid cases in Europe back to March level...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200902122737-li5yq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/EU-ECDC:COVID-19 cases in Europe back to March level, EU health body says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video in Black man's suffocation shows cops put hood on him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c2f0cf366e560b7f41ebb3c964b099c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Black man who had run naked through the streets of a western New York city died of asphyxiation after a group of police officers put a hood over his head, then pressed his face into the pavement...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
