<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Joe needs to atone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/31/democratic-debates-joe-biden-crime-record-2020-1441932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president’s crime-fighting record was once a signature strength. In the current Democratic Party, it might be a liability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is NASA hiding? Mysterious plane scanning San Andreas Fault...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1159768/Big-One-California-earthquake-NASA-airplane-San-Andreas-conspiracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS NASA aircraft flying unusually low to the ground has sparked alarm in California, with speculation that the aircraft was monitoring the volatile San Andreas Fault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi spat at in German capital; police investigating...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c922365fe9864a4ca721ad40e0f8240e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network roasted over production...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/455498-cnn-roasted-over-debate-production-format-a-disservice-to-serious-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN faced backlash for its first primary debate of the 2020 campaign season, with members of the media comparing its production to a sporting event or movie trailer and others lamenting the time spent to kick off the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected drunk DELTA pilot arrested just before flight...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/31/suspected-drunk-delta-pilot-arrested-kicked-off-plane-just-before-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Delta pilot who authorities suspect was boozed up was booted off a fully boarded plane in Minneapolis and arrested, according to new reports. Gabriel Lyle Schroeder, 37, was cuffed just after 11 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insane Baseball Brawl Mars Ugly REDS vs. PIRATES Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/watch-insane-baseball-brawl-mars-ugly-reds-vs-pirates-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baseball brawls are very often more chest-out posturing, pushing and holding back teammates than actual fights. Last night's fight between the Cincinnati Reds and the Pittsburgh Pirates, however,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveals 'De-Aging' Techniques...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/martin-scorseses-irishman-trailer-offers-first-look-at-films-de-aging-vfx-techniques-1227349 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biographical film stars Robert De Niro as Frank "The Irishman" Sheeran, a labor union leader and alleged hitman for the Bufalino crime family, and Al Pacino as union activist Jimmy Hoffa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brad Pitt's Moment: Two Oscar Contenders...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/movies/brad-pitt-big-year-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor hasn't appeared in a film since 2017's Netflix drama War Machine, and this year has two Oscar contenders in the mix</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN: Notes of common sense at debate -- will Dems listen?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/31/notes-of-common-sense-at-debate-but-will-the-democrats-listen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Tuesday night’s debate had taken place six months ago, the questions and answers would have been dominated by Russia, Russia, Russia. But with the accusations that President Trump was a traitor …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Harris to square off in Round two...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-debate/biden-and-harris-to-square-off-in-round-two-of-democratic-presidential-debate-idUSKCN1UQ150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential front-runner Joe Biden and rival Kamala Harris will stag...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marty the grocery store robot glimpse into hell-ish future...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/stop-and-shop-marty-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop them so we can shop in peace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: CNN Steals Show, and Everyone Loses...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/someone-please-vote-cnn-off-034812093.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Ten of the Democrats debated on Tuesday night. But the debate was dominated by Jake Tapper, Dana Bash and Don Lemon – CNN’s moderators. Norm Ornstein got it right:It’s not just that the time allocations were harsh. (The candidates were constantly being cut off, sometimes after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese forces gathering at Hong Kong border...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/asia/chinese-forces-gathering-at-hong-kong-border-white-house-officials-monitoring-escalation/news-story/82621253f4c093c69834e041713ab34d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is monitoring the sudden “congregation” of Chinese forces at the border with Hong Kong, according to reports, following another night of unrest and clashes between protesters and police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood mocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/07/30/hollywood-mocks-democrat-debate-like-a-west-wing-episode-fcked-an-auction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a dozen Democrat presidential hopefuls took the stage in Detroit, Michigan, Tuesday evening for CNN’s presidential debate and the Hollywood left was not impressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FREE EVERYTHING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/07/31/sanders-and-warren-leading-liberals-fight-off-accusations-they-are-impractical/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - DETROIT — The leading liberal populists in the Democratic presidential primary, Senators Bernie Sanders and Elizabeth Warren, strenuously fought back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang likens debate to 'boring football game'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/455439-yang-on-watching-democratic-debates-we-are-about-to-watch-the-most-boring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Andrew Yang took a shot at his Democratic rivals appearing in Tuesday night's primary debate, likening the event to a "boring football game."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren pushing party not to be timid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3490d16f9014613ac2458c963063874</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight with moderate rivals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1576034c95f4429788c743836d2a6c77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN:  NKorea fires short-range ballistic missiles...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190731000806-6sfvw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/SOUTHKOREA (UPDATE 5):UPDATE 5-North Korea fires short-range ballistic missiles - South Korean military</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zucker Defends... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jeff-zucker-defends-cnns-trump-coverage-pans-destructive-fox-news-in-interview-ahead-of-debates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As CNN prepares to hold the second Democratic primary debate of the 2020 election, network chief Jeff Zucker swung at Fox News in an interview he gave ahead of the festivities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio Grande Valley passes 300K apprehensions, sets annual border record...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/rio-grande-valley-passes-300k-apprehensions-sets-annual-border-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where is Congress? On vacation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>114 private jets for elite to talk 'global warming' with GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/07/30/a-listers-flock-to-google-summit-in-private-jets-mega-yachts-to-talk-climate-change/?_ga=2.74028817.263768670.1564409595-1619352479.1515542892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each were personally invited by the search giant for discussions primarily about climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BDG postpones GAWKER relaunch, lays off entire staff...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/30/bdg-postpones-gawker-relaunch-lays-off-entire-staff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A planned relaunch of snarky news and gossip web site Gawker is on hold indefinitely, The Post has learned. Bustle Digital Group, which owns Gawker, laid off the website’s entire staff Tuesday and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Lee's Daughter Rips Tarantino for 'Mockery' of Dad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bruce-lee-daughter-mockery-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-shannon-lee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Lee's daughter, Shannon Lee, says it was "disheartening" to see how Quentin Tarantino portrayed her father in "Once Upon a Time... in Hollywood"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon issues forceful rebuke of ORACLE as debate over massive federal contract turns caustic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Pentagon-issues-forceful-rebuke-of-Oracle-as-14268151.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Pentagon has issued an unusually strong rebuke of Oracle over the weekend, accusing the company of employing "poorly-informed and often manipulative speculation" in its efforts to undermine the military's process of awarding a massive 10-year contract for cloud computing technology.  The remarks were the latest flash point in the long-running dispute over the bidding process for the Joint Enterprise Defense Infrastructure, or JEDI, a $10 billion contract that would be one of the federal government's most expensive information technology procurements ever.  Oracle alleged in a lawsuit that the Defense Department's bidding process has been plagued with potential conflicts of interest and rigged in favor of Amazon's cloud computing business. Oracle's attempt to block the award was rejected earlier this month, with the judge in charge of the case explaining his reasoning in a lengthy document unsealed Friday. But in his decision, the judge posed new questions about the Pentagon's legal argument for awarding one big contract.  Department of Defense spokeswoman Elissa Smith noted in a statement that the judge also affirmed that the Pentagon was "reasonably justified" to award a single contract. Despite the "tension" in the judge's ruling, the department has said it plans to move ahead and award the contract in August, nearly a year and a half after it was announced.  Smith's statement, which was emailed to reporters Sunday night, also contained the harsh words for Oracle. Smith appeared to take a second swipe at the company as well: "DOD officials directly involved in the work of this procurement along with the senior leaders charged with making the critical decisions related to JEDI have always placed the interests of the warfighter first and have acted without bias, prejudice, or self-interest. The same...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/democratic-debate-july-30-2019/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty Democratic presidential hopefuls will face off at the CNN primary debate in Detroit. Follow live here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Head of DEADSPIN, THE ONION facing heat from own reporters...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/30/head-of-deadspin-the-onion-facing-heat-from-own-reporters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of G/O Media, which owns The Onion, Jezebel and other websites, is going on the defensive over a planned expose on his hiring practices — to be published by one of his own publications. G/…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBATE NIGHT:  LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://go.cnn.com/?stream=cnn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;go.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNNgo is a revolutionary news-watching experience that offers the live CNN broadcast with unprecedented features. You can catch-up on the stories you‘ve missed, go deeper and learn more about the stories that interest you with related coverage, and enjoy the most popular On Demand Shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk of farm aid goes to biggest and wealthiest farmers... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190730175400-li5as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/FARMING (PIX):Bulk of Trump's U.S. farm aid goes to biggest and wealthiest farmers -advocacy group</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN's 2020 Strategy: Live Events With 'Game Show' Theatrics...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cnn-democratic-debates-network-betting-live-events-a-touch-game-show-theatrics-1228089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The network has been cutting away from Trump rallies while doubling down on live candidate events (25 town halls) and experimenting with a live debate lottery ahead of the Detroit Democratic showdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network stuck in 3rd place...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/07/hannity-fox-news-ratings-tops-cnn-msnbc-rachel-maddow-rupert-murdoch-1202657280/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean Hannity will be competing with the first night of the CNN hosted Democratic debates tonight, but the Fox News Channel host won’t likely get even a scratch when it comes to the ratings. Holding…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  TRASH TALK TURNS OFF SUBURBAN WOMEN...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1d98f7567f947d49f698e3ee0f234a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain signals decoded into written text...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jul/30/neuroscientists-decode-brain-speech-signals-into-actual-sentences</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study funded by Facebook aims to improve communication with paralysed patients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In globalized world, music fragments take unexpected roads...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/article233302837.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLAINS HER MAGICAL THINKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/07/marianne-williamson-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview, the self-help author running to be America’s spiritualist in chief discusses meditation, war, David Brooks, and why the public should take her seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE beats Street; Stock soars...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/30/apple-earnings-q3-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's services and wearables businesses are becoming increasingly critical for the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah Letting Lots of Govt Employees Work From Home...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/07/30/utah-is-letting-lots-of-government-employees-work-from-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it's actually kind of great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Even Funerals Are Livestreamed...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/funerals-livestreamed-families-grateful/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With friends and relatives dispersed, a growing number of funeral homes will stream services, and demand is increasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ex-AMAZON engineer charged in CAPITAL ONE breach may have other companies' data...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2019/07/30/suspect-behind-capital-one-data-breach-may-have-more/1865848001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Seattle software engineer, arrested Monday in connection with the theft of data from Capital One, may have stolen data from other entities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Man Discovers Baby Corpse Believed to Be Sister in Freezer...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksdk.com/article/news/local/i-want-more-answers-man-finds-frozen-baby-in-moms-freezer-in-south-st-louis/63-e0f2345f-5de1-4b08-935f-acb6496ad142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksdk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm 37 and it has been in my freezer for 37 years and I was always told it was a wedding cake top," Smith said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential envoy sent to Sweden for A$AP Rocky's trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ae4a9d93a2a49b69d3b4b9d989ece7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry: Will only have TWO kids -- to help save planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7301321/Prince-Harry-interviewed-Dr-Jane-Goodall-Meghans-edition-British-Vogue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of Sussex, 34, made the revelation in an interview with conservationist Dr Jane Goodall as part of his wife Meghan Markle's edition of British Vogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Says 'Zero Strategy' in Attacking Baltimore...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/455360-trump-theres-no-strategy-in-attacks-on-cummings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday said his ongoing barrage of attacks on Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political pressure complicates Fed's expected rate cut...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/political-pressure-complicates-feds-expected-rate-cut-163451376.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve is set to "vaccinate" the US economy against a slowdown with the first interest rate cut in a decade, but the decision has been made more difficult by unrelenting political pressure. President Donald Trump has constantly berated the Fed and its chairman, Jerome Powell,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama library to have 'adverse impact' on historic park, review concludes...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/2019/7/30/20747215/obama-presidential-center-foundation-lease-jackson-park-federal-review-lightfoot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The finding by the Federal Highway Administration puts pressure on the Obama Foundation to find a way to ‘resolve adverse effects’ and turns up the heat on Mayor Lori Lightfoot to order the foundation to make those changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhinoceros conceived artificially born at zoo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d6a9ccddf16d4435b66690fe345302bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New bill would ban autoplay videos, endless scrolling...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/7/30/20746878/josh-hawley-dark-patterns-platform-design-autoplay-youtube-videos-scrolling-snapstreaks-illegal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking aim at "features that are designed to be addictive."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>79-year-old sentenced to jail for feeding stray cats...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/year-old-woman-sentenced-days-jail-for-feeding-stray-cats/fg42yOOt3gQbCdLoA8udlK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 79-year-old woman from Ohio will have to spend 10 days in jail for feeding stray cats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Warns of Terror Strikes in San Fran, NYC, London...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/isis-warns-of-terror-strikes-in-san-francisco-new-york-london/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ISIS terrorist organization is threatening to launch new attacks in San Francisco, New York, and London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US issues hacking security alert for small planes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6219f26c3ea145b6b29b5e69115504a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Gov. Newsom to Sign Bill Targeting Trump Tax Returns...</title>
      <link>https://yashar.substack.com/p/exclusive-newsom-trump-tax-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;yashar.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to share this post on social media, please use this link: https://yashar.substack.com/ Exclusive: California Gov. Newsom to Sign Bill Targeting Trump Tax Returns California Gov. Gavin Newsom, my former boss, tells me that he has decided to sign a bill that would require all presidential and gubernatorial candidates to submit five years of tax returns in order to qualify for the primary ballot in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  LEADS PRAYER SESSION FOR WHITE PEOPLE TO APOLOGIZE FOR WRONGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n1Mxs06hBe8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribe to our channel! https://goo.gl/pyGqbu Footage has emerged of the 2020 Democratic Candidate leading a prayer which called for the audience to apolog...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not much desert diversity: Burning Man attendees white, well-off...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Burning-Man-Census-2018-diversity-inclusion-Burner-14151360.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Black Rock City Census Project shows us demographics of Burning Man 2018 participants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica wants to end beatings and paddling of kids, saying it leads to later violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/latinamerica/top-stories/jamaica-wants-to-end-beatings-paddling-of-kids-saying-it-leads-to-later-violence/ar-AAENQ8b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing portrait emerges of  Garlic Festival shooter...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/disturbing-portrait-emerges-of-gilroy-garlic-festival-shooter/ar-AAF49v3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brad Pitt Compares Weinstein Scandal To Manson Murders...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/brad-pitt-compares-harvey-weinstein-scandal-to-manson-murders-129510 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's more that I think we're getting recalibrated, but in a good way."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO SHOT DEAD AT WALMART IN TN...</title>
      <link>https://www.commercialappeal.com/story/news/2019/07/30/southaven-mississippi-walmart-shooting-police-respond-report-active-shooter/1864992001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.commercialappeal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two were killed and at least two injured at a Southaven, Mississippi, Walmart outside of Memphis Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARIANNE WILLIAMSON: I'M NOT A NEW-AGE NUT!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/455311-marianne-williamson-i-am-not-a-wacky-new-age-nutcase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Marianne Williamson pushed back against what she described as a false narrative surrounding her, insisting that she is not a “wacky new-age nutcase.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tech firm eyes IPO for gay dating app GRINDR...</title>
      <link>https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/china-tech-firm-eyes-ipo-104659233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese parent company of the popular gay dating app Grindr on Tuesday said it will "restart" plans for a public listing after a US national security panel dropped its opposition to the move. US authorities had earlier raised concerns about the potential misuse of the app's data by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLASH OF THE LIBS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/clash-liberals-warren-sanders-set-showdown-141610910.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading liberals in the 2020 presidential race will command the spotlight in Tuesday's Democratic debate, and sparks could fly as Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders battle over who will be torchbearer for the party's progressive wing. Frontrunner Joe Biden takes the stage Wednesday night between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Center tracking two tropical waves in Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/weather/hurricane/fl-ne-two-tropical-waves-atlantic-20190730-lh5k6dxdkbh7bkdna5g5fjqtoi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tropical wave that’s path points toward Florida could strengthen by the weekend. Meanwhile, another disturbance has formed off the west coast of Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 COMCASTNBC Execs Funded Harris Campaign Before Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/business/joseph-vazquez/2019/07/29/12-nbccomcast-execs-funded-harris-campaign-debate </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN head Zucker calls the shots but checks his aim...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/CNN-head-Zucker-calls-the-shots-but-checks-his-aim-14250723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Side shot! Side shot! Side shot!"  It's Mueller Day in Washington, and the man calling out instructions in the darkened control room of CNN's Washington bureau gets his wish as the screens on the wall in front him, along with TV screens across the country, change at his command. These decisions are usually made by one of the network's many producers, but this particular camera angle was emphatically suggested by none other than network president Jeff Zucker, who came down from New York to prepare for this week's Democratic primary debate and decided to make a quick stop in the control room. Mueller's halting testimony was not making for the most riveting TV, and Zucker was doing his best to liven things up.  Zucker has long prided himself on his ability to do just that. He oversaw NBC's "Today" show in its prime Katie Couric years. He bought the reality show "The Apprentice," which turned into a monster hit and turned Donald Trump into a TV star. But since he has come to CNN, the network has been in third place in the cable-news ratings race, and someone, somewhere - often but certainly not exclusively the resident of the White House - always seems to be pointing out how CNN is messing up.  The first debates last month on NBC networks set viewership records for Democratic primary season, and now CNN plays host for two nights with 20 candidates in Detroit on Tuesday and Wednesday. It's the network's biggest moment yet in the 2020 election cycle - an election cycle that could serve as a sort of do-over for Zucker, for CNN and for the media in general.  Zucker came under intense criticism for CNN's mode of coverage in the 2016 election. He has acknowledged some mistakes while defending the network overall, and vows that this time will be different.  The network won't air any candidate rallies live and unedited, as it did...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia blamed for radioactive cloud over Europe...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/07/30/russia-blamed-nuclear-accident-sent-radioactive-cloud-floating-across-europe-10481891/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious incident in 2017 was the worst release of radioactive material since Fukushima.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fly buzzes Duterte as he attacks priests...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/philippines/fly-buzzes-rodrigo-duterte-as-he-attacks-philippine-priests-1.65532509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President uses the incident to criticise the country’s influential Catholic church</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body of 1930s gangster John Dillinger to be exhumed...</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2019/07/29/body-of-1930s-gangster-john-dillinger-to-be-exhumed-from-grave-at-crown-hill-cemetery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS, Ind. – The body of gangster John Dillinger is set to be exhumed from his grave at Indianapolis’ Crown Hill Cemetery. A permit to disinter, remove and reinter Dillinger’s remains was issued on June 18, according to documents from the Indiana State Department of Health. Michael C. Thompson, who is listed as Dillinger’s nephew, is the person who applied for the permit. FOX59 is working to determine why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Oscar Buzz For Joaquin Phoenix 'JOKER'?</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/dc/2019/07/30/joker-joaquin-phoenix-oscar-nominations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not the first time we've heard this, but it looks like Todd Phillips' Joker is shaping up to [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS:  Drone makes 50 mile commercial delivery...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/drone-makes-first-commercial-delivery-in-the-bahamas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone successfully made a commercial delivery in The Bahamas last month traveling&amp;nbsp;more than 50 miles over land and water in 28 minutes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
