<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Central Park raccoons die from viral 'zombie' outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/21/dozens-of-raccoons-die-from-viral-zombie-outbreak-in-central-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen Central Park raccoons have died in an ongoing viral outbreak that causes “zombie” behavior in the critters, authorities determined. Of 26 raccoons found dead inside the park sin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dust Storm Invades Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/weather/dust-storm-invades-las-vegas-heat-wave-coming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Light sprinkles and intermittent showers are possible Saturday evening after gusts kicked up dusts in the morning, according to the National Weather Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US fighter jet intercepts plane near Trump resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article215313405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Air Force F-16 fighter jet on Saturday intercepted a small plane near Donald Trump's private golf resort in New Jersey, where the president is currently staying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINCLAIR fumbles imperil mega-merger...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/398149-sinclairs-fumbles-imperil-mega-merger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FCC's rejection of the deal is a striking reversal of fortune for the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TARGETS APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-targets-apple-with-push-into-advanced-smartphone-screens-1532260804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOE Technology Group, a supplier of screens for iPads and MacBooks, now wants to provide Apple with advanced organic light-emitting diode, or OLED, smartphone screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense bill to end Cabinet's direct control of nuclear agency...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/22/trump-administration-control-national-nuclear-secu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bill being negotiated in Congress would essentially end the Trump administration’s direct supervision of an agency that oversees the nation’s nuclear weapons stockpile. The Senate-approved bill would remove the National Nuclear Security Administration from direct control of the Energy Department, where it’s been since its creation in 2000, and empower it to act nearly on its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How long will Mueller investigation go on?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/22/politics/robert-mueller-russia-investigation-length/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week's indictments could be the high point for his team. Or it could be simply the crest of one of several coming waves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractor rampages through downtown Denver in police pursuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/22/tractor-pursuit-through-downtown-denver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Denver Police squad cars pursued a tractor through downtown Denver on Friday night before finally stopping it at 15th and Market streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Russian agent met with Obama Treasury, Fed officials...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-russia-butina-exclusive/exclusive-accused-russian-agent-butina-met-with-u-s-treasury-fed-officials-idUKKBN1KC0DE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused Russian agent Maria Butina had wider high-level contacts in Washington than previously known, taking part in 2015 meetings between a visiting Russian official and two senior officials at the U.S. Federal Reserve and Treasury Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MLB pitcher punished for tweets gets standing ovation...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/mlb/2018/07/21/josh-hader-standing-ovation-tweet-scandal-milwaukee-brewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several of Hader's years-old racist and homophobic tweets surfaced during the All-Star Game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super rich boost political giving...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/07/21/super-rich-step-up-their-giving-ahead-midterm-election-fight/813088002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group committed to helping Republicans retain the House has raised more money than any other super PAC ahead of the Nov. 6 midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran warns Trump about 'mother of all wars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-nuclear-usa-rouhani/irans-rouhani-warns-trump-about-mother-of-all-wars-idUSKBN1KC07Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani on Sunday cautioned U.S. President Donald Trump about pursuing hostile policies against Tehran, saying "America should know ... war with Iran is the mother of all wars," but he did not rule out peace between the two countries, either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh scandal erupts over vaccines in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fresh-scandal-erupts-over-vaccine-safety-china-095141360--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scandal over faulty vaccines in China has sparked anger on social media, underscoring the difficulties regulators face in rebuilding trust after years of food and drug safety controversies. The incident is a major blow for Beijing, which has been trying to push domestically made vaccines and for China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK SHOCK: Toddler injured in acid attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6837529/three-year-old-seriously-injured-in-acid-attack-as-police-released-image-of-three-men-they-are-hunting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A THREE year old boy has been seriously injured in a suspected acid attack, West Mercia Police have said. Cops released images of three men after the tot was injured in a suspected acid attack in H…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver puts videos of hundreds of passengers online. Most have no idea...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/metro/st-louis-uber-driver-has-put-video-of-hundreds-of/article_9060fd2f-f683-5321-8c67-ebba5559c753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you taken an Uber or Lyft ride in St. Louis this year? You may have been streamed to an online audience without ever knowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. launches campaign to erode support for Iran's leaders...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180721211735-3xasc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/:U.S. launches campaign to erode support for Iran's leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAVILY REDACTED:  Carter Page FISA Court Docs released...</title>
      <link>https://www.judicialwatch.org/press-room/press-releases/judicial-watch-obtains-carter-page-fisa-court-documents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.judicialwatch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Washington, DC) – Judicial Watch President Tom Fitton made the following statement regarding today’s release of 412 pages of documents about FISA (Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act) warrants targeting Carter Page, who had been a Trump campaign adviser: These documents are heavily redacted but seem to confirm the FBI and DOJ misled the courts in withholding the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico man who fed wildlife at his home bitten by bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexico-man-fed-wildlife-home-bitten-bear-194851590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALAMOGORDO, N.M. (AP) — Officials say a 70-year-old southern New Mexico man who regularly fed wildlife at his home suffered multiple injuries when he was bitten by a bear as he stepped outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020:  Hillary Clinton appears at Central Park summer festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hillary-clinton-appear-central-park-summer-festival-025859714.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hillary Clinton was part of a star-studded lineup at a summer festival in New York's Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Gaza and Israel, war fears mount despite truce...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/gaza-israel-war-fears-mount-despite-truce-162401826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After seven chaotic and violent hours, quiet returned to the Gaza Strip overnight. The fatal shooting by a Palestinian of an Israeli soldier during protests along the border Friday sparked a widespread wave of Israeli bombing, with three fighters from Gaza's Islamist rulers Hamas killed and dozens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Who Lost 9 Relatives in Boating Accident Struggles With Why She Survived...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/woman-who-lost-nine-relatives-in-boating-accident-struggles-with-why-she-survived-1532214034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tia Coleman said she can’t understand how she and a teenage nephew survived the sinking of an amphibious tour boat in a sudden violent storm on Thursday while nine other members of her family died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hollywood, 'Anything Goes' Becomes 'You're Fired'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-hollywood-anything-goes-becomes-youre-fired-1532181601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood’s longstanding say-anything, do-anything culture is rapidly turning into one where the wrong words can kill careers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba aims to build socialism, not communism, in draft constitution...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/cubas-president-names-cabinet-resembling-castros-161410089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Sarah Marsh HAVANA (Reuters) - A draft of Cuba's new constitution keeps the Communist Party as its leading political force but states as its aim the construction of socialism rather than communism, reflecting changing times, top officials told lawmakers this weekend. Cuba is replacing its Soviet-era</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE SUNDAY:  In private, Trump vents his frustration over lack of progress on NKorea... </title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-trump-north-korea-negotiations-20180721-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the weeks since the two leaders met, U.S. negotiators have faced stiff resistance from a North Korean team practiced in the art of delay and obfuscation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostages...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Pursuit-Ends-With-gunshots-at-Trader-Joe-in-Silverlake-488810971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A police pursuit in the Hollywood area ended in the Silver Lake area at a Trader Joe's with a suspect inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort faces federal trial with hint of presidential pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/manafort-faces-federal-trial-with-a-hint-of-a-presidential-pardon/ar-BBKTJKH?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA authorities recorded privileged attorney-client conversations, district attorney says...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2104485?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES -- After Los Angeles County's public defender expressed concerns about possibly illegal recordings of privileged attorney-client meetings at a downtown courthouse, a spokeswoman for the district attorney has acknowledged that such recordings had "inadvertently...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting Suspect Barricaded Inside Los Angeles TRADER JOE'S...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/21/reports-of-possible-active-shooter-at-silver-lake-trader-joes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police were responding to a report of shooting at the Trader Joe's near Hyperion Avenue and Silver Lake Boulevard in Silver Lake Saturday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES FRONT PAGE SUNDAY:  European govts rethinking their reliance on USA as ally...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-pol-trump-europe-20180718-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deeply alarmed at President Trump’s attacks on NATO and the transatlantic relationship, European governments are rethinking their reliance on the United States as an ally, a potentially momentous shift that could eventually lead to new security arrangements independent of Washington, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>http://abc7.com/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live streaming video on ABC7.com and stay up-to-date with the latest KABC news broadcasts as well as live breaking news whenever it happens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN:  MUSK IS A TOTAL FRAUD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/21/elon-musk-is-a-total-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One disastrous tweet has finally revealed Elon Musk for what he is: a fraud. Enraged that a British cave diver called his idea to rescue the Thai soccer team for what it was — “a p.r. stunt [with] …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELLS FRIENDS:  HE'S UNFIT TO BE PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/michael-cohen-questions-trumps-fitness-to-be-president-e1ce27b0-414b-4e26-b135-4996687dc06e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things have been heating up since the tape was reported Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic researchers reverse wrinkles, gray hair and balding in mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/20/genetic-researchers-reverse-wrinkles-gray-hair-and/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science has made a mouse look good by reversing age-related wrinkles and hair loss at the genetic level. Humanity could get a similar make-over in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran transient hurled Chihuahua off 7th floor garage, jury says...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article215271300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wakeen Best, a 35-year-old homeless San Francisco woman, was found guilty of burglary and animal cruelty after throwing a Chihuahua seven stories off a parking garage during a car burglary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender Ax Attacker Blames Voices in Head, Demon Possession in Court Defense...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/transgender-ax-attacker-uses-drugs-demon-possession-to-defender-himself-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After vodka, ecstasy, and pot, the suspect heard a voice saying, "kill... and start the rise of hell on earth."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAST:  'Impeach Trump!'</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/movies/2018/07/21/fantastic-beasts-impeach-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The panel for Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald had a few surprises in store for Comic-Con's Hall H on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivers fascist speech in character ...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/johnny-depp-makes-surprise-comic-con-appearance-during-fantastic-beasts-panel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp surprised San Diego Comic-Con audiences in full character from "Fantastic Beasts," emerging after an embarrassing Rolling Stone article</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEPP FREAKOUT AT COMIC-CON...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/fantastic-beasts-new-trailer-arrives-at-comic-con-1128993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depp, dressed in character, delivered a creepy speech as Eddie Redmayne, Jude Law and Ezra Miller (as Super Mario's Toadette) looked on in Hall H.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP Poll:  Americans don't mention 'global warming' as problem...</title>
      <link>http://www.climatedepot.com/2018/07/21/new-gallup-poll-americans-do-not-even-mention-global-warming-as-a-problem-36-problems-cited-but-not-climate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba's new president names cabinet resembling Castro's...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cubas-president-names-cabinet-resembling-castros-175015115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba's new President Miguel Diaz-Canel named his cabinet on Saturday, keeping a majority of ministers from predecessor Raul Castro including in the key posts of defense, interior and foreign relations, signaling continuity rather than change. Diaz-Canel, 58, who replaced Castro in April, announced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Consultants to Get Dragged Into Manafort Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/20/democratic-consultants-to-get-dragged-into-paul-manafort-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Consultants to Get Dragged Into Paul Manafort Trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale sharks bigger than had been thought and can live 130 years, study finds...</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/whale-sharks-are-bigger-than-had-been-thought-and-can/article_71a44a50-96d1-5715-956c-a32ab69fa27b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Whale sharks, the largest of the shark species, can travel the ocean for up to 130 years and can grow as long as 61.7 feet, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba moves toward changes to officially recognize private property, foreign investment...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Cuba-moves-toward-changes-to-officially-recognize-13094090.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI - In communist Cuba, the right to own private property would be enshrined and foreign investment encouraged - and "guaranteed." Where Fidel Castro reigned as a towering 20th-century figure, power would no longer be concentrated in the hands of one ruler. Cuba's legislators are expected to take a major leap this weekend toward adopting those and other changes in the island nation's most significant bid for constitutional reform in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: Ecuador Will Imminently Withdraw Asylum for Assange...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/07/21/ecuador-will-imminently-withdraw-asylum-for-julian-assange-and-hand-him-over-to-the-uk-what-comes-next/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will journalists, due to hatred of Assange, unite behind the Trump DOJ in support of one of the gravest threats to press freedom in years?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tabloid in Middle of Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/21/us/politics/trump-michael-cohen-american-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors believe that American Media Inc. acted more as a political supporter than as a news organization as it helped Michael D. Cohen prevent embarrassing coverage of Donald J. Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked vacations gaining momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/better/pop-culture/why-travel-s-latest-trend-nacation-gaining-momentum-ncna893151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, 4.3 billion dollars was directly spent on nude travel in the state of Florida alone. Psychologists say the trend isn't surprising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation traces from Fukushima nuke disaster found in Californian wine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/718016/fukushima-nuclear-disaster-california-wine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-earning musicians mostly 'heritage artists'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/20/americas-top-earning-musicians-are-mostly-heritage-artists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You rock ’n’ rollers may be getting older — but you’re still shelling out big bucks for your favorite acts. In fact, of America’s 50 top-earning musical artists last year, 29 are considered “herita…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pampered pooch owns 3 sports cars, 175 pairs of sunglasses, 65 outfits...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/pampered-dog-owns-three-sports-12958353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Princess Cleopatra Superchill also feasts on steak for dinner and travels around in a £1,500 pram - so she doesn't get her paws dirty when out and about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare summer nor'easter expected to pound NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/21/rare-summer-noreaster-expected-to-pound-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will see heavy rainfall Saturday night as a rare July nor’easter passes through the tri-state area.​ The heaviest and steadiest rain will fall overnight and most of the city wil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia demands US release 'spy', calls charges false...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russia-demands-us-release-spy-calls-charges-false-155001279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov told his US counterpart Mike Pompeo on Saturday that the arrest of a Russian gun rights enthusiast on espionage charges in the United States was "unacceptable", his ministry said. US prosecutors say Maria Butina, 29, exploited her close links with the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super blood moon apocalypse: Bible prophecy predicts end of world 'days away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/716008/blood-moon-end-of-the-world-july-27-2018-bible-apocalypse-christian-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot human clones: Firm using 3D printers to scan, make replicas of people...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/717872/sex-robot-doll-human-clones-3d-printer-ds-doll-replicas-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midlife crisis myth? Life gets better after 50...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/jul/21/midlife-crisis-myth-life-gets-better-after-50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We don’t peak in middle age, say the experts. So forget about the stereotypes and embrace change</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
