<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bernie group hacked in quarter-million-dollar email scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/29/email-scammers-stole-berniesanders-backed-our-revolution-1023851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our Revolution had raised the money to help a Native American tribe fight an oil pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mudslide, flooding fears intensify as storm rolls across fire-scarred regions of CA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-rain-flood-warning-20181129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service issued a flood advisory early Thursday in areas recently scarred by devastating wildfires in Los Angeles and Ventura counties as steady rain continues to fall on the region heightening concerns over possible shallow mudslides and debris flow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen freed after being stuck in vault at abandoned bank...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dad616921bc44db2bc2bf21869fa0d8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOLLYWOOD, Fla. (AP) — Officials say a teen has been freed after spending more than three hours in the vault of an abandoned Florida bank. News outlets report that Hollywood firefighters tried to drill through a wall to break into the vault Wednesday afternoon after the 17-year-old's friend called 911. But they were stymied until a worker at the bank's new branch across the street heard of the predicament. That worker remembered the code and was able to open the vault's massive door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basketball broadcaster suspended for ripping team on-air...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/bigten/2018/11/28/iowa-hawkeyes-broadcaster-suspended-ripping-basketball-team-air/2146717002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime IowaÂ Hawkeyes basketball radio broadcaster Gary DolphinÂ has been suspended for two games afterÂ critical comments that were airedÂ Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Execs Coming to White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-house-to-hold-roundtable-with-tech-executives-1543511161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration will hold a roundtable on innovation with major tech executives, in a move that marks an easing of tensions between the White House and big Silicon Valley firms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA recruited Mafia gangster to 'whack' Fidel Castro...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6442951/CIA-recruited-Mafia-gangster-whack-Fidel-Castro-height-Cold-War.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new book tells the story of Chicago Outfit mobster Handsome Johnny Roselli. He was approached by the CIA to take down a common enemy, Fidel Castro, in the early 1960s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA and FORD accused of spying on citizens for Chinese govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/motors/7859854/tesla-ford-accused-car-giants-spying-citizens-chinese-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL car giants are feeding real-time information from electric vehicles to China’s ‘big brother’ government, it’s been reported. The revelations come as President Xi Jinp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Ma using AI to create dystopian cities?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/28/jack-ma-ai-dystopian-cities-communist-party-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News that Ma is a member of Communist party of China should set alarm bells ringing, says author Alfie Bown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA chief:  We will have permanent manned presence on moon within 10 years!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/418877-nasa-administrator-says-us-is-within-10-years-of-continuous-manned-presence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA Administrator Jim Bridenstine says the U.S. is within 10 years of having a continuous manned presence on the moon, which will lay the groundwork for expanding space exploration to Mars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER:  TRUMP'S GREAT WALL BECOMES TRUMP'S GREAT STALL...</title>
      <link>http://www.anncoulter.com/columns/2018-11-28.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.anncoulter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY's wealthiest cut losses as city's real estate languishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-yorks-wealthiest-cut-losses-as-manhattan-real-estate-falters-1543508960</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury homeowners struggle to accept the new reality of home prices falling after a decadelong property boom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Laser Dots Float on President's Chest and Face During White House Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/frightening-red-lazer-dots-float-on-president-trumps-chest-and-face-during-white-house-speech-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For 2020 Dems, There's a Lot of 'Thinking About It'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/29/us/politics/democrats-2020-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of possible 2020 Democratic candidates are mulling, weighing, considering, wondering. Here is a guide to how they are communicating a desire to run without announcing it outright.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says Cohen 'weak person' who is 'lying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6442641/Former-Trump-lawyer-Michael-Cohen-court-enter-new-guilty-plea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen, once a close Trump confidant and fixer, has publicly turned against the president since the FBI raided his home and offices in April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump denies working on Moscow real estate project...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-denies-working-moscow-real-estate-project-153846323.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday denied working on a Trump Organization real estate project in Moscow, which his former lawyer Michael Cohen said they had pursued until June 2016, during the presidential campaign. Cohen pleaded guilty on Thursday to making false statements to Congress regarding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Shares Plunge After Fake Putin Purge...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-29/twitter-shares-plunge-after-fake-putin-purge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAMILY DOLLAR shopper stabbed to death with knives plucked from store's shelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/family-dollar-shopper-stabbed-to-death-with-knives-plucked-from/article_559687b2-82af-5937-8d83-8ae2b6a5734f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police gave no motive, but said the two were strangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two San Diego teens killed execution-style in triple slaying in Tijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/sd-me-san-diego-teens-triple-murder-tijuana-execution-shooting-20181128-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two San Diego teenagers were shot and killed execution-style in a triple homicide Sunday morning at a Tijuana apartment complex, according to family members, school officials and Mexican media reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 'world's biggest cow' will NEVER stop growing... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7855872/worlds-biggest-cow-growth-genetic-disease-celeb-vet/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KNICKERS, the giant steer that is too beefy to be turned into a steak feast, may never stop growing, a celebrity vet has warned. The enormous 1.4-tonne beast which has been saved from getting the c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panama new flashpoint in China's growing presence in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/28/panama-china-us-latin-america-canal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spat over the site of China’s embassy has underlined the strategic value of the canal – through which two-thirds of ships to or from the US pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen Cooperation 'Nightmare' For President...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/us-attorney-reacts-to-michael-cohens-cooperation-with-mueller-worst-possible-legal-nightmare-for-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Speaker nomination, Pelosi slurs words, stutters during press remarks...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-pelosi-slurs-words-stutters-after-nominated-for-house-speaker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Nancy Pelosi was so overjoyed on Wednesday that she could hardly contain her face spasms. Democrats officially nominated Pelosi to become Speaker, setting up a full vote on the House floor in early January. The California Democrat was able to secure the support of her fellow House Democrats, but she had a hard time verbalizing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The croc whisperer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6441805/Monster-crocodiles-captured-terrifying-close-free-divers-swim-biting-range.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German videographer Florian Fischer, who has also worked with sharks and killer whales, filmed the American Saltwater Crocodiles while visiting the atoll reef Banco Chinchorro in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The humongous three-foot-high cockerel...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7847812/humongous-three-foot-high-cockerel-shacks-up-with-two-chickens-as-owner-branches-into-the-monster-egg-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GIANT cockerel who ruffled feathers when footage emerged of him towering over his poultry pals has moved into the egg business after shacking up with two chickens. The three-foot high bird –…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN commentator calls for elimination of Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/cnn-commentator-calls-for-elimination-of-israel-endorses-violent-palestinian-resistance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN commentator Marc Lamont Hill, in a Wednesday speech to the United Nations, called for violent resistance against Israel and advocated expanding Palestine “from the river to the sea,” a phrase used by those who believe that Israel should be eliminated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brokaw Accuser Calls on COMCAST to Hire 'Outside Counsel' to Investigate NBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tom-brokaw-accuser-calls-on-comcast-to-hire-outside-counsel-to-investigate-nbc-misconduct-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Sweeping problems under the rug should not be the corporate goal," says Linda Vester in a new Op-Ed published Wednesday on Fox News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-13 Member Busted...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/border-patrol-arrests-ms-13-member-migrant-caravan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honduran national Jose Villalobos-Jobel, 29, was arrested in the U.S. on Saturday and has admitted to membership in the gang, according to CPB officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family faces thousands in fines for Christmas light spectacle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-jersey-family-faces-thousands-in-fines-christmas-light-display/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price of spreading joy is skyrocketing, as some neighbors argue the display creates chaos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Claims Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/jobless-claims-increased-last-week-1543498386</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing applications for new unemployment benefits rose last week, but remained at a low level indicative of a tight labor market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male Birth Control Gel Nears...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/male-birth-control-moves-closer-as-u-s-tests-hormone-skin-gel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Male Birth Control Gel Is Getting Closer to Reality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'LL DOWNLOAD ON DEMS!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/28/trump-threatens-to-declassify-devastating-docs-about-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a wide-ranging, exclusive interview with The Post, President Trump said Wednesday that if House Democrats launched probes into his administration — which he called “presidential harassment” — th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replace condoms...</title>
      <link>/https://nypost.com/2018/11/28/male-birth-control-gel-could-replace-condoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA's 'first biometric terminal' ready to go at Atlanta airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/todayinthesky/2018/11/29/delta-usas-first-biometric-terminal-ready-go-atlanta-airport/2145655002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta says Atlanta's Terminal F has become 'first biometric terminal' in the USA where flyers can use facial recognition technology 'from curb to gate.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini ice age in months?</title>
      <link>https://www.iceagenow.info/mini-ice-age-in-a-matter-of-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iceagenow.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian website is concerned about the lack of sunspots. Here are excerpts: _________________ 26 Nov 2018 – Today’s lack of sunspots, characteristic of a solar minimum, could bring record low temperatures, but some experts suggest it could even produce a “mini ice age,” warns this article on mateoweb.eu. “Something unusual, but perhaps not so unusual ... Read moreMini ice age in a “matter of months”?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ramps up attacks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/418840-trump-ramps-up-attacks-on-mueller</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump started Thursday on Twitter the same way he ended it on Wednesday, attacking special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into Russia’s interference in the 2016 presidential election and possible collusion between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China halts work by team on gene-edited babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0be63430c5914f09a124b968c844d994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — China's government ordered a halt Thursday to work by a medical team that claimed to have helped make the world's first gene-edited babies, as a group of leading scientists declared that it's still too soon to try to make permanent changes to DNA that can be inherited by future generations. Chinese Vice Minister of Science and Technology Xu Nanping told state broadcaster CCTV that his ministry is strongly opposed to the efforts that reportedly produced twin girls born earlier this month. Xu called the team's actions illegal and unacceptable and said an investigation had been ordered, but made no mention of specific actions taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Car Hits Elephant, Animal Kills Driver...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eee71cdde33c45aabfcb427d7d94f9d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Police say a man was killed by a wild elephant after his speeding car hit the animal near a national park in northeastern Thailand. Police Lt. Col. Kemchat Paedkaew says the accident occurred at dusk Wednesday on a small road that has signs telling drivers to beware of wild animals that sometimes stray from Khao Yai National Park. He said the driver was not from the area and failed to slow down when he encountered the elephant. When the vehicle struck the elephant's back legs, the animal responded by stomping on the car, destroying the engine and killing the driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK mulled charging for access to user data...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181129-facebook-mulled-charging-access-user-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bull run finale not far off?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-stocks-global-poll/bull-run-finale-for-global-stocks-not-far-off-now-reuters-poll-idUSKCN1NY00L</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An end to the bull run in global stocks is not far away, according to a Reuters ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola epicenter hit with malaria outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/745154/ebola-malaria-double-epidemic-democratic-republic-of-kivu-world-health-organisation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2-FOOT-TALL squirrels in NCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article222294420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Carolina coast has a seldom seen breed of squirrel that is 2 feet tall and weighs as much as a chihuahua. A state camera trap program is capturing images of these fox squirrels in remote areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVERDOSES RECORD HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-life-expectancy-drops-again-overdoses-climb-055720445.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life expectancy in the United States dropped yet again as drug overdose deaths continued to climb -- taking more than 70,000 lives in 2017 -- and suicides rose, a US government report said Thursday. The drug overdose rate rose 9.6 percent compared to 2016, while suicides climbed 3.7 percent, said the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK, Computer: How Much Is House Worth?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ok-computer-how-much-is-my-house-worth-1543492800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal regulators have proposed loosening real-estate appraisal requirements to enable a majority of U.S. homes to be bought and sold without being evaluated by a licensed human appraiser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Abs, Hottest Workout for Fingers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/forget-your-washboard-abs-the-hottest-workout-is-for-your-fingers-1543422250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serious rock climbers train their digits by clinging to tiny ledges inches off the ground, lifting heavy grocery bags, and something called the ‘Transgression.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Watch adds years to life?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/apple-watch-could-add-two-years-life-research-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple watches could add two years to your life, a major study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUICIDES 50-YEAR PEAK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/de57909c5bcc4162b122948539ed9c6a </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Suicides and drug overdoses pushed up U.S. deaths last year, and drove a continuing decline in how long Americans are expected to live. Overall, there were more than 2.8 million U.S. deaths in 2017, or nearly 70,000 more than the previous year, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Thursday. It was the most deaths in a single year since the government began counting more than a century ago. The increase partly reflects the nation's growing and aging population. But it's deaths in younger age groups — particularly middle-aged people — that have had the largest impact on calculations of life expectancy, experts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If your TESLA knows where you are, Beijing may too...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4a749a4211904784826b45e812cff4ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHANGHAI (AP) — When Shan Junhua bought his white Tesla Model X, he knew it was a fast, beautiful car. What he didn't know is that Tesla constantly sends information about the precise location of his car to the Chinese government. Tesla is not alone. China has called upon all electric vehicle manufacturers in China to make the same kind of reports — potentially adding to the rich kit of surveillance tools available to the Chinese government as President Xi Jinping steps up the use of technology to track Chinese citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German antitrust agency opens AMAZON investigation...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-german-antitrust-agency-amazon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's antitrust agency says it has begun an investigation of online retailer Amazon to over complaints it's abusing its position to the detriment of sellers who use its "marketplace" platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE EXPECTANCY FALLS FURTHER</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-life-expectancy-falls-further-1543467660</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life expectancy for Americans fell again last year, despite growing recognition of the problems driving the decline and federal and local funds invested in stemming them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK Offices Searched in Money-Laundering Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/german-prosecutors-search-deutsche-bank-premises-over-money-laundering-probe-1543484932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank offices were searched by police and prosecutors seeking evidence in connection with alleged money laundering, the Frankfurt prosecutor’s office said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi, Backing Away From Plea Deal, Wants to Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/corsi-backing-away-from-plea-deal-wants-to-take-on-mueller</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corsi, Backing Away From Plea Deal, Wants to Take On Mueller</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jay-Z says panel 'too white' to be fair in trademark case...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/28/jay-z-says-panel-is-too-white-to-be-fair-in-trademark-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best-selling rapper and entrepreneur is suing to stop the American Arbitration Association from judging a trademark case, saying the panel is too lily-white to be fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Ma using AI to create dystopian cities?</title>
      <link>Jack Ma using AI to create dystopian cities?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Economy, Storm Clouds on Horizon...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/for-the-u-s-economy-storm-clouds-on-the-horizon/18025978/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Emerging signs of weakness in major economic sectors, including auto manufacturing, agriculture and home building, are prompting some forecasters to warn that one of the longest periods of economic growth in U.S. history may be approaching the end of its run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Bobbie Talks, I'm Finished': How Moonves Tried to Silence Accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraphindia.com/world/if-bobbie-talks-i-m-finished-how-cbs-boss-les-moonves-tried-to-silence-an-accuser/cid/1676977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraphindia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress recollected Moonves saying: “Be my girlfriend and I’ll put you on any show.” Then he grabbed her by the neck, pushed her to her knees and forced his penis into her mouth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORMY: Avenatti Filed Trump Defamation Case Against My Wishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/stormy-daniels-michael-avenatti-filed-defamation-case-against-trump-against-my-wishes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The porn star also says her lawyer refused to give her information about how her crowdfunding money was being spent, and launched a second crowdfund without her knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel investigating candidate Trump's late-night calls to Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Mueller-s-team-investigating-candidate-Trump-s-13429790.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The calls almost always came deep into the night. Caller ID labeled them "unknown," but Roger Stone said he knew to pick up fast during those harried months of the 2016 presidential campaign. There would be a good chance that the voice on the other end of the line would belong to his decadeslong friend - the restless, insomniac candidate Donald Trump - dialing from a blocked phone number. Those nocturnal chats and other contacts between the man who now occupies the Oval Office and an infamous political trickster have come under intensifying scrutiny as special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation bores into whether Stone served as a bridge between Trump and WikiLeaks as the group was publishing hacked Democratic emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani bragging may prove problematic...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2018/11/28/giulianis-bizarre-bragging-about-manafort-trump-alliance-raises-new-obstruction-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could Giuliani and Paul Manafort's lawyer get in any trouble?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glowing green fireball seen over Putin secret weapons lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7854332/mystery-glowing-green-fireball-top-secret-research-lab-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GLOWING green fireball buzzing over Russia’s hi-tech “scientific city” in Siberia has sparked claims Vladimir Putin could be developing space weapons. The bright flash and streaking tail was seen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Time to set record straight'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/stormy-daniels-says-michael-avenatti-sued-trump-defamation-against-her-n941446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a phone interview with NBC News, Avenatti said he was surprised by her allegations, and said "a number of things" were "not accurate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: PRESIDENT'S KEY ANSWERS MADE UNDER OATH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/trump-mueller-answers-wikileaks-trump-tower/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump told special counsel Robert Mueller in writing that Roger Stone did not tell him about WikiLeaks, nor was he told about the 2016 Trump Tower meeting between his son, campaign officials and a Russian lawyer promising dirt on Hillary Clinton, according to two sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff says written responses not adequate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/418807-schiff-says-trumps-written-responses-to-mueller-are-not-adequate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind man with seeing eye dog attacked on DC Metro...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/local/dc/18-year-old-juvenile-arrested-for-assault-of-blind-man-on-metro-red-line-train/65-618510816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The assault happened at the Rhode Island Avenue Metro Stop on the Red Line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half As Many Employees Protest China Censored Search As Protested Pentagon Project...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/28/google-employees-chinese-surveillance-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Don't be evil'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities raid TX Archdiocese, search for 'secret archives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Authorities-raid-Archdiocese-of-Galveston-Houston-13427999.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are raiding the offices of the Archdiocese of Galveston-Houston for additional evidence in the case of a Conroe priest accused of sexual misconduct, according to the Montgomery County District Attorney’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm terrorized by rhyme and riddle extortion; Barn burned, animals harmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/fbi-investigates-violence-threats-targeting-hollis-farm/25325208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials are investigating an extortion case involving a Hollis farm that they said has been the target of violence, threats and animal abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alien artifacts' may be lurking in solar system, Harvard astronomers claim...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/28/mysterious-alien-artefacts-could-be-lurking-in-our-solar-system-astronomer-claims-8185768/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stargazer says studying 'interstellar objects' which arrived here from deep space could allow us to discover proof of extraterrestrial life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online sex ads rebound after shutdown of BACKPAGE...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-online-sex-ads-rebound-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smaller escort websites are vying for the lucrative online sex-for-hire market Backpage.com dominated before U.S. authorities shut it down earlier this year, a move that fractured the industry and forced law enforcement to adapt their efforts combating sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger says DELTA pilot used GRINDR to hit on him DURING flight...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/28/passenger-says-delta-pilot-used-grindr-to-hit-on-him-during-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger onboard a Delta plane was creeped out after a pilot messaged him on Grindr during their flight. JP Thorn, a 27-year-old college student, told The Post that the strange interaction happe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian hackers charged with attacks on US cities...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2018/11/28/news/nation/justice-department-charges-iranian-hackers-with-attacks-on-us-cities-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defendants, Faramarz Shah Savandi and Mohammad Mehd Shah Mansouri, were charged with conspiring to hack victims between December 2015 and this month. The suspects are believed to be in Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alberto Gonzales: Problem With Perjury Traps...</title>
      <link>http://insider.foxnews.com/2018/11/28/alberto-gonzales-robert-mueller-setting-perjury-traps-would-be-unfair-and-unprofessional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;insider.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Attorney General Alberto Gonzales said that it'd be "unfair" and "unprofessional" for the special counsel's team to set perjury traps in its Russia probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-year-old dies after duo crash into her...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/90-year-old-woman-dies-collision-electric-scooter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 90-year-old Spanish woman has died after a collision with an electric scooter in what is believed to be the first accident of its kind in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Bobbie Talks, I'm Finished': How Moonves Tried to Silence Accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/28/business/les-moonves-bobbie-phillips-marv-dauer-cbs-severance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trove of text messages details a plan by Mr. Moonves and a faded Hollywood manager to bury a sexual assault allegation. Instead, the scheme helped sink the CBS chief, and may cost him $120 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mnuchin Says His TWITTER Was Compromised, Deletes GM Retweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-28/mnuchin-suggests-his-twitter-was-compromised-deletes-retweet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein returns -- at least on screen...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/sundance-film-festival-premieres-lineup-harvey-weinstein-movie-toni-morrison-miles-davis-dr-ruth-full-list-1202510342/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein is returning to the Sundance Film Festival, at least on screen. A looming and powerful presence at the Robert Redford founded huddle for decades, an Ursula MacFarlane directed docu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asked about RNC platform change regarding Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/mueller-asked-trump-2016-rnc-platform-change-ukraine/story?id=59476035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller asked Trump about 2016 RNC platform change regarding Ukraine: Sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems overwhelmingly nominate Pelosi as Speaker amid rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/418653-democrats-overwhelmingly-nominate-pelosi-as-speaker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats voted overwhelmingly Wednesday to nominate Rep. Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) to the Speakership in a 203-32 vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Helium Shortage Making Party Balloons Scarce...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/11/27/deflated-excitement-national-helium-shortage-making-party-balloons-hard-to-find/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nationally, helium is in demand for things more important than balloons right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data scientist cracks NYTIMES Best Seller list code...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/a-data-scientist-cracks-the-code-to-landing-on-the-new-york-times-best-seller-list-2018-11-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Write a mystery, romance or memoir. And publish in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB Slammed as 'Anti-Semitic'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/trump-admin-congress-slam-airbnb-boycott-israel-anti-semitic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent decision by Airbnb to stop its services for Jews living in the West Bank of Israel is being met with criticism by the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBERXXX: MAN WHO 'LIKED TO MASTURBATE IN FRONT OF DRIVERS' ARRESTED...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/indecent-exposure/the-sharing-economy-375902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iowa man was arrested today for allegedly exposing himself in an Uber car and telling the driver that he “liked to masturbate in front of Uber drivers,” according to a court complaint. Christopher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisoners sextort $500k from troops in dating app scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2018/11/28/prisoners-steal-more-than-500k-from-troops-through-dating-app-sextortion-ring/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NCIS agents executed arrest warrants Wednesday in connection to a sextortion ring that has victimized hundreds of service members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta postal workers busted delivering cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/postal-workers-took-bribes-deliver-cocaine-metro-atlanta/uHYRAe7ASqytzDBRReJFqO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixteen U.S. Postal Servies workers in metro Atlanta were sentenced for delivering cocaine in exchange for bribes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes poised to limit police power to seize property...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f60d5690704648edbf7a967cb6d6e8df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court left little doubt Wednesday that it would rule that the Constitution's ban on excessive fines applies to the states, an outcome that could help an Indiana man recover the $40,000 Land Rover police seized when they arrested him for selling about $400 worth of heroin. A decision in favor of 37-year-old Tyson Timbs, of Marion, Indiana, also could buttress efforts to limit the confiscation by local law enforcement of property belonging to someone suspected of a crime. Police and prosecutors often keep the proceeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Suspect Scrap Metal Thieves In Theft Of 300-Pound Menorah From Synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/28/menorah-stolen-brookline-temple-emeth-found-west-roxbury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Menorah stolen from a temple in Brookline was found in Boston Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATTIS:  'No smoking gun' linking to Khashoggi killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa-mattis-statement/u-s-defense-chief-no-smoking-gun-linking-saudi-crown-prince-to-khashoggi-killing-idUSKCN1NX2JE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary James Mattis said on Wednesday the United States has &amp;quo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Crashes On Highway -- While Watching NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/27/netflix-while-driving-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Patrol is reminding people not to Netflix and drive after a woman crashed her vehicle while watching the streaming service on her iPad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French film star Depardieu questioned in rape probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-film-star-depardieu-questioned-rape-probe-173951109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police have questioned film star Gerard Depardieu over allegations that he raped a young actress, which he strongly denies, a police source said Wednesday. The source said the 69-year-old actor attended a police interview on Tuesday and is not being kept in custody. "Gerard Depardieu absolutely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 78-year-old man may be most prolific serial killer in US history...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/78-old-man-may-most-prolific-serial-killer-180730498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 78-year-old drifter in prison in Texas has confessed to 90 murders and is being investigated as possibly the most prolific serial killer in US history. Samuel Little preyed mainly on drug addicts and prostitutes during a decades-long murder spree that stretched from coast to coast, the Federal Bureau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  White liberals dumb down vocabulary when speaking to minorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/nov/28/white-liberals-patronize-minorities-downplaying-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White liberals present themselves as less competent when addressing minorities, while conservatives use the same vocabulary no matter what the race of their audience, according to a newly released study.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
