<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul fears impeachment will 'dumb down' country...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/15/rand-paul-fears-donald-trump-impeachment-will-dumb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rand Paul, Kentucky Republican, said Sunday he worried that the Democratic effort to impeach President Trump would “dumb down and destroy the country.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOR YOUR CONSIDERATION:  Weinstein shares hospital pic in bid to prove he isn't faking it...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10555563/harvey-weinstein-hospital-photo-fake-injury-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARVEY Weinstein has released a photograph of himself sitting in a hospital room – in a bid to prove he is genuinely ill ahead of his trial. The image shows the disgraced movie mogul on the phone w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe calls on NASA for help as Mars mission runs into serious trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/europe-calls-nasa-help-mars-21103688</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ExoMars, and its robot rover Rosalind Franklin, may miss its launch window unless JPL engineers can fix some last minute bugs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland blizzard brings 149 mph winds, up to 10 feet of snow!</title>
      <link>https://www.columbian.com/news/2019/dec/12/iceland-blizzard-brings-149-mph-gusts-up-to-10-feet-of-mountain-snow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.columbian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of Iceland is digging out following a potent blizzard that brought winds topping 100 mph and yards of snow to some areas amid what one Icelandic meteorologist referred to as a “10-year storm.” As</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greta Thunberg Apologizes After Saying Politicians Should Be Put 'Against The Wall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/greta-thunberg-climate-activist-apologizes-for-against-the-wall-comment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thunberg says she was translating a Swedish saying into English and was not calling for violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:   50% say Trump should be impeached and removed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/474633-fox-news-poll-50-percent-of-americans-say-trump-should-be-impeached</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News poll released Sunday found half of Americans say President Trump should be impeached and removed from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions mount over French transport strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tensions-mount-over-french-transport-strike-053555853.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between the French government and unions opposed to pension reforms mounted on the 11th day of a crippling transport strike Sunday, with the prime minister warning the French would not tolerate being stranded at Christmas. The pensions overhaul, unveiled this week by Prime Minister Edouard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: FOXNEWS WILL DIE...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/14/trump-fox-news-comey-schiff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump once again attacked Fox News in a tweet Saturday night, accusing the network of trying to be &amp;quot;politically correct.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Pharma empire behind OxyContin now selling overdose cure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6751b84767e8a1ebbaea6cb628ac2a11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gleaming white booth towered over the medical conference in Italy in October, advertising a new brand of antidote for opioid overdoses. “Be prepared. Get naloxone. Save a life,” the slogan on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico objects over US bill on ratifying trade pact...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/319fb954f1c10ad1be50da18951d63be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Just days after a landmark agreement on a trade pact to replace the North American Free Trade Agreement, Mexico objected Saturday to legislation introduced in the U.S. Congress...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot link to psychosis, schizophrenia real, warn doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/12/15/weed-psychosis-high-thc-cause-suicide-schizophrenia/4168315002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government health officials say excessive use of today’s potent THC can lead to psychosis. Marijuana advocates say they can't be trusted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Bloomberg's Money Built a Political Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/mayors-for-mike-how-bloombergs-money-built-a-2020-political-network/ar-AAK7nlP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey admits error in FBI's FISA process: 'I was wrong'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/comey-defends-fbis-fisa-process-after-scathing-ig-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI Director James Comey admitted on "Fox News Sunday" that the recently released Justice Department Inspector General’s report on the launch of the FBI’s Russia investigation and their use of the surveillance process showed that he was "overconfident" when he defended his former agency's use of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act (FISA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivering the goods: Drones, robots making way to your door...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/delivering-the-goods-drones-and-robots-are-making-their-way-to-your-door/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With companies offering free shipping to gain a competitive edge, radical new technologies are being tested to cut the cost of the supply chain's expensive "last mile"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates fight DNC over debate rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/14/dnc-debate-qualifications-085083</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cory Booker and Julián Castro may not make the January and February debates under current rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Trump job approval ticks up, views on impeachment steady...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-poll-trump-job-approval-ticks-up-views-on-impeachment-steady</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weeks of congressional hearings and debate have failed to move the electorate on impeachment, according to the latest Fox News Poll.  At the same time, approval of President Trump’s job performance has climbed three points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden gaining momentum...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/474551-biden-gets-polling-boost-heading-into-next-democratic-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden appears to be gaining momentum in the polls ahead of Thursday’s Democratic presidential debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest UN climate talks end with no deal on carbon markets...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aca79ab4956f370b8892ba574fe56834</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Marathon international climate talks ended Sunday with major polluters resisting calls to ramp up efforts to keep global warming at bay and negotiators postponing the regulation of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative groups target 'Dirty 30'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/15/conservative-groups-wage-war-on-impeachment-083396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advocacy organizations are running ads against the House Democrats who represent districts that Donald Trump won in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills synagogue vandalized...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/vandalism-synagogue-beverly-hills-california-investigated-possible-hate-crime-n1102351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect overturned furniture and damaged several "Jewish relics," police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA SECRETLY EXPELS CHINESE DIPLOMATS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-secretly-expelled-chinese-officials-suspected-of-spying-after-breach-of-military-base/ar-AAK8JgO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lofty promises for autonomous cars unfulfilled...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lofty-promises-autonomous-cars-unfulfilled-014746257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first driverless cars were supposed to be deployed on the roads of American cities in 2019, but just a few days before the end of the year, the lofty promises of car manufacturers and Silicon Valley remain far from becoming reality. Recent accidents, such as those involving Tesla cars equipped with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more late fees for overdue books at LA's public library...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/12/13/los-angeles-public-library-to-eliminate-late-fines-starting-next-spring/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bibliophiles, rejoice: late fees are about to become a thing of the past at the Los Angeles Public Library. That's because the library has decided to end overdue fines on books and other items beginning next spring, Mayor Eric Garcetti announced Friday. When that happens, LAPL will become the largest public library in the nation to scrap the late fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scuffles break out at Rep. Schiff town hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-12-14/adam-schiff-armenian-town-hall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a town hall event where an Armenian organization was thanking U.S. government officials for their support of a resolution recognizing the Armenian Genocide, a scuffle broke out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German piglets 'sue over castration'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/little-piggy-went-court-german-piglets-sue-over-033201501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little piggies go to market, but in Germany they also go to court. In a legal first, animal rights activists have asked Germany's top court to ban the practice of castrating young male pigs without anaesthetic -- with the piglets themselves listed as the plaintiffs. Farmers argue that the castration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China state TV 'will no longer show ARSENAL match' after player's criticism...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/chinas-state-tv-will-no-longer-show-arsenal-match-after-mesut-ozil-remarks-11887171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The German midfielder criticised Beijing's policies towards its Uighur Muslim minority population on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houses of worship attacked with deadly frequency...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bab315d2e6851d2c118b838e0b1d1382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Dec. 1, a band of assailants opened fire on worshippers at a small-town Protestant church in Burkina Faso, an impoverished West African country where the Christian minority is increasingly a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALLMARK pulls gay-themed wedding ads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7926c82c3a646ebe73c13d98d1c43bd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Under pressure from a conservative advocacy group, The Hallmark Channel has pulled ads for a wedding-planning website that featured two brides kissing at the altar. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Commissioner's Wife Facing Charges for Pouring Drink on Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://allongeorgia.com/chattooga-local-government/video-commissioners-wife-facing-charges-for-assault-on-allongeorgia-reporter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;allongeorgia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wife of a county commissioner is facing criminal charges after an incident at a budget hearing Friday morning involving a reporter. The woman says the whole thing was an accident, but witness testimony and video evidence show the commissioner's wife saying the reporter 'deserved' it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academies probe 'white power' hand signs broadcast during Army-Navy game...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/15/army-navy-game-white-power-hand-signs-prompt-inves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army and Navy academies are looking into hand signs flashed by students that can be associated with “white power” and were televised during the Army-Navy football game on Saturday, school officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem impeachment critic planning to switch parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/14/jeff-van-drew-change-parties-085036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Jersey lawmaker is one of two Democrats who didn't back opening an impeachment inquiry into Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Dutch girls who seduced Nazis -- and lured them to deaths...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/14/meet-the-dutch-girls-who-seduced-nazis-and-lured-them-to-their-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When she came across a Nazi killing an infant by repeatedly swinging its tiny body against a brick wall, Truus Oversteegen didn’t flinch. The freckle-faced teenager, who was just three months shy o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Jones Says 'Fired' From Show For 'Wrong Message For Black America'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/orlando-jones-fired-american-gods-racism-gabrielle-union-fremantle-starz-neil-gaiman-1202809444/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tumultuous run of American Gods looks to have taken another turn, with Orlando Jones declaring he has been fired from the Starz series for having “the wrong message for black America.” In a vid…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
