<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FX Boss Landgraf Tears Apart NETFLIX Viewership Boasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/john-landgraf-netflix-ratings-not-remotely-accurate-fx/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has recently begun to release viewer data for its programming. Now FX boss John Landgraf is tearing about the service for boasting about ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squirrel on menu as diners turn to 'sustainable meat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/02/03/grey-squirrel-menu-diners-turn-wild-meat-help-boost-reds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are often an unwanted visitor to gardens, thanks to their reputation for raiding bird feeders and stripping trees of bark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash shows cockpit computers no substitute for pilot skills...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-lion-air-crash-20190204-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aviation experts say automated systems have made planes safer than ever and are a major reason why crash rates have declined all over the world. But they are also implicated in a series of incidents in which they made the wrong decisions and pilots did not fully understand the complex software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Ratings 'Myth'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/john-landgraf-smacks-down-netflix-ratings-myth-tca-1202549106/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FX CEO John Landgraf used his TCA appearance to take down Netflix’s release of selective — and, in his opinion, misleading — ratings information, as well as the reporters who swal…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious island didn't exist 4 years ago, now 'teeming with life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8350278/mysterious-island-that-didnt-exist-four-years-ago-is-now-teeming-with-life-sea-volcano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS volcanic island that suddenly burst from the Pacific Ocean is now teeming with life. The miracle outcrop known as Hunga Tonga has only existed for four years, yet creatures including h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY IN DIXIE</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/virginia/government-politics/updated-lt-gov-justin-fairfax-denies-sexual-assault-allegation-in/article_40dbcfef-5af6-5f91-9b4f-fa73050594d8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: After the Senate took a break, Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax addressed a swarm of reporters in the Capitol and said the woman alleging he'd assaulted her was lying in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo warns budget troubles as wealthy flee New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsday.com/news/region-state/state-budget-revenue-decline-1.26892647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuomo says he will have to revise his proposed budget as personal income tax collections drop $2.8 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORTHAM BEGS FOR POLITICAL LIFE</title>
      <link>https://wtkr.com/2019/02/04/embattled-northam-tells-cabinet-he-wont-resign-and-be-known-as-a-racist-for-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtkr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to that source, the governor specifically said that if he resigns, he would be resigning as a "racist for life," and that the only way he can clear his name is to stay in office and convince people that he is not in that photo and that the photo does not represent who he is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bettor X' loses nearly $3.8 million...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/bettor-x-lost-approximately-3-8-million-rams-super-bowl-loss-060611978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bettor X lost $3.8 million betting on the Rams on Sunday in the Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto investors locked out of $190,000,000 after exchange founder dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/feb/04/quadrigacx-canada-cryptocurrency-exchange-locked-gerald-cotten</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QuadrigaCX, Canada’s largest exchange, was unable to access password or recovery key after Gerald Cotten died last December</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danger as 'predictive data' threatens personal autonomy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/why-data-not-privacy-real-danger-n966621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While it's creepy to imagine companies are listening in to your conversations, it's perhaps more creepy that they can predict what you’re talking about without actually listening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of Mueller probe to push DOJ towards battle with Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/end-of-mueller-investigation-could-spark-battle-between-justice-dept-and-congress-over-release-of-special-counsels-report/ar-BBTaJgH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shocking' rise in obesity-related cancers among young adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/obesity-related-cancers-rising-fastest-among-millennials-study-finds-n966656</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study could be a warning that if the obesity epidemic continues, fat-sensitive cancers will explode in the years to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gut feeling: Depression linked to digestive bacteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190204-gut-feeling-study-links-depression-digestive-bacteria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gut feeling: study links depression to digestive bacteria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mystery of Pelosi's Favorite Bible Verse: Not in Bible...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/human-interest/2019/02/nancy-pelosi-bible-quote-minister-needs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the next best thing to the Prophet Isaiah himself appearing on the House floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liam Neeson says he wanted to kill a 'black b*st*rd' after friend's rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/liam-neeson-rape-black-man-attack-cosh-cold-pursuit-sexual-assault-interview-a8760866.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphic details published...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/washpost-pushes-back-against-justin-fairfax-statement-on-sexual-assault-allegation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graphic new details are emerging about a newly revealed allegation of sexual assault against Virginia Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax, as The Washington Post pushes back against Fairfax’s claim that the newspaper found serious problems with the original accusation when it initially opted not to publish the account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Half-Dozen Attend Draft Beto Event...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/hardly-anyone-attended-a-draftbeto-event-in-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  50% of Virginia Dems Approve Of Governor...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/02/04/virginia-voters-quickly-sour-on-northam-amid-blackface-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in Virginia have soured on Gov. Ralph Northam (D-Va.) in the immediate aftermath of the blackface scandal that has many leaders, including top Democrats, calling for him to resign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disbelief' In White House After Trump Schedule Leak...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/04/white-house-disgust-trump-executive-schedule-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Aghast and disgusted'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US preps to start building portion of Texas border wall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e653d5a305114835bb399e480ac44ab8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — The U.S. government is preparing to begin construction of more border walls and fencing in South Texas' Rio Grande Valley, likely on federally owned land set aside as wildlife refuge property. Heavy construction equipment was expected to arrive starting Monday, U.S. Customs and Border Protection said. A photo posted by the nonprofit National Butterfly Center shows an excavator parked next to its property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy Scouts inaugurate first all-girls troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/2/first-all-girl-troops-welcomed-boy-scouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., marked the end — and the beginning — of an era this weekend when the Boy Scouts of America established its first all-girl troops in the nation’s capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise and fall of 'El Chapo,' Mexico's most wanted kingpin...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-mexico-el-chapo-profile/the-rise-and-fall-of-el-chapo-mexicos-most-wanted-kingpin-idUSKCN1PT1XS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman is Mexico's most notorious kingpin who ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN anchor fired for leaking plans to sue...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/04/adnan-virk-plots-espn-lawsuit-after-firing-over-mlb-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fired ESPN anchor Adnan Virk is pursuing legal action against his ex-employer, sources have told The Post. Virk was let go Friday after being accused of leaking confidential information on multiple…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military steps in as Australia floods bring crocs to streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/military-steps-australia-floods-bring-crocs-streets-021942887.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's military has been deployed to tackle devastating "once-in-a-century" floods that have inundated homes, schools and airports in the country's northeast, forcing hundreds to flee and bringing crocodiles onto the streets. The Australian Defence Forces delivered 70,000 sandbags</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Stop Man In Brady Jersey Sneaking Into PATS Locker Room...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/02/04/video-shows-police-stopping-man-in-tom-brady-jersey-trying-sneak-into-patriots-locker-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cell phone video appears to show a Patriots fan with a security jacket trying to sneak into the team's Super Bowl locker room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspense Novelist's Trail of Deceptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2019/02/11/a-suspense-novelists-trail-of-deceptions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan Mallory, who writes under the name A. J. Finn, went to No. 1 with his début thriller, “The Woman in the Window.” His life contains even stranger twists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marie Kondo and the rise of clutter shaming...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/820681/marie-kondo-rise-clutter-shaming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In defense of stuff, and having a lot of it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: GANNETT turns down hedge fund buyout...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ca7b9e1e8f44e7db36db523b996c201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The publisher of USA Today and dozens of other newspapers said no to a hedge-fund backed media group with a reputation for slashing jobs, but the buyout fight may not be over. Gannett on Monday said its board has unanimously rejected an unsolicited $1.36 billion buyout from MNG Enterprises , better known as Digital First Media. Digital First then said that it might nominate new Gannett board directors to consider its offer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  CNN OVER FOX; DRUDGE OVER GOOGLENEWS; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Era's Biggest Winner: Jeff Bezos, Presidential Nemesis!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-04/trump-era-s-biggest-winner-is-jeff-bezos-presidential-nemesis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Navy has new weapon that makes targets hallucinate, vomit...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/428346-russian-navy-has-new-weapon-that-makes-target-hallucinate-and-vomit-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian Navy reportedly has a new weapon that can disrupt the eyesight of targets as well as make them hallucinate and vomit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why no one really quits GOOGLE or FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2019/02/04/why-no-one-really-quits-google-or-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another week, another set of scandals at Facebook and Google. This past week, my colleagues reported that Facebook and Google had abused Apple enterprise developer certificates in order to distribute info-scraping research apps, at times from underage users in the case of Facebook. Apple responded …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hate maps' and 'hate groups'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/splc-hires-high-powered-defamation-lawyer-to-defend-tax-exempt-status-in-rico-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-Left smear factory seems to be taking the threat seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASH:  SUPER BOWL RATINGS 10-YEAR LOW...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/super-bowl-ratings-patriots-rams-marron-5-worlds-best-cbs-1202548893/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots’ 13-3 victory over the Los Angeles Rams last night wasn’t the most exciting Super Bowl ever played by any measure, but the 2019 NFL championship game was sure o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In year of the pig, Hong Kong debates its boar problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pig-perfect-hong-kong-review-boar-problem-070359548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — It may be the year of the pig, but Hong Kong has had enough of the wild ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Biden in lead...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/4/joe-biden-is-democratic-front-runner-in-iowa-caucu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joseph R. Biden is the strongest Democratic contender for the Iowa primary, according to a new poll of likely caucusgoers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going to Be War Within Party'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/02/04/the-insurgents-behind-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-224542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who are the Justice Democrats—and do they care if they blow their own party up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp demographic divides in economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksl.com/article/46483289/ap-norc-poll-how-financial-security-varies-by-age-income?print=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just how financially secure you feel depends on your age, your race, your education and — perhaps not surprisingly — your income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Methodists face vote on LGBTQ issues. Will it rip church apart?</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/nation-world/sns-tns-bc-relig-methodists-lgbtq-20190204-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLLEYVILLE, Texas On a Tuesday in January, pastor Katie Lewis was surprised to have even 26 members of the United Methodist Church of Colleyville attend her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER SUED  -- AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/roncoleman/status/1092432360640000000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Full copy of the complaint in McInnes v. SPLC https://t.co/QYWS237DbN https://t.co/6BOa4LZRXz”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous cars aren't coming anytime soon; rattled consumers...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/5-reasons-why-autonomous-cars-150448399.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of autonomous vehicles, Pittsburgh and Silicon Valley are bustling hubs of development and testing. The fatal crash in Arizona involving an Uber autonomous vehicle in March slowed progress, largely because it hurt the public's perception of the safety of vehicles. Google's Waymo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'YOUNG AND RESTLESS' star found dead at home...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/02/04/the-young-and-the-restless-star-kristoff-st-john-dead-at-52/?_ga=2.172586403.1075717749.1549231653-124232095.1548706750</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No cause of death has been revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads Lecture America...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/03/super-bowl-ads-lecture-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WaPo Took out an ad promoting the free press</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREATEST</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf0c0abdfc584bde84422d3bed2d524c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Graying but still gritty, Tom Brady, Bill Belichick and the Patriots came to the Super Bowl intending to stave off, for at least one more game, the inevitable onslaught of the NFL's future. Job well done. Pro football never looked flatter, older and more stuck in the days of the VCR than it did Sunday. In a Super Bowl only New England could love, the Patriots won their sixth title by lumbering their way to a 13-3 victory over the Los Angeles Rams — that young, brash, high-flying team with the 33-year-old coach and the 24-year-old quarterback who were, we thought, changing football before our very eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns against 'fake news'... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0ddb190d6c3d46a0be910aadf61e3564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABU DHABI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The Latest on Pope Francis's visit to the United Arab Emirates (all times local): 8 p.m. The head of Sunni Islam's highest seat of learning has told an audience that includes Pope Francis and hundreds of other religious figures from around the world that Islam is a religion of peace that values human life. At an event Monday evening during the first-ever papal visit to the Gulf, Sheikh Ahmed el-Tayeb, the head of Al-Azhar, quoted numerous Quranic verses about the value of life, including one that says: "Whoever kills a person it is as though he has killed all mankind. And whoever saves a life, it is as though he had saved all mankind." The grand mufti said all faiths denounce terrorism in all its forms and that acts of terrorism are carried out by criminals, not by true believers of God. The sheikh said that after the 9/11 attacks the media made Islam look like a "bloodthirsty" religion and that Muslims paid a heavy price for the acts of a few. He spoke after the Muslim Council of Elders and the pope met for an interreligious dialogue that recognized efforts by the pope and al-Tayeb to foster peace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'YOUNG AND RESTLESS' star found dead at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/04/kristoff-st-john-dead-dies-alcohol-young-and-the-restless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kristoff St. John, longtime 'Y&amp;R' soap opera star, was found dead Sunday at his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous Oscar Voter Blasts 'Smear Campaigns' Against 'GREEN BOOK,' 'BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/anonymous-oscar-voters-blasts-smear-campaigns-against-green-book-and-bohemian-rhapsody</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the fifth consecutive year, an Oscar voter spills all to Michael Musto, from their thoughts on the ‘Green Book’ and ‘Bohemian Rhapsody’ controversies to the hosting fiasco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran said to mount 'guided warheads' on missiles capable of reaching Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.i24news.tv/en/news/international/middle-east/194580-190204-iran-said-to-mount-guided-warheads-on-missiles-capable-of-reaching-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.i24news.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celery juice new health miracle?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/beauty/body/celery-juice-new-health-miracle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The green stuff is having a moment in the spotlight, but is it all it&amp;rsquo;s cracked up to be?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Troll...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/saints/2019/02/new-england-wins-the-super-bowl-but-new-orleans-wins-the-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City's day of protest steals the spotlight from world's biggest sporting event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATTKISSON: Intel op against president going strong...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/428288-intel-operation-against-trump-still-going-strong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the newest press salvo, unnamed intel officials fanned out to air anonymous grievances against their commander-in-chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Take Over Commercials...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/03/robots-super-bowl-ads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are they trying to tell us something?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak the rich? Americans say go for it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/04/democrats-taxes-economy-policy-2020-1144874</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Policies once seen as far-left enjoy broad support in polling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Man wants to sue parents for giving birth 'without his consent'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6664843/Man-wants-sue-parents-giving-birth-without-consent.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raphael Samuel from Mumbai - pictured in a post on his anti-natalist Facebook page - said he had a 'great relationship' with his parents but has compared having children to 'kidnapping and slavery'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first floating tunnel...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/beta-story-container/International/crossing-norways-fjords-easier-worlds-submerged-floating-tunnel/story?id=60812122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tunnel would sit about 100 feet below the surface of a fjord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Startup Takes Microbes From Volcano to Table...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/food-startup-takes-microbes-from-the-volcano-to-the-table-11549256460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sustainable Bioproducts LLC is working on doing just that, using NASA-funded research on microbes that have evolved to withstand some of the harshest environments on earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who accused John of God of rape mysteriously kills self...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8346590/activist-probe-arrest-rapist-john-of-god-commits-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ACTIVIST whose claims led to the “rape” arrest of a celebrity healer called John of God has taken her own life at her hideaway in Spain. Sex abuse support group Victimas Unidas, whic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shocking' rise in obesity-related cancers among young adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/02/04/shocking-rise-obesity-related-cancers-among-young-adults/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rates of obesity-fuelled cancers are now rising in successively younger age groups, a landmark study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In conservative Catholic Poland, gay and atheist politician seizing moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-conservative-Catholic-Poland-a-gay-and-13586751.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SZCZECIN, Poland - When left-wing Polish politician Robert Biedron celebrated late last year that his party was polling at almost 10 percent, it was surprising in more than just one way. For one, Biedron's party did not yet exist. With no name or agenda and almost two years to go until presidential elections, he had nevertheless embarked on an improvised road trip across Poland to rally crowds for his cause. Speaking in shopping centers or community halls, the 42 year-old was being welcomed by mostly young and urban audiences, who applauded his demands to separate church and state, phase out coal and improve LGBT and women's rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten quakes strike coast of Northern California in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/napa-northern-california-earthquake/article/earthquakes-ten-norcal-coast-eureka-petrolia-usgs-13585870.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten earthquakes of preliminary magnitudes between 3.0 and 4.5 struck off the coast of Northern California between Saturday and Sunday, the United States Geological Survey reports.  The series of earthquakes rumbled beneath the Pacific Ocean, between 3 miles and 27 miles west of Petrolia in Humboldt County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Tackled Subway Crime. But Starting to Come Back?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/04/nyregion/nyc-subway-crime.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transit crime rose by nearly 4 percent last year. New Yorkers are worried about their safety on the system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blew lid on 'sex slave farm'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6664777/Woman-arrest-John-God-takes-life.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sabrina Bittencourt (pictured), 38, died at her home in Barcelona just days after accusing Brazilian faith healer John of God - real name Joao Teixeira de Faria - of running a 'sex slave farm'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Ops suicides triple...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/02/politics/socom-military-suicide-spike-2018/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicides among active duty military personnel assigned to US Special Operations Command tripled in 2018, in a disturbing and as yet unexplained spike, CNN has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk shows off SPACEX dazzling Raptor rocket engine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/spacex-raptor-rocket-engine-dazzles-with-first-test-firing-elon-musk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Raptor engine is designed to power Starship to our lunar neighbor and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUAWEI Sting Offers Rare Glimpse of USA Targeting Chinese Giant...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/huawei-sting-offers-rare-glimpse-of-u-s-targeting-chinese-giant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. believes Huawei poses a national security threat, in part, because it could build undetectable backdoors into 5G technology.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign takes steps to prevent challenge within GOP...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/33438efb7d794b5caf0b60f815192500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Worried about a potential Republican primary challenge, President Donald Trump's campaign has launched a state-by-state effort to prevent an intraparty fight that could spill over into the general-election campaign. The nascent initiative has been an intense focus in recent weeks and includes taking steps to change state party rules, crowd out potential rivals and quell any early signs of opposition that could embarrass the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty. Boring. Basic. Sleepy. Skippable. Unfulfilling. Unnecessary...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2b96498bcd8e4e129a1a5f087b5c3fd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are a number of words you could use to describe Maroon 5's halftime show performance: Empty. Boring. Basic. Sleepy. Skippable. Unfulfilling. Unnecessary. And those who came to help save the day didn't do their jobs: If you blinked you would have missed that Travis Scott and Big Boi performed. Even the gospel choir singer was a struggle — clearly they let the wrong one sing lead Sunday. Adam Levine and friends kicked off the performance as fireworks burst from a stage designed like the letter "M," which should have stood for "magic," because they needed some.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal injuries in wild hit record high...</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/environment/animal-injuries-in-the-wild-hit-record-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii considers ban on cigarette sales...</title>
      <link>https://abc30.com/society/hawaii-considers-ban-on-cigarette-sales/5119182/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc30.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii is flirting with the idea of becoming the first state to ban the sale of cigarettes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI warns if partner in argumentative mood...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/ai-system-warn-you-your-13950005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The system monitors and tracks a user’s emotional state, and could soon be used to flag if your partner is in an argumentative mood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men who live on main road 'more likely to struggle to get erection'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6664915/Men-live-main-road-likely-struggle-erection.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of rats were exposed to polluted air over a few months in a Chinese study. Their ability to get an erection was 'significantly reduced', according to scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREATEST</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/super-bowl-liii-rams-patriots-live-updates-score-halftime-show-commercials-today-2019-02-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots have won their sixth NFL championship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWFLAKE HITS OUT. DUMBO FEARS HE'S NEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/02/new-york-times-mary-poppins-racist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may never see the 1964 film “Mary Poppins” on television again – now that the New York Times has labeled it racist. In a piece for the paper by Professor Daniel Pollack-Pelzner, criticizes one of the film’s iconic moments, when Mary Poppins joins Dick Van Dyke’s Bert to dance on a rooftop for the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6!</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001016157/article/patriots-defeat-rams-133-in-super-bowl-liii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A low-scoring affair has returned the Patriots to the throne of pro football. New England defeated the Los Angeles Rams 13-3 in Super Bowl LIII on Sunday in Atlanta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lowest-scoring Super Bowl EVER...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/25918235/patriots-rams-combine-16-points-lowest-scoring-super-bowl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots took a 3-0 lead over the Los Angeles Rams into halftime, as the teams combined for the second-lowest-scoring half in Super Bowl history on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY, THE GREATEST</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/02/03/patriots-outlast-rams-in-win-sixth-super-bowl-franchise-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No, this is not a misprint. The New England Patriots are champions. Again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, JANET JACKSON:  Adam Levin shows his breasts during halftime show!</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/03/maroon-5-super-bowl-liii-halftime-show-shirtless-adam-levine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Levine sizzles during the Super Bowl halftime show ... shirtless, no less.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott Events in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/boycott-bowl-events-happening-in-new-orleans-sunday/26120355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a growing list of events happening around the New Orleans area where you can still show your support for the Black and Gold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male cheerleaders make history...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/8345660/super-bowl-male-cheerleaders-wow-crowd-la-rams-new-england-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Super Bowl’s first ever male cheerleaders took to the field tonight to wow the crowds as the epic clash kicked off in Atlanta. Quinton Peron and Napoleon Jinnies – who cheer for the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN anchor fired for leaking company information...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/03/rising-espn-star-adnan-virk-fired-escorted-out-in-leak-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN rising star Adnan Virk has been fired by the network, sources told The Post. Virk is accused of leaking confidential company information to the media on multiple occasions, according to source…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gladys Knight stuns crowds with exquisite national anthem...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/8345367/super-bowl-national-anthem-gladys-knight-star-spangled-banner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLADYS Knight stunned the crowds at the Super Bowl stadium tonight with her soulful rendition of the national anthem. The Empress of Soul had the audience in tears as she sang the Star-Spangled Ban…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM TOLD TO PURGE SUICIDE IMAGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2019/02/03/duty-care-matt-hancock-prepares-tell-instagram-boss-purge-site/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Health Secretary will tell the boss of Instagram he must use his experience of rooting out terrorist-related posts to purge the social media site of suicide and self-harm images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY POPPINS CALLED RACIST!  </title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/us-academic-sparks-mary-poppins-blackface-row-a4056126.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The classic family film Mary Poppins has been branded racist by a US academic who accuses Dame Julie Andrews of 'blacking up' with soot while dancing with chimney sweeps. In a piece for the New York Times, Professor Daniel Pollack-Pelzner criticises one of the film's iconic moments, when Mary Poppins joins Dick Van Dyke's Bert to dance on a rooftop for the classic song Step in Time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5G: Expert warns superfast broadband could cause cancer in humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/757194/5g-wireless-network-deadly-cancer-Arthur-Robert-Firstenberg-technology-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dementia patients to be tracked by smart meters in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6663779/Dementia-patients-tracked-smart-meters-doctors-monitor-sudden-changes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ministers have promised to install the devices in every home by 2020 to reduce energy consumption, but the rollout is massively over budget and behind schedule. Critics also warn of huge privacy concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-super-bowl/0ap3000001016001/Gladys-Knight-performs-National-Anthem-at-SBLIII</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gladys Knight sings the National Anthem at Super Bowl LIII.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
