<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Snowden questioned veracity of reports about 'invasion' of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>http://www.china.org.cn/world/2022-02/16/content_78051824.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.china.org.cn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADOLF PUTIN graffiti sprayed across buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4775344/russia-ukraine-news-protests-vladimir-putin-hitler/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURIOUS Russians protesting Vladimir Putin’s violent invasion of Ukraine have scrawled graffiti comparing their hardman President to Nazi monster Adolf Hitler. Demonstrations against Russia&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA TO INSTALL OWN GOVT</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2638540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A senior defense official told reporters that the Pentagon view is that Russia intends to “decapitate” the government of Ukraine and install its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First pandemic, then recession, now, WAR. Anything else, world?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-pandemic-then-recession-now-235415083.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A war in Ukraine and a looming humanitarian crisis triggered fresh anxiety and depression for Americans who have endured two years of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe says it has 'financial nuclear weapon'. But  uncertain if it wants to use it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/europe-says-it-has-a-financial-nuclear-weapon-against-russia-but-it-s-uncertain-if-it-wants-to-use-it/ar-AAUjDEJ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA KEEPS MASK ORDER FOR ALL FLIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/catching-a-flight-you-ll-still-need-a-mask-despite-the-cdc-s-new-guidance/ar-AAUjGzQ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some records taken by The Don are so sensitive they may not be described in public...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/some-records-taken-by-trump-are-so-sensitive-they-may-not-be-described-in-public/ar-AAUi7On?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden nominates Ketanji Brown Jackson to be first Black woman to sit on Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/supreme-court-ketanji-brown-jackson/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden nominated Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Friday, setting in motion a historic confirmation process for the first Black woman to sit on the highest court in the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands arrested at anti-war demonstrations in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/photos-people-protest-russia-war-against-ukraine-c7fecd0e-6dfe-436f-8959-7016797ceeca.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people around the world gathered for protests against Russia's invasion of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump NY criminal probe has new prosecutor after lawyers quit...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-york-criminal-probe-prosecutor-163522880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new prosecutor has been chosen to lead a criminal probe into former U.S. President Donald Trump, the Manhattan district attorney's office said on Friday, after the departures of two top lawyers threw the investigation's future into question. Susan Hoffinger will now lead the probe into Trump and the practices of his family business, the Trump Organization, according to Danielle Filson, a spokeswoman for Alvin Bragg, the Manhattan district attorney. This week Special Counsel Carey Dunne and Mark Pomerantz - who had been leading the probe begun by former District Attorney Cyrus Vance - resigned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Snowden questioned veracity of reports about 'invasion' of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://news.cgtn.com/news/2022-02-16/Snowden-questions-veracity-of-reports-about-invasion-of-Ukraine-17GQHqbF3NK/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.cgtn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Gauge Highest Since '82, and War Could Make WORSE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-prices-inflation-e44ad9b2088aa352015868a4f6b17785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An inflation gauge that is closely monitored by the Federal Reserve jumped 6.1% in January compared with a year ago, the latest evidence that Americans are enduring sharp price increases that will likely worsen after Russia's invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After decades of lobbying, supporters say they have votes in House to pass reparations bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2022/02/25/reparations-bill-congress-support/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;H.R. 40 would create a commission on reparations for Black Americans modeled on the process Japanese Americans went through to receive reparations for being imprisoned in internment camps during World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death By Robots? Automation Ruining Lives, Raising Mortality Rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/death-by-robots-automation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found automation in manufacturing companies is linked to a rise of suicides and drug overdoses among working-class adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS in AZ unionizes, dealing blow to coffee chain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/25/starbucks-restaurant-in-mesa-arizona-votes-to-unionize.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's now the third company-owned Starbucks location to vote in support of unionizing and the first outside of the Buffalo, New York, area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$6 a gallon? At least 1 gas station in LA hits mark...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/gas-prices-over-6-dollars/11599980/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average price of gas in Los Angeles County has risen to $4.848 a gallon, but one station near the Beverly Center has topped out at over $6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Unveil 'Unified Genealogy of Modern and Ancient Humans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epxqzp/scientists-unveil-unified-genealogy-of-modern-and-ancient-humans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 3,600 individual genome sequences that date back more than 100,000 years, it is largest human family tree ever created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of international law...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/article-698654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The narrative that democracy and international law were on the rise has now been squashed by Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Vax Pass Quietly Rolled Out -- And Red States Getting On Board...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/suzannerowankelleher/2022/02/24/national-vaccine-quietly-rolled-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of all US states now make the SMART Health Card accessible to their residents or have plans to do so soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Adults Over 60 Feel 'Unseen' In Society Due To Their Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/adults-over-60-feel-unseen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A OnePoll study of 2,000 British adults found those in their seventh decade feel most ignored when clothes shopping, going out to dinner, or having a drink at a bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Cuomo TV ads to air as gov seeks redemption...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pro-andrew-cuomo-tv-ads-to-air-on-monday-as-governor-seeks-redemption/ar-AAUjl1C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True scale of homeless crisis on subway revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10552293/NYC-transit-officials-say-350-homeless-people-living-89-subway-stations-tunnels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of homeless people were found camping out in New York City's subway tunnels and stations earlier this month, MTA officials said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Jets, Superyachts Roam Free as Ukraine Attack Rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/russian-billionaire-jets-and-superyachts-roam-free-as-ukraine-attack-rages/ar-AAUjrwo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of new Europe 'iron curtain'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220225-russia-attack-conjures-up-fears-of-new-europe-iron-curtain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's attack on Ukraine could herald a Cold War revival in Europe with two blocs armed to the teeth pointing nuclear weapons at each other across an iron curtain, politicians and experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang claims ransomware attack on MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10553013/Russia-linked-hacker-gang-claims-ransomware-attack-McDonalds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hacker gang Snatch on Friday claimed to have stolen 500 gigabytes of data from the fast-food giant headquartered in Chicago, posting their demand for a ransom on the dark web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At-Home Abortion Demand Skyrocketed Since Texas Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgd7g3/abortion-pill-texas-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group that helps people perform their own abortions initially saw a 1180 percent increase in requests for help from Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Readies 'father of all bombs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10552743/Furious-Putin-prepares-use-father-bombs-brave-Ukrainians-hold-advance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They fear Vladimir Putin could resort to high-power thermobaric weapons - dubbed the 'father of all bombs' - as brave Ukrainians resist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA imposes sanctions on Vlad...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/25/us-to-impose-sanctions-on-vladimir-putin-and-top-aide-white-house-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States will impose a slate of sanctions on Russian President Vladimir Putin and Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC relaxes indoor mask guidelines...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/25/cdc-relaxes-indoor-mask-guidelines-as-covid-cases-in-us-drop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC relaxed their mask guidelines Friday after the agency acknowledged the risk of severe COVID-19 cases has gone down as the Biden administration moves to shift its focus on how it’ll manage t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITISH AIR suffers major outage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-british-airways-suffers-major-26333636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers are having problems at Heathrow Airport tonight as British Airways suffers a big outage, causing the website to fail and flights to be grounded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Z' tank flies Soviet flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17774640/russian-tank-flies-soviet-union-flag-ukraine-ussr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN ‘Z’ tank has been spotted displaying the old flag of the Soviet Union as claims continue to say Vladimir Putin wants to “rebuild the USSR”. Exactly where the footage was filmed it not kno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why sexual identities shifted during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20220224-why-sexual-identities-shifted-during-the-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With time to contemplate and reassess, some people have begun exploring new sexual identities and other desires “beyond the binary”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 more foreign ships hit in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://splash247.com/two-more-ships-hit-in-the-black-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;splash247.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another two ships have been hit by missiles in the Black Sea: the Moldova-flagged chemical tanker Millennial Spirit and the Panama-flagged bulk carrier Namura Queen. The 1974-built Millennial Spirit, formerly Freyja, was fired upon by a Russian Navy ship 12 nautical miles south of Ukraine’s Yuzhniy port, the General Staff of the Armed Forces of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gang threatens countries that punish Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/25/russian-ransomware-gang-threatens-countries-ukraine-00011896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security experts have warned that any cyberattacks on Russia could prompt digital retaliation by either Moscow or sympathetic criminal hackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health ministry docs: Preparing for major medical event...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2022-02-25/russian-health-ministry-documents-show-how-russia-is-preparing-for-casualties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The document indicates Russia is anticipating a massive medical emergency and has ordered health organisations to identify medical staff ready to relocate. | ITV National News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knee pain sidelines Pope...</title>
      <link>https://www.wric.com/news/u-s-world/pope-nixes-florence-visit-ash-wednesday-due-to-knee-pain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wric.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis has canceled a scheduled Sunday visit to Florence and will not preside over Ash Wednesday commemorations next week because of what the Vatican described Friday as a flareup…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Navy Launches Amphibious Assault...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2022/02/25/russian-navy-launches-amphibious-assault-on-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia launched an amphibious assault on Ukraine, bringing in thousands of naval personnel ashore, a senior defense official said Friday. The amphibious assault is underway into Ukraine, through the Sea of Azov, coming into west of Mariupol, the senior defense official told reporters. Until now, the Russian navy largely played a supporting role in the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero Ukrainian soldier blows himself up to destroy bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4771553/ukrainian-soldier-dies-blowing-up-bridge-russian-tanks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HERO Ukrainian soldier blew himself up to destroy a bridge and stop Russian forces from storming in from Crimea. Generals hailed the sacrifice of Vitaly Skakun Volodymyrovych for halting a column…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian space chief threatens to allow ISS to FALL onto USA or Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4771384/warning-us-hit-debilitating-strike-space-war-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US could be hit with the most debilitating and destructive strike ever in a potential space war with Russia, an expert warns. Relations between Moscow and Washington have plunged to new lows am…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's losses now stand at 2,800 troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10550799/Ukraine-hits-airfield-Russia-missile-strike-blow-Putin-downing-six-helicopters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage posted online purported to show the tail end of a missile strike on the Russian military's airbase around 10am local time (8am GMT) with several buildings on the site engulfed in flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 50,000 flee in 48 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/thousands-flee-ukraine-russia-invasion-04020d01-2707-4ea2-9371-fb06c3d0ad1c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Many more are moving towards" Ukraine's borders, the UN refugee agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews seek refuge in synagogues...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ukraines-jews-seek-refuge-synagogues-100018433.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's invasion of Ukraine has evoked traumatic memories for Holocaust survivors as rabbis turn synagogues into shelters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With war over the border, young Hungarians scorn Orban's Russian ties...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/war-over-border-young-hungarians-163934844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungarian Prime Minister Viktor Orban has never made any secret of his desire for warm ties with Russia and President Vladimir Putin. But five weeks before the toughest election the 58-year-old has faced in his 12 years in power, that friendship looks likely to cost him votes among young people upset at Putin's war on Hungary's neighbour Ukraine. "He has been rather two-faced," said Dora Bicskei, 22, who joined an opposition protest against the Russian invasion on Thursday at the Russian embassy in Budapest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Russia facing more resistance than it expected!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-facing-more-resistance-expected-163328164.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is facing more resistance than Moscow anticipated in its invasion of Ukraine, including in its advance on the capital, Kyiv, and appears to have lost some of its momentum, a senior U.S. defense official said on Friday. Russian missiles pounded Kyiv on Friday, families cowered in shelters and authorities told residents to prepare Molotov cocktails to defend Ukraine's capital from an assault that the mayor said had already begun with saboteurs in the city. But the U.S. official, who spoke on condition of anonymity, suggested a mixed picture for the Russian effort to press an offensive that Washington and Kyiv say is aimed at decapitating the government and installing a puppet regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden presented options for massive cyberattacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/biden-presented-options-massive-cyberattacks-russia-rcna17558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The options presented include disrupting the internet across Russia, shutting off power and stopping trains in their tracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identical twins turn 100, reflect on life...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/identical-twins-turn-100-reflect-on-life-of-scandal-and-joy-people-love-that-were-still-together/ar-AAU7vlF?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby boomers moving in together to save money...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/retirement/the-new-golden-girls-baby-boomers-are-moving-in-together-to-save-money/ar-AAUj9RX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPANSION BEYOND UKRAINE</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-antony-blinken-soviet-bloc-expansion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secretary of state said he is concerned about the safety of Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky and other government officials still in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO FAILS TO STOP</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/erdogan-says-nato-western-reaction-121544982.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA (Reuters) -Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan said on Friday that reaction from NATO and Western countries to Russia's assault on Ukraine had not been decisive, adding he hoped a NATO summit on Friday would lead to a more determined approach from the alliance. NATO member Turkey borders Ukraine and Russia in the Black Sea and has good ties with both.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Tank Crushes Car With Civilian Inside in Shocking Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/russian-tank-crushes-car-ukrain-civilian-inside-viral-video-1682598</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video footage has also emerged of other civilians attempting to rescue the man trapped in the crushed vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin after more than land -- he wants religious soul of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://religionnews.com/2022/02/24/putin-is-after-more-than-land-he-wants-the-religious-soul-of-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;religionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — Make no mistake, Putin is seeking full capitulation from Ukraine — both physical and spiritual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks from within seen as growing threat to elections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-presidential-elections-michigan-elections-76957524a0ef7fa0208ddc636aabac2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election officials preparing for this year’s midterms have yet another security concern to add to an already long list that includes death threats, disinformation, ransomware and cyberattacks — threats from within.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky 'No. 1 target' but will stay in city...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Zelensky-says-he-s-Russia-s-No-1-target-but-16946927.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky pledged to remain in the capital even as Russian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews seek refuge in synagogues...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraines-jews-seek-refuge-in-synagogues-as-russia-invades/ar-AAUhPLf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avocado heartland held hostage by cartels...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220225-mexico-s-avocado-heartland-held-hostage-by-drug-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Super Bowl fans devoured tons of guacamole in the United States, soldiers in the world's biggest avocado-producing region in Mexico were deactivating makeshift landmines left by warring drug traff…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ghost of Kyiv': Fighter pilot credited with shooting down six Russian jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/ghost-of-kyiv-lone-fighter-pilot-credited-with-shooting-down-six-russian-jets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Ukrainian fighter pilot dubbed the "Ghost of Kyiv" has emerged as an unconfirmed heroic figure as Ukraine pushes back against invading Russian troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Eating Meat Less Than 5 Times A Week Lowers Cancer Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eating-meat-cancer-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of Oxford report consuming meat five times or less per week is associated with a lower overall cancer risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian space chief threatens to allow ISS to FALL onto USA or Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4770269/iss-russia-nasa-fall-us-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has warned President Biden that it needs their tech and expertise to prevent the International Space Station from crashing down onto the US or Europe. The country is a key part of the 15-nat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Leaves Off Front Pages as Xi Stays Silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/china-leaves-russia-s-war-off-front-pages-as-xi-stays-silent-1.1728611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese state media left Russia’s invasion of Ukraine off their front pages Friday as Beijing weighed its response, even as the outbreak of war in Europe dominated conversations on Chinese social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Queer Young Comics Redefining American Humor...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/25/the-queer-young-comics-redefining-american-humor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEN DEWAYNE PERKINS was a teenager growing up on the South Side of Chicago, he would occasionally turn to Google</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Panel Widens Investigation of Trump Handling of Documents...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/25/house-panel-widens-investigation-of-trumps-handling-of-documents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A House committee on Friday expanded its investigation into former President Donald J. Trump’s destruction and removal of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Woman Kicked Down Stairs, Bashed in Head With Hammer in NYC Subway...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/57-year-old-woman-attacked-with-hammer-in-subway/3571618/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 57-year-old woman was kicked down the stairs and bashed in the head with a hammer before being robbed Thursday night at the Queens Plaza subway station in Long Island City, authorities say. The woman walked into the station shortly before 11:30 p.m. and was ambushed from behind. Cops say the stranger pulled out the hammer after kicking her down…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous declares 'cyber war' against Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10549849/Hacking-collective-Anonymous-declares-cyber-war-against-Vladimir-Putins-government.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The elusive computer experts issued the stark announcement on their Twitter account on Thursday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYIV SET TO TO FALL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-volodymyr-zelenskyy-boris-johnson-business-08f569df695831ee467979527ea2e241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russia pressed its invasion of Ukraine  to the outskirts of the capital Friday after unleashing airstrikes on cities and military bases and sending in troops and tanks from three sides in an attack that could rewrite the global post-Cold War security order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propaganda, fake videos of bombard users...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-technology-europe-media-social-media-123c7975a879b89b85c06877f1f12908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The messages, videos and photos flying across Twitter, Facebook and Telegram far outnumber the airstrikes raining down on Ukraine. They claim to show Russian fighter jets being shot down or Ukrainians dodging for cover in their own homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's bear battalion! Hank the Tank turns out to be 3 bears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-environment-and-nature-lakes-california-environment-88d0877a87956c563016476fc5e1c58f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH LAKE TAHOE, Calif. (AP) — Hank the Tank is actually a three-bear battalion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Force Expands Ability To Monitor Threats In 'Deep Space'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/44432/space-force-expands-its-ability-to-monitor-threats-in-deep-space</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The service's new radar system is said to be more advanced than existing radar or optical-based orbital space surveillance systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Man faces charges for urinating in SOUTHWEST cabin during flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/california-man-faces-charges-for-urinating-in-southwest-airlines-cabin-during-dallas-burbank-flight/ar-AAUgWCx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chernobyl radiation levels 'exceeded,' as forces take control...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraine-says-chernobyl-radiation-levels-exceeded-as-russia-confirms-its-forces-took-control-of-the-power-plant/ar-AAUhPsd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saga of chained mother of eight continues to roil China, inspiring rare social activism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/saga-of-the-chained-mother-of-eight-continues-to-roil-china-inspiring-rare-social-activism/ar-AAUi0ZI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In world's first crypto war, uncertainty about who will benefit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-ukraine-in-the-world-e2-80-99s-first-crypto-war-uncertainty-about-who-will-benefit/ar-AAUhUNl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine juror to be questioned about childhood sex abuse allegation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ghislaine-maxwell-trial-juror-questioned-200600183.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — A juror who convicted Ghislaine Maxwell will be questioned publicly about whether he was forthcoming about being sexually abused as a child before being selected for the panel, a judge ruled Thursday. Federal Judge Alison Nathan’s order comes after weeks of speculation about how the court would handle statements Scotty David made after finding Maxwell guilty of enticing and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US intel predicted Russia invasion plans. Did it matter?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-business-europe-8acc2106b95554429e93dfee5e253743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For months, the White House made highly unusual releases of intelligence findings about Russian President Vladimir Putin's plans to attack Ukraine. Hoping to preempt an invasion, it released details of Russian troop buildups and warned repeatedly that a major assault was imminent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC to significantly ease mask guidelines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-pandemics-centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention-0be4f20f94f125c511dbca42ae317546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration will significantly loosen federal mask-wearing guidelines to protect against COVID-19 transmission on Friday, according to two people familiar with the matter, meaning most Americans will no longer be advised to wear masks in indoor public settings.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
