<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Russia jails Jehovah's Witness for six years in landmark case; 'Extremism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-politics-religion/russia-jails-jehovahs-witness-for-six-years-in-extremism-case-idUSKCN1PV0W2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian court on Wednesday found a Danish adherent of the Jehovah's Witne...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Marijuana Linked to HIGHER Sperm Counts?</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64693-marijuana-sperm-counts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings contradict previous research, but they are far from conclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Miami estate sells for record $50 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/06/miami-estate-sells-for-a-record-50-million.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An estate on Indian Creek Island sells for $50 million, making it the most expensive single-family home ever sold in the Miami area, according to people familiar with the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torture still scars Iranians 40 years after revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/072580b5f24b4f8ea2402221d530257e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — The halls of the former prison in the heart of Iran's capital now are hushed, befitting the sounds of the museum that it has become. Wax mannequins silently portray the horrific acts of torture that once were carried out within its walls. But the surviving inmates still remember the screams. Exhibits in the former Anti-Sabotage Joint Committee Prison that was run under Shah Mohammad Reza Pahlavi include a frightened man trapped in a small metal cage as a cigarette-smoking interrogator shouts above him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Starts to Worry Maduro Grip Slipping...</title>
      <link>https://themoscowtimes.com/news/russia-starts-to-worry-maduros-grip-is-slipping-in-venezuela-64416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow is acutely aware of how few levers it has to rescue Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Special place in Hell' for Brexiteers: EU leader...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/special-place-hell-brexiteers-eu-leader-005252544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Union leader Donald Tusk on Wednesday condemned those calling for Brexit with no idea how to carry it out, saying he hopes Theresa May now has a "realistic" plan. The British prime minister is due in Brussels on Thursday to discuss ways to ensure Britain's orderly withdrawal from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuns 'sex slaves' scandal fresh blow to Catholic church...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/nuns-sex-slaves-scandal-fresh-blow-catholic-church-002950866.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis's public admission that priests have used nuns as "sexual slaves" -- and may still be doing so -- marks a new chapter in the abuse crisis rocking the Catholic church. "It is the first time that the pope, but also the church as an institution, has publicly admitted this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Tested in Philly...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/health/patient-being-tested-for-ebola-at-hospital-of-the-university-of-pennsylvania/5123171/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patient is being tested for Ebola at the Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania in Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacteria-killing travel robot cleans hotel bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6658027/The-bacteria-killing-travel-robot-cleans-hotel-bed-enjoy-holiday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 'marvel of engineering and design', the U.S-made CleanseBot weighs just 220 grams – less than half a pound – and kills 99.99 per cent of bacteria, germs, and dust mites, it's claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watching TV could give bowel cancer?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6669889/Watching-TV-BOWEL-CANCER-hour-day-increase-young-peoples-risk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study looked at sedentary behaviours of 90,000 women. Researcher Dr Yin Cao from Washington University School of Medicine said younger people may benefit from screening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola Fears Take Monkey Meat Off Menu...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/ebola-fears-stalking-congo-s-neighbor-put-monkey-meat-off-menu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ebola Fears Take Monkey Meat Off the Menu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Racing to Make Pot Like Booze So Can Drink It...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/scientists-are-racing-to-make-pot-like-booze-so-you-can-drink-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists Are Racing to Make Pot Like Booze So You Can Drink It</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filings raise prospect of more indictments...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/428616-mueller-probe-filings-raise-prospect-of-more-indictments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller’s references to “uncharged individuals” in recent court filings that aim to restrict certain evidence are being read by some as an indication more people could be indicted in his sprawling investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it sign? Huge wooden cross washes ashore on Fort Lauderdale beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/fort-lauderdale/fl-lauderdale-cross-comes-ashore-20190205-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A very large barnacle-encrusted wooden cross washed ashore in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, behind the Ocean Manor Beach Resort along Galt Ocean Mile during the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN: 59%  Had 'Very Positive' View of Speech...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-cnn-our-poll-respondents-had-very-positive-view-trump-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘59%, very positive’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare of Human Organ Harvesting in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-nightmare-of-human-organ-harvesting-in-china-11549411056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transplants far outnumber official donors. Prisoners of conscience evidently account for the difference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS POLL: 76% APPROVE OF SPEECH</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/02/poll-stunner-76-percent-of-viewers-approve-president-trumps-state-of-the-union-speech-72-percent-approve-his-immigration-ideas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Dem Jaime Harrison may challenge Sen. Lindsey Graham in SC...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/politics/ahead-of-re-election-lindsey-graham-s-challenge-shifts-from/article_ea44940a-2635-11e9-bdc9-8b57192462f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the "First in the South" 2020 presidential primary has garnered much of the attention in recent weeks, South Carolina Democrats have also been using the early days of 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris fire: Ten dead as woman arrested for 'revenge arson attack on fireman neighbor'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/seven-reported-dead-many-injured-044920085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 10 people died and 37 were injured in an overnight blaze at an apartment block in Paris that police are treating as possible arson. At least one of the victims is a "young child", according to the local mayor. The fire on the upper floors of the building in the rue Erlanger in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Actor Liam Neeson denies racism after admitting hunt for black men...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/liam-neeson-denies-racism-hunting-black-men-attack-190441412.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood star Liam Neeson insisted on Tuesday he was "not racist" after confessing that he once set out to attack a random black man after a friend of his told him she had been raped. "I'm not a racist," Neeson said on ABC News, while admitting he had felt a "primal urge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidneys grown in rats could pave way for human transplants...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kidneys-grown-rats-could-pave-way-human-transplant-160119583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tokyo (AFP) - Scientists said Wednesday they have successfully used mice stem cells to grow kidneys in rat embryos, using a technique that could one day help grow human kidneys for transplant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest speech since Clinton 2000...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trumps-2019-state-of-the-union-address-was-the-longest-since-clintons-in-2000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s State of the Union address Tuesday night, at 82 minutes in length, was the longest such speech since President Bill Clinton's 89-minute one in 2000 and the third-longest ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WE WILL NEVER BE SOCIALIST COUNTRY'</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/02/05/trump_america_will_never_be_a_socialist_country_we_were_born_free_and_we_shall_stay_free.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We stand with the venezuelan people in their noble quest for freedom -- and we condemn the brutality of the maduro regime, whose socialist policies have turned that nation from being the wealthiest in south America into a state of abject poverty and despair. [applause] pres. Here, in the United States, we are alarmed by new calls to adopt socialism in our country. America was founded on liberty and independence - not government coercion, domination, and control. We are born free, and we will stay free. Tonight, we renew our resolve that America will never be a socialist country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts elite as they push for open borders 'while living behind walls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8363077/state-of-the-union-address-donald-trump-border-wall-elite-hypocrisy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump tonight blasted wealthy elites for backing “open borders while living behind walls”. In a State of the Union speech marked by calls for unity, the president did not hold ba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Chuck Todd Blasts 'Theater of the Absurd'...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/nicholas-fondacaro/2019/02/05/chuck-todd-blasts-trumps-sotu-theater-absurd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In advance of Tuesday’s State of the Union address, the White House told the press that President Trump wanted to use the occasion to hit the reset button on strained relationships in Washington, D.C. and to bring Americans to together. But liberal media folks like MSNBC’s Chuck Todd couldn’t believe it. During that evening’s MTP Daily, Todd denounced Trump’s second SOTU as “shaping up to be a night of absurdist theater”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takes swipe at Mueller investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/card/trump-takes-swipe-mueller-investigation-n967916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ROCKS   HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6672199/We-work-says-Trump-uses-State-Union-call-bipartisan-unity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a State of the Union address Tuesday night designed to call for an end to partisan bickering, President Donald Trump stressed that he could bring bipartisan unity to Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern District Eyes Trump Org Execs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/05/politics/new-york-federal-prosecutors-trump-organization-executives/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors in New York have requested interviews in recent weeks with executives at the Trump Organization, according to people familiar with the matter, signaling a growing potential threat to President Donald Trump and those in his orbit from criminal investigations by the Manhattan US Attorney's office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Wins over Dems After Touting Job Gains for Women...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-gets-applause-democrats-no-one-has-benefitted-more-our</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We also have more women serving in the Congress than ever before’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto will decide if 2020 run by month's end...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7a7de74cd5074caabad81eabb97b0b9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Breaking months of near-silence about his political future, Democrat Beto O'Rourke said Tuesday that he would announce his decision about a 2020 presidential run "before the end of the month" and suggested he's leaning toward it. The former Texas congressman, who found political stardom in his unsuccessful Senate bid last fall, opened up about a potential 2020 run in a conversation with a bigger star, Oprah Winfrey, during a taping of her program "Oprah's SuperSoul Conversations from Times Square."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls on divided Congress to end political stalemate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/449885686d4b4db7b0724314bdba6577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In his first State of the Union address to a divided Congress, President Donald Trump warned Democrats on Tuesday that "ridiculous partisan investigations" could derail the nation's economic progress. Trump peppered his speech with calls for bipartisanship, urging Washington to govern "not as two parties, but as one nation." But his message clashed with the rancorous atmosphere he has helped cultivate in the nation's capital, as well as the desire of most Democrats to block his path during his next two years in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez refuses applause for 'cooperation, compromise, common good'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-sour-ocasio-cortez-refuses-to-applaud-cooperation-compromise-common-good/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has no interest in working with President Trump, or applauding his call for “cooperation, compromise, and the common good.” “But we must reject the politics of revenge, resistance and retribution, and embrace the boundless potential of cooperation, compromise, and the common good,” Trump said during his State of the Union address. As …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST: Was Bezos Affair Expose Political Hit Job?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/was-tabloid-expose-of-bezos-affair-just-juicy-gossip-or-a-political-hit-job/2019/02/05/03d2f716-2633-11e9-90cd-dedb0c92dc17_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dueling investigations seek to learn how the National Enquirer obtained texts sent by the owner of The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian media threatens US with nuclear doomsday device...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/russia-threatens-us-with-nuclear-doomsday-device-after-inf-failure-2019-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It cannot be excluded that one of the Poseidon with a 100 megaton nuclear warhead will lay low off the US coast, becoming 'the doomsday weapon.'"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jumps aboard moving AMTRAK train, tries to take over controls...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/la-me-ln-dylan-thomas-baldini-moving-train-20190205-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities said the 26-year-old man tried to change the locomotive’s controls and blasted the train's horn several times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidential Memo: Company of Inaugural Chair Sought to Profit From Connections...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-podcast-tom-barrack-colony-company-of-trump-inaugural-chair-sought-to-profit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The memo outlines how Colony, the company founded by Tom Barrack, an investor who chaired the inaugural, aimed to exploit its connections to Donald Trump. Federal prosecutors are conducting a wide-ranging probe into the nonprofit that ran the inaugural.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren identified as 'American Indian' for State Bar registration; Additional docs to surface?</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/politics/2019/02/05/elizabeth-warren-identified-native-american-her-state-bar-texas-registration/fevojNFJErrYPmNK5jR25J/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator apologized for identifying herself as a Native American for almost two decades, reflecting her ongoing struggle to quiet a controversy that continues to haunt her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK ministers hold secret talks of delaying Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu/uk-ministers-hold-secret-talks-of-delaying-brexit-by-eight-weeks-the-telegraph-idUSKCN1PU2ML</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK cabinet ministers have secretly held talks on plans to delay Brexit by eight ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former TESLA workers paint grim picture: 'Building plane as we're flying it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wivb.com/news/investigates/former-tesla-workers-paint-grim-picture-of-buffalo-plant/1754568826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wivb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of former Tesla workers in Buffalo are breaking their silence about problems they witnessed at the plant, including what they termed as “a lack of urgency” shown by management to improve operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia scandal puts 'believe all accusers' standard to test...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/justin-fairfax-is-testing-the-lefts-believe-all-accusers-standard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sexual assault allegation against Democratic Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax has added to the chaos in a state already reeling from the publication of Democratic Gov. Ralph Northam's yearbook page that included a photo featuring one person in blackface and another one in a Ku Klux Klan costume. But more…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial shoe thief says crimes motivated by sexual pleasure of sniffing used footwear...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/2185097/japanese-shoe-sniffer-admits-stealing-used-footwear-sexual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Makoto Endo, 40, is suspected of stealing 70 pairs of shoes worth nearly US$3,000 over a 13-month period</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE OF THE ART</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-touts-drudge-report-labelling-him-teflon-donald-ahead-of-state-of-the-union/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of decapitated fish with bladders torn out wash ashore in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/757887/thousands-of-headless-fish-wash-up-bladders-torn-out-BIZARRE-video-Germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLF NOW 'CONTACT SPORT'; BAD BACK EPIDEMIC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6667923/Golf-bad-participants-CONTACT-sport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A focus on strength over style is making spinal injuries common among both amateurs and professionals. More than half of those who golf for a living suffer from back injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Husband opens fire after wife tryst in hot tub with friend...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/hot-tub-tryst-603941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 5--An “enraged” Florida Man fired two shots after discovering his wife performing a sex act on a male friend of the couple’s while the pair were in a backyard hot tub, police report. Accordi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg rips AMAZON tax breaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/albany/story/2019/02/05/bloomberg-billionaire-and-possible-presidential-candidate-disputes-tax-breaks-for-amazon-837970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg inveighing against corporate welfare gives the potential Democratic candidate a connection to an economic populist message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER BRAWL: Fists fly at PATRIOS parade...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/05/patriots-fans-celebrate-super-bowl-53-win-with-all-out-brawl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots fans sure have an odd way of celebrating the team’s Super Bowl win. Tuesday’s parade for the six-time NFL champions began by irking local commuters by bringing thousands of fan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORCED ABORTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/397f2c76afc04532908035a66ccaacc8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABOARD THE PAPAL PLANE (AP) — Pope Francis has for the first time publicly acknowledged the scandal of priests and bishops sexually abusing nuns and says he is committed to doing more to fight the problem. Speaking to reporters Tuesday, Francis noted that Pope Benedict XVI had taken action against a France-based order after some of its religious sisters had been reduced to "sexual slavery" at the hands of the priest who founded the order and other priests. "Should we do something more? Yes. Is there the will? Yes. But it's a path that we have already begun," Francis said while returning home from the United Arab Emirates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt workers busted getting on cruise to sell drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.sunherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article225545255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sunherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two government contractors trying to board a cruise ship at PortMiami, FL were arrested after cops say they were planning on selling drugs to passengers. Police were notified by Homeland Security agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRASSLEY: MUELLER REPORT 'WITHIN MONTH'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6670771/Republican-senator-says-expects-Mueller-report-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting Attorney General Matt Whitaker said eight days ago that the Mueller probe was in its final stages. Grassly thinks it will be done 'within a month' but doesn't know if Congress will see it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED TRIES AGAIN:  Secret Files Show Trump Moscow Connection!</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/azeenghorayshi/trump-tower-moscow-the-secret-files-cohen-sater-putin?ref=bfnsplash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of Michael Cohen’s testimony, read the original paper trail behind the campaign to build Europe’s tallest tower in Moscow — and how it played out alongside Donald Trump’s presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Reunited With Blind, Deaf Pooch -- Missing For 6 Years!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/02/04/milo-the-poodle-hart-family-hempstead-animal-shelter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was an incredible reunion on Long Island this weekend, between a family and a very long-lost four-legged loved one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milky Way galaxy truly warped...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f963341f5b24658b23321900dfc86ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — It turns out our Milky Way galaxy is truly warped, at least around the far edges. Scientists in China and Australia released an updated 3D map of the Milky Way on Tuesday. They used 1,339 pulsating stars — young, newly catalogued stars bigger and brighter than our sun — to map the galaxy's shape. The farther from the center, the more warping, or twisting, there is in the Milky Way's outer hydrogen gas disc. Researchers say the warped, spiral pattern is likely caused by the spinning force of the massive inner disc of stars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First trans designer shows at NY Fashion Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190205-first-transgender-designer-shows-new-york-fashion-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First transgender designer shows at New York Fashion Week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK OKs museum nudes after all...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26dc0db03bba4a3980d1c40ea7c375b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — It seems Facebook can be friends with a topless Venus after all. The social media giant said Tuesday it mistakenly blocked a museum in Switzerland from using images of two statues — a marble Venus and a bronze of a nude, kneeling man — to promote an upcoming exhibit. The Museum of Art and History in Geneva had protested Facebook's citing of nudity concerns to keep the images off. The two statues are part of the exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases of mystery disease increasing in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Valley-Fever-cases-in-California-continue-to-13581647.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A potentially deadly illness found in the soil and dusty winds of California's Central Valley is on the rise, state health officials say. Documented cases of Valley Fever rose 11 percent in 2018 - a preliminary total of 7,886 cases compared to 7,090 cases for the same period in 2017, according to California Department of Public Health. Health officials said final data for 2018 will be available in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basketball bribes: How ADIDAS bankrolled black market for teen talent...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/business/2019/02/basketball-bribes-how-adidas-bankrolled-a-black-market-for-top-teenage-talent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adidas, the second-largest athletic apparel and footwear brand in the world, funded a "black opps" crew that funneled payments to high school basketball players' families so their sons would attend an Adidas-affiliated school. Dramatic testimony from an Adidas bagman-turned government witness at a criminal fraud trial in October ripped the lid off the corruption long suspected in the sport and the footwear companies' role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem field smaller than expected?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/428529-dem-presidential-field-looks-smaller-than-expected</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic field in the 2020 election is shaping up to be much smaller than originally anticipated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man eaten by bear had overdosed on meth...</title>
      <link>https://www.wate.com/news/local-news/autopsy-man-overdosed-on-meth-in-gsmnp-before-bear-scavenged-his-remains/1754392016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The autopsy report from the Knox County Regional Forensic Center revealed Monday that William Lee Hill Jr., 30, died of an "accidental methamphetamine intoxication" in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park in September, prior to his remains being scavenged by a bear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF ROBOT REPORTERS!</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/05/business/media/artificial-intelligence-journalism-robots.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fast, accurate and no typos! Bloomberg News, The Washington Post and The Associated Press test out machine-generated journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  'We will build a Human Wall if necessary'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/05/donald-trump-promises-human-wall-of-troops-to-block-migrant-caravans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump promised Tuesday to keep a flood of migrants from the southern border by sending in more military forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Killed After Vape Pen Explodes While Inhaling...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/05/texas-man-killed-by-exploding-vape-pen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 24-year-old man was killed in Texas last week when his vape pen exploded — slicing open his carotid artery and leaving his grandmother’s car covered in blood. William Brown died after his l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: No pictures from Ruth Bader Ginsburg 'public appearance'?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/mystery-no-pictures-from-first-ginsburg-public-appearance-since-surgery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg attended a concert put on by her daughter-in-law at the National Museum of Women in the Arts on Monday, marking her first public appearance since cancer surgery in December. Attendees at the Notorious RBG in Song described Ginsburg as “glam,” and “resplendent,” and “magnificent,” but you’ll have to take …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP APPROVAL 48%</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/political_updates/prez_track_feb05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin taunts Trump: 400 Russian military contractors sent in support of Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/4/vladimir-putin-backs-nicolas-maduro-military-contr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is playing a high-stakes game in the mounting crisis in Venezuela, where socialist President Nicolas Maduro has been mortgaging part of the country’s oil resources in exchange for financial and military support from Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deficit reduction remains pipe dream...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/the-state-of-the-union-deficit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The experience of the last two years illustrates the difficulty Congress has had in taking action on reducing the deficit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEFLON DONALD</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/02/04/trump-start-over-state-of-the-union-2019-224667</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State of the Union address rarely matters, but this one does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tijuana Trump' fends off critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/tijuana-trump-fends-off-critics/article_4c7cc6fc-5407-5323-945f-2e9a6f8962cd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico — When the mayor of Tijuana refused to apologize for comments he made about a caravan of Central American migrants, the coalition of human rights groups who demanded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRISPR revolutionized gene editing. Now its toolbox expanding...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldcourier.com/news/national/crispr-revolutionized-gene-editing-now-its-toolbox-is-expanding/article_1df85645-b2ad-56d0-82bf-7c6f12cd7960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gene-editing tool that has revolutionized biology is becoming even more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big hotel chains become arms of the surveillance state...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/archives/2019/02/05/hotel-surveillance-state-sex-trafficking </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How hotel chains became the new frontier in the surveillance state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE MELTDOWN! Waters begs Americans to 'turn the television off' during  State of Union...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/maxine-sotu-meltdown-trump-not-worthy-of-being-listened-to-i-hope-people-turn-the-television-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxine Waters doesn’t want to hear what Donald Trump has to say tonight. The California congresswoman melted down when asked if she would be listening to Trump’s second State of the Union address this evening. #AClassyClapback served the way only Auntie Maxine can- straight, no chaser. Read why @RepMaxineWaters still isn't here for Trump’s #SOTU …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incredible photos reveal Earth's stunning natural beauty in all its glory...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8357099/photos-freezing-penguins-waterfalls-earth-natural-beauty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INCREDIBLE entries to the world’s biggest photography competition have been revealed today as the shortlist has been decided. Now in its 12th year, the Sony World Photography Awards celebrates the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karl Marx grave vandalized in hammer attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2019/feb/05/karl-marx-london-grave-vandalised-suspected-hammer-attack-highgate-cemetery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friends of Highgate Cemetery calls attack a ‘particularly inarticulate form of political comment’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM mosquitoes: Playing God or only way to wipe out malaria?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/gm-mosquitoes-playing-god-way-wipe-malaria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The villagers of Bana in Burkina Faso survive by working the land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball killed woman at DODGER STADIUM; First foul-ball death in 50 years...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/espn/otl/story/_/id/25926592/fan-struck-head-foul-ball-dodgers-game-died-blunt-force-injury</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California woman died in August as a result of being hit in the head by a batted ball at Dodger Stadium, according to a Los Angeles County coroner's report obtained by ESPN's "Outside the Lines" and details her daughter revealed to OTL in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France carries out rare simulation of nuclear deterrent strike...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190205142736-nszld</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NUCLEAR/:France carries out rare simulation of nuclear deterrent strike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55 million devotees for busiest days of Hindu megafestival...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190205-55-million-devotees-busiest-days-hindu-megafestival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;55 million devotees for busiest days of Hindu megafestival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jogger kills mountain lion with 'BARE HANDS' in self-defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6668795/Colorado-jogger-fends-kills-mountain-lion-rural-trail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was jogging on the West Ridge of the Horsetooth Mountain Open Space in Colorado. He was attacked from behind by the juvenile lion but killed it in 'self-defense' with his bare hands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
