<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WWE owner, 76, still has 3 AM workouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/2491488/wwe-vince-mcmahon-workout-personal-trainer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WWE boss Vince McMahon is still a ‘meathead’ due to his incredible 3am workouts despite being aged 76. The billionaire, who lives in a sprawling £32million mansion, is still showing no signs of slo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAHER: I Don't Want to Live in Your Mask Paranoid World Anymore...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2022/01/22/bill_maher_i_dont_want_to_live_in_your_mask_paranoid_world_anymore.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill kicks off the 20th season of Real Time with jokes about President Biden's press conference and our perpetual pandemic panic: "It's just gone on too long, nobody cares anymore," Maher said. "I don't want to live in your mask paranoid world anymore. You go out it's silly now: you have to have a mask, you have a booster, they scan your head. Like you're a cashier and I'm a bunch of bananas. I'm not bananas, you are."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT SUNDANCE:  Dunham Says New Film Shows Porn 'Can Be Really Healing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/sharp-stick-porn-can-be-really-healing-says-lena-dunham/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lena Dunham’s Sharp Stick shows the porn industry in a rare, positive light. She says that was 100% intentional. “I think many of us were — especially people who started maybe, like, reading second-wave feminist literature early — were shaped by a kind of feminism that maybe didn’t give porn it’s due as something that […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA passenger takes off pants, attacks passenger...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/delta-passenger-mooned-flight-attendant-threw-can-at-traveler-fbi-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man from Ireland who was heading to the U.S. to teach soccer is accused of repeatedly disrupting an eight-hour Delta Air Lines flight with "scary" and violent behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX:  BIDEN APPROVAL 47%...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/biden-gets-his-best-polling-news-of-2022-from-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden woke up, Sunday morning, to his best polling news in quite some time. And it came from a rather unlikely source: Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:   Americans sour on nation's direction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/downhill-divisive-americans-sour-nation-s-direction-new-nbc-news-n1287888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large majorities say the U.S. is going in the wrong direction, that they are falling behind economically and that political polarization will continue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE BRACES FOR ATTACK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/21/europe/gallery/ukraine-russia-fadek/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 500 yards away from Russian-backed separatists, a group of Ukrainian soldiers waits for a fight it's sure is coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman ordered to remove Peng Shuai shirt at Aus Open...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/sport/tennis/australian-open-security-orders-woman-to-remove-shirt-featuring-message-supporting-peng-shuai/news-story/af49c0ee20576677296d1853dc13d9b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennis Australia is standing by its decision to order an Australian Open spectator to remove a shirt that featured a message in support of Peng Shuai amid ongoing concerns for the Chinese tennis star’s welfare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does LA want billionaire mayor?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/does-l-a-want-a-billionaire-mayor-rick-caruso-is-trying-to-find-out/ar-AAT3u6u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German navy chief resigns after suggesting Putin 'deserved respect'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/23/europe/german-navy-chief-resignation-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief of German navy has resigned after suggesting that Crimea would "never come back" to Ukraine, a statement that is in direct contradiction to the stance taken by the German government, the European Union and NATO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 3-week isolation, unvaccinated athletes wait...</title>
      <link>https://www.wyff4.com/article/patrizia-kummer-unvaccinated-athlete-waits-for-olympics/38850497#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wyff4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swiss snowboarder Patrizia Kummer is spending three weeks alone in a hotel room before she competes at the Olympics because she is unvaccinated against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First non-binary Winter Olympian...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220121152307-dwe5y/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing district orders mass virus testing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-coronavirus-pandemic-sports-health-beijing-466341324e7977c9586be4012739ad41</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — People in a Beijing district with some 2 million residents were ordered Sunday to undergo mass coronavirus testing following a series of infections as China tightened anti-disease controls ahead of the Winter Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities see large increases in carjackings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/23/us/carjackings-rise-major-cities-pandemic/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carjackings have risen dramatically over the past two years in some of America's biggest cities. Large cities that track the crime reported increases in 2020 and 2021, especially as the pandemic took hold of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burrow's BENGALS 'Coming for It All'...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/bengals/news/joe-burrow-bold-statement-bengals-win-over-titans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cincinnati won a road playoff game for the first time in franchise history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious ice formations in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/22/weather/midwest-chicago-lake-michigan-ice-pancakes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You've heard of blizzards and maybe even the polar vortex, but have you heard of ice pancakes? What about ice bites or ice jams? These unique names sound fascinating but require specific weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy G elated: 'F**k the PACKERS'...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/10024681-jimmy-garoppolo-overheard-saying-f--k-the-packers-in-postgame-celebration-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco 49ers defeated the Green Bay Packers 13-10 in the NFC Divisional Round on Saturday at Lambeau Field, and Jimmy Garoppolo had some choice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady to mull future...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33126668/tom-brady-take-season-committing-return-tampa-bay-buccaneers-2022-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady will mull his future after this season concludes and take time before committing to a return to football in 2022, sources tell ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But first: RAMS operation...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/surgical-brady-readies-rams-operation-011022061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady says the Tampa Bay Buccaneers' regular season drubbing by the Los Angeles Rams will count for little when the two sides collide in the NFL playoffs on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guns, Catfishing, Lies:  Wildest Sheriff Race in America...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/guns-catfishing-subterfuge-most-bonkers-221312615.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/Getty/Mellinger for Sheriff Facebook/West Virginia Regional JailIt was 2019, and a contentious, mudslinging election for Jackson County, West Virginia sheriff was underway. In the blue corner, a Jackson County deputy named Ross Mellinger. In the red corner, GOP contender Noel Braley, an Army veteran and retired cop who had served as a deputy in nearby Kanawha County for two decades. The Nov. 2020 election was still more than a year off.Tha</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake ambulance with 28 migrants aboard found in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-mexico-central-america-crime-bc89c281a8650a92c8a90d82bea52983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican authorities have detected many strange schemes to smuggle Central American migrants to the U.S. border, but on Saturday they said they found a new one: a fake ambulance loaded with 28 Nicaraguans, including nine unaccompanied children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 lab monkeys accounted for after crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Don-t-approach-lab-monkey-missing-after-crash-16796244.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANVILLE, Pa. (AP) — The last of the escaped monkeys from the crash of a truck towing a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China builds own movie empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-builds-its-own-movie-empire-f22b9298-b592-405e-a83c-c2ee99878abf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China surpassed the U.S. as the world's largest theatrical market in 2020 and 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodgers career over in shocking thud?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/23/aaron-rodgers-career-may-have-just-ended-in-shocking-thud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was definitely the end of a Packers season that looked like it had potential to end in the Super Bowl a few weeks from now. Of much greater magnitude, though, the night very possibly marked the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Hong Kong hamster tests positive as city lockdown grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/one-surrendered-hong-kong-hamster-tests-covid-positive-as-city-lockdown-grows/ar-AAT3mBD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin v. NYT trial will be 'excruciating' for paper...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/22/media/sarah-palin-new-york-times-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday marks the start of jury selection for a trial over Sarah Palin's defamation lawsuit against the newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family believes Jamaican immigrant's death in rural Pa. was 'modern-day lynching'...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/pennsylvania/rural-pittsburgh-shooting-venango-spencer-shooting-20220121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family members of Peter Bernardo Spencer say the man who shot him 9 times may be claiming self-defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat Loaf Daughter Pens Tribute Following Rock Legend's Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/meat-loafs-daughter-pens-tribute-following-rock-legends-death-178185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pearl Aday posted the tribute on Instagram two days after Meat Loaf's passing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Dems censure Sinema over voting rights bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/voting-rights-kyrsten-sinema-phoenix-arizona-voting-af9409b7dbab996a1a8df329c053fce0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — U.S. Sen. Kyrsten Sinema is growing increasingly isolated from some of her party’s most influential officials and donors after playing a key role in scuttling voting rights legislation that many Democrats consider essential to preserving democracy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
