<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA ranked 128th most peaceful nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jun/12/annual-global-index-rates-us-128th-most-peaceful-n/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world has gotten a little more peaceful, according to the 13th annual Global Peace Index, a complex study that ranks 163 nations on factors such as homicide and incarceration rates, the presence of small arms, military expenditures, ongoing conflicts, terrorism, the overall economic impact of violence and even climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR OF BLUE TEXAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/fear-of-a-blue-texas-new-gop-group-to-spend-millions-registering-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy Republican donors are preparing a multimillion-dollar effort to register more than 1 million new GOP voters in Texas for 2020 amid anxiety that President Trump could be in more trouble in this reliably red state than some in the party realize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX named worst airport --- in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/06/12/fodors-travel-awards-best-worst-airports-airlines-cruises/1421927001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fodor'sÂ Travel Awards has named the best airports, airlines andÂ cruises across the U.S. and the world in a variety of categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crocodiles and monkeys left in garbage-filled cages at world's filthiest zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9280305/disgusting-zoo-depressed-monkeys-crocodiles-rotting-rubbish-cages-indonesia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zoo in Indonesia has sparked outrage after images emerged showing monkeys and crocodiles rotting in rubbish-strewn cages. The photos were taken at a compound for the Strategic Army Command, a bra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUIET PLEASE:  WOULD THE WORLD BE BETTER ON MUTE?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/jun/12/hit-mute-button-why-everyone-trying-to-silence-outside-world-uber</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber is trialling a feature that allows customers to stop their drivers from talking. But there’s growing evidence that cutting ourselves off like this isn’t healthy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>By 2040, Most 'Meat' -- Won't Be Meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/jun/12/most-meat-in-2040-will-not-come-from-slaughtered-animals-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consultants say 60% will be grown in vats or plant-based products that taste like meat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House press corps publicly airing its grievances... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/White-House-press-corps-publicly-airing-its-13975595.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House Correspondents' Association typically keeps a low profile in its discussions with the White House press secretary over issues involving the news media. It tends not to wade into controversy, at least not in public.  But faced with the president's continued hostility and confronted by false official statements, the two candidates vying to become president of the group want to take a bolder - and more confrontational - approach.  "We as an organization need to be more concerned about getting lied to as a matter of course - and the American public getting lied to, through us - than about access," HuffPost correspondent S.V. Date wrote in an email touting his candidacy to the WHCA's 425 voting members.  He added, "I've been in this business more than three decades, and what's happening now is unprecedented. We are attacked on a near daily basis using Stalinist language. We are called corrupt and dishonest. We are given false information from staff who often know full well that it is false."  CBS News Radio reporter Steven Portnoy, 38, uses less explosive language in his pitch for support, but makes clear his disappointment that the White House hasn't held a press briefing in a record 93 days as of Wednesday.  Ticking off a long list of news stories that have transpired in that time (for example, "Pelosi-Schumer talks implode as Pelosi accuses Trump of 'cover up' "), Portnoy wrote: "As the president continues to call news organizations 'corrupt,' these are just some of the issues he has ducked by not having his aides appear regularly before the press corps."  The two journalists' statements suggest that the White House press corps has grown more frustrated - and is willing to say so publicly - after more than two years of disparagement by Trump and press...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna vs. Bruce:  New Albums Released SAME DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/06/06/madonna-vs-bruce-new-albums-coming-june-14th-springsteen-is-already-number-1-on-amazon-madge-is-at-97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Circle next Friday, June 14th (yes, it’s almost the middle of June). That’s the day Bruce Springsteen and Madonna go head to head with album releases. Bruce has “Western Stars.&amp;#8…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top AI researchers race to detect deepfake videos: 'Outgunned'......</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Top-AI-researchers-race-to-detect-deepfake-13975018.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top artificial-intelligence researchers across the country are racing to defuse an extraordinary political weapon: computer-generated fake videos that could undermine candidates and mislead voters during the 2020 presidential campaign.  And they have a message: We're not ready.  The researchers have designed automatic systems that can analyze videos for the telltale indicators of a fake, assessing light, shadows, blinking patterns - and, in one potentially groundbreaking method, even how a candidate's real-world facial movements relate to each other, like the angle they tilt their head when they smile.  But for all that progress, the researchers say they remain vastly overwhelmed by a technology they fear could herald a damaging new wave of disinformation campaigns, much in the same way fake news stories and deceptive Facebook groups were deployed to influence public opinion during the 2016 race.  Powerful new AI software has effectively democratized the creation of convincing "deepfake" videos, making it easier than ever to fabricate someone appearing to say or do something they didn't really do, from harmless satires and film tweaks to targeted harassment and deepfake porn.  And researchers fear it's only a matter of time before the videos are deployed for maximum damage - to sow confusion, fuel doubt or undermine an opponent, potentially on the eve of a White House vote.  "We are outgunned," said Hany Farid, a computer-science professor and digital-forensics expert at the University of California, Berkeley. "The number of people working on the video-synthesis side, as opposed to the detector side, is 100 to 1."  These AI-generated videos have yet to drive their own political scandal in the U.S. But even simple tweaks to existing videos can create turmoil, as happened...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Hell Is Going On In Dominican Republic?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/dominican-republic-grand-bahia-hard-rock-american-tourist-death-846888/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though it’s unclear if they’re connected, at least six American tourists have died under mysterious circumstances in the last year alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media has big problem: Who will pay for news?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-media/the-media-has-a-big-problem-reuters-institute-says-who-will-pay-for-the-news-idUSKCN1TC2WV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News organizations are being challenged by technology giants and unsettled by a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Robots and End of Civilization...</title>
      <link>https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/darwins-subterranean-world/201906/sex-robots-and-the-end-civilization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.psychologytoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-13 member sentenced to 55 years in machete quadruple murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsday.com/long-island/crime/ms-13-machete-murders-central-islip-1.32294790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An MS-13 street gang member apologized Wednesday for the “heinous" hacking to death of four teens in a Central Islip park before a federal judge sentenced him to 55 years in prison. Josue Portillo, wh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD swarm Manhattan streets after mysterious cages appear...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Police-Swarm-Midtown-Corner-After-Cage-Appears-Chained-to-Street-Sign-511176041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police swarmed the corner of 6th Avenue and West 48th Street in the heart of Midtown, where a cage appeared on the street corner Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious snake-like UFO seen glowing above desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/men-film-glowing-snake-like-16506345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cody Kennedy and his friends captured a bright moving tail in the sky over a desert in California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With classified filing, feds eye national security case against Mar-a-Lago intruder...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article231465918.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  MSNBC Shakeup as Andy Lack Fumes Over Ratings Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/exclusive-msnbc-shakeup-puts-jonathan-wald-and-dan-arnall-in-charge-of-dayside-programming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC implemented a big shakeup in programming this week, Mediaite has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 Penises in One Episode! HBO 'EUPHORIA' Courts Controversy with Graphic Teen Sex, Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hbos-explicit-euphoria-courts-controversy-how-teen-sex-is-1217606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty penises in one episode? Zendaya’s new series, filled with graphic nudity, violence and drug use among young people, is so extreme that one star quit mid-shoot, but the network hopes that authenticity will help the show break through: "It's not sensational to be sensational."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Gayle King Steady CBSNEWS?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/gayle-king-cbs-news-woes-charlie-rose-r-kelly-staying-at-cbs-1217434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a year of scandal and upheaval, King takes the lead (and a new three-year deal) at 'CBS This Morning' as she opens up on Charlie Rose, that R. Kelly interview, advice from Oprah and becoming the face of the news division: "I am now a part of that history. Let's see what we do."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Le Pen to go on trial for tweeting gruesome ISIS images...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190612-frances-le-pen-go-trial-tweeting-gruesome-images</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's Le Pen to go on trial for tweeting gruesome IS images</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino R-rated 'STAR TREK' will be f*cking foulmouthed...</title>
      <link>https://www.empireonline.com/movies/news/tarantino-star-trek-project-sweary-r-rated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.empireonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Navy fighter loses stealth coating at high speeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/air/2019/06/12/supersonic-speeds-could-cause-big-problems-for-the-f-35s-stealth-coating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supersonic flight at the edge of the F-35 jet's flight envelope could cause structural damage or degrade its stealth coating, warn documents exclusively obtained by Defense News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPE HICKS BACK TO TESTIFY ON HILL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7135071/Hope-Hicks-testify-Democrat-run-House-hearing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House communications director Hope Hicks has agreed to appear before the House Judiciary Committee next week - the first former White House aide to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDERAL SPENDING SOARS PAST $3T</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-spending-tops-3-trillion-through-may-first-time-deficit-hits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Win McNamee)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice Roberts about to show his cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/12/politics/chief-justice-john-roberts-supreme-court-june/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a deadline for nearly 30 cases looming and weighty issues of religion, gerrymandering and the 2020 census pending, Chief Justice John Roberts took his black leather chair at the bench this week and said three decisions were ready to be announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy pigs found beaten to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/11/us/therapy-pigs-beaten-killed-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cereals contain ROUNDUP ingredient, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/glyphosate-breakfast-cereal-still-contains-roundup-ingredient-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An environmental group says its test results show many glyphosate levels above what it considers safe for children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Loses Third of Primetime Audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/06/12/death-spiral-continues-cnn-loses-one-third-primetime-audience/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The far-left CNN's ratings death spiral marched into last week as the fake news network lost one-third of its primetime audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>