<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UNITED offers pilots triple pay to ease disruptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/31/united-airlines-offers-pilots-triple-pay-to-ease-omicron-flight-disruptions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United is among the airlines offering pilots and flight attendants extra pay as omicron drives up crew sick calls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unearthed interview reveals how Maxwell helped kill VANITY FAIR expose...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/31/interview-reveals-how-ghislaine-maxwell-killed-vanity-fair-expose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell ripped a Vanity Fair reporter nearly 20 years ago to help bury an exposé of her sex crimes — while claiming pedophile Jeffrey Epstein was generous, according to a released transcr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why JK Rowling snubbed from 'POTTER' reunion...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/tv/streaming/why-jk-rowling-has-been-snubbed-from-the-harry-potter-reunion/news-story/6fcf71eaabca98e3abddfde6f6f447fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She single-handedly created one of the most distinguished fictional worlds in literary, cinematic and popular culture history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Planned Parenthood destroyed in fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-fires-tennessee-knoxville-planned-parenthood-524edc1a8bd12e46774c1fcdf37c6c72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee Planned Parenthood building was destroyed by an early morning fire on Friday, Planned Parenthood officials said. Knoxville Fire Department crews were called about 6:40 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz Daughter Disses Him on TIKTOK:  'Disagree With Most of His Views'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasobserver.com/news/the-internet-might-have-a-new-claudia-conway-in-ted-cruzs-daughter-13113373</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sen. Ted Cruz may run for president again, but his own daughter recently announced she doesn't agree with his politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge resigns after video showed her using racial slurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/louisiana-judge-resigns-video-showed-using-racial-slurs-rcna10535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana judge Michelle Odinet resigned from her position Friday, weeks after home video showed her and other people using racial slurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish fall from sky in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.kxxv.com/news/local-news/fish-fall-from-the-sky-during-rain-in-east-texas-city-reacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxxv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This uncommon phenomenon is referred to as "animal rain" and occurs when small water animals are swept up in waterspouts or drafts that occur on the surface of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Coaches made teen eat pizza despite religion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-football-religion-education-ohio-c7c93a7b6592f2bbe9ea14e472f6f68a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANTON, Ohio (AP) — An Ohio high school football player who says coaches forced him to eat a pizza covered with pepperoni grease in violation of his religious beliefs is suing his former district and the ousted coaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal Spray to Cure Dementia?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/nasal-spray-may-cure-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potentially groundbreaking treatment combines an antibiotic called rifampicin with resveratrol -- an antioxidant found in plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doesn't Infect Lungs Very Well, Animal Studies Find...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/omicron-doesnt-infect-the-lungs-very-well-animal-studies-find/ar-AASjwVO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Miracle' -- no loss of life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-casualties-reported-colorado-wildfire-173128776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado officials said on Friday that it was a "miracle" that no deaths were reported in an unprecedented urban wildfire that moved at breakneck speeds across towns north of Denver, destroying upward of 1,000 homes. The winds created a "mosaic" burn pattern that saw untouched homes standing next to those left in ashes. The blaze swept through about 6,000 acres in just a couple of hours, destroyed at least 500 homes and may have burned down up to 1,000, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers demand proof Prince Andrew can't sweat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/31/us/virginia-giuffre-prince-andrew-court-filing-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew has been asked to provide documents proving his "alleged medical inability to sweat" in a court filing by attorneys for Virginia Roberts Giuffre, who has accused the royal of sexual assault in a US civil lawsuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMTRAK trains canceled...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc-transit/2021/12/some-amtrak-trains-canceled-starting-new-years-eve-following-bad-weather-covid-19-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bad weather and employee COVID-19 cases led Amtrak to reduce its trains’ schedule between New Year’s Eve and Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should kids be vaccinated? Brazil turns to online survey...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-public-health-brazil-jair-bolsonaro-a013cc47a3d4a69bf4ba68f02a958677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASILIA, Brazil (AP) — As world leaders rely on public health specialists to inform their decisions about whether and how to vaccinate children against the coronavirus, Brazil's government is asking the online public for guidance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 15 in London infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-united-nations-middle-east-a1d448ba830f29ac1967971cf2f59458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — New figures from Britain’s official statistics body estimate that about 1 in 25 people in private households in England had COVID-19 in the week before Christmas, as the highly transmissible omicron variant spread rapidly across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia schools going virtual...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-georgia-jonesboro-1c8ea9409edde6dc6ca68503d5d0d9f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JONESBORO, Ga. (AP) — One of Georgia's largest school districts will start the second semester virtually amid the state's surge in COVID cases. Clayton County Public Schools south of Atlanta said Thursday students will learn remotely from Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic Videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/apocalyptic-videos-emerge-from-boulder-fire-i-dont-know-if-my-home-is-still-there/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stunning videos have emerged from the fires that have ravaged neighborhoods in Boulder County, Colorado Thursday that led to massive evacuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some cautious, many fed up, Americans ring in New Year...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211231105707-fxtdj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW-YEAR/USA (PIX):Some cautious, many fed up, Americans prepare to ring in the New Year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First LGBT+ cryptocurrency bets on 'changing world'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211231145947-60pl4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPAIN-CRYPTO-CURRENCY/LGBT (PIX):First LGBT+ cryptocurrency bets on 'changing the world'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORST IN STATE HISTORY</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4368929/boulder-county-fire-most-destructive-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE wildfire raging in Boulder County is thought to be the most destructive in Colorado’s history as hundreds of homes were devastated and thousands fled in fear. There were fears of a potential ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 'whiff of infected breath' all it takes...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4370091/whiff-infected-breath-catch-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUST a ‘whiff of infected breath’ is all that it takes to catch Omicron, an expert has warned today. While it might be easier to catch the bug, scientists say that those who get it will…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes turn to Prince Andrew...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/eyes-turn-prince-andrew-ghislaine-maxwells-sex-trafficking-conviction-rcna10397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Prince Andrew is facing scrutiny after Ghislaine Maxwell's conviction for helping to lure teenage girls for abuse by financier Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Colonists Will Likely Resort to Cannibalism, Scientist Says...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/space-colonists-resort-cannibalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts now say that future space colonists are likely going to face food troubles — and that might just turn them into cannibals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More quakes shake S Carolina...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-environment-and-nature-south-carolina-columbia-charleston-3ad3a90a3c26e1125c485d912789232f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELGIN, S.C. (AP) — Two more earthquakes have struck near Columbia, South Carolina, where seven quakes have been felt since Monday. The most recent earthquakes struck Tuesday in the Elgin area, about 20 miles (32 kilometers) northeast of Columbia, WLTX-TV reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents selling children shows desperation of Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-business-marriage-taliban-07933f71b06e4dfa5484e76a74292967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHEDAI CAMP, Afghanistan (AP) — In a sprawling settlement of mud brick huts in western Afghanistan housing people displaced by drought and war, a woman is fighting to save her daughter. Aziz Gul’s husband sold their 10-year-old into marriage without telling his wife, taking a down-payment so he could feed his family of five children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans seeking to renounce citizenship stuck with it for now...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/31/americans-seeking-renounce-citizenship-stuck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 30,000 citizens living abroad have been unable to secure a ‘loss of nationality’ interview during the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brink of OVER-vaccinating?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10358555/Experts-warn-dishing-fourth-jabs-spring-pointless.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Experts have warned against offer a second Covid booster arguing it is not practical to do so every three months. Claims of Omicron as a 'natural vaccine' are debatable experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years after end of her iconic show, Oprah still best embodies TV today...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/10-years-after-the-end-of-her-iconic-show-oprah-winfrey-still-best-embodies-tv-today/ar-AASiZql</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron passed peak in S Africa, causing few deaths and hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/omicron-has-passed-peak-in-south-africa-causing-relatively-few-deaths-and-hospitalizations-authorities-say/ar-AASiKZ7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Incoming Mayor Inherits Finances Soured by Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/nyc-s-incoming-mayor-inherits-finances-soured-by-the-pandemic-1.1701725</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Adams will take over as New York City’s mayor on Jan. 1 staring down a host of fiscal challenges largely stemming from the pandemic and the uncertain outlook it’s created for the biggest U.S. city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA warns of continued flight delays...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/587795-faa-warns-of-continued-flight-delays-amid-rising-covid-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) on Thursday warned that travelers can expect more flights to be canceled as the omicron variant continues to surge around the country,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Pumped Up Stocks. In '22, It May Pull Plug...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/31/the-feds-moves-pumped-up-stocks-in-2022-it-may-pull-the-plug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two years, the stock market has been largely able to ignore the lived reality of Americans during the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is That Burning Bush? Mt. Sinai? Solstice Bolsters Claim...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/31/is-that-a-burning-bush-is-this-mt-sinai-solstice-bolsters-a-claim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOUNT KARKOM, Israel — The mountain kept its secrets for centuries, its air of sacred mystery enhanced by a remote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Housing Market Stunning Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/31/in-2021-new-yorks-housing-market-made-a-stunning-comeback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year ago, while most of the country was seeing record home sales and prices, driven by low mortgage rates</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
