<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE sued by Black ex-employee over 'racially biased' culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/google-sued-by-black-ex-employee-over-e2-80-98racially-biased-e2-80-99-culture/ar-AAVfJAN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil bans TELEGRAM messaging service in crackdown on 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/brazil-bans-telegram-messaging-service-in-crackdown-on-e2-80-98fake-news-e2-80-99/ar-AAVfsMm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The push to shut Telegram in Brazil is part of wide-reaching efforts to combat misinformation and falsehoods about the country’s electoral system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAT team enforces emergency curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article259474324.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Miami Beach are saying a “silent prayer” as large spring break crowds once again pack South Beach a year after revelers overwhelmed the city and led police to call in a SWAT team to enforce its emergency curfew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Truckers Could Replace 500,000 Jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/self-driving-trucks-could-replace-90-of-long-haul-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot Truckers CouldÂ Replace 500K U.S. Jobs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwhelmed prosecutors quitting in tears amid staffing crisis, NYC district attorneys say...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/overwhelmed-prosecutors-quitting-tears-amid-231200659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Underpaid prosecutors overwhelmed by a mammoth backlog of cases are quitting in droves when their work is needed more than ever, the city’s district attorneys told the City Council on Friday. “Former staffers cited the responsibilities of discovery, managing the backlog of cases, and increased night and weekend shifts among the reasons why they leave,” Bronx District Attorney Darcel Clark told ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Scott says Supreme Court vote on Judge Jackson won't be based on skin color...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article259547289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee is scheduled to start Monday the first of several confirmation hearings for Supreme Court nominee Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO wants to avoid getting dragged into  war  -- by mistake...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/europe/2022-03-18/nato-avoid-war-russia-5389776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military commanders from NATO countries are working the phones with their Russian counterparts to make sure the U.S. and its allies don’t get dragged into a war over a misunderstanding on the Ukrainian border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Russians breaking through digital iron curtain -- leading to fights with friends and family...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/some-russians-are-breaking-through-putin-e2-80-99s-digital-iron-curtain-e2-80-94-leading-to-fights-with-friends-and-family/ar-AAVfYwb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney World criticized over 'racist' performance by Texas high school at Magic Kingdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/disney-world-criticized-over-racist-performance-by-texas-high-school-at-magic-kingdom/ar-AAVfxPG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives have scored big in Philly politics. Here comes establishment pushback...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/progressives-have-scored-big-in-philly-politics-here-comes-the-establishment-pushback/ar-AAVe3PH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa caucuses could lose their top status. Jimmy Carter put them on the map...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Iowa-caucuses-could-lose-their-top-status-Jimmy-17013513.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-shot presidential candidate arrived in Le Mars, Iowa, brimming with a confidence...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELEGRAM booms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/telegram-booms-russias-digital-landscape-044602058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Telegram messaging app has become a go-to platform since Russia's invasion of Ukraine, despite concerns over its data security and defenses against misinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly find shelter in subways...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/elderly-ukrainians-shelter-metro-carriages-102912348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is not clear what makes Valentyna Katkova cry more: illness and old age, or the fact that she now lives in a Kyiv subway car, fleeing Russian bombing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother of Chicago twins who helped take down 'El Chapo' admits to burying millions in drug proceeds under porch...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brother-chicago-twins-helped-down-181200879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Chicago twins Pedro and Margarito Flores were just 16 when their older brother Armando was arrested in the late 1990s for selling narcotics out of a Cicero auto dealership. Armando was later sentenced to five years in federal prison, and his absence created a vacuum for his younger brothers to fill. Within a few years, the twins had risen to the highest levels of Chicago’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 American Marines killed during  exercise in Norway...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/4-american-marines-killed-during-123117908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Jonas Gahr Stoere tweeted that the plane crash occurred overnight while troops were participating in the NATO Cold Response exercise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the transfer of foreign military equipment to Ukrainian soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/europe/2022-03-18/secret-transfer-military-equipment-ukrainian-soldiers-5390190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were no passport officers on the dirt road, no customs lane, no signs marking this isolated patch of farmland for what it has become: a clandestine gateway for military supplies entering Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERLIN:  Ukrainian Jews find refuge in what was once Europe's 'center of darkness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/purim-in-berlin-ukrainian-jews-find-refuge-in-what-was-once-europe-s-center-of-darkness/ar-AAVg20g?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin rallies Russians forced to attend by employers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-channels-hitler-sinister-new-26505434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian president gave a pro-war speech in front of tens of thousands of “Z” flag-waving supporters at a Moscow stadium, which has now been compared to Hitler's speeches in Nazi Germany</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN USES HYPERSONIC MISSILES</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-putin-uses-deadly-hypersonic-26506222</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadly conflict in Ukraine has taken a sinister turn as Russia's leader Vladimir Putin has decided to unleash hypersonic missiles for the first time as he continues his invasion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's 70 degrees warmer than normal in Antarctica. Scientists are flabbergasted...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/it-e2-80-99s-70-degrees-warmer-than-normal-in-eastern-antarctica-scientists-are-flabbergasted/ar-AAVfk4m?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEED CUT ON STATE TV</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putins-speech-at-staged-patriotic-rally-is-abruptly-cut-off-kremlin-claims-it-was-just-a-glitch/ar-AAVfoGS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed signals from Zelensky and his aides leave West confused about his end game...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mixed-signals-from-ukraine-e2-80-99s-president-and-his-aides-leave-west-confused-about-his-end-game/ar-AAVffAp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALES OF THE DEAD:  William Hurt's Former Partner on Surviving Abuse and Speaking Her Truth...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/donna-kaz-william-hurt-former-partner-surviving-abuse-1235208312/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donna Kaz is a multi-genre writer and the author of “Un/Masked, Memoirs of a Guerrilla Girl On Tour,” which covers her relationship with the late William Hurt and her path to becoming a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man pleads guilty to taking two bear cubs from den...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/man-pleads-guilty-taking-two-113020579.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cubs were estimated to have been less than 4 weeks old when they were taken, wildlife officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp &amp; Amber Heard Calling James Franco, Elon Musk As Witnesses In $100M Trial...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/johnny-depp-trial-amber-heard-lawsuit-domestic-abuse-james-franco-paul-bettany-elon-musk-disney-lapd-witnesses-1234982065/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There likely won’t be a red carpet rolled out in front of the Fairfax County courthouse, but some big names are coming to Johnny Depp’s now $100 million defamation battle with ex-wife A…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOLING DEMAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/wrapup-1-higher-mortgage-rates-152922142.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. home sales fell by the most in a year in February as a perennial shortage of houses and double-digit price growth continued to squeeze first-time buyers out of the market. With mortgage rates rising above 4% for the first time in nearly three years, sales are likely to slow this year, though that would do little to curb house price inflation. Existing home sales dropped 7.2% to a seasonally adjusted annual rate of 6.02 million units last month, the largest decrease since February 2021, the National Association of Realtors said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost children survive 25-day ordeal in Amazon...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220318-lost-children-survive-25-day-ordeal-in-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Brazilian Indigenous boys aged seven and nine have been found after surviving 25 days lost in the Amazon rainforest, where they ate fruit and drank rainwater to stay alive, officials said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syria's Assad visits UAE, 1st trip to Arab country since war...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/world/article259554114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Syrian presidency says President Bashar Assad has travelled to the United Arab Emirates, marking his first visit to an Arab country since Syria’s civil war erupted in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retiring Dem Rep Decries Party's Radical Turn...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/retiring-dem-rep-decries-partys-radical-turn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview published Friday by Politico, retiring Rep. Stephanie Murphy (D., Fla.) decried the Democratic Party's radical turn on issues ranging from immigration to infrastructure to capitalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABRUPTLY CUT OFF</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-s-speech-at-staged-patriotic-rally-was-abruptly-cut-off-the-kremlin-claims-it-was-a-glitch/ar-AAVfoGS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST PUBLIC APPEARANCE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-makes-his-first-public-appearance-since-the-invasion-of-ukraine/ar-AAVfhcv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN MASS RALLY</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-state-tv-cuts-away-140224438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian state television suddenly cut away from Putin hailing what Russia calls its special operation in Ukraine and the bravery of its soldiers, to show patriotic songs being played at the event instead. It later aired the full speech, which ended a few seconds after the cutaway with Putin leaving the stage as thousands of spectators waved Russian flags at the 80,000-capacity Luzhniki stadium. Russia sent tens of thousands of troops into Ukraine on Feb. 24 in an effort to degrade its southern neighbour’s military capabilities and root out people it called dangerous nationalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will NJ wave hello to new source of energy from ocean?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-new-jersey-environment-atlantic-city-94675aeaeecea90c7f0c36ff5fe564d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — Some New Jersey lawmakers want to harness the power of the ocean's waves to create a new source of clean electricity, and several companies say they are eager to build projects there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad signs for US as Covid cases rise in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/18/us-covid-next-surge-variant-ba2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US must prepare now for the next surge or variant, whether it’s BA.2 or a different one, experts say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside lab where you can clone your pet...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4897814/viagen-dog-cat-clone-lab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US company that clones cats and dogs has a “huge waiting list” after interest spiked during Covid. ViaGen has been “extremely successful” cloning cats and dogs since 2015,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive NFL surprise...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/18/deshaun-watson-being-traded-to-cleveland-browns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When he’s able to suit up again next remains a question, as the NFL’s personal conduct investigation into the 26-year-old is reportedly ongoing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governor proposes $850 inflation-relief checks...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/mar/18/janet-mills-maine-governor-proposes-850-inflation-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maine’s governor released a revised budget proposal on Friday that would increase checks the state plans to send to residents to $850.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watson's Record $230M BROWNS Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33538489/deshaun-watson-willing-waive-no-trade-clause-cleveland-browns-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texans quarterback Deshaun Watson has decided that he wants to play for the Browns, who are set to give him a new five-year, $230 million contract that is fully guaranteed, sources told ESPN's Adam Schefter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk on track to be world's first trillionaire...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/money/4926214/elon-musk-first-trillionaire-jeff-bezos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk is on track to become the world’s first trillionaire, according to a new study. While the 50-year-old’s SpaceX founder’s personal wealth could reach $1trillion dollars i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivor of Afghan Bombings: Working for TESLA Was Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/survivor-of-afghanistan-bombings-working-for-tesla-was-hell/ar-AAVf6UD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian foreign minister praises FOXNEWS for coverage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-foreign-minister-praises-fox-news-for-ukraine-coverage-184200756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After three weeks of bitter and barbaric fighting in Ukraine, Russian Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov praised the coverage of the war from one American media outlet: Fox News.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
