<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SUPERMOON SAVES THE SUEZ</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14484562/suez-canal-ship-refloated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE mega-ship blocking the Suez Canal has FINALLY been refloated and moved down the channel thanks to a supermoon. Officials said that rescuers have successfully freed the front end of the monster …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandstorms turn sun blue and sky yellow in Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/mar/29/sandstorms-turn-sun-blue-and-sky-yellow-in-beijing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thick dust carrying extremely high levels of hazardous particles blows in from drought-hit Mongolia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Year Is It? Oldies Take Up 8 of the Top 20 on iTunes...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/03/29/what-year-is-it-oldies-take-up-8-of-the-top-20-on-itunes-including-1994-zombie-and-1970-spirit-in-the-sky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What year is it again? While Lil Nas X’s “Montero (Call Me By Your Name)” is number 1, and Justin Bieber is in the top 10, the iTunes chart continues to be rife with Oldies. Oldie…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Your vacation is my home': Hawaii residents speaking out against tourists behaving badly...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/hawaii/article/hawaii-residents-locals-tourists-behaving-badly-16056414.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having had a taste of a tourist-free state, some residents have come to prefer the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New warehouse worker robot can shift 800 boxes an hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tech-robots-boston-dynamics-stretch/boston-dynamics-introduces-stretch-new-warehouse-worker-robot-idUSKBN2BL15U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. robotics company Boston Dynamics on Monday unveiled a new robot called Stretch, designed to perform one very specific warehouse job: moving boxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials, forged by recession and ridicule, ascendant in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/millennials-forged-recession-ridicule-are-ascendant-washington-n1262002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The much-maligned generation is aging into the ruling class, forged by near-constant crises and institutional failures — plus a side of avocado toast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her pet chickens were source of emotional support during pandemic. Then, the hawks came...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/her-pet-chickens-were-a-source-of-emotional-support-during-the-pandemic-then-the-hawks-came/ar-BB1f5owR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pet chickens provide pandemic relief, owners, say. But they can also bring heartache.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS PUTS LARA ON PAYROLL...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/fox-news-hires-lara-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lara Trump, the daughter-in-law of former president Donald Trump, is joining the cable channel as a contributor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIL NAS 'Satan' shoes stirs new political controversy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/545332-lil-nas-x-releases-unofficial-satan-shoes-featuring-a-drop-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Lil Nas X has released an unofficial pair of custom “Satan Shoes” that feature a drop of human blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Church membership dips below 50% for first time...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/341963/church-membership-falls-below-majority-first-time.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in Gallup's polling history, less than half of U.S. adults report belonging to a church, synagogue or mosque.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange, Distant Space Object Sending Out Ultra-Low Frequency...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/strange-distant-space-object-sending-out-ultra-low-frequency-radio-signals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have discovered a distant space object that is emitting ultra-low radio frequencies — in the shape of a jellyfish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In San Fran, Turmoil Over Reopening Schools Turns City Against Self...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/29/in-san-francisco-turmoil-over-reopening-schools-turns-a-city-against-itself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — The pandemic has brought grinding frustrations for parents, educators and students across the country. But perhaps no</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alliance of Autocracies? China to Lead New World Order...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/29/an-alliance-of-autocracies-china-wants-to-lead-a-new-world-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden wants to forge an “alliance of democracies.” China wants to make clear that it has alliances of its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauvin trial in George Floyd death underway...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trials-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-minneapolis-7423d17dfc00daa660fce0b35b87a163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The former Minneapolis police officer charged with killing George Floyd went on trial Monday, with a prosecutor telling the jury that the figure to remember is 9 minutes, 29...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Normal: Were you really that great in first place?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-coronavirus-pandemic-taylor-swift-160aebc4aef58fbe97395ec08ababa60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dear Normal, Everyone wants you back. It seems every day of this late-stage pandemic era is marked with someone wistfully talking about Normal: going back to you, starting new with you. It’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global banks warn of possible hedge fund defaults...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-b0ffd8047469e566ea24ba5609c6ed23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Swiss bank Credit Suisse said Monday it may have suffered a “highly significant” loss from a default by a U.S.-based hedge fund on margin calls that it and other banks made last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO:  ANIMALS STARTED IT!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/animals-coronavirus-pandemic-bats-united-nations-china-8a839c179c330c56fa46a763b7286a7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A joint World Health Organization-China study on the origins of COVID-19 says that transmission of the virus from bats to humans through another animal is the most likely scenario...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief criticizes wealthy countries for 'stockpile'...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/un-secretary-general-antonio-guterres-criticises-wealthy-countries-for-stockpile-of-covid-19-vaccines-2401318</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres criticized developed countries for creating a "stockpile" of Covid-19 vaccines, and called on them to share with the rest of the world to help end the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris urges caution as England takes first big step out of lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/28/johnson-urges-caution-as-england-takes-first-big-step-out-of-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outdoor group socialising allowed from Monday but ad campaign stresses Covid risks of indoor meeting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate accused of pandering after he transforms into cowboy for TX congressional run...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/GOP-candidate-accused-of-pandering-after-he-16059538.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey boy. Pro wrestler. Republican candidate in Nevada. Dan Rodimer has led many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oil for vaccines,' offers Venezuela's Maduro as Covid bites...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/venezuelas-maduro-proposes-paying-coronavirus-000107796.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro on Sunday proposed paying for vaccines against the novel coronavirus with oil, though he provided few details about how such a scheme would work. The crisis-stricken OPEC nation's crude exports have plummeted to their lowest levels in decades since Washington sanctioned state oil company Petroleos de Venezuela in 2019, cutting off Venezuela's exports to the United States and dissuading many other customers from buying Venezuelan oil as well. Maduro said Venezuela was working to pay for vaccines from the World Health Organization's (WHO) COVAX mechanism - which provides vaccine access to poor countries - both through Venezuelan funds frozen in overseas accounts due to sanctions, and through oil shipments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINION won't rule out suing Trump next!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/dominion-wont-rule-out-lawsuit-against-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump may yet face a lawsuit from Dominion Voting Systems for spreading election fraud claims about the 2020 contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO GRAND JURIES INVESTIGATING TRUMP IN GA</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-unlikely-team-hunting-team-donald-trump-in-georgia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public integrity unit at the Fulton County District Attorney’s office once had a miserable reputation. Now, a new crew there is investigating the biggest target of them all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>;l;;gmlxzssaw:  US Strategic Command posts bizarre tweet sparking hacking fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2599127/us-strategic-command-bizarre-tweet-fears-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BIZARRE tweet from the US Strategic Command has prompted a flurry on Twitter as people try and decipher what it may mean. The government account tweet came around 7:50pm, and began to go viral as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discarded Face Masks Killing Wildlife Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-waste-face-masks-killing-wildlife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers warn that pets are also at risk of accidentally swallowing a face mask, especially dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious disease killing young California bears in Tahoe. One symptom: Fearlessness...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article250247805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sickly female cub was covered in ticks when it was captured. What veterinarians discovered about her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis threatens to sue CDC if doesn't lift ban on cruises...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/florida-desantis-lawsuit-threat-cdc-cruise-covid-order-41427821-dff9-44fe-a84f-c1d87c3614b9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say it's "too early" for cruises to resume, given the higher risk of COVID spreading among passengers on ships, per AP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY SOME BOXOFFICE:  'GODZILLA VS KONG' sets pandemic record...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/box-office-coming-back-godzilla-191405637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros.' 'Godzilla Vs. Kong' debuted to $121.8 million in international markets, while Universal's 'Nobody' was solid in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's true death toll 60% higher than official figure!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2597851/mexico-covid-death-toll-higher-second-wave-brazil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO’S government has acknowledged that the country’s true death toll from the coronavirus pandemic now stands above 321,000, almost 60 per cent more than the official test-confirmed number…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Paid LA Lifeguards Earn Up To $392,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamandrzejewski/2021/03/27/top-paid-la-lifeguards-earned-up-to-392000-in-2019/?sh=f3f2d0240129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven lifeguards made more than $300,000 and 82 lifeguards had total earnings that exceed $200,000 in 2019, the latest year available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fuels travel boom -- in virtual reality!</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2021-03-pandemic-fuels-boomin-virtual-reality.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jem Jenkins Jones was stuck at home in Wales for much of the past year amid pandemic lockdowns but managed to fulfill a promise to her 10-year-old daughter to see the northern lights from Iceland and South Africa's game reserves—in virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman dies after being struck by car while chasing robbery suspects...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/woman-dies-being-struck-car-163306641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman died Friday after she was struck by a car while chasing after two men who might have robbed her in Lancaster, investigators said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Professor Wins Preferred Gender Pronouns Case...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/first-amendment/trump-bush-appeals-court-judges-rule-in-favor-of-professor-of-christian-thought-who-refused-to-call-students-by-their-preferred-gender-pronouns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 6th Circuit on Friday ruled in favor of a "devout Christian" professor who was disciplined because he "refused to refer to students by their 'preferred pronouns.'"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems could undo Trump policies faster, but they're not. Why?</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/congressional-review-act-why-democrats-are-not-undoing-trump-health-policies-faster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The little-used Congressional Review Act allows a new administration and Congress to fast-track the repeal of regulations and other executive actions of the previous administration. But neither law…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauvin trial represents 'defining moment in America's racial history'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/derek-chauvin-trial-represents-defining-214600581.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Floyd pleading for his life under the knee of a Minneapolis police officer has become a defining moment of our time. What began 10 months ago at the corner of 38th Street and Chicago Avenue has transformed into nothing less than an American reckoning on justice, racial equity, the proper role of law enforcement and the historical wrongs society has perpetrated on Black people. Monday ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Brazilians disregard the pleas to stay at home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-brazil-rio-de-janeiro-coronavirus-pandemic-holidays-f7acdacac7446ca40753aacf5c77cb3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Authorities in Sao Paulo and Rio de Janeiro begged the population to stay home, but thousands of Brazilians are traveling to coastal cities and ignoring recommendations on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurors face heavy burden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-shootings-trials-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-d89d8aa796d203681a04bef0c1ca5fe7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — One prospective juror's voice quivered as she told attorneys during jury selection that she feared for her family's safety if chosen for the panel that will decide the fate of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris doctors warn of catastrophic overload...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-paris-coronavirus-pandemic-france-emmanuel-macron-f0cb190686641139ffb41e493afd3d2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Critical care doctors in Paris say surging coronavirus infections could soon overwhelm their ability to care for the sick in the French capital's hospitals, possibly forcing them to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network tricked director?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/03/28/exclusive-cbs-never-told-woody-allen-team-news-interview-would-move-to-pay-service-lied-to-us-month-after-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Lee Cowan interviewed Woody Allen last July for “CBS Sunday Morning,” it was a news segment tied to the release of Allen’s memoir, “Apropos of Nothing.” But the p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic, deadly flooding grips Nashville...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/nashville-inundated-by-life-threatening-flooding-after-severe-storms-tear-across-south/923109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid another round of severe weather this March across the southern U.S., heavy downpours and flooding became "extremely dangerous and life-threatening" in Tennessee, resulting in four fatalities.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
