<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Warns of Mutants as Tougher Curbs Take Effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/merkel-warns-of-virus-mutants-as-tougher-curbs-take-effect/ar-BB1g01Mw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany’s new lockdown law, which automatically imposes tougher curbs in places where new infections exceed a certain threshold, came into effect on Saturday after both houses of parliament backed Chancellor Angela Merkel’s bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLD CITY UNREST</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9508445/Clashes-Jerusalem-continue-Israeli-Prime-Minister-calls-calm-sides.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh clashes broke out later Saturday between Palestinians and police after Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu called for 'calm on all sides' after several nights of unrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first 'floating' sky pool...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/14741221/rooftop-swimming-pool-london-nine-elms-sky/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s first ‘floating’ sky pool with a glass bottom and views from 115ft above the streets of London is opening next month. The pool, located between two blocks of luxury flats in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians Won't Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2765537/caitlyn-jenner-dons-cap-california-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAITLYN Jenner was spotted wearing a “Caitlyn for California” cap just hours after announcing her plans to run for governor. The former Olympian and Keeping Up With the Kardashians star…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCALATION OVER JERUSALEM</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/escalation-over-jerusalem-is-how-wars-start-analysis-666229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is important to understand that this timeline is similar to how tensions grew in 2014 and other cycles that led to tensions in Gaza and Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costa Rica hits record infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210424211635-yadcz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/COSTA RICA (PIX):Costa Rica hits new daily record of COVID-19 infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontrunner 'NOMADLAND' Set For Lowest Boxoffice Ever For Best Picture...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/oscars-best-picture-winner-lowest-box-office-record-nomadland-minari-1234742718/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter which film takes home Best Picture Sunday night, that title will be the lowest-grossing in Oscar history. According to Comscore, Kathryn Bigelow’s 2009 title The Hurt Locker stands …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR TREK' Shuts Down After Scare In Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/covid-star-trek-discovery-shutdown-toronto-cbs-studios-1234742843/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: As the coronavirus infections surge in and around Toronto once again, Star Trek Discovery has hit the pause button on production. Months into shooting its fourth season, the Sonequa Mart…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA's exodus overshadowed by migration within its borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-churning-golden-state-on-the-eve-of-new-population-numbers/ar-BB1g0GYe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has seen an out-of-state exodus, but its internal migration is equally profound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians Won't Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9507317/The-Kardashians-NOT-hit-campaign-trail-Caitlyn-Jenner-announced-bid-Governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not a single member of the Kardashian klan has spoken out about Jenner's run over a day after she formally announced her campaign Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran fuel tanker attacked off Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210424-iran-fuel-tanker-attacked-off-syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran fuel tanker attacked off Syria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early front-runners like Yang usually win NYC mayoral primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/24/politics/nyc-mayoral-race-analysis/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York City Democratic mayoral primary is now less than two months away, on June 22. The polls indicate that businessman and former 2020 presidential candidate Andrew Yang continues to hold a clear lead in the first New York City mayoral election being held under ranked choice voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala skillfully running silent and deep...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/549369-kamala-harris-skillfully-running-silent-and-deep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When immersed in turbulent political waters, experienced politicians know to hold their cards to their chests and consider all obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world isolates. A New Zealand band plays to 50,000 fans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-health-music-sports-arts-and-entertainment-13fbb155e4796d07c239030af7a7c6c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand (AP) — Singer Matiu Walters grinned as he gazed out over 50,000 damp but delirious fans and said those magic words: “So, what’s up Eden Park?” While much of the world remains hunkered down, the band Six60 has been playing to huge crowds in New Zealand, where social distancing isn't required after the nation stamped out the coronavirus. The band’s tour finale on Saturday night was billed as the largest concert in the world since the pandemic began. Equally momentous for a band which met while playing rugby at university was getting to play the first concert ever held at the storied Eden Park rugby stadium. And finding themselves at the apex of world music came as a twist for Six60, which has enjoyed unparalleled success in New Zealand but whose forays abroad have ended without the breakthroughs they sought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden will close first chapter of presidency before sparse crowd - and with historic backdrop...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Biden-will-close-the-first-chapter-of-his-16125959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - For eight years, Joe Biden was a fixture at President Barack Obama's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling to stay afloat, people turn to strangers online for help...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/Struggling-to-stay-afloat-during-the-pandemic-16126025.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - It took Josh Mitchell weeks to convince his sister to let him set up a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes before Trump left office, millions of Pentagon's dormant IP addresses sprang to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Minutes-before-Trump-left-office-millions-of-the-16126007.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - While the world was distracted with President Donald Trump leaving office on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornadoes, hail and stunning skies make for unforgettable Texas storm chase...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Tornadoes-hail-and-stunning-skies-make-for-16126049.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WICHITA FALLS, Texas - I've stalked tornadoes, floods, solar eclipses and hurricanes; my...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIA SOS</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-56870410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients are dying because of a lack of medical oxygen supplies, doctors warn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest space station crowd in decade after SPACEX arrival...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-53d48c39d1dfaa941dea519a9199aa3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The International Space Station's population swelled to 11 on Saturday with the jubilant arrival of SpaceX's third crew capsule in less than a year. It's the biggest crowd up there in more than a decade. All of the astronauts — representing the U.S., Russia, Japan and France — managed to squeeze into camera view for a congratulatory call from the leaders of their space agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volatile and Vengeful: How Scott Rudin Wielded Power in Show Business...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/volatile-and-vengeful-how-scott-rudin-wielded-power-in-show-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Rudin has long been one of the most celebrated and powerful producers in Hollywood and, especially, on Broadway —</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrorism Fears Feed Rise of France's Extreme Right...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/terrorism-fears-feed-the-rise-of-frances-extreme-right/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — “Marine Le Pen does not have to say anything,” said Alain Frachon, a former editor of the French</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Arms Merchant in  Sights of Russia's Elite Assassination Squad...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/the-arms-merchant-in-the-sights-of-russias-elite-assassination-squad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a major arms merchant, Emilian Gebrev cuts the modest figure of a bemused grandfather, preferring soccer jerseys and polo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London protest: Thousands march in fury over lockdown and vaccine passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1427536/london-news-protest-oxford-street-vaccine-passport-lockdown-police-breaking-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of protestors have gathered in central London this afternoon to object to the continued lockdown measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists probe mysterious melting of Earth's crust...</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-04/uow-spm042221.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unusual belt of igneous rocks stretches for over 2,000 miles from British Columbia, Canada, to Sonora, Mexico, running through Idaho, Montana, Nevada, southeast California and Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk warns 'people will probably die' during SPACEX mission to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-warns-people-probably-23974161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk told Peter Diamandis people will "probably die" during Space X's Mars mission but claimed that it will be "an amazing experience" for voyagers, calling the trip a "glorious adventure"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash Over 'Gov Jenner'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9506971/Caitlyn-Jenner-faces-backlash-LGBTQ-community-bid-Californias-governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jenner, 71, announced her run on social media Friday under the slogan 'Caitlyn For California' sparking an instant backlash on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Investor Reveals Secret to Success: Shrooms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/billionaire-investor-reveals-secret-success-184839538.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/Andreas Rentz/GettyGerman investor Christian Angermayer—a 42-year-old billionaire who bears a not-negligible resemblance to Jared Leto in Blade Runner 2049—has made a fortune betting on a host of sci-fi-sounding finance fads. Among them: space travel, crypto, psychedelics, movies, weed, SPACs, and “life extension.”Those ventures have done pretty well for him. In the past year alone, seven companies Angermayer’s family office funded went public, raising a combined $1 billion; another 10 companies are slated to issue IPOs this year, according to Bloomberg Wealth. But in a recent profile, Angermayer cited a single experience as having paved the way for his billions: doing hallucinogenic mushrooms.When the investor Zoomed with Bloomberg last month, he called in from his home in London, where he’d hung an “ancient statue of Hecate, the Greek goddess of witchcraft, in the background.” From there, Angermayer detailed his conversion from life-long straight-edge to something out of a Phish festival, after a revelatory chat with a neuroscientist eight years prior.Sean Hannity Drops $5 Million on Mansion Near Mar-a-LagoAngermayer said the doctor confirmed his instinct to avoid hard drugs, but suggested psilocybin mushrooms were less dangerous than other vices, like alcohol. British researcher David Nutt, for example, published a chart of drugs ranked by harmfulness, which lists alcohol at the top and shrooms dead last.When Angermayer went on a trip to the Caribbean with some close friends in 2015, he gave shrooms a try. The experience, the billionaire said, “was the single most meaningful thing I’ve done in my whole life.”In the ego death of his hallucinations, Angermayer “finally understood Bitcoin.”The Bloomberg piece describes Angermayer as “a German version of Chamath Palihapitiya, the serial SPAC-dealmaker who views himself as the Warren Buffett of the Reddit era.” And like Palihapitiya, the billionaire has been bullish on SPACs or “special purpose acquisition companies”—the blank-check companies that soared in popularity early this year, drawing warnings from the SEC and financial advisers. One of Angermayer’s is looking to raise some $200 million.Investigators to Elon Musk: Instead of Tweeting, Give Us Crash DataHe has also gotten involved in some murky corporate deals. Last summer, Angermayer collected multimillion-dollar fees for brokering a Softbank deal with the German financial company Wirecard, not long after the latter collapsed and was accused of widespread fraud. A friend whom Angermayer had helped get a board position at Deutsche Bank AG was later served with a criminal complaint for charges related to the Wirecard scandal.On Tuesday, one of Angermayer’s investments filed for an IPO. It was a company called Atai Life Sciences–a biotech company backed by Palantir co-founder Peter Thiel, the guy who paid for Hulk Hogan to sue Gawker into non-existence. The firm, valued at $2 billion, focuses on psychedelics.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARLEY Unleashes the Silent E-Hogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/harley-unleashes-the-silent-e-hogs/ar-BB1g04yW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company is all-in on electric motorcycles, though the financial gearing still isn’t great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani, Lindell win Razzies for worst film performances...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/trump-supporters-giuliani-lindell-win-razzies-for-worst-film-performances-666196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Mayor Rudy Giuliani's unwitting appearance in "Borat Subsequent Moviefilm" was named one of the year's worst performances by voters for the annual Razzie prizes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Hunt for Ways Around Tax Hikes They Were Warned About...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-04-24/rich-americans-hunt-for-ways-around-tax-hikes-they-were-warned-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Joe Biden and state lawmakers target millionaires and billionaires, wealth advisers are trying to help their clients adapt to the new rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn after being misgendered on 'THE VIEW': 'Bigger issues than pronouns'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/550093-caitlyn-jenner-on-being-misgendered-by-the-view-co-host-california-has-bigger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner responded to "The View" co-host Joy Behar after the daytime talk show figure repeatedly misgendered her on Friday, telling her not to "sweat it" and focusing instead on her gubernatorial bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro says military would follow his orders to take streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210424011831-g1ikl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/BOLSONARO:Brazil's Bolsonaro says military would follow his orders to take the streets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Approval Rating Has Fallen. He Could Still Win Re-Election...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/cuomos-approval-rating-has-fallen-he-could-still-win-re-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo of New York has not had much good news over the past few months. His poll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the cave: French isolation study ends after 40 days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-health-science-environment-and-nature-caves-82c18f720f0e08962191ddb68e2eeb39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOMBRIVES CAVE, France (AP) — Ever wonder what it would feel like to unplug from a hyperconnected world and hide away in a cave for a few weeks? Fifteen people in France found out. After 40 days in voluntary isolation in a dark, damp and vast cave, eight men and seven women who took part in a scientific experiment emerged Saturday from their self-segregation in the Pyrenees. With big smiles on their pale faces, the 15 participants exited the Lombrives cave to a round of applause and basked in the light of day while wearing special glasses to protect their eyes after so long in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza militants fire rockets after clashes flare in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/24/gaza-militants-fire-rockets-after-clashes-flare-in-jerusalem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rockets seen as response to unrest in mostly Palestinian east Jerusalem, including far-right Jewish groups chanting ‘death to Arabs’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those who got covid between doses urge caution: 'We were so close'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Those-who-got-covid-between-vaccine-doses-urge-16125805.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abbey Quinn regrets the Easter dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia may label Navalny opposition networks extremists groups. Even T-shirts outlawed?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Russia-may-label-Navalny-s-opposition-networks-as-16125797.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - A closed-door Moscow court hearing Monday is expected to officially ban the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As pandemic surges anew, global envy and anger over U.S. vax abundance...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/As-pandemic-surges-anew-global-envy-and-anger-16125800.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As India announced a grim records - the highest daily coronavirus infection tallies in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon UFO report: They 'acknowledged the reality,' whistleblower says...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/24/pentagon-ufo-report-its-a-reality-whistleblower-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US government is gearing up to share the “reality” of UFOs with the public — and not a moment too soon, says the man who claims to have run the Pentagon’s UFO program for 9 ye…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacKenzie Scott Gave Away Billions. The Scam Artists Followed...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/mackenzie-scott-gave-away-billions-the-scam-artists-followed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danielle Churchill needed help. She was raising five children in Wollongong, on the Australian coast south of Sydney, and had</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
