<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Avg Age of Startup Founder: 34...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-21/what-s-the-average-age-of-a-startup-founder-it-s-34-study-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research undercuts the perception that creating successful companies is a young person’s game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians clash with Israeli police in Jerusalem hours after Gaza truce...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210521105316-9nv5m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/JERUSALEM (PIX):Palestinians clash with Israeli police in Jerusalem hours after Gaza truce</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHC says 40% chance of cyclone over western Gulf of Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210521104716-xo4rp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-ATLANTIC/GULFMEXICO (URGENT):NHC says 40% chance of cyclone over western Gulf of Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New type of coronavirus originating in dogs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210521075401-ui3w9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ANIMALS:New type of coronavirus originating in dogs found - study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Tax Gathers Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/global-tax-revamp-gathers-pace-as-europe-salutes-u-s-proposal/ar-AAKerQK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. proposal for a global minimum corporate tax of at least 15% met with an enthusiastic reception in Europe, bringing the world closer to a deal on sweeping changes to how much multinationals pay, and to which governments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World-Dominating Superstar Firms Get Bigger, Techier, More Chinese...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2021-biggest-global-companies-growth-trends/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty years of data shows just how big the biggest have grown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major dating apps adding vax badges to profiles...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/554687-major-dating-apps-including-tinder-okcupid-adding-vaccination-badges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major dating apps are adding vaccination badges and special benefits to users' profiles who say they received the coronavirus vaccine in an effort to reach the Biden administration's July 4 inoculation goal.&amp;nb</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shows Like 'COPS' Fell Out of Favor. Now Texas May Ban Them...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/21/shows-like-cops-fell-out-of-favor-now-texas-may-ban-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years ago, a television crew gathered in the small city of Hawkins, Texas, to film the life and work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Since leaving office, Donald has charged Secret Service $40,000 to use space at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Since-leaving-office-Trump-has-charged-the-16193254.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former president Donald Trump charged the Secret Service more than $40,000 this spring...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry tells Oprah mom's death led him to drugs, accuses royals of 'neglect'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/prince-harry-tells-oprah-diana-s-death-led-him-drink-n1268106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I was so angry with what happened to her, and the fact that there was no justice at all," Prince Harry told Oprah Winfrey about his mother's death in a new interview released Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot paramedic used for first time to carry out chest compressions in ambulance...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/business/technology/arid-40295015.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot paramedic used for first time to carry out chest compressions in ambulance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive FBI dig continues on bank of lake in Florida community...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/secretive-fbi-dig-continues-on-the-bank-of-a-lake-in-oakland-park-residential-community/article_62b4df7a-ae28-5097-a7fd-a0124c734228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND PARK, Fla. — Human remains? Evidence? Whatever it is the FBI and Broward Sheriff’s Office have been digging for since Wednesday, they are keeping a tight lid on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-camera EMDR session...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9603585/Prince-Harry-tells-trauama-therapist-fears-visiting-UK.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of Sussex said in his new mental health documentary series with Oprah Winfrey that he has 'always felt worried' for most of his life when he flies back to London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz insulted 'woke, emasculated' Army ad. Angry vets fired back...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Sen-Ted-Cruz-insulted-a-woke-emasculated-U-S-16193325.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first half of the TikTok video shows a muscular Russian man with a shaved head doing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears history repeating with Meghan...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/05/21/harry-likens-relationship-with-meghan-to-diana-and-dodi-fayeds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry compared the consistent hounding of the Duchess of Sussex to the relationship that his mother had to Dodi Fayed who was with her when Diana was killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Excess deaths much higher than reported virus toll...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-05-excess-deaths-due-pandemic-higher.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up to three times more people have died due to the pandemic than indicated by the officially reported COVID deaths, the World Health Organization said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Half See Favorite Local Store Close...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/shoppers-swearing-off-big-box-stores-local-shops-shut-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of 2,000 people reveals 68 percent personally know a local business owner impacted by the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy calls with aides, lawyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/chris-cuomo-took-part-in-strategy-calls-advising-his-brother-the-new-york-governor-on-how-to-respond-to-sexual-harassment-allegations/ar-AAKcCly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement, CNN acknowledged that the anchor engaged in conversations with Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo and his staff, saying that his participation was ‘inappropriate’ and that he will not take part in such discussions in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates Carefully Curated Dad-Geek Image Unravels in Two Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://techcentral.co.za/bill-gatess-carefully-curated-dad-geek-image-unravels/107408/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcentral.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before all the revelations about his divorce, dubious workplace behaviour and ties to Jeffrey Epstein, Bill Gates was just America’s huggable billionaire techno-philanthropist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Israel-Hamas truce takes hold after 11 days of fighting...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210520230505-96knj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 2-Israel-Hamas truce takes hold after 11 days of fighting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin to would-be aggressors: 'Will knock their teeth out'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-government-and-politics-849973d3f0a216d135b32571b99ecc1a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin alleged Thursday that some of the country's foreign foes dream about biting off pieces of the country's vast territory, warning that Moscow would “knock their teeth out” if they ever try.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Teammate Says Tebow 'Wasn't Good', Rips JAGS For Signing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/former-nfl-teammate-says-tim-tebow-wasnt-good-as-te-says-tebow-joining-jaguars-would-be-stupid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tebow continues to face scrutiny as he awaits the Jaguars' decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese syringes getting stuck in patients' arms...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210520201457-9lz96</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-SYRINGES (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-FDA recommends not using syringes from Chinese firm after safety issues with vaccine injections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken does NOT want to buy Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210520183650-w9fyo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENLAND-USA/ (URGENT):Blinken confirms the U.S. does not want to buy Greenland after Trump proposal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall of the House of Gates?</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/society/gates-me-too-divorce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fully reckoning with Bill Gates means not just focusing on how he treats women—vital as that is—but also confronting our own deep-seated worship of wealth and hard-wired belief in hero narratives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Wants Miami Un-Woke, Pro-Bitcoin, Tech Billionaire's Paradise...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/2021/05/20/mayor-francis-suarez-wants-to-turn-miami-into-an-un-woke-pro-bitcoin-tech-billionaires-paradise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ignore the hype: Latin American immigration is (still) the city’s greatest strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance Giant Pays $40 Million in Ransom After Cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://www.swfinstitute.org/news/86466/cna-financial-pays-40-million-in-ransom-after-cyberattack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.swfinstitute.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promise and Perils of New Fertility Entrepreneurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/tech/annals-of-technology/the-promise-and-perils-of-the-new-fertility-entrepreneurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Startups are pushing a breezy but proactive attitude toward reproduction, centered on preëmptive treatments during one’s most fertile years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>43% of Millennials 'Don't Know, Care, or Believe God Exists'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2021/05/20/survey-43-millennials-dont-know-care-believe-god-exists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey from Arizona Christian University found Millennials are rejecting faith in God and looking to government to provide a better life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How dating apps became new drug of choice...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2021-5-15/where-love-goes-to-die</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing Personal, the latest book from The Bling Ring author Nancy Jo Sales, is all about dating apps. Jennifer Weiner, author of In Her Shoes, reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth gap in Tahoe town extreme...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/renotahoe/article/Incline-Village-Lake-Tahoe-Gene-Simmons-Wealth-Gap-16188867.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 10-minute drive from the California-Nevada state border, Incline Village is like the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA proposes global 15% corporate tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/us-proposes-global-minimum-corporate-tax-rate-of-15percent-with-an-eye-on-something-even-higher.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporations around the world should pay at least a 15% tax on their earnings, the Treasury Department said Thursday in its push for a global minimum levy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt database exploited by vaccine critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210520-us-government-database-exploited-by-covid-19-vaccine-critics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US government database exploited by Covid-19 vaccine critics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MD To Give Away $2M...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/05/20/governor-larry-hogan-announces-vaccine-lottery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maryland Governor Larry Hogan said the state health department has partnered with Maryland Lottery to bring $2 million in prize money for lucky vaccinated Marylanders. The grand prize is $400,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keys, Wallet, Pepper Spray: New Reality for Asian-Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/keys-wallet-pepper-spray-the-new-reality-for-asian-americans/ar-AAKbGd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last spring Annie Chen, who works in human resources, read about an Asian woman who had been punched in the face and yelled at by a stranger just a few blocks from where she lived in Midtown Manhattan. Five days later, Ms. Chen, 25, bought her first canister of pepper spray. She had been struck by the way the public perception of Asian-Americans had suddenly changed, she said, and simply wanted to protect herself. “I felt like if people had any...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ceasefire imminent...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/no-rocket-sirens-since-1-am-as-israel-hamas-ceasefire-said-to-be-close-668607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egyptian security source - whose country has been mediating between the sides - said they had agreed in principle to a mutual halt in hostilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY offers lottery scratch tickets for vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-taiwan-pandemics-coronavirus-vaccine-coronavirus-pandemic-20ce42c66cd77cdc1d557d956b9d7799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — People who get vaccinated at select state-run vaccination sites in New York next week will receive a lottery scratch ticket as the state tries to boost slowing vaccination rates. Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Logging 4,500 Steps A Day Will Add Years To Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/taking-more-steps-live-longer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find each additional 1,000 steps contributes to a 28 percent decrease in death among study participants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC new floating park a marvel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/20/nycs-new-floating-park-little-island-is-a-marvel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers deserved a miracle after all we’ve been through. Little Island proves that one man’s vision can prevail against odds and that even after the darkest winter, spring will come again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY GIANTS Had Violent Culture Off Field, Lawsuit Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-20/n-y-giants-had-violent-culture-off-the-field-lawsuit-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Giants fostered a workplace rife with intimidation and physical violence, according to a lawsuit filed by the team’s former video director, who claims he was fired for complaining about an assault on another worker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish journalist wins legal battle against US activist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-donald-trump-europe-journalists-government-and-politics-9cb9a543a95d89b34f9a56ce8b8e6c69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — A Polish journalist who described a U.S. conservative activist as part of a global war against democracy by right-wing actors with indirect ties to Russia has won a years-long legal battle with the American.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazi Group Recruiting Again, Despite FBI Takedown...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx5n8x/neo-nazi-group-the-base-is-recruiting-again-despite-fbi-takedown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Base's founder, a former Homeland Security employee who is living in Russia, has retaken a leadership position after briefly leaving the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS EXPAND PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/feds-expand-cuomo-probe-will-look-at-whether-he-gave-family-priority-access-to-covid-testing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have reportedly expanded a probe of New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D) to look at allegations that he provided "priority access" to Covid-19 testing for "close associates" at the height of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid school reopenings may have led to thousands of cases, hundreds of deaths in TX...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/rapid-school-reopenings-led-thousands-covid-cases-hundreds/story?id=77778717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 43,000 people contracted COVID-19 and 800 died in Texas two months after reopening schools statewide, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX FIGHT:  Geraldo Throws Paper, Turns Back on Camera During Another Bongino Throwdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/stop-attacking-me-punk-geraldo-rivera-calls-out-dan-bongino-in-heated-segment-on-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geraldo Rivera continued to call out Israel and demand a ceasefire in a heated segment Wednesday night on Sean Hannity's program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Children of God' cult survivor recalls torture...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/children-god-cult-survivor-recalls-24150625</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharen Seitz, 33, of Boulder, Colorado in the US grew up inside the Children of God cult. She remembers being beaten and locked in a closet forced to memorise Bible passages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI dermatologist will diagnose 288 skin conditions in virtual appointments...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/dr-google-ai-dermatologist-diagnose-24151153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is allowing people to sign up to its outreach list which will update them on future research and early access programmes to the AI-powered dermatology assistant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's who in criminal probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9600829/Ex-Trump-Organization-exec-thinks-CFO-Allen-Weisselberg-flipped-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen Weisselberg, the longtime CFO of the Trump Organization and a key lieutenant of Donald Trump's, has turned on the former president, an ex-top executive predicted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS COMPLIANCE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/us-treasury-calls-for-stricter-cryptocurrency-compliance-with-irs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Treasury Department announced that it will require any transfer worth $10,000 or more to be reported to the IRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Drama Shaking Up NYT Styles Section...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-drama-shaking-up-the-new-york-times-styles-section</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under Choire Sicha, the section became a must-read. Why isn’t he still running it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women want 'ugly, rich men,' science says...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2920056/science-women-charm-men-looks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE confirms what we all knew ­­— women are turned on by charm and cash while men go on looks. In a discovery which surprises no one, a study found fellas value sexy bodies and attractive faces…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOULD BE KING GETS JABBED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2922001/prince-william-covid-vaccine-coronavirus-jab-over-35s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE William has shown off his guns as he received his Covid vaccine after catching the bug last year. The Duke of Cambridge, 38, shared a picture to Twitter today of himself receiving the jab as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS PLOT NEW RULES TO REIN IN CRYPTO</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/fintech/bitcoin-cryptocurrency-regulations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC, CFTC, IRS, FinCEN and Congress all want a piece of crypto oversight. The confusion has some in the industry calling for clearer regulations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Number of 401(k) and IRA millionaires hits record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/fidelity-number-of-401k-millionaires-hits-record-a-year-after-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although many Americans are still out of work and struggling, the recent stock market run up has buoyed retirement savings account balances to record levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking to boost profits, dentists push unnecessary procedures...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/looking-to-boost-profits-some-dentists-push-unnecessary-procedures/article_0a4b1523-1b9a-5a6f-be40-59140daf65be.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1993, Dr. David Silber, a dentist now practicing in Plano, Texas, was fired from the first dental clinic he worked for. He’d been assigned to a patient another dentist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER tries to curb offensive messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tinder-offensive-messages-75c8df0b-77e5-4454-8871-130081a7d6cc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tinder says it has reduced potentially disrespectful language by 10% in early testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does vaccine still protect you? Testing can't say for sure yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/how-long-do-vaccine-protections-last-science-can-t-say-for-sure/ar-AAKcfyL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protection from coronavirus vaccines is expected to wane, but no one knows when. It could be as soon as this fall for the first wave of people vaccinated last winter, and many predict that Covid boosters will soon join annual flu shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook Faces Judge With Stakes Beyond $142 Billion of Apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/apple-s-tim-cook-faces-judge-with-stakes-beyond-142-billion-of-apps/ar-AAKca1T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel shoots down armed Iranian drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-news/israel-shot-down-armed-iranian-drone-netanyahu-668658</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downing happened on sidelines of Gaza fighting. “I think that says everything about the real patron of terror in the Middle East and the world – Iran.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi defies Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/bibi-defies-biden-vows-more-strikes-101621477549394.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a 25-minute attack overnight, Israel bombarded targets including what its military said were tunnels in the southern Gaza Strip used by Hamas. Some 50 rockets were fired from the enclave, the Israeli military said, with sirens sounding in the coastal city of Ashdod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New name emerges in Gaetz investigation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/554508-new-name-emerges-in-gaetz-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scandal surrounding Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-Fla.) has now ensnared Joe Ellicot, a friend and former employee of a tax collector who has already pleaded guilty to an array of crimes associated with the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Circles of Friendship Churn, Evolve Over Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/05/robin-dunbar-explains-circles-friendship-dunbars-number/618931/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The evolutionary psychologist Robin Dunbar explains the limits on how many connections humans can maintain, and the trade-offs involved when you invest in a new relationship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quincy Jones Reflects on Career, Michael Jackson and Why He Wouldn't Work With Elvis...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/quincy-jones-michael-jackson-elvis-presley-1234955138/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a screening room in a Bel Air estate, the walls tell the story of American popular music: Framed Frank Sinatra albums hang alongside a 30-times-platinum “Thriller” certification and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt in possession of 'exotic material' from UFOs, ex-Pentagon officer claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/government-possession-exotic-material-ufos-24149071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luis Elizondo headed up the Pentagon's UFO programme before it was halted in 2012. He has since been at the forefront of UFO disclosure in the US and has played a key role in the release of footage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIDEAST TRUCE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/gaza-israel-middle-east-israel-palestinian-conflict-caac81bc36fe9be67ac2f7c27000c74b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Israel unleashed another wave of airstrikes across the Gaza Strip early Thursday, killing at least one Palestinian and wounding several, and Hamas fired more rockets, even as expectations rose that a cease-fire could be coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geraldo Throws Paper, Turns Back on Camera During Another Bongino Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/geraldo-rivera-throws-paper-turns-back-on-camera-during-another-dan-bongino-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of the on-air food fight, Hannity basically gave away the game. “Mediaite has their headline!” he crowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims new pandemic low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economist surveyed by Dow Jones had been expecting 452,000 new claims as the jobs picture continues to improve.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
