<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden plays to tens next to pool table in Des Moines bar...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/jill-biden-plays-to-tens-next-to-pool-table-in-des-moines-bar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s crowds are smaller, and his wife’s audiences are even smaller. The First Lady wannabe played to a handful of voters at the Blazing Saddle in Des Moines on Wednesday: “Tomorrow night, Donald Trump is coming here to your city,” Jill Biden says at The Blazing Saddle “He ain’t coming in here,” man says …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaken Caribbean back to normal after major quake...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200129192332-4dqub</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAMAICA-QUAKE/ (TV):Shaken Caribbean tiptoes back to normal after shock of major quake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren proposes criminal penalties for spreading disinfo online...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/29/warren-proposes-criminal-penalties-for-spreading-disinformation-online.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren on Wednesday released a plan to fight disinformation to hold tech companies accountable for their actions in light of the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans could move to quick acquittal vote...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/480528-senate-gop-could-move-to-quick-trump-acquittal-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are eyeing a quick acquittal of President Trump that could have the trial wrap as soon as Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-cocktail waitress tells trial Weinstein raped her...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/weinstein-demanded-threesome-aspiring-actress-trial-hears-175438127.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former cocktail waitress told Harvey Weinstein's sex assault trial Wednesday that the ex-Hollywood mega-producer pinned her down and raped her in his New York apartment in 2005. Tarale Wulff, 43, said she was driven to Weinstein's home after turning up at his office for what she believed would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faced with high smog levels, Milan to ban cars on Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/faced-high-smog-levels-milan-ban-cars-sunday-201251184.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milan will ban cars from driving within the city on Sunday, a measure aimed at tackling high pollution levels, even as authorities consider new measures, such as prohibiting smoking at bus stops. The measure - which is not the first time that Italy's economic capital has banned driving within city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo wades into feud with media...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/defensive-mike-pompeo-wades-feud-media-204255412.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused of failing to defend his own diplomats in the Ukraine scandal that led to the impeachment of his boss, Mike Pompeo -- who as secretary of state is meant to defend press freedoms around the world -- has now waded into a bitter feud with the media. A key ally of Donald Trump, Pompeo has often</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans from hot zone evaluated at military base...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3f13d6f778eae1dd6a062499ed889e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIVERSIDE, Calif. (AP) — The 195 Americans evacuated from the Chinese city at the center of the new virus outbreak are undergoing three days of testing and monitoring at a California military base...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED CHAIR WARNS ECON THREAT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a787b346cb7244deae80e80fe7dd0e30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Just as the outlook for the global economy had been brightening in recent months, a new threat has suddenly emerged in the form of the viral outbreak in China. That was the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVEY:  IT'S SHOWBIZ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8fc80c6e9e7c45bd05c66395c19f888d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Harvey Weinstein callously preceded an alleged rape with reassurances that he'd had a vasectomy, one accuser testified Wednesday. Another accuser on the witness stand at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOR THE WIN!  Bernie setting high expectations in Iowa... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5cf79ce25a24987ee268e78aeb96c23b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX CITY, Iowa (AP) — Most presidential candidates try to manage expectations in the final stretch of a campaign knowing a surprise win is always better than an expected one. Not Bernie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tenants flee LA high-rise fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/17d40df23395933603ce2de7c23856d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Firefighters made a dramatic ladder rescue of a man about to jump from a burning Los Angeles apartment building on Wednesday and helicopters plucked people from the roof of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest drug tunnel ever found on CA-MEX border...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article239772258.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMERICAN DIRT' book tour canceled by publisher because of safety concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/american-dirt-book-tour-canceled-publisher-because-safety-concerns-n1125926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision follows continued criticism from Latino critics that the novel is stereotypical and racist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/29/tesla-tsla-earnings-q4-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has already reported deliveries of 112,000 vehicles globally during the fourth quarter, a quarterly best for Tesla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is America Poised for Another World's Fair Embarrassment?</title>
      <link>https://www.architectmagazine.com/design/is-america-poised-for-another-worlds-fair-embarrassment_o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architectmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Why Life on Other Planets Will Resemble Ours...</title>
      <link>https://onezero.medium.com/alien-nations-why-life-on-other-planets-will-resemble-ours-15fb4ede6fe7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;onezero.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hard science offers a remarkably detailed portrait of how extraterrestrials may live — and clues on where our own civilization is headed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS TV News Crew Caught In Crossfire Of NYC Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/01/28/cbs2-news-brooklyn-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS2's Ali Bauman was working but didn't have an assignment, so she and two photographers parked their news truck in Brooklyn to be on standby in case there was breaking news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANYTHING Trump does to get re-elected is UNIMPEACHABLE, says Dershowitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7942607/Senators-ask-questions-Donald-Trumps-impeachment-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alan Dershowitz, one Donald Trump's lawyers, argued that any action taken by the president to benefit his re-election is in the public interest and therefore not impeachable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Asians hit back at racism with 'I'm not a virus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51294305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus outbreak in Wuhan prompts French Asians to complain of a backlash against them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO voices 'grave concern' about person-to-person spread...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/wuhan-china-coronavirus-outbreak-latest-news-updates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada will send a plane to evacuate 160 Canadians from Wuhan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE shuts offices...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/healthcare/google-shuts-down-offices-in-china-coronavirus-concerns-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google joins wave of shutdowns in China as coronavirus concerns mount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRIDAY CLIFFHANGER</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/29/trumps-defense-team-expects-cliffhanger-in-senate-witness-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s impeachment defense team expects a Friday cliffhanger when senators vote on whether to call witnesses in Trump’s trial. If Democrats find four Republicans to vote for …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities find longest US-Mexico border smuggling tunnel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/971db8e2487ab58337218d2ddfdcce5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The publisher of Jeanine Cummins' controversial novel “American Dirt" has cancelled the remainder of her promotional tour, citing concerns for her safety. The novel about a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK BLOCK?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/01/29/donald-trump-security-officials-threaten-block-john-boltons-book/4609730002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manuscript of John Bolton's book "appears to contain significant amounts of classified information," a National Security Council letter said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Traffic Surging; Crash Worries Grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/01/29/800433686/space-traffic-is-surging-and-critics-worry-there-could-be-a-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As private companies race into orbit, some experts in satellite operations say there isn't enough public infrastructure to keep all the satellites safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Club Receives Threats After Comedian's Jokes About Kobe...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/new-york-comedy-club-receives-threats-comedians-kobe-bryant-jokes-1274600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The venue canceled Ari Shaffir's scheduled performance following a video he made on Twitter about the late Laker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foul Smells Worsening Air Quality In Denver...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/29/smells-odor-air-quality-pollution/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air quality data from across the country shows the Denver metro area has the fourth worst air quality in the country. That includes smelly air that contributes to the degrading air quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia takes new steps to stop spread...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/748c0065d28cf67934ad7782573abff2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The Latest on the outbreak of a new virus from China that has sickened thousands of people and killed more than 100: 4:10 a.m. Officials say 201 Americans evacuated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Public Utility Commission Allegedly Hacked by Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.electricchoice.com/blog/breaking-news-puct-website-hacked-by-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.electricchoice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON backed company to build LINCOLN electric car...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/tesla-rival-rivian-will-make-platform-for-lincolns-ev-2020-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rivian will make the platform — which includes the motors, suspension, and battery pack — for Lincoln's first electric vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases top SARS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a980aeb44b3840341c674a6e67c19da6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — World health officials, back from a visit to Beijing, expressed great concern Wednesday that a dangerous new virus is spreading between people outside of China, even as the number...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETA calls for Punxsutawney Phil to be replaced by robot groundhog...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/peta-calls-for-punxsutawney-phil-to-retire-be-replaced-with-ai-robot-for-groundhog-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PETA suggested that the Punxsutawney Groundhog Club use an animatronic version with artificial intelligence could predict the weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Congressional Budget Office projects trillion-dollar deficits indefinitely...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/horowitz-congressional-budget-office-projects-trillion-dollar-deficits-indefinitely/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite high revenue and low unemployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS
</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/29/politics/donald-trump-john-bolton-white-house-book/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has issued a formal threat to former national security adviser John Bolton to keep him from publishing his book, "The Room Where It Happened: A White House Memoir," sources familiar with the matter tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/jackkensington/status/1222564406757748738?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Fire on Wilshire &amp;amp; #Barrington outside my office in #Brentwood https://t.co/T5fA4WaAdZ”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can 49ERS Stop Him?</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/01/28/49ers-chiefs-super-bowl-liv-patrick-mahomes-nick-bosa-ray-lewis-inside-nfl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can the 49ers defense, as dominant as they've been, slow a Chiefs offense with this many weapons and this much speed?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 firefighters on scene...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/01/29/fire-engulfs-high-rise-building-in-brentwood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were unconfirmed reports that people may have been forced to jump out of the building, the fire department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles fire: Blaze hits 25-story tower...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2020/01/29/fire-erupts-at-high-rise-apartment-building-near-brentwood-for-2nd-time-since-2013/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people were hospitalized, one in critical condition, after a fire ripped through a 25-story apartment building on L.A.'s westside Wednesday morning that was the scene of a destructive blaze six years ago, officials said. The flames broke out on the 6th floor in one of three buildings at the Barrington Plaza complex, located at 11740 Wilshire Blvd., around 8:37 a.m., according to a Los Angeles Fire Department alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a deeper Jewish identity on the 2020 trail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/38d217df36e903a671089dfb4e669218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Bernie Sanders is approaching next week’s Iowa caucuses in a position to become the first major-party Jewish presidential nominee in the nation’s history. And at a time of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE INTERNALS:  SET FOR BIG IOWA WIN... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/sanders-campaign-predicting-iowa-caucuses-victory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa — Bernie Sanders's campaign has been telling staffers that it expects to win the Iowa caucuses, setting expectations high in the final days leading up to the Feb. 3 contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOWA IN A WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/29/biden-sanders-iowa-poll-108755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president got 23 percent to the senator's 21 percent in a new Monmouth poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffett Bails on Newspapers...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stop-spreading-the-news-warren-buffett-throws-in-the-towel-on-newspaper-business-2020-01-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren Buffett is throwing in the towel on his newspaper business in the latest sign of the pressure on print media in a rapidly changing landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco official in charge of cleaning up city's filthy streets arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/san-francisco-public-works-official-arrested</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco’s head of Public Works, in charge of cleaning up the city’s feces-filled streets, has been arrested by the FBI on suspicion of public corruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANG GANG COULD GO SANDERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-29/yang-says-supporters-may-go-to-sanders-in-iowa-caucus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aims to break free from tech platforms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-corp-aggregator-aims-break-free-tech-platforms-170115095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch's News Corp. on Wednesday unveiled an online news aggregation service, aiming to break away from the dominant tech platforms with dominate digital media. The application called Knewz will include content from more than 400 sources in the US and worldwide, including Al-Jazeera, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN SAYS HE NEEDS STRONG VP BECAUSE HE'S OLD...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-joe-biden-whomever-i-pick-vp-needs-be-able-be-president-beca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I’m an old guy’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW AGE: University Ditches Textbooks...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/01/29/bethel-university-working-to-reduce-student-costs-by-ditching-textbooks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new initiative at Bethel Univesity is working to reduce student costs by ditching textbooks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA High School Teacher Rants To Students How Kobe Was 'Horrible Person'; 'Killed His Family'...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/01/28/east-la-teacher-calls-kobe-bryant-horrible-person-rapist-hours-after-lakers-legend-dies-in-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;School officials are urging increased sensitivity on campus after a video surfaced of a teacher calling Kobe Bryant a "horrible basketball player" and a rapist just one day after the Laker legend's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>START SPREADING THE KNEWZ! Murdoch Launches New Site...</title>
      <link>https://knewz.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knewz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Balanced News from a Wide Range of Sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITNESS:  Weinstein Teased Film Roles in Exchange for Threesome...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/dawn-dunning-harvey-weinstein-trial-testimony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dawn Dunning testified as one of the prosecution's "prior bad acts" witnesses on Wednesday morning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Would End NSA Surveillance Programs Revealed by Snowden...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/policy/2020/01/bill-would-reform-nsa-surveillance-program/162681/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bipartisan legislation could curtail long-running National Security Agency data collection efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interior Department grounds drone fleet over cybersecurity fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberscoop.com/drone-ban-interior-department-cybersecurity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cyberscoop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Secretary of the Interior issued an order grounding all non-emergency drones so that the Department of Interior can assess cybersecurity concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Launches New Site...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/digital/news/news-corp-launches-knewz-with-400-plus-publishers-promising-no-clickbait-or-narrow-minded-nonsense-1203485249/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch’s News Corp says it’s trying to battle fake news and social-media clickbait with Knewz, its own curated headline-aggregation service. The company’s new Knewz.com si…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO to Weigh Emergency Call...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-death-toll-climbs-132-005314172.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The World Health Organization called a meeting of its Emergency Committee Thursday to discuss the coronavirus after the number of confirmed cases in China surpassed the official number of SARS infections in the country during that epidemic.Governments tightened international travel and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL DOESN'T HAVE VOTES TO BLOCK WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/34f8a36cfc3a15ffeede3a74cd0c123a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's impeachment trial is shifting to questions from senators, a pivotal juncture as Republicans lack the votes to block witnesses and face a potential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Plague Of Of Locusts Threatens To Create Horrific End-Times Famine...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/health/plague-billions-locusts-threatens-create-horrific-end-times-famine-across-africa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oldest woman in world' dies at 127; Last person to remember 1800s...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/oldest-woman-world-dies-aged-21384123</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fotima Mirzokulova, from Tajikistan in Central Asia, was reportedly born on March 13, 1893, and lived through Tsarist Russia, the Soviet Union, and the fall of communism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Roberts Center Stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/29/politics/john-roberts-awkward-impeachment-questions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the Senate impeachment trial began last week, Chief Justice John Roberts has been mainly out of the camera's line of sight. He has, clerk-like, enforced Senate procedures and kept the clock for the lawyers at the lectern. He has tried to maintain the chamber's decorum, as when he admonished the legal teams against nastiness, citing a 1905 Senate trial precedent against use of the word "pettifogging."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRLINES CANCEL FLIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/29/coronavirus-american-airlines-reduces-china-service-as-outbreak-grows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines joined United in cutting some China flights as the coronavirus spreads and the government increased its travel warning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING posts first annual loss in more than two decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/29/boeing-ba-earnings-q4-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing said its costs from the 737 Max debacle would nearly double from a previous forecast to close to $19 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes relishes battle with history at Super Bowl...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/mahomes-relishes-battle-history-super-bowl-224947636--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Mahomes will battle against the weight of history as well the vaunted San Francisco defense as he attempts to join an exclusive club of Super Bowl winners on Sunday. The gifted Kansas City star would become only the third quarterback of African-American descent to lift the Vince Lombardi Trophy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helicopter lacked terrain awareness system...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/29/kobe-bryants-helicopter-lacked-proper-terrain-awareness-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The helicopter that slammed into a suburban Los Angeles hillside, killing Kobe Bryant, his daughter and seven others, lacked a terrain awareness system that could have warned the pilot he was too c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA TURNS ON BOLTON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cc7316d191075ac57e0bcd34f05d70b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For much of the last 20 years, John Bolton was a conservative poster child, a Republican hawk whose worldview helped shape the GOP establishment’s approach to dicey foreign...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RAGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/trump-rages-bolton-says-former-adviser-would-have-caused-world-n1125351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's latest attack on his ex-national security adviser comes as the Senate is weighing calling him as a witness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary could be Sanders vs. Bloomberg?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/opinion/story/2020-01-28/polls-bernie-sanders-mike-bloomberg-rising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two new polls show momentum for two polar opposites in the Democratic presidential race: Bernie Sanders and Mike Bloomberg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems fear push to stop Bernie would backfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Sanders-surge-worries-some-Democrats-but-they-15012763.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Democrats are increasingly alarmed that Sen. Bernie Sanders could gain unstoppable momentum from the primary voting that starts next week, but they also fear that any anti-Sanders effort would backfire, and that has sidelined any significant stop-Sanders effort for now.  Even the hint of an organized anti-Sanders movement would risk alienating the Vermont senator's sometimes belligerent supporters and play into claims that the process is "rigged," many Democrats say privately. Democratic House candidates in swing districts say they are nervous about running on the same ticket as Sanders, but they, too, are reluctant to say so publicly.  That's leading some Democratic centrists to warn that the silence carries a risk of waiting until it's too late.  "People need to start taking Bernie pretty seriously - there is a really substantial risk of him becoming unstoppable if he wins these early states by large numbers," said Matt Bennett, vice president of Third Way, a centrist Democratic group.  But despite "some discussions among people wringing their hands," Bennett said, "It's not like our phone is ringing from people saying, 'Let's do something.' "  Third Way blasted out an email to Iowa Democrats on Tuesday saying that Sanders has a "politically toxic background" and "his far left positions will repel swing voters." And Democratic Majority for Israel, a group of pro-Israel Democrats, has reserved $700,000 in television ads that will begin airing Wednesday, apparently the most concerted effort on television so far to attack Sanders.  But those moves remain the exception within the party. Some Democrats say they erred in 2016 by antagonizing Sanders and his supporters, and they are loath to risk doing so again. Others warn that treating Sanders too gently, however, could repeat the Republicans' experience of 2016, when...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITISH AIRWAYS cancels flights.  Will others follow?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/British-Airways-cancels-flights-to-China-over-15012992.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Airways canceled all direct flights to and from mainland China, joining a growing cluster of international carriers that have cut their routes as the country confirmed nearly 6,000 cases of coronavirus.  The London-based carrier typically runs one direct flight per day from Heathrow Airport to Beijing and another to Shanghai. Britain's Foreign and Commonwealth Office has discouraged anything but essential travel to China, excluding Hong Kong and Macao, and urged against all travel to Hubei province, where the crisis originated. Indirect routes to China via connecting flights were still available on the British Airways website, and the carrier's flights to Hong Kong were not affected.  British Airways' move could put pressure on other airlines as coronavirus spreads around the world. On Tuesday, United Airlines said it would temporarily suspend flights to China between Feb. 1 and Feb. 8 because of a "significant decline in demand." Those changes affect 24 round trips between the United States and Beijing, Hong Kong and Shanghai.  Seoul Air and Indonesia's Lion Air also suspended all flights to China, and Hong Kong's Cathay Pacific said it would cut flights to and from China by at least 50% through the end of March.  American Airlines, Delta Air Lines and United extended their change fee waivers through the end of February.  CNBC reported that the White House has told airline executives it is considering suspending flights from China, although it has not yet done so.  Meanwhile, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said screening for the virus at U.S. airports would be expanded.  As of Wednesday morning local time, the death toll had risen to 132 in China, with 5,974 confirmed cases of infection - a day-over-day increase of more than 1,000. The United Arab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabin fever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb8aba68717061e34c5fde2881693566</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Chinese around the country confined to their apartments either by choice or by order are making the best of the situation as cities remain in lockdown in a desperate bid to contain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priests in group shut down by Vatican accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9e502dedcd0b98999e1db829bfea6efe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Nine priests and brothers of a Catholic group recently shut down by the Vatican are under investigation by Italian authorities for allegedly sexually abusing two brothers,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actors' union issues standards for supervisors of sex scenes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7223ea603c7006f72e891ac7f11647d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The union that represents actors and television performers issued a series of standards and guidelines Wednesday for crew members who supervise scenes involving sex and nudity....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doorbell Cam Captures Chilling Audio of Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kobe-bryant-crash-audio-captured-on-doorbell-cam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recording emerged as investigators said the helicopter was not fitted with a warning system that may have prevented the disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allies target African American voters with new tactic: Cash giveaways...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/29/trump-black-voters-cash-giveaways-108072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the first event, organizers lavished praise on the president — as they handed out thousands of dollars to lucky attendees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Is Red Hot Once Again and Ready to Score Huge Payday...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/the-nfl-is-red-hot-once-again-and-ready-to-score-a-huge-payday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL Is Red Hot Once Again and Ready to Score a Huge Payday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$500 Million: This Could Be America's Most Expensive Home Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/this-could-be-america-s-most-expensive-home-ever-if-it-can-find-a-buyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven years in the making, $500 million California mansion will test ultra-luxury appetite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showbiz apes find peace through painting in Florida retirement...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/showbiz-apes-peace-painting-florida-retirement-093455708.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of them worked alongside Clint Eastwood, others acted in the remake of sci-fi classic "Planet of the Apes", while yet another was the darling favorite of Michael Jackson. All of these great apes were raised by humans and lack the basic survival skills to ever live in the wild. The lucky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski's new film tops French 'Oscar' nominations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/roman-polanskis-film-tops-french-oscar-nominations-102042147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roman Polanski's new film "An Officer and a Spy" topped the list of nominations on Wednesday for the "French Oscars", the Cesars. The controversial director has been wanted in the US for the statutory rape of a 13-year-old girl since 1978 and is persona non grata in Hollywood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health care in America: For one family, a $300,000 debt nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/health-care-america-one-family-300-000-debt-014156698.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maccoux family receive visitors to their beautiful home in a Minneapolis suburb with an infectious warmth that belies the fact their youngest daughter Olivia has had more than 140 brain surgeries, all by the age of 24. Mom Cathy smiles tenderly as she scrolls through photos of Olivia on hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More accusers on deck...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200129102536-gt5y7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-HARVEY WEINSTEIN/ (PIX):Waitress turned model expected to take the stand at Weinstein's rape trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrified passengers wearing plastic containers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/10844438/coronavirus-desperate-passengers-plastic-bottles-helmets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desperate air passengers have been spotted wearing everything from plastic bottles to motorbike helmets in a bid to protect themselves from the deadly coronavirus. It comes as airlines such as Brit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISSATISFACTION WITH DEMOCRACY ALL-TIME GLOBAL HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/28/global-dissatisfaction-with-democracy-at-a-record-high-research-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer than 50% of Americans are now content with democracy in their country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECISIONS LOOM</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-defense-team-presents-third-day-of-15010862.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - White House lawyers pleaded with senators Tuesday to acquit President Donald Trump based on "the Constitution and your common sense," concluding their defense even as Senate GOP leaders struggled to block demands for new witnesses that could throw the trial into turmoil.  In a closed-door meeting following closing remarks, Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., told colleagues he doesn't have the votes to block witnesses, according to people familiar with his remarks who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe them. Just four GOP senators would have to join with Democrats to produce the majority needed to call witnesses - an outcome McConnell has sought to avoid since it could invite new controversy and draw out the divisive proceedings.  An initial vote to allow witnesses, expected Friday, doesn't ensure witnesses would actually be called, since the Senate would have to subsequently hold separate votes on summoning each individual witness. And Trump's ultimate acquittal still remains all but assured, since a two-thirds vote would be required to remove him in the GOP-run Senate.  But the debate over witnesses has roiled the Senate since the emergence of revelations Sunday from an unpublished book manuscript by former national security adviser John Bolton. In the book Bolton recounts a conversation with Trump in which the president described wanting to withhold military assistance from Ukraine until Kyiv announced investigations into political rivals.  That would make Bolton the first official to provide a firsthand account of the alleged quid pro quo at the heart of House Democrats' abuse of power charge against the president, one of the two articles of impeachment they approved in December. The other charged Trump with obstruction of Congress.  Amid the debate over witnesses, White House...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
