<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kid Rock says Trump asked him for advice on ISIS and NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/kid-rock-shares-shocking-insider-story-on-trumps-rock-and-roll-foreign-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famously unconventional former President Donald Trump asked Kid Rock what he should tweet about crushing the Islamic State group's caliphate, the rock star recalled during a new interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feel real-life pain in the metaverse!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4943580/feel-virtual-reality-pain-in-the-metaverse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you thought living in the virtual reality of the metaverse would let you escape the pains of the real world, you made need to think again. A Sony backed Japanese start-up company called H2L Tech…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK STATE OF EMERGENCY; SHOOTINGS ROCK MIAMI BEACH...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/miami-beach-declares-state-of-emergency-following-multiple-spring-break-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH, FLA. (WSVN) - Officials with the City of Miami Beach have declared a state of emergency after a weekend that included shootings and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report details Russian oligarchs' global assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/mar/21/global-assets-russians-alleged-ties-putin-wealth-oligarchs-navalny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International collaboration tracks wealth of oligarchs and officials accused by western governments of being president’s supporters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Al Michaels to leave NBC,  headed to AMAZON for Thursday Night Streaming...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/21/al-michaels-headed-to-amazon-for-joe-buck-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary NFL play-by-player Al Michaels is in agreement with Amazon Prime Video to lead its booth when it begins its exclusive coverage of Thursday Night Football in the fall, The Post has learned…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad's superyacht faces seizure from Italian marina...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-officials-superyacht-could-putins-151210484.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — U.S. officials are examining the ownership of a $700 million superyacht currently in a dry dock in an Italian seacoast town and believe it could be associated with President Vladimir Putin of Russia, according to multiple people briefed on the information. U.S. intelligence agencies have made no final conclusions about the ownership of the superyacht — called the Scheherazade — but U.S. officials said they had found initial indications that it was linked to Putin. The information fr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC launches voter registration drives at gas stations...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/mar/21/rnc-launches-voter-registration-drives-gas-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican National Committee announced Monday a nationwide initiative to register voters at gas stations to highlight the rising fuel prices at the pump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Holocaust survivor killed by shelling...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4945441/survivor-hitler-concentration-camps-killed-putin-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SURVIVOR of four World War Two Nazi concentration camps was killed in the bombing on his home in the north-eastern city of Kharkiv. Boris Romantschenko, 96, “actively campaigned for the mem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BIG APPLE ROTTING FROM ITS CORE': Guardian Angels founder warns NYC heading back to crime-ridden days...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4941618/guardian-angels-new-york-subway-attacks-violent-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York City is heading back towards the dark days of the 1970s and 80s amid a terrifying surge in violent attacks and other major crimes, the founder of Guardian Angels has warned. Curtis Sliwa, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refugees flooding into Warsaw...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukrainian-refugees-are-flooding-into-warsaw-its-mayor-warns-its-on-the-brink/ar-AAViKnI?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia says it can't be held responsible for oil shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/saudi-arabia-says-it-can-t-be-held-responsible-for-oil-shortages-after-houthis-attack-energy-facilities/ar-AAVkyVy?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC cherry blossoms hit peak 10 DAYS early...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Washington-D-C-s-cherry-blossoms-hit-their-peak-17018665.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aided by unseasonably warm weather since mid-February, Washington, D.C.'s famed cherry...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami jail officer faces rare prosecution under 'revenge porn' law...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2652240</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — A Miami-Dade corrections officer has been relieved of duty after he was arrested for allegedly posting explicit images of his ex-wife on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump delayed weapons to Ukraine and praised Putin. Did that trigger invasion?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-trump-delayed-weapons-110005981.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president attempted to extort Zelensky for political favors and made Ukraine a pawn. Putin took note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask mandate RETURNS to six Chicago classrooms amid spike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mask-mandate-returns-six-chicago-141000717.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brenna O’Brien, a parent of a second grader and a fourth grader at Chicago’s John C. Coonley Elementary School, wasn’t sure over the weekend what she’s going to do Monday when her kids were supposed to be back in their classrooms. They’d lost four days of instruction due to illness. “I’ve repeatedly tested them — we’ve done PCR tests — and it’s just repeatedly been negative,” she said Saturday ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  DISNEY Chaos! CEO Under Fire Over Florida Don't Say Gay; Walkout Planned...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/disney-postpones-management-retreat-ceo-bob-chapek-continues-outreach-town-hall-florida-dont-say-gay-bill-lgbtq-1234983486/#recipient_hashed=7e24db67d1bcd7e3e2e90e7d1bc3fed9fe2d0ae6edc848546f7b1fa66fb9c7f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many of its LGBTQ+ employees get set for a full-day walkout Tuesday, Disney has decided to postpone a management retreat set for next week as it continues efforts to calm internal waters. News o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE MASSIVE GLOBAL OUTAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4944089/apple-maps-down-icloud-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE suffered a major global outage for more than four hours on Monday after appearing to be hit with server issues. Thousands of users reported problems with Apple Maps, Apple Music and several o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Medical Marijuana Fails To Improve Pain, Anxiety, Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/medical-marijuana-addiction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Massachusetts General Hospital add that up to one in five users may develop cannabis use disorder (CUD).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs' strict orders to castrate all captured men...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/ukrainian-doctors-told-castrate-captured-26523466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;War-zone hospital owner Gennadiy Druzenko told his doctors to castrate captured Russian soldiers, he claims. He is set to be added to the Kremlin's most wanted list</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Rogan Defends Deep State...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/joe-rogan-defends-deep-state-do-you-know-how-fcked-we-would-be-without-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"One of the things that the tinfoil-hat brigade likes to talk about is the deep state."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving Tribute to Family, Country...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-ketanji-brown-jackson-gets-widespread-praise-for-moving-tribute-to-family-and-country-in-opening-statement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ketanji Brown Jackson delivered an opening statement on Monday that included a tribute to her family and to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer claims responsibility...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/viral-tesla-crash-sparks-lapd-investigation-influencer-claims-s-stunt-rcna20884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On TikTok, Dominykas Zeglaitis, also known as Durte Dom, claimed responsibility for the crash. Other influencers say he wasn't even there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,500 soldiers' corpses shipped back as morgues overrun...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/radio-free-europe-more-than-2500-russian-soldiers-corpses-shipped-back-as-morgues-overrun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ape develop own languages -- just like humans...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/03/21/apes-develop-their-own-languages-just-like-humans-16315305/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers believe their study could provide clues about how our languages developed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New tracker details oligarchs' assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/21/business/russian-asset-tracker/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nonprofit reporting network launched Monday the Russian Asset Tracker, a database to track the assets of prominent Russians who have links to Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLIGARCHS PLOTTING?</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2022/03/21/are-putins-oligarchs-plotting-to-topple-him_partner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will seizing their wealth aid in ending the war in Ukraine?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson pledges to decide cases 'without fear or favor'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ketanji-brown-jackson-confirmation-hearing-live-updates-54fe3957e4cca1a6d6dde5202631d0c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate Judiciary Committee begins historic confirmation hearings Monday for Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson, who would be the first Black woman on the Supreme Court. Live updates here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shoppers Literally Fighting Each Other for Sugar...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjbm95/russia-sugar-shortages-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In scenes reminiscent of the last days of the Soviet Union, Russians are scrambling to get their hands on basic goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book bans, threat of censorship rev up political activism in suburbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/03/21/1087000890/book-bans-and-the-threat-of-censorship-rev-up-political-activism-in-the-suburbs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A conservative campaign to ban certain books from schools is prompting other parents to push back. The issue is often framed as the latest "culture war" battle, but some see democracy itself at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Not Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/justice-thomass-illness-not-covid-175101038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Clarence Thomas, who was absent from Supreme Court oral arguments Monday due to illness, does not have COVID-19, a court spokesperson confirmed.Thomas, 73, was admitted to Sibley Memorial Hospital in Washington, D.C., on Friday evening with flu-like symptoms and diagnosed with an infection, a Supreme Court spokesperson said in a statement Sunday, adding that he was being treated with intravenous antibiotics.Reuters first reported on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$700M Superyacht Belongs to Putin, New Navalny Investigation Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kbqn9/dollar700m-superyacht-belongs-to-putin-new-navalny-investigation-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The claim has been dropped in a YouTube video that is going megaviral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden warns cyberattacks coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/21/biden-russia-cyberattacks-00018942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Monday warned U.S. companies to be on guard against Russian cyberattacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Teamsters head vows to take on AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/599063-new-teamsters-head-vows-to-take-on-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incoming Teamsters president says he is ready to take on the challenge of unionizing Amazon despite tough odds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Watch Memory Form in Living Brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/scientists-watch-a-memory-form-in-a-living-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While observing fearful memories take shape in the brains of fish, neuroscientists saw an unexpected level of synaptic rewiring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Threatens to Cause Global Food Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraine-war-threatens-to-cause-a-global-food-crisis/ar-AAVibSi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWELL:  'Inflation much too high'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/21/powell-says-inflation-is-much-too-high-and-the-fed-will-take-necessary-steps-to-address.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell vowed tough action on inflation, which he said jeopardizes an otherwise strong recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacuum bombs fired on besieged Mariupol...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4942327/terrifying-moment-russia-vacuum-bomb-mariupol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the terrifying moment Russian forces launch vacuum bombs on the besieged city of Mariupol while brave civilians continue to fight back. Shocking footage shared by Russia today shows a TOS-1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Airport calls COPS on Ted Cruz after argument over missed flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10636047/Montana-airport-calls-COPS-Ted-Cruz-heated-forth-recorded-video.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airport told DailyMail.com that one of its public safety officers 'was in the ticket lobby and was asked to assist with a frustrated passenger' -- but did not know it was Cruz until after the fact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin quotes Jesus to justify invasion...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/russia/1011510/putin-quotes-jesus-to-justify-invasion-of-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-wife accuses top Missouri Republican Senate candidate of abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-campaigns-eric-greitens-missouri-texas-5cb2c458155b4f611b0e9a3377d9d970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, Mo. (AP) — Former Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens, now a leading Republican Senate candidate , was physically abusive and demonstrated such “unstable and coercive behavior” that steps were taken to limit his access to firearms, according to new allegations from his ex-wife revealed in court records on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  MOST BORING JOBS IN WORLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/most-boring-person-in-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study examining the "science of boredom" has ranked the jobs, characteristics, and hobbies that people consider the dullest in society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Shanghai closes again over surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/disney-shanghai-temporarily-closes-as-china-battles-another-covid-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney guests who have been impacted will be provided a refund or exchange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists face an avalanche of anti-transgender bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Activists-face-an-avalanche-of-anti-transgender-17017935.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Bell had traveled from Selma to Montgomery thousands of times, but still, he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivor killed by shelling...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/world/ukrainian-holocaust-survivor-killed-by-russian-shelling-5K20t9rbMyUSIoCdAPt9zA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MAN WHO WOULD REPLACE PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4939080/russian-top-brass-plan-to-poison-vladimir-putin-and-have-chosen-his-successor-according-to-ukrainian-intelligence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINIAN intelligence has claimed that members of the Russian elite are planning to poison Vladimir Putin. The Chief Directorate of Intelligence of the Ministry of Defence of Ukraine has said that…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC covid cases rising again as transmission jumps in Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/nyc-covid-cases-rising-manhattan-transmission-jumps-but-well-below-peak/3608149/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID cases are on the rise again in New York City as the BA.2 variant grows more prevalent, though the numbers are still a tiny fraction of the peaks seen earlier this year. As of Monday morning, the city’s latest data had the rolling seven-day average of new cases at 610, up nearly 10% in a week. Transmission rates are…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GODFATHER' Cast Speak Out, 50 Years Later...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/the-godfather-at-50-james-caan-robert-duvall-talia-shire-reminisce-1235109266/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Caan, Robert Duvall, Talia Shire and John Martino talk Marlon Brando, including his acting trick that screwed the rest of them up; bitterness over a cut scene; nailing a dangerous moment in one take; and a loathing for cannolis; among much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI HORROR:  'Suicide drone' that picks own targets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/kamikaze-drone-used-ukraine-horror-26518751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kalashnikov drone can loiter over a battle zone for up to 30 minutes before identifying a target and deliberately smashing into it, detonating its high explosive payload</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  CHURCH AND BIKE BEFORE EU TRIP...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/politics/ahead-of-europe-trip-biden-spends-weekend-in-delaware</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden spent a low-key weekend in Rehoboth Beach, Delaware ahead of his much-anticipated trip this week to Europe, where he’ll meet with with G7 leaders, NATO and the European Council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING FEVER:  Record-challenging heatwave to send temps near 100 in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/spring-heat-wave-could-challenge-record-highs-in-la-san-francisco/1159912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first week of spring will feel more like the middle of summer in the West, and one city could come close to the 100-degree mark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS:  NO ZELENSKY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/amy-schumer-zelenskyy-oscars-1235210388/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amy Schumer is co-hosting the 94th Academy Awards with Regina Hall and Wanda Sykes, and she’s revealed at least one idea she planned for the upcoming ceremony: having Ukrainian president Volo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In World First, Scientists Find Drug That Stops Breast Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/supplement-mitoq-breast-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The treatment, called the MitoQ molecule, stopped cancer's spread in 80 percent of cases and recurrence in 75 percent of patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court bans FACEBOOK, INSTAGRAM after META found 'extremist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russian-court-bans-facebook-instagram-after-meta-found-extremist-tass-2022-03-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian court on Monday banned Facebook and Instagram in the country after finding Meta Platforms Inc "extremist", TASS news agency reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian leftist Lula leads Bolsonaro ahead of election, poll shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazilian-leftist-lula-leads-bolsonaro-ahead-october-election-poll-shows-2022-03-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former leftist President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva holds a comfortable lead in the run-up to Brazil's October election while voters blame incumbent far-right President Jair Bolsonaro for surging fuel prices, a poll showed on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1986 dystopian novel basically predicted Vladimir...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-1986-dystopian-russian-novel-basically-predicted-vladimir-putin/ar-AAVjwxz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US admiral says China fully militarized isles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-china-beijing-xi-jinping-south-china-sea-d229070bc2373be1ca515390960a6e6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OVER THE SOUTH CHINA SEA (AP) — China has fully militarized at least three of several islands it built in the disputed South China Sea, arming them with anti-ship and anti-aircraft missile systems, laser and jamming equipment, and fighter jets in an increasingly aggressive move that threatens all nations operating nearby, a top U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID cases surging anew overseas. Is USA next?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/covid-19-cases-are-surging-anew-overseas-is-the-us-next/ar-AAVhRgU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Co-Founder Wozniak still looking for next big thing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-steve-wozniak-lance-bass-rosie-rios-e4fe9d0f065a6c257d7fc899aed0b32e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple co-founder Steve Wozniak has remained immersed in technology while also pursuing divergent interests since his 1985 departure from the revolutionary company he started with the late Steve Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil surges again as EU considers Russian ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/21/oil-markets-european-union-russia-saudi-refinery-output.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices jumped $3 on Monday, with Brent above $110 a barrel, as European Union nations consider joining the United States in a Russian oil embargo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plunging at 350MPH...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/china-eastern-airlines-boeing-737-with-133-aboard-crashes-in-mountainous-guanxi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boeing 737-800 slammed into a hillside in southern China in what could be the country’s worst plane crash in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.1 mag quake shakes Britain; Houses rattle for minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-uk-earthquake-51-magnitude-26519216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was felt in Shetland, Aberdeen, Ellon, Stonehaven, Helmsdale, Inverurie, Lairg, Huntly, Banff and Fraserburgh, according to The British Geological Survey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unarmed driver asked to speak with officer's supervisor. Cop used Taser on him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-unarmed-driver-asked-to-speak-with-a-police-officer-e2-80-99s-supervisor-the-officer-used-a-taser-on-him-video-shows/ar-AAVjCuj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Names on list: Fleeing Mariupol, one checkpoint at a time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-edf7240a9d990e7e3e32f82ca351dede</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — The Russians were hunting us down. They had a list of names, including ours, and they were closing in. We had been documenting the siege of the Ukrainian city by Russian troops for more than two weeks and were the only international journalists left in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to visit Poland...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-biden-boris-johnson-andrzej-duda-duda-adb431bc8fe12682a65d0ece555b941d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden has added a stop in Poland to his trip this week to Europe for urgent talks with NATO and European allies, as Russian forces concentrate their fire upon cities and trapped civilians in a nearly month-old invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Waters Ready to Defend Worst People in World...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2022/03/21/magazine/john-waters-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m fascinated by people’s behavior, especially people I can’t understand.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto, the Quietly Booming Tech Town...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/21/toronto-the-quietly-booming-tech-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO — In late February, Microsoft opened four floors of new office space near the top of a 50-story glass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Virus Hunter in the Wuhan Market...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/21/he-goes-where-the-fire-is-a-virus-hunter-in-the-wuhan-market/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As soon as Edward Holmes saw the dark-ringed eyes of the raccoon dogs staring at him through the bars of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: China passenger jet filmed nosediving from 30,000ft...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4940493/china-eastern-airlines-crash-jet-mountain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a passenger plane carrying 132 nosedives vertically into a mountain at 400mph. Horrifying footage shows the Boeing 737 plummets to the ground after falling from 29,100ft…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpredictable risks of new Russian debt crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-unpredictable-risks-of-a-new-russian-debt-crisis/ar-AAViTr3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some breaking through digital iron curtain -- leading to fights with friends, family...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/some-russians-are-breaking-through-putin-e2-80-99s-digital-iron-curtain-e2-80-94-leading-to-fights-with-friends-and-family/ar-AAVfYwb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher food costs pushing Americans back to food banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/higher-food-prices-pushing-more-low-income-americans-back-to-food-banks/ar-AAVjvFw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History-making Jackson set for Senate hearing for high court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ketanji-brown-jackson-biden-stephen-breyer-us-supreme-court-election-2020-54fe3957e4cca1a6d6dde5202631d0c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate Judiciary Committee begins historic confirmation hearings Monday for Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson , who would be the first Black woman on the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War could be headed toward stalemate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russias-war-for-ukraine-could-be-headed-toward-stalemate/ar-AAVhmrM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No gun. No helmet. No action: Frustrations of novice Americans who signed up to fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/no-gun-no-helmet-no-action-the-frustrations-of-some-novice-americans-who-signed-up-to-fight-in-ukraine/ar-AAVicf3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
