<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of dead fish found in and around Hudson River...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-dead-fish-hudson-river-20200707-2swhsxxl75bixcvyvcsla4dhhq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a fishy situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida lawyer attends court in HAZMAT SUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8498865/Florida-lawyer-attends-court-HAZMAT-SUIT-amid-COVID-19-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samuel J. Rabin Jr. donned the protective garb for a client's sentencing hearing which was held at Miami federal courthouse last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW MODEL: 208,000 deaths in USA by November...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/webview/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-07-07-20-intl/h_c5c9c0b1f6e8db4ffbd3dc5dcca35387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has brought countries to a standstill. In many places, as countries reopen, Covid-19 cases are on the rise. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Record: 10,028 New Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/texas-says-new-coronavirus-cases-jumped-by-more-than-10000-for-the-first-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas reported more than 10,000 additional Covid-19 cases Tuesday, a record-breaking daily surge in cases as the state responds to a growing outbreak and an increase in hospitalizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Defiant: Reopening on track for Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200707201123-t9d0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DISNEY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Disney says Walt Disney World reopening is on track for Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County to arrest positive residents who refuse to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/07/07/texas-county-to-arrest-covid-positive-residents-who-refuse-to-self-isolate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Texas county isn't taking any chances when it comes to the coronavirus, issuing a warning that anyone who tests positive and refuses to self-isolate could end up in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland protesters hit with federal charges in officer assaults, courthouse destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/7/portland-protesters-face-federal-charges-assaultin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Attorney in Oregon announced federal charges Tuesday against seven protesters who are accused in court papers of defacing a federal courthouse and assaulting federal officers during protests in Portland, Oregon against racial injustice and police brutality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors hit Black Lives Matter protesters with rare felony 'leak' charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/7/black-lives-matter-protesters-face-felony-leak-cha/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in Iowa have filed a rarely used leak charge against Black Lives Matter protesters accused of stealing a confidential police document and displaying it during a television news broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell eyes MORE virus aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.theledger.com/news/20200707/mcconnell-eyes-virus-aid-as-evictions-benefits-cuts-loom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — An eviction moratorium is lifting. Extra unemployment benefits are ending. Parents are being called to work, but schools are struggling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm Animals May Be Key To Forecasting Earthquakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/not-a-myth-after-all-farm-animals-may-be-key-to-forecasting-earthquakes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study by German scientists provides scientific evidence to support claims of odd animal behavior prior to earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS CORP CEO says 'digital denouement looming'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/news-corp-robert-thomson-digital-denouement-looming-journalism-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Corp CEO Robert Thomson discussed tech giants such as Amazon, Facebook and Google and their role in the journalism landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Sheriffs Refuse to Enforce Gov's Orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/texas-sheriffs-refuse-to-enforce-governor-greg-abbott-mask-executive-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least nine counties have publicly said they will not enforce the executive order requiring face masks in public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yet another blast reportedly damages factory in Iran, latest in series of blasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/explosion-reportedly-damages-factory-in-iran-the-latest-in-series-of-blasts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 said killed and 3 injured at facility in Kahrizak, south of Tehran; local governor says explosion caused by human error as oxygen tanks were being filled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dangerous Vaccine Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/07/vaccine-race-covid-national-pride-348072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The international competition for a coronavirus vaccine harkens back to the golden age of Edison and the Wright Brothers. But excesses of national pride and one-upmanship are threatening to overwhelm the common good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.K. Rowling, Noam Chomsky Sign Open Letter Calling for End to Cancel Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/j-k-rowling-bari-weiss-and-noam-chomsky-among-dozens-to-sign-open-letter-calling-for-end-to-cancel-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.K. Rowling, Bari Weiss, Noam Chomsky, and more than 100 other writers, scholars, and academics signed an open letter calling for "open debate" and an end to cancel culture, sparking backla</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International investors bought bonds backed by Italian mafia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/international-investors-reportedly-bought-bonds-backed-by-the-italian-mafia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors around the globe were buying bonds backed by a notorious mafia in Italy for four years, The Financial Times reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Staffers Face Layoffs as Palaces Lose Millions in Tourism Income...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/royals/royal-staff-face-layoffs-as-palaces-lose-millions-of-dollars-in-tourism-income-amid-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal staff face layoffs as palaces lose millions of tourism dollars because of closures during coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Omar Calls For 'Dismantling' Of US Economy, Political System...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/07/07/ilhan-omar-calls-for-the-dismantling-of-us-economy-political-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Minnesota Rep. Ilhan Omar called for the &amp;quot;dismantling&amp;quot; of the U.S. economy and political system Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YAHOO engineer gets off with only probation after hacking 6,000 accounts to look for porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/yahoo-engineer-gets-no-jail-time-after-hacking-6000-accounts-to-look-for-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hacker sentenced to five years probation, with home confinement condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Office Delivery Trucks Keep Catching on Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/z3ezx4/post-office-delivery-trucks-keep-catching-on-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of the iconic Post Office delivery trucks have caught on fire in recent years, thanks to a 30-year-old fleet and a manufactured budget crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  DUNKIN closing 450 locations...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/food/2020/07/07/dunkin-closures-2020-speedway-gas-stations-convenience-stores/5389869002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the end of 2020, Dunkin' will close approximately 450 locations in Speedway gas station convenience stores, a move first announced in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY: 'Real headwinds' if election turns into 'referendum'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/07/mick-mulvaney-trump-general-election-350337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blunt acknowledgment from the president’s former top aide comes amid escalating anxiety among congressional Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Florida ICUs at full capacity...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200707154532-vlax5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FLORIDA (URGENT):Dozens of Florida hospitals at full ICU capacity -state data report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY  Heads Toward Hedge-Fund Ownership...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/06/mcclatchy-a-family-newspaper-business-heads-toward-hedge-fund-ownership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The McClatchy family has been in journalism since 1857, when its flagship publication, The Daily Bee, chronicled the latest for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch police uncover makeshift torture chamber...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bbe6743f42e5ab1dc6b06d2524fef32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — Dutch police arrested six men after discovering sea containers that had been converted into a makeshift prison and sound-proofed “torture chamber” complete with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy could 'section' people who refuse treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jul/07/italy-could-section-people-who-refuse-treatment-for-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minister proposes mandatory hospital care as country grapples with fresh outbreaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER, NEWSMAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumps-small-biz-rescue-bailed-out-kushners-family-obamas-aides-and-other-political-elite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PPP program was designed to help small businesses. And it has. But some of the most connected figures in politics also cashed in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grover Norquist's anti-government spending group took cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/nation/2020/07/06/grover-norquists-anti-spending-group-took-small-business-relief/112067360/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Americans for Tax Reform Foundation, a conservative group headed by anti-tax activist Grover Norquist, took Covid-19 small business relief funds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-sized giant bat leaves people convinced they've seen a demon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/giant-human-sized-bat-leaves-22313648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The golden-crowned flying fox in the Philippines is a huge bat with a 1.7m wing span that – but thankfully, the beast typically feasts on fruit rather than flesh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY, NJ expands list of quarantine states...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/new-york-and-new-jersey-expand-list-of-states-that-trigger-quarantine-orders-for-travelers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo and New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy added three more states to their travel advisory on Tuesday, requiring all individuals from the list of states to self-quarantine for 14 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herd immunity strategies called into question...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/herd-immunity-questioned-after-spanish-coronavirus-antibody-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 antibodies in Spain's population "are insufficient to provide herd immunity," a new study has claimed, despite the country being one of the worst-affected by the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Jogger Finds Human Head on Side of Road...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/crime/2020/07/07/police-florida-jogger-finds-human-head-on-side-of-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A human head was discovered Tuesday on the side of a road in St. Petersburg, Florida, according to authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI GOV: 'Not Going to Be Bullied' into Opening...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/07/07/michigan-gov-whitmer-on-reopening-im-not-going-to-be-bullied-into-moving-before-its-safe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dialing back reopening right before the July 4 holiday, Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer (D) affirmed Tuesday on CNN's "New Day" that she will not be "bullied" into reopening her state too quickly amid the ongoing coronavirus pandemic. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Pandemic accelerating, still short of peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/coronavirus-pandemic-accelerating-still-short-of-peak-who-01594137005?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 400,000 new cases of COVID-19 were reported over the weekend and the new coronavirus pandemic shows no sign of slowing down, the World Health Organization said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP worries Trump's divisive June imperils Senate control...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8e962577a52e4803c51f6761cf619da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's June began with his Bible-clutching photo op outside a church after authorities used chemicals and batons to scatter peaceful demonstrators. It never got...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIECE EXPOSES DYNASTY</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trumps-worldview-forged-by-neglect-and-trauma-at-home-his-niece-says-in-new-book/2020/07/07/b19b22f6-bf9d-11ea-864a-0dd31b9d6917_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump, who has a doctoral degree in clinical psychology, shares a history of family tragedy and division with President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded tourist begs to be rescued after being stuck in airport for 100 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1098646/tourist-stranded-coronavirus-real-life-terminal-tom-hanks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOURIST is pleading to be rescued after spending more than 100 days living in an airport in a real life echo of Tom Hanks film The Terminal. Roman Trofimov has been staying in the departures…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY expands list of quarantine states...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ny-nj-ct-add-three-more-states-added-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People arriving to New York, New Jersey and Connecticut from three more states will have to quarantine for 14-days due to concerns over the spread of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON On Track To Be First $2 Trillion Company...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90525091/how-high-can-amazon-stock-go-4-reasons-it-keeps-rising-during-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like the weather outside your window right now, Amazon is hot. The Seattle-based e-tail giant’s stock price keeps hitting all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY:  TRUMP ABUSED BY DAD</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8498179/Donald-Trump-suffered-child-abuse-hands-father-niece-claims-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump, Donald Trump's niece, will claim in her bombshell memoir he suffered 'child abuse' at the hands of his workaholic father Fred Trump Sr. The book will be released on July 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Brazil's Bolsonaro tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/07/americas/brazil-bolsonaro-positive-coronavirus-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro has tested positive for Covid-19, following months of downplaying the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires and country clubs receive 'small business loans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/the-billionaires-and-country-clubs-that-received-ppp-loans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaires, country clubs, private jet companies and Kanye West all received millions in government funding under the Paycheck Protection Program, according to filings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church of Scientology bailed out!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fresh-outrage-well-connected-firms-nab-us-loans-153140732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A centerpiece of US President Donald Trump's economic relief program was under renewed scrutiny Tuesday following revelations it aided white-shoe lobbying firms and businesses linked to Kanye West and other billionaires. The controversy is the latest to befall the PPP, which was launched in April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Televangelists, Dallas megachurch that hosted Pence approved for millions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200707021948-4ednx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PPP-RELIGIOUS:Televangelists, Dallas megachurch that hosted Pence approved for millions in pandemic aid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Stock Hits Record High Amid Ad Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/facebook-stock-hits-record-high-amid-ad-boycott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors don't appear to be too worried about advertisers boycotting Facebook, with the social network's stock price racing to a new all-time high</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why China Wants Trump to Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2020/07/why-china-wants-donald-trump-win/613864/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four more years might present tantalizing opportunities for Beijing to expand its influence around East Asia and the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Bolsonaro Positive? Awaiting Test After Showing Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/coronavirus-brazils-bolsonaro-tested-for-covid-19-after-feeling-ill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian media said Bolsonaro has canceled all his official activities until he gets the results of his test for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp, Amber Heard courtroom showdown off to explosive start...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/07/johnny-depp-and-amber-heards-domestic-violence-trial-gets-off-to-explosive-start/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp and ex-wife Amber Heard arrived at separate entrances to a London court for a showdown over mutual accusations of violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protective gear for medical workers begins to run low again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/481d933b0caa6f5fc61f466c86d4777b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The personal protective gear that was in dangerously short supply during the early weeks of the coronavirus crisis in the U.S. is running low again as the virus resumes its rapid spread and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lives upended around $20 cheeseburger...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/dc-md-va/2020/07/07/le-diplomate-burger-beef-supply-chain-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cash-strapped rancher, a virus-stricken meatpacker, an underpaid chef, a hungry engineer: All their lives have been upended</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duckworth condemns Tucker for questioning patriotism: 'Walk mile in my legs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/walk-a-mile-in-my-legs-tammy-duckworth-condemns-tucker-carlson-for-questioning-her-patriotism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Tammy Duckworth criticized Fox News host Tucker Carlson for questioning her love for the United States after she said she would consider removing statues of George Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highest-ever security team monitoring Ghislaine every move in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1096649/ghislaine-maxwell-security-monitoring-epstein-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell’s every move will be monitored behind bars following the jail cell death of her former lover. The Brit socialite has been transferred to New York’s tough Metropolitan …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK hit with $150 million penalty for Epstein relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/jeffrey-epstein-case-deutsche-bank-fined-150-million-penalty-for-relationship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused child sex trafficker Jeffrey Epstein was a former friend of Presidents Donald Trump and Bill Clinton, as well as of Prince Andrew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Germany Fell Back in Love With Merkel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/07/how-germany-fell-back-in-love-with-angela-merkel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Angela Merkel of Germany is on her way out. After almost 15 years in office, the pandemic is likely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors say experimental treatment may have rid man of HIV...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/32171d5b5edb3babe25ba6edc4b505d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian man infected with the AIDS virus has shown no sign of it for more than a year since he stopped HIV medicines after an intense experimental drug therapy aimed at purging hidden, dormant...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Porn Star Accused of Sexual Abuse; 'Blood Everywhere'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ryan-madison-accused-of-sexual-abuse-by-10-women-there-was-blood-everywhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten women allege that the porn star violently abused them in the middle of shooting scenes—often after his wife lured them in with promises of a safe, female-fronted environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT Mocks Raft of Leaks and Disloyalty: 'They Expect You to Lose'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/new-lincoln-project-ad-mocks-white-house-for-raft-of-anti-trump-leaks-and-disloyalty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lincoln Project went after President Donald Trump's paranoia on Tuesday by claiming "everyone" is disloyal to him, and that's the reason why his administration has so many leak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires risk turning nation into 'powder keg' as wealth surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-richest-billionaires-risk-turning-22288193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wealth of the top 1% has soared during lockdown, but the booming fortunes of tech billionaires like Facebook boss Mark Zuckerberg and Amazon's Jeff Bezos reveal deep faultlines in society</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot 'replicant' of real person; Unable to tell difference... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-replicant-pornhub-star-22312814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pornhub chart-topped Asa Akira has been pictured with a sex robot produced by RealDoll that was based on her. Amazed fans said they could barely tell the difference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN claims Trump broke international law with killing of Soleimani...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8495837/U-N-expert-deems-U-S-drone-strike-Irans-Soleimani-unlawful-killing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The January U.S. drone strike in Iraq that killed top Iranian general Qassem Soleimani and nine others represented a violation of international law, a U.N. human rights investigator said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KOREAN AIR!?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/among-companies-getting-millions-in-ppp-loans-korean-air.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Seoul-based airline has about 500 employees in the U.S. and says it is using most of the funds to pay staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt's boxed food aid promise falls short...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-food-aid-exclusive-idUSKBN248184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government delivered far less food aid than it had pledged by the end of June, according to food bank managers and data from the agriculture department sent to Reuters, after it hired inexperienced companies to box food during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations jump 50% in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-california/hospitalizations-jump-50-in-california-as-coronavirus-infections-soar-idUSKBN2472UL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New coronavirus cases soared in California over the July Fourth weekend, stressing some hospital systems and leading to the temporary closure of the state capitol building in Sacramento for deep cleaning, officials said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singles having kids with strangers in co-parenting trend...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/06/singles-are-having-kids-with-strangers-as-part-of-the-co-parenting-trend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No need for love and marriage — just the baby carriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View mask refusers like drunk drivers: leading scientist...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/view-mask-refusers-drink-drivers-leading-scientist-084912790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who refuse to wear face masks during the coronavirus pandemic should be stigmatised the same as drink drivers, the head of the prestigious Royal Society science journal said Tuesday. The comments from Venki Ramakrishnan come as two new peer-reviewed studies showed how wearing face coverings may</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli sabotage? Mysterious damage to Iran nuke site...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mysterious-damage-iran-nuclear-know-100512867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious incident in the early hours of Thursday, July 2, badly damaged a building at Iran's Natanz nuclear complex and sparked speculation over the cause. The incident came at the end of a week marked by two explosions in Tehran, including one near a military site. Israel and the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil shocked by woman held as slave for years at family mansion...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200706195032-xuzb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former executive at Avon was found to have kept a domestic worker in slavery-like conditions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Focus Starts to Turn Toward Biden Victory...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/market-focus-starts-turn-toward-175908724.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A number of analysts are highlighting fresh investor interest in the implications of Joe Biden beating Donald Trump in November.Conversations with clients have begun to slowly shift toward what a Democratic sweep may mean, Compass Point’s managing director for policy research Isaac Boltansky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX dogged by claims of racism, sexual abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b32900c7a2e838dfe471f60daeea8f69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Last month, when former Major League All-star Torii Hunter said he’d been called the N-word “a hundred times” at Boston’s storied Fenway Park, the Red Sox were quick to back him up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How risky is dining out?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab7c92bcaa55ccbf4ff01b69daf0204e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How risky is dining out during the COVID-19 pandemic? There is some risk, but health officials say there are precautions you can take to minimize the chances you'll be exposed to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can United States pull itself together? Troubles cleave nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ff1254f0017af3aa02f0311bb2c67ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAGINAW, Mich. (AP) — It was difficult to celebrate America in Saginaw this year. The deadly coronavirus had torn through the county. Unemployment had surged five-fold. Weeks of protest over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black activist says he was victim of 'attempted lynching' by white group in incident partially caught on video...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/i-was-almost-the-victim-of-an-attempted-lynching-black-man-says-group-of-white-men-assaulted-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bloomington, Indiana civil rights activist says he was assaulted by a group of white men at a lake. Two people were hit by a car at a protest over the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Internet Fight Begins...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/07/hong-kong-security-law-sets-stage-for-global-internet-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Hong Kong grapples with a draconian new security law, the tiny territory is emerging as the front line in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferson's descendant wants memorial pulled down...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1095610/thomas-jeffersons-descendant-washington-dc-memorial-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DESCENDANT of Thomas Jefferson wants the Washington DC memorial to be removed because the Founding Father “owned more than 600 slaves”. In an opinion piece published in the New York T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music icon Charlie Daniels dead at 83...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/entertainment/music/2020/07/06/charlie-daniels-country-music-dies/5384087002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlie Daniels, a member of the Country Music Hall of Fame best known for "The Devil Went Down to Georgia," has died at age 83.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Bolsonaro Undergoing Test After Showing Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bolsonaro-undergoing-covid-19-test-after-showing-symptoms/ar-BB16pILd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrested Under New Law, Hong Kong Protesters Get Swabbed for DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/arrested-under-new-law-hong-kong-protesters-get-swabbed-for-dna/ar-BB16pF3E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States mandate masks, begin to shut down again, as coronavirus cases soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/states-mandate-masks-begin-to-shut-down-again-as-coronavirus-cases-soar-and-hospitalizations-rise/ar-BB16pmw8?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi's husband among lawmaker-linked recipients...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/06/nancy-pelosis-husband-among-lawmaker-linked-loan-recipients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A firm partially owned by House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s husband was among the lawmaker-linked businesses that got Paycheck Protection Program loans, according to data released Monday. Companies owne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governors' companies grabbed bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9544ec851527b8712ff63adf9180b47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Governors who ordered shutdowns as their states responded to the coronavirus pandemic were among millions of beneficiaries of the loan program created to help small...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Support Withering in Hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-support-withering-in-areas-where-virus-cases-are-rising/ar-BB16nPCi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Camp Sees 'Desperation' in Ever-Changing Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-camp-sees-desperation-in-trumps-ever-changing-attacks/ar-BB16nYnH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA: July 4 weekend air travel down 70%t compared to last year...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/506094-tsa-july-4-weekend-air-travel-down-70-percent-compared-to-last</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. air travel over the July Fourth weekend dropped significantly this year over last year as Americans remain wary of mass transit amid the ongoing coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom, coming under fire, ramps up enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-coming-under-fire-ramps-214430011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom vows to crack down on restaurants and bars that ignored restrictions over the July 4 weekend. Some critics say it is too little, too late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE WEST'S CLOTHING LINE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8798e58a0ddc490ad549329b343e551c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The government's small business lending program has benefited millions of companies, with the goal of minimizing the number of layoffs Americans have suffered in the face of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music icon Charlie Daniels dead at 83...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1093709/country-star-charlie-daniels-dead-stroke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COUNTRY Hall of Fame star Charlie Daniels passed away Monday morning at the age of 83. His death was confirmed in a statement by his publicist Don Murry Grubbs, the Tennessean reported. Doctors det…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquor store employee scooped everyone with news...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/sports/spt-columns-blogs/for-petes-sake/article244030892.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small business bailouts went beyond hard-hit companies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2c79abd6acb08843b13f8a5be877b7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The government on Monday identified roughly 650,000 mostly small businesses and nonprofits that received taxpayer money through a federal program that was designed to soften job...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals approaching capacity as Miami closes restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edb298e959d070aea5851d3bd1d8ffbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Hospitals rapidly approached capacity across the Sunbelt, and the Miami area closed restaurants and gyms again because of the surging coronavirus Monday, as the U.S. emerged from a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Mayor infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e758a52a3e5a275549f1a4e426021a65</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Atlanta mayor Keisha Lance Bottoms announced Monday that she had tested positive for COVID-19. The 50-year-old Democrat is among the women named as a potential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Mayor infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/atlanta-mayor-keisha-lance-bottoms-tests-positive-for-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"COVID-19 has literally hit home," Bottoms said in a tweet. "I have had NO symptoms and have tested positive."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
