<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ENOUGH IS ENOUGH:  Queen tells top aides to plot legal blitz on Harry &amp; Meghan...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15930851/queen-legal-fightback-harry-meghan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has ordered senior Palace aides to plan a legal fightback amid ­hurtful attacks by Harry and Meghan — declaring: “Enough is enough.” The monarchy’s legal team is consulting libel experts …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAIR BLASTS BIDEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/21/tony-blair-western-troops-must-stay-afghanistan-until-eligible-evacuated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former prime minister says abandonment of Afghanistan shows UK is now a second-rate power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Jesse Jackson hospitalized with covid...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/news/coronavirus/jesse-jackson-sr-jacqueline-jackson-test-positive-for-covid-19-currently-hospitalized-at-northwestern/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Reverend Jesse Jackson Sr. and his wife, Jacqueline Jackson have both tested positive for COVID-19 and are hospitalized at Northwestern Memorial Hospital, according to a statement from Ra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE LONG ISLAND, HAMPTONS</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2021-08-21-tropical-storm-hurricane-henri-new-york-new-england-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Henri is now a hurricane, and will threaten portions of the Northeast while it is near hurricane strength. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative talkshow host Phil Valentine dies after covid battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/conservative-talk-show-host-phil-valentine-dies-after-covid-19-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative radio talk show host Phil Valentine has died after weeks in a Nashville area hospital battling COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Iowa, Marjorie Taylor Greene tests national appeal...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation-politics/in-iowa-marjorie-taylor-greene-tests-her-national-appeal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia U.S. Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, in her debut political trip to Iowa, is trying to build her nationwide profile as a lawmaker, though her far-right views and past beliefs in the QAnon conspiracy theory have made her a pariah...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA:  'Seriously, y'all. Stop it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article253662138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Food and Drug Administration issued a strong and unusual warning on Saturday: “You are not a horse. You are not a cow. Seriously, y’all. Stop it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 23,000 Atlanta students in quarantine!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/over-23000-metro-atlanta-students-quarantine-weeks-into-school-year/6FP3J5IHTBBAJMOTQDBWCGE65U/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those numbers are just a fraction of how many students are likely quarantined: Only a select few districts release quarantine numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi infected who refuse self-isolate face fines, jail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/568868-mississippi-covid-19-patients-who-refuse-to-self-isolate-could-face-fines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state health officer for Mississippi issued a COVID-19 isolation order on Friday, telling people that if they test positive for COVID-19 and refuse to self-isolate, they could face fines or possible ja</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=ir&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=40.500:-78.500:32.000:-64.500&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeasterners scramble to hunker down...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/northeasterners-scramble-to-hunker-down-as-hurricane-henri-takes-aim/ar-AANAcYe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People across coastal New England and Long Island made last-minute preparations ahead of Henri's anticipated landfall Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four weeks in July: Inside Biden struggle to contain delta surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/four-weeks-in-july-inside-the-biden-administration-e2-80-99s-struggle-to-contain-the-delta-surge/ar-AANA8py?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After declaring ‘independence from a deadly virus’ on July Fourth, Biden and his team were caught flat-footed as the delta crisis spiraled out of control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The vaccinated are worried and scientists don't have answers.</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/the-vaccinated-are-worried-and-scientists-don-t-have-answers/ar-AANzgN7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Anecdotes tell us what the data can’t: Vaccinated people appear to be getting the coronavirus at a surprisingly high rate. But exactly how often isn’t clear, nor is it certain how likely they are to spread the virus to others. And now, there’s growing concern that vaccinated people may be more vulnerable to serious illness than previously thought. There’s a dearth of scientific studies with concrete answers, leaving public policy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some people ingesting livestock dewormer after FOXNEWS push...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/fda-horse-dewormer-covid-fox-news-1215168/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You are not a horse. You are not a cow,” the Food and Drug Administration said about using the drug that hosts on Fox News have been pushing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor accused of sacrificing animals for 'Santeria' witchcraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/doctor-accused-sacrificing-animals-apartment-24810434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a tip-off from a neighbour, investigators found at least 22 farm animals in Emilio Otero's three-bedroom apartment in New Jersey including goats, chickens and a dead pigeon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disinfection robots and thermal body cameras: Welcome back to the office...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/money/2021/aug/21/covid-free-office-h3-bucharest-disinfection-robots-thermal-body-cameras</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A workplace in Bucharest filled with anti-virus innovations could become the new normal in office design, its creators hope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside horrific 'Children of God' cult...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-horrors-of-growing-up-in-a-pedophilic-sex-cult</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Discovery+ docuseries ‘Children of the Cult’ centers on those that left the Children of God, a hellish pro-pedophilia cult founded by David Berg that ensnared several celebs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PR offensive falters...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210821142109-4gzty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/TALIBAN-COMMUNICATION (PIX):As Kabul turmoil mounts, Taliban's PR offensive falters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prospect of reparations sparks tension as Charleston seeks to atone for sins of slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/charleston/article253600568.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If something is damaged, then it needs repair. It’s that simple,” a councilman said. “Charleston — and this state — must lead this fight. We have to lead the fight because we led in the oppression of a people.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine resistance inmilitary remains strong; Dilemma for Pentagon as mandate looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccine-resistance-in-the-military-remains-strong-a-dilemma-for-pentagon-as-mandate-looms/ar-AANzoCc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon hints at expanded operations in Kabul, as evacuations face new hurdles and roadblocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Taliban-co-founder-in-Kabul-for-talks-as-group-16402556.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon's spokesman strongly hinted Saturday that U.S. troops could begin leaving...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest tax hike on wealthy in decades bogged down in Congress..</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/politics/politicalnews/s-2557209?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy Americans wondering how much more taxes they’ll owe after Democrats pass their sweeping social-spending package may have to wait until deep into the fall, or later, to find out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nursing shortage at crisis levels in GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/coronavirus/georgia-nursing-shortage-at-crisis-levels/G37X6GW2HRDEXGWB6OS6OBA5KE/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 has turned Georgia’s chronic nursing shortage into a crisis, with hospitals having to scale back services for lack of staff. Exhausted nurses also are dealing with patients who can be abusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom's big recall vulnerability: State's broken unemployment system...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsoms-other-covid-19-recall-120011819.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-standing problems at California's Employment Development Department have become a leading issue for the campaign seeking to recall Gov. Gavin Newsom from office on Sept. 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients demand blood transfusions  -- only from unvaxxed!</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/tainted-blood-covid-skeptics-request-blood-transfusions-from-unvaccinated-donors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another twist on covid vaccine hesitancy, blood centers say they are starting to hear from transfusion patients demanding blood from unvaccinated donors. Experts say the option is neither practi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban Order Women Off TV...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/taliban-afghanistan-media-censorship-fear-us-withdrawal-1234818263/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editor’s note: Seasoned foreign affairs correspondent and Only Cry for the Living: Memos from Inside the ISIS Battlefield author Hollie McKay recently returned to Afghanistan to cover the pla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US most wanted Al Qaeda terrorist reappears...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3515523/most-wanted-al-qaeda-terrorist-khalil-haqqani-kabul-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of America’s most wanted terrorists with a $5million bounty on his head has reappeared in Kabul as Taliban leaders gather to map out the future of the war-torn country. Al-Qaeda terrorist…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBT marches held in Poland under heavy police security...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-europe-religion-poland-5fe0233e2072a10b7623ed3abf0ef9d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CZESTOCHOWA, Poland (AP) — Parades for LGBT rights took place under heavy police presence Saturday at the foot of Catholic Poland’s most revered monastery in Czestochowa, in the south, and in Gdansk, on the Baltic coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Lt. Gov. Blames Blacks and Libs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-dan-patrick-fbed18dc7adf4441fbe66495069b9452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas' lieutenant governor blamed rising hospitalization and death rates from COVID-19 on unvaccinated Black people — comments that were quickly denounced as racist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French virus passport in full use but protests keep going...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-8a27d8a9cbfad3789e0fca8e24daaef4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Thousands marched Saturday in cities across France to protest the COVID-19 health pass that is now required to access restaurants and cafes, cultural venues, sports arenas and long-distance travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LudN6M6Mmao</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone to sue ABCNEWS for $25M...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/08/21/roger-stone-plans-to-sue-abc-news-for-25-million-over-jan-6-articles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I can't wait to have their reporters under oath in a courtroom," Stone said on the conspiracy site Infowars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST..</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/live-news/hurricane-henri-long-island-new-york-new-england-live-updates/1003782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forecasters warn time is running out for Long Islanders and residents of southern New England to prepare for not only the immediate impacts of Henri, but also a few that could last through the following week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Johansson Rips 'Misogynistic' DISNEY In Battle Over Profits...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/scalett-johansson-disney-lawsuit-black-widow-response-arbitration-1234819262/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 8:44 AM: As anyone who has seen a Marvel movie or read the comics knows, the Black Widow moves fast and deadly – – and that’s exactly what Scarlett Johansson did this morn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IS threat forces changes to evacuations at Kabul airport... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-middle-east-evacuations-kabul-11e1590d8f9976fae13e7ee83a6b193a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Potential Islamic State threats against Americans in Afghanistan are forcing the U.S. military to develop new ways to get evacuees to the airport in Kabul, a senior U.S. official said Saturday, adding a new complication to the already chaotic efforts to get people out of the country after its swift fall to the Taliban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo bans chimp-loving fan who blows kisses to ape...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3514361/zoo-bans-woman-chimp-visiting-blow-kisses-antwerp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ZOO has banned a woman who “loves” one of its chimps after she and the ape would blow kisses and wave to each other during weekly visits. Adie Timmermans has been left heartbroken by …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Marines cradle Afghan babies as evacuees airlifted to safety...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3514040/us-marines-cradle-babies-afghan-air-lift-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEART-warming pictures of Marines tending to Afghani children have gone viral as evacuations continue following the Taliban’s takeover of the country six days ago. The images, taken by a US s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside horrific 'Children of God' cult...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3513885/children-of-god-cult-david-berg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEARING a woman walk through the door, 11-year-old Verity Carter prayed she would finally be saved from the ‘uncle’ who was raping her. But her ‘rescuer’ turned and quietly walked away, leaving her…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PICTURES:  World's worst zoo attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3496211/worlds-worst-ever-zoo-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FROM the other side of a zoo cage, most animals look tame and arguably approachable – but rest assured, these are still very much wild creatures with feral instincts. Just this month a woman …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS stars 'betrayed' with ban on porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/3511692/onlyfans-courtney-tillia-betrayed-explicit-content-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONLYFANS model Courtney Tillia says she feels “betrayed” after the social media platform kept its creators in the dark about banning explicit content, she told The Sun exclusively. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORNING AFTER:  Jerusalem could have all gone up in smoke in latest wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jerusalem-could-have-all-gone-up-in-smoke-in-latest-wildfire-677221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENVIRONMENTAL AFFAIRS: One of the country’s worst fires devastated areas around Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Iowa, Marjorie Taylor Greene tests her national appeal...</title>
      <link>https://omaha.com/news/in-iowa-marjorie-taylor-greene-tests-her-national-appeal/article_52ced3bf-5971-5576-a865-0b22980e7bac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa. — She rattled off pullups at the Iowa State Fair, trailed by a pack of reporters and onlookers. She dodged questions about her political future. And she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach suspends law used by cops to arrest people who film them; Training ordered...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-beach-suspends-law-used-210908289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami Beach police say they have stopped enforcing a new law that critics believe has emboldened officers to arrest bystanders using their phones to film police on duty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recall candidate Larry Elder draws fire for N-word comedy clip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/larry-elder-draws-fire-n-021039847.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The clip, which was recorded in the 1990s, was recently unearthed by KBLA radio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variants likely to bring a fall and winter of mandates, anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/delta-variant-likely-bring-fall-120056591.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many health experts believe mask mandates and tougher vaccine requirements will be needed in the coming months to avoid more serious coronavirus surges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid oxygen shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wesh.com/article/orlando-mayor-to-hold-newser-on-unprecedented-event-requiring-community-assistance/37359831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wesh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dyer explained that many COVID-19 patients require liquid oxygen for their treatment. OUC has used liquid oxygen to treat the water supply for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Most Face Masks WILL NOT Stop Covid; Cloth Only Filters 10% Of Exhaled Aerosols...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/masks-wont-stop-covid-indoors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite wearing a mask, the study finds a large buildup of aerosol droplets suspended in the air coming from wearers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toddler, 1, survives three nights in forest with bears and wolves...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/toddler-girl-survives-three-nights-24808291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyuda, the daughter of a nuclear physicist, was miraculously located after three nights in an area of thick forest, around two-and-a-half miles from her home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mad House Getting Off Cape Cod!</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/08/20/tropical-storm-henri-cape-cod-preparations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harbormasters, residents, and business owners on Cape Cod are preparing for Tropical Storm Henri to hit the area hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  HENRI NEW ENGLAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/henri-long-island-new-england-northeast-landfall-hurricane/1003672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been nearly 36 years since a hurricane has made landfall on Long Island. Plus, New York City was under a tropical storm warning as Henri picked up speed on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=wv&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=37.750:-79.750:29.250:-65.750&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST HIT IN 30 YEARS?</title>
      <link>https://www.ny1.com/nyc/all-boroughs/weather/2021/08/20/live-blog-henri-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ny1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest updates as the storm heads north.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADVISORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211148.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Extremely worrisome'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-hurricanes-9c64eb1be8ccdf184861a53161e4d5f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLYMOUTH, Mass. (AP) — Parts of the Northeast could begin to feel the effects of Tropical Storm Henri as soon as late Saturday, as the system that is expected to become a hurricane by the end of the day barrels toward the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  HENRI NEW ENGLAND...</title>
      <link>?https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/henri-long-island-new-england-northeast-landfall-hurricane/1003672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
