<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CNN moderator assumes Bernie lying about women...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/debate-moderator-assumes-bernie-sanders-was-lying-about-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A moderator from the CNN/Des Moines Register debate sided with Elizabeth Warren in the he-said-she-said dispute over whether Bernie Sanders said a woman couldn’t be president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Cop standing on Manhattan subway platform smashed in face with bike chain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/police-search-for-man-who-randomly-threw-metal-chain-at-off-duty-officers-face-in-subway/2260028/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seemingly random attack on an off-duty police officer at a Lower Manhattan subway station left commuters uneasy as the NYPD continued to search for the suspect on Wednesday. Police say a man threw a metal bicycle chain through a subway car’s open door, hitting a 37-year-old cop in her face at the Park Place 2 train station on Tuesday….</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida plans to buy Everglades land targeted for oil drilling...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/environment/article239311568.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronan Farrow, HBO Making Doc About Threats Against Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ronan-farrow-hbo-team-doc-threats-journalists-1269872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The project is the first to go into production under a multi-film deal the 'Catch and Kill' author signed with the premium cable outlet in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man hangs large swastika in station...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/video-shows-man-hanging-large-swastika-in-subway-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City police detectives are looking for a man who stuck a swastika on the outside of an elevator inside a subway station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage at world's first trans kid doll with penis and dress...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-first-transgender-doll-penis-21287500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC CONTENT — The small doll has divided Russians after it was spotted in the Planeta Igrushek (Planet Of Toys) shop in the Siberian city of Novosibirsk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDIDATES DUCK IT OUT IN DES MOINES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7889093/Amy-Klobuchar-Donald-Trump-crowned-winners-2020-Democratic-debate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While none of the candidates pulled off a runaway win at Tuesday night's debate, Minnesota Sen Amy Klobuchar was widely praised by analysts for her pragmatic performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal accused of raping, killing 92-year old...</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/news/queens-murder-suspect-should-have-been-deported-ice-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials say the suspect in the murder of a 92-year-old woman should've been turned over to immigration officers months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film execs: Next James Bond can't be a woman!</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/features/james-bond-no-time-to-die-barbara-broccoli-michael-wilson-1203466601/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For nearly 60 years on the silver screen, James Bond, the rakish secret agent who jets from one exotic port of call to another, romancing women and besting bad guys in the name of queen and country…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Would Require California Teachers To Teach About 'Climate Change'...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/14/california-teachers-required-teach-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California schools may soon be required to teach about the causes and effects of climate change under a bill introduced on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST Braces For Top Editor's Retirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/washington-post-braces-for-top-editors-retirement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marty Baron “has been saying he’s gonna retire for the past three years,” one Post staffer tells The Beast. This time, it looks like he’s serious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even when sober, frequent pot users are dangerous drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/even-when-sober-frequent-marijuana-users-are-worse-drivers-report-n1115681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers tested participants in a driving simulator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG TWEETS MEATBALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/bloomberg-campaign-raises-eyebrows-with-a-meatball-featuring-the-candidates-face</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bloomberg campaign raised eyebrows on Tuesday evening over a bizarre tweet featuring the face of former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg on a meatball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell makes case for Trump acquittal ahead of trial...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478369-mcconnell-makes-case-for-trump-acquittal-ahead-of-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) on Wednesday ripped House Democrats and made the case for the upper chamber acquitting President Trump as he waits for the articles of impeachment to be transmitted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538 ROUNDUP...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/trump-approval-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking Donald Trump’s approval ratings throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Stumbles and Mumbles His Way Through...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-supercut-biden-stumbles-his-way-through-final-democratic-deb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Excuse me’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  Trump's Impeachment 'Will Last Forever'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-pelosi-trump-was-impeached-and-it-will-last-forever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘An impeachment that will last forever’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEAM IMPEACHMENT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3ff484c069f314f03dfb4e15e8d85c67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Speaker Nancy Pelosi on Wednesday named two House chairmen who led President Donald Trump's impeachment inquiry as prosecutors for Trump's Senate trial. Intelligence...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Under Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/cnn-under-fire-overtly-hostile-treatment-sanders-iowa-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland ranked best country in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-countries/articles/us-news-unveils-best-countries-rankings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female lion at Chicago zoo dies from mysterious fall into moat after death of longtime mate...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/female-lion-at-chicago-area-zoo-dies-from-mysterious-fall/article_0f02b499-1edd-5d82-a868-463237a6cc48.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — In the span of two weeks, Brookfield Zoo in suburban Chicago has lost both of its African lions, the longtime male-female pair Zenda and Isis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top hotel suites...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-7885967/The-worlds-100-hotel-suites-revealed-Las-Vegas-Lanesborough-London.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private jet lifestyle magazine Elite Traveler has drawn up the list, which includes the 10 biggest - and the 10 most expensive - suites from every region around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE: She Stuck Knife in Back...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/MMFlint/status/1217446338784309249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Elizabeth &amp;amp; Bernie have appeared in my films. I love them both. Why Elizabeth chose to stick a knife in Bernie’s back is beyond me. At a time when job #1 is to remove Trump, how did this help? My new RUMBLE podcast “The Sad Downfall of Elizabeth Warren.” https://t.co/uFwOFNka9U”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock announcement...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-govt-shock-resignation-putin-calls-reforms-144841748.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's government resigned in a shock announcement on Wednesday after President Vladimir Putin proposed a shake-up of the constitution. The announcement by Putin's longtime ally Dmitry Medvedev came after the president used his annual state of the nation address to call for a nationwide vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 Honduran migrants preparing new US-bound caravan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/1-000-honduran-migrants-preparing-us-bound-caravan-142453927.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Close to 1,000 people have gathered in Honduras' second city forming a migrant caravan that will soon head for the United States, a human rights activist told AFP. Thousands of Central American migrants have been braving the risk of extortion, kidnap and even murder as they flee poverty and gang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020: LOWEST SOLAR ACTIVITY IN 200 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/2020-the-lowest-solar-activity-in-over-200-years_01142020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man has video camera implanted in prosthetic eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/eyeborg-video-camera-implanted-prosthetic-21279787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rob Spence has replaced an eye in which he is blind with a video camera placed in a prosthetic eye that allows him to record for up to 30 minutes before the batteries run out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In quake-hit Puerto Rico even bees fleeing their homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-puertorico-quake-bees/in-quake-hit-puerto-rico-even-the-bees-are-fleeing-their-homes-idUSKBN1ZE19U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Puerto Rican bees are abandoning hives as weeks of earthquakes disrupt colonies,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brave New World Of Retail: WALMART Robots Just Beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joanverdon/2020/01/14/brave-new-world-of-retail-walmarts-robots-are-just-the-beginning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The retail industry has decided that robots and other automated inventory systems are better than humans for certain tasks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women prefer men with beards; More 'dominant and attractive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/women-prefer-men-beards-theyre-21284152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study carried out by the University of Queensland found that almost all women preferred men with full beards, but those who didn't had a fear of parasites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#NeverWarren trends...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/15/politics/bernie-sanders-elizabeth-warren-debate-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone is lying. Or, at the very least, badly misremembering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos promises $1 billion in bid to see off Indian e-commerce storm...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-tycoon-bezos-flies-internet-trading-storm-india-070321823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon tycoon Jeff Bezos promised Wednesday a new billion-dollar investment in India, just two days after authorities launched an anti-trust investigation into the e-commerce giant. A three-day visit by Bezos, whose worth has been estimated at more than $110 billion, sparked protests in New Delhi and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theories persist about mystery drones seen in rural region...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08e24017555a00fe37a67316069aa2ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHEYENNE, Wyo. (AP) — People insist they have spotted fleets of large drones crisscrossing rural America’s night sky, their mission mysterious, raising questions that have veered into conspiracy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos sparks protests across India...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7889655/Jeff-Bezos-sparks-protests-India-traders-claim-Amazon-destroying-livelihoods.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire, who is facing an investigation by the country's competition commission, announced a $1billion investment programme when he spoke at a business conference in New Delhi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rigged': Critics Cry Foul as Debate Slants Against Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/2020-election/2020/01/14/rigged-critics-cry-foul-as-cnn-debate-slants-against-bernie-sanders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders supporters are infuriated by Tuesday's Democrat debate in Iowa because it appears CNN moderators favored Elizabeth Warren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI MOVES...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478287-senate-braces-for-trump-impeachment-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate is preparing to begin President Trump’s impeachment trial on Tuesday, a grueling process that senators expect will be highly partisan and likely drag on past the State of the Union address in early February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY launches playlists for dogs left home alone...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200115105532-amqlm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ODD-SPOTIFY/DOGS:Spotify launches playlists for dogs left home alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAN JONES:  'Nothing I Saw Tonight Would Take Trump Out'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnns-van-jones-buries-2020-field-after-debate-nothing-i-saw-tonight-would-be-able-to-take-donald-trump-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN's Van Jones tonight said he was dispirited by the Democratic debate and that nothing he saw from any of the candidates looked like any of them could beat President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Refuses to Shake His Hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/watch-warren-refuses-to-shake-bernies-hand-after-debate-bernie-throws-up-hands-after-they-speak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) and Senator Bernie Sanders (I-VT) did not shake hands following the conclusion of a tense Democratic primary debate in De Moines, Iowa Tuesday night. In the video above</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  Dull Night Of The Living Dead... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/democratic-debate-review-iowa-vote-bernie-sanders-donald-trump-elizabeth-warren-pete-buttigieg-joe-biden-cnn-1202830934/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first actual votes of the 2020 Presidential campaign will be cast on February 3, and tonight saw the six leading Democrats for the White House take the stage for the CNN cameras for their final…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN debate moderator assumes Bernie lying about women...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/debate-moderator-assumes-bernie-sanders-was-lying-about-women  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A moderator from the CNN/Des Moines Register debate completely sided with Elizabeth Warren in the he-said-she-said dispute over whether Bernie Sanders said a woman couldn’t be president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>86-year-old man who robbed a bank pulled over 1 mile away...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/article239270123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana's Oldest Living Woman Celebrates 108th Birthday; Never Smoked, Rarely Drank, Takes No Meds...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/01/14/oldest-known-person-in-indiana-108-year-old-jennie-zawada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennie Zawada, who mowed her lawn and drove her own car until age 104, may just be the oldest person living in Indiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL STAR KUECHLY SHOCKS WITH RETIREMENT; HISTORY OF CONCUSSIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/sports/nfl/carolina-panthers/article239299573.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10491032/results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**DRUDGE POLL** WHO WON?</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10491032</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Jim Rogers warns economic system not sound...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/insanity-jim-rogers-warns-horrible-time-ahead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Feet Entering China May Presage New Trading Era!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-chicken-feet-entering-china-may-presage-new-trading-era/ar-BBYXNFy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL DEBATE BEFORE VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/january-democratic-debate-live/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CNN/Des Moines Register Democratic presidential debate features six qualifying candidates in January. Watch livestream and follow live coverage here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempers rise... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tempers-rise-democrats-hold-final-debate-iowa-vote-010312565.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Democrats braced for fireworks at Tuesday's presidential debate, with liberal Bernie Sanders signalling he could clash with rivals in the final showdown before voters in Iowa kick off the nomination process. While former vice president Joe Biden, the 77-year-old establishment candidate, is leading</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census Bureau kicks off 2020 ad campaign amid fears about privacy and hacking...</title>
      <link>http://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Census-Bureau-kicks-off-2020-ad-campaign-amid-14975521.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Census Bureau on Tuesday unveiled an ad campaign to persuade every household in America to fill out the once-a-decade survey, which begins next week in remote parts of Alaska.  The decennial count of everyone living in the United States is used to determine a decade's worth of congressional apportionment, redistricting, and hundreds of billions of dollars in federal funding. But a rising distrust of government, combined with the battle over whether to add a citizenship question and fears that the newly digital survey could be hacked, may make counting every person more difficult than ever.  Many of the 1,000-plus print, television, radio and Internet ads target immigrant and minority communities, which are traditionally among the hardest to count, and emphasize that data collected by the Census Bureau is confidential and cannot be shared, even with other government agencies.  Bureau Director Steven Dillingham, who will fly this week to Toksook Bay, Alaska, population about 660, to count the first person in the census, introduced the campaign in the District of Columbia, where placards displayed print and television ads, along with a coloring book about the census that will go to more than 117,000 schools across the nation.  In one Spanish-language television spot featuring young Hispanic men, one says he is worried it could be dangerous to fill out the form. Not at all, his friend assures him, saying he filled out the census 10 years ago and it was fine.  The campaign targets audiences in 13 languages, along with African Americans, Native Americans and children, who also are typically undercounted.  But some immigrant advocates said they were distressed that there was no mention in the ads of the citizenship question the Supreme Court blocked from the survey last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1917': Film's Single, Continuous Shot Challenges a Short-Attention Span...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/archives/news/watching-1917-in-2020-when-our-lives-are-more-edited-than-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching 1917 in 2020 was a jarring experience for me: My broken attention span isn't used to watching continuous, unbroken scenes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat Loaf sues Dallas hotel, convention after fall from stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/courts/2020/01/14/meat-loaf-sues-dallas-hotel-convention-after-fall-from-stage-that-hes-still-recovering-from/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer Meat Loaf is suing a Dallas hotel and a horror convention after a fall from a stage last year that he said left him seriously injured and unable...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDERAL SPENDING SETS RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/1163090000000-federal-spending-sets-record-through-december</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government spent a record $1,163,090,000,000 in the first three months of fiscal 2020 (October through December), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement released Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://go.cnn.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;go.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNNgo is a revolutionary news-watching experience that offers the live CNN broadcast with unprecedented features. You can catch-up on the stories you‘ve missed, go deeper and learn more about the stories that interest you with related coverage, and enjoy the most popular On Demand Shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Enhances Privacy and Perhaps Itself at the Same Time...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-enhances-privacy-perhaps-itself-211227826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- If you lived west of the Mississippi at the dawn of the 20th century, there must have been a moment when it became clear that the Wild West of old was no more. Perhaps it was the arrival of the railroad, or the last stagecoach robbery or the introduction of a federal income tax.For</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSU's Big Win Scores Over 25M Viewers, Biggest Cable Audience In Two Years...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/lsu-win-ncaa-national-championship-football-clemson-espn-viewership-up-donald-trump-vince-vaughn-1202830464/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a lot of social media spittle flying over Vince Vaughn shaking hands with Donald Trump at Monday’s 2020 College Football Playoff National Championship in New Orleans, but the real action wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRACKDOWN WILL LIMIT PRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/impeachment-trial-security-crackdown-will-limit-capitol-press-access</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unprecedented crackdown on the Capitol press corps will be unleashed for the Senate impeachment trial of President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate War Powers Resolution Has 51 Votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/senate-war-powers-resolution-has-51-votes-democrat-kaine-says/ar-BBYXlDE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff sends evidence from Rudy associate...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/schiff-lev-parnas-ukraine-impeachment-5562caa2-dd94-4ecf-a05d-1bdce494c67c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new evidence includes communications between Parnas and Ukrainian officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 17 Students, 9 Adults Exposed After Aircraft Dumps Fuel On Elementary School Near LAX...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/01/14/jet-fuel-aircraft-dump-cudahy-lax-students-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen elementary school kids in Cudahy were being evaluated Tuesday after an aircraft dumped fuel on its final approach to LAX, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Indiana man sparked Secret Service investigation shouting outside Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article239243583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daredevil Wallenda to make 1,800-foot wirewalk over active volcano on live TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/news/20200114/sarasotarsquos-nik-wallenda-to-wirewalk-over-active-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daredevil will perform the feat live on television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aircraft near LAX 'dumps jet fuel on elementary school playground'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7887443/Aircraft-final-approach-LAX-dumps-jet-fuel-elementary-school-playground.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paramedics are on the scene in Cudahy, according to local fire crews. Around 30 children at Park Avenue Elementary School reported a reaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman Caught Trying To Build Bomb Inside WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/01/14/supplies-needed-mass-destruction-florida-woman-build-bomb-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman is accused of trying to build and detonate an explosive device inside a Tampa Walmart store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA drinking more now than just before Prohibition...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1f81ade0748410aaeb6eeab7a772bf7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Americans are drinking more now than when Prohibition was enacted. What’s more, it’s been rising for two decades, and it’s not clear when it will fall again. That’s the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars struggle to breathe at Australian Open...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/player-quits-australian-open-after-coughing-fit-smoke-filled-air-n1115046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The air quality in Melbourne was “the worst in the world” overnight, according to Victoria state’s chief health officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Seniors Getting Roommates To Help Save Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/senior-citizens-getting-roommates-to-help-save-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More senior citizens are moving in together to make ends meet financially. In New York, one senior who picked up a roommate said the financial relief is "like a step into heaven."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tragic kingdom: Dad in custody after family found slain in DISNEY community...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/14/dad-in-custody-after-family-found-slain-inside-disney-world-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fairytale Florida community built by Disney World has turned into a horror scene after cops discovered four bodies in the home of a missing former Connecticut family. A man identified by neighbor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ: LET'S HEAR FROM MORE WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/14/ted-cruz-senate-call-witnesses-whistleblower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ted Cruz said in a new interview that he is &amp;quot;open&amp;quot; to the Senate calling witnesses in an impeachment trial, specifically naming the Trump-Ukraine whistleblower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Security Fears, Caucuses Will Use New Smartphone App...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/01/14/795906732/despite-election-security-fears-iowa-caucuses-will-use-new-smartphone-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iowa Democratic Party confirmed to Iowa Public Radio and NPR that it plans to use an Internet-based app to transmit results, but it declined to provide any more specifics or security details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man requests 'trial by combat' with Japanese swords to settle dispute with ex-wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/crime-and-courts/2020/01/13/iowa-courts-david-ostrom-requests-trial-combat-swords-settle-dispute/4456079002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ostrom asked an Iowa court to give him 12 weeks notice to "source or forge" a katana and wakizashi for the duel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59 year-old Afghanistan vet re-enlists in US Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2020/01/14/59-year-old-afghanistan-veteran-will-report-to-army-basic-training-this-summer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighborhood Fights Plans To Install 5G Cell Service Over Health Worries...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/hinsdale-neighbors-fight-plans-to-install-5g-cell-service-citing-health-worries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;5G internet means more cellphone towers – which will appear every 12 homes in some neighborhoods. Some Hinsdale neighbors are worried about health risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROUGHER SHOVING EXPECTED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec4da97dd1619a43474fab2c819a22a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Rougher shoving and sharper jabs are expected as a tighter field of Democrats takes the stage for Tuesday night's final debate before Iowa's leadoff presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrified residents flee homes as crazed gang of 400 monkeys raid village...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/crazed-gang-400-monkeys-raid-21279520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monkeys from the Indian village of Narasapuram have been terrorising residents, raiding homes and stealing food, leading to many being forced to flee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION TAME...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2020/01/14/consumer-price-index-shows-very-low-inflation-persists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation has been slowing down for the last two months, suggesting that the Fed will not hike rates this year. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARK BITE NORTH CAROLINA IN JANUARY... </title>
      <link>https://wpde.com/news/local/surfer-bitten-by-shark-nc-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wpde.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RODANTHE, Dare County &amp;mdash; A North Carolina man taking advantage of unseasonably warm weather was bitten by a shark while surfing off the coast Monday afternoon, according to a chief beach ranger. A 26-year-old was taken to the Outer Banks Hospital about 2:30 p. m. with injuries that weren&amp;rsquo;t considered life-threatening, Boone Vandzura, chief ranger with Cape Hatteras National Seashore, said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Brady Moves to Greenwich, Stadium Suite Cleaned Out...</title>
      <link>https://weei.radio.com/blogs/weei/tom-brady-rumors-qb-has-moved-to-greenwich-connecticut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weei.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Greg Hill, Tom Brady's Gillette Stadium suite has been cleaned out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOMELAND' star accuses Trump of trying to have it both ways on intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/478145-homeland-star-accuses-trump-of-trying-to-have-it-both-ways-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Homeland" star Mandy Patinkin is accusing President Trump of wanting to have it "both ways" with the U.S. intelligence community and selectively picking which conclusions to support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Video Stages Assassinations...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-video-stages-assassination-of-trump-pompeo-netanyahu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iranian propaganda video dramatizes the assassination of President Donald Trump, Secretary Mike Pompeo, and Israeli prime minister Benjamin Netanyahu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Colorado Scaling Back Drone Investigation; 'Unaware Of Any Crime Being Committed'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/state-scaling-back-drone-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado Department of Public Safety said Monday it will be scaling back operations of its investigations into suspicious drone activity in northeastern Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions of racism linger as Harry, Meghan step back... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1420bd1ff04ac8f330bdd9cf9d061e52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — When accomplished, glamorous American actress Meghan Markle married Prince Harry in 2018, she was hailed as a breath of fresh air for Britain’s fusty royal family. That honeymoon...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
