<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'NO TIME TO DIE' Gets New Trailer as 007 Marketing Engine Roars Back to Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/no-time-to-die-gets-new-trailer-as-007-marketing-engine-roars-back-to-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Faces Pressure to Drop Russian Pipeline to Hit Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/merkel-faces-pressure-to-drop-russian-gas-pipeline-after-navalny-s-poisoning/story-cb4jKpOMpZf5hEYZVR7ibI.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norbert Roettgen, head of the German parliament’s foreign affairs committee and a candidate to head Merkel’s Christian Democratic party, said the Nord Stream 2 pipeline needs to be stopped because completing it would reward rather than punish Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would military intervene in election results?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/514789-would-the-united-states-military-intervene-in-the-election-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is notable that we even have to ask this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO: Trump better have army to protect him if comes to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/02/cuomo-trump-better-have-an-army-to-protect-him-if-he-comes-to-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo on Wednesday all but threatened President Trump’s safety if he returns to New York City in a rant responding to an exclusive story by The Post that Trump is looking…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pull Out of Kentucky Derby? Pressure on Black Owner Mounts...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/03/pull-out-of-the-kentucky-derby-pressure-on-a-black-owner-mounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In any other year, Greg Harbut would be enjoying the achievement of a lifetime. On Saturday, he will watch his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Burning Man Internet's Ultimate Test?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/03/is-virtual-burning-man-the-internets-ultimate-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What makes Burning Man so special to those who attend — the cliché among the faithful is “life-changing” — is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Act of Heresy, NRA Former No. 2 Calls for Gun Control...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/03/in-act-of-heresy-n-r-a-s-former-no-2-calls-for-gun-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association’s former second-in-command is breaking with the group’s orthodoxy and calling for universal background checks and so-called</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increased risk of civil unrest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/45d5266e50df78175141544a136242d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just two months left until the U.S. presidential election, Facebook says it is taking more steps to encourage voting, minimize misinformation and reduce the likelihood of post-election “civil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Kenosha, Biden to test his promise to unify nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2373c9517d2781ab11b92e1ee0dd5273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Joe Biden faces the most intense test yet of his pledge to be a calming, unifying leader for a divided nation when he travels Thursday to Kenosha, Wisconsin, a city now at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEESE: Can you tell me woke joke?</title>
      <link>http://www.irishnews.com/magazine/entertainment/2020/09/03/news/john-cleese-can-you-tell-me-a-woke-joke--2055272/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran comedian warned that organising ‘a society around the sensibilities of the most easily upset people' leads to a ‘very neurotic society'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA DEBATE RAGES</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Debate-rages-over-whether-FDA-should-use-15538911.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A fierce debate has erupted over whether the Food and Drug Administration should use its emergency authority to clear a coronavirus vaccine before it is formally approved - a move opponents warn could pose safety dangers and inflame anti-vaccination sentiment but others say could save thousands of lives by speeding protection from the virus.  With concerns growing about the politicization of the FDA amid a botched White House rollout of the agency's emergency authorization of convalescent plasma and sharply criticized comments by FDA Commissioner Stephen Hahn, some scientists and bioethicists are demanding the agency forgo use of its emergency authority for a vaccine. They worry its very flexibility, which gives FDA officials broad latitude, could it make it easier for the White House to pressure the agency into clearing an unproven vaccine before Election Day, Nov. 3.  President Donald Trump's repeated promise to deliver a safe and effective vaccine this year, "or maybe even sooner," has become central to his reelection campaign and has sparked concerns in the scientific community in particular that the White House could pressure regulators to cut corners.  Those concerns come against the backdrop of an accelerating race to develop a coronavirus vaccine as three vaccine makers - pharmaceutical giant Pfizer, biotechnology firm Moderna and drugmaker AstraZeneca - conduct Phase 3 clinical trials, the last before seeking a green light from regulators.  A recent report by Morgan Stanley said the most likely timing for data from one or more of the trials is November. But others say it's possible some results might be available in October if the vaccines prove spectacularly effective and there are enough viral infections in the community to prove the shots are protecting patients who receive them.  The CDC has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden garners more Republican endorsements, this time from ex-govs...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden-republicans-exclus-idUSKBN25U1AK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 100 Republican and independent leaders will endorse Democrat Joe Biden for president on Thursday, including one-time 2020 Republican presidential candidate Bill Weld and the former Republican governors of Michigan and New Jersey, people involved in the effort told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBD/TIPP POLL:  BIDEN +8...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/politics/joe-biden-holds-solid-lead-over-president-donald-trump-no-convention-bump-ibd-tipp-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rochester erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8692307/Disturbing-new-video-shows-black-man-41-suffocating-death-New-York-police-custody.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Prude was left brain dead after the incident and later died on March 30 after he was taken off of life support - seven days after the encounter with police in Rochester, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP VACCINE BY NOV 1</title>
      <link>https://www.centredaily.com/news/coronavirus/article245406245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.centredaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
THE ROCK reveals COVID battle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rock-reveals-family-coronavirus-battle-012121233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dwayne &amp;quot;The Rock&amp;quot; Johnson and his entire family tested positive for coronavirus but have made a full recovery, the professional wrestler turned Hollywood A-lister said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid cases in Europe back to March level...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200902122737-li5yq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/EU-ECDC:COVID-19 cases in Europe back to March level, EU health body says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video in Black man's suffocation shows cops put hood on him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c2f0cf366e560b7f41ebb3c964b099c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Black man who had run naked through the streets of a western New York city died of asphyxiation after a group of police officers put a hood over his head, then pressed his face into the pavement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image of Woman Fondling Tiger's Testicles at Zoo Prompts Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_asia/article/935vx5/image-of-woman-holding-drugged-tigers-testicles-at-thai-zoo-prompts-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The photo is yet another case of big cats in captivity being mistreated for the sake of tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Told Press Sec to Take 'One For Team' After  Kim Jong Un Flirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/sep/01/donald-trump-sarah-sanders-take-one-for-the-team-kim-jong-un-wink-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former press secretary describes boorish remarks by president in memoir Speaking for Myself, due out next week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Black Hole Collision Ever Detected Creates Cosmic Monster...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/biggest-black-hole-collision-ever-detected-creates-a-cosmic-monster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two monster black holes met, danced and fell into each other. Their collision formed a black hole 150 times more massive than the sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lung cancer patient kicked out of bingo for not masking breathing hole in neck...</title>
      <link>https://toronto.ctvnews.ca/ontario-woman-kicked-out-of-bingo-hall-for-not-using-mask-to-cover-breathing-hole-in-her-neck-1.5085291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;toronto.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ontario woman battling lung cancer, who breathes through a hole in her neck, was kicked out of her local bingo hall because her breathing hole wasn't covered, her son says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Reports Predict Bannon's '$500 Used Car' Wall Will Fall into Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/awkward/court-mandated-engineering-reports-predict-section-of-steve-bannons-500-used-car-border-wall-will-fall-into-rio-grande/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent August in NYC: Shootings Double, Murder Up by 50%...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/02/a-violent-august-in-n-y-c-shootings-double-and-murder-is-up-by-50/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The steep rise in gun violence that has rattled New York City and intensified the debate over policing continued at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi calls salon visit 'set-up,' refuses to apologize...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/Speaker-Pelosi-calls-salon-visit-a-set-up-15538247.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco Democrat said if anyone was owed an apology, it was her by the salon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacKenzie Scott becomes world's richest woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8690509/Jeff-Bezos-ex-wife-MacKenzie-Scott-worlds-richest-woman-Amazon-shares-surged.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MacKenzie Scott, who owns a 4 percent stake in Amazon after her 2019 divorce from Bezos, now has a net worth of $67.4 billion, according to Bloomberg Billionaires Index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  DOW CLOSES AT 29,100...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/01/stock-futures-rise-slightly-after-strong-start-to-september.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose as traders took profits out of high-flying names and snapped up shares in more beaten-down parts of the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians buying their own fire trucks on CRAIGSLIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/living-in-sf/article/People-are-buying-their-own-fire-trucks-15532111.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For $17,000, an imported 1995 Japanese Toyota Hilux fire truck can be yours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rules NSA phone snooping illegal -- after seven-year delay...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/02/court-rules-nsa-phone-snooping-illegal-407727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the controversial phone metadata program played little role in the terror-fundraising case at issue, the long-awaited ruling says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON cash influx, rare Bezos donation...</title>
      <link>https://coloradosun.com/2020/09/01/cory-gardner-john-hickenlooper-big-tech-positions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coloradosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The experience of PopSockets in Colorado illustrates the bipartisan push in Congress to regulate Big Tech. Republican Cory Gardner and Democrat John Hickenlooper both have ties to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First death tied to Sturgis Rally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/caad0620f9d24506bf5e8629045d9218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — A Minnesota man who attended the Sturgis Motorcycle Rally in South Dakota last month has died from COVID-19, Minnesota health officials reported on Wednesday. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa Sen. Ernst: 'So skeptical' of case counts...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/politics/2020/09/02/iowa-sen-joni-ernst-so-skeptical-coronavirus-case-counts/5690416002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sen. Joni Ernst questioned at a campaign stop this week whether coronavirus cases are being overcounted nationally, echoing conspiracy theories that have spread in recent days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi to vote on new flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/news/politics/2020/09/02/new-mississippi-state-flag-commission-final-design/3455475001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision came down to two flags Wednesday, after nearly 3,000 designs were submitted to a state commission for consideration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNGER SPIKES: 10% of U.S. households going hungry...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/935466/10th-american-households-say-havent-enough-food-during-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stock market is recovering from the COVID-19 pandemic, but working Americans are not. The coronavirus pandemic led to business shutdowns that in turn translated into the biggest employment numbers the country has ever seen. The slumping economy shocked even the most food secure states in the U.S., with one in ten Americans reporting they didn't have enough food during a given week amid the pandemic, Bloomberg reports. While the U.S. is no stranger to hunger, it usually is at its worst in the rural south, while midwestern states ranked among the most food secure in the country. And when the whole country has gone hungry in the past, it usually stemmed from food shortages, like during the Dust Bowl or World War II rationing, Bloomberg notes. During the COVID-19 pandemic, meanwhile, farmers had to dump millions of gallons of milk and other food they couldn't sell or donate. Even Americans 'surrounded by food' haven't been able to afford to eat during this pandemic, Bloomberg writes. That included people in the farm-rich state of Minnesota, where nearly 70 percent of those accessing emergency food pantries were doing so for the first time. Across the country, a third of hungry Americans used emergency food distributors for the first time as well, according to Feeding America. And with millions of Americans still out of work, many people are still without sufficient food supplies. President Trump on Tuesday didn't mention the rampant hunger still lingering throughout the U.S. as he praised August's 'very impressive' stock market rebound. Read more at Bloomberg. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside story of $8 million heist from CARNEGIE LIBRARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/arts-culture/theft-carnegie-library-books-maps-artworks-180975506/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smithsonianmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Precious maps, books and artworks vanished from the Pittsburgh archive, and the caper’s final chapter was just written</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  Comedian Chris D'Elia accused of exposing himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/02/entertainment/chris-delia-accused-of-exposing-himself/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris D'Elia, a comedian and actor, is accused of exposing himself to several women during the last decade. He denies the accusations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland Mayor moving to avoid rioters targeting his home...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/02/portland-mayor-wheeler-moving-to-avoid-rioters-targeting-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic mayor of Portland, Ore. is moving from his $840,000 condo to avoid rioters who have repeatedly targeted the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercomputer Analyzed -- and New Theory Emerged...</title>
      <link>https://elemental.medium.com/a-supercomputer-analyzed-covid-19-and-an-interesting-new-theory-has-emerged-31cb8eba9d63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;elemental.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A closer look at the Bradykinin hypothesis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force One getting ready to go supersonic...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/2/pentagon-takes-first-step-toward-building-superson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air Force One is already one of the fastest passenger planes in the world — but the Pentagon wants to make it a lot faster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton: Donald will be 'stacking sandbags' to stay in White House after defeat...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/bill-clinton-trump-will-be-stacking-sandbags-to-stay-in-white-house-after-defeat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Bill Clinton and his wife Hillary Rodham Clinton are increasing their warnings that President Trump will not accept defeat in the fall election and will scheme to keep control of the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaine lands safely after stunt!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1409907/david-blaine-balloons-ascension-stunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ILLUSIONIST David Blaine parachuted towards the ground after releasing himself from a bunch of 52 helium balloons today. On Wednesday, Blaine returned to solid ground in the Arizona deser…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FAKE' MEDICINE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fauci-coronavirus-vaccine-trials-stopped-early-good-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phase 3 trials are currently underway for three of six vaccine candidates backed by Operation Warp Speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Who Lost 7 Relatives Becomes First American To Trial Oxford Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-vaccine-oxford-trial-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I know there was a risk because it's like — it's a trial," 23-year-old Jacob Serrano said. "But I'd rather have us one step closer, no matter what it takes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia woman arrested for FACEBOOK post 'inciting' lockdown protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/09/02/watch-pregnant-aussie-mother-arrested-for-allegedly-inciting-coronavirus-lockdown-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Australia arrested a pregnant 28-year-old woman for planning a coronavirus lockdown protest and promoting it on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORDS SMASHED:  Biden pulls in $365 million in August...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-august-fundraising-2214d49b-bf97-468f-abc3-9e1a843b5d23.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's believed to be the most ever raised by a U.S. presidential candidate in a month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON!  DEBATE MODERATORS ANNOUNCED...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/514782-moderators-announced-for-presidential-debates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential debates between President Trump and Democratic nominee Joe Biden&amp;nbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private payrolls miss expectations, point to slowing labor market recovery...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200902134643-cg1ph</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/EMPLOYMENT (WRAPUP 2, PIX):WRAPUP 2-U.S. private payrolls miss expectations, point to slowing labor market recovery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN DREAM:  Harry and Meghan sign mega NETFLIX deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1409596/meghan-markle-prince-harry-netflix-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN Markle and Prince Harry have signed a deal with Netflix. The Duke and Duchess of Sussex have founded an unnamed production company and signed a multi-year deal with the streaming giants. ⚠️ …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA AND BLM DUKE IT OUT AFTER TRUMP VISIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1407868/trump-supporter-black-lives-matter-protester-brawl-kenosha/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TRUMP supporter and a Black Lives Matter protester brawled in Kenosha shortly after the president payed a visit to the violence-plagued city. Just hours after President Donald Trump witnessed fir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk promises 'glorious' Martian city...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1409591/elon-musk-mars-city-starship-fleet-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has detailed his plot to build a “glorious” city on Mars – but says early visitors will probably die. The star-gazing billionaire has reaffirmed his vision for a Martian colon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Flares in New Hot Spots as Americans Let Guard Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/covid-flares-in-new-us-hot-spots-as-americans-let-guard-down/ar-BB18DdMP?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Rage, More Stress...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/09/02/how-to-deal-with-covid-anger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic is causing unusual levels of anger and stress among everyone and one family counselor says cutting yourself a break is more important than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Seizes Property From Church Challenging Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/coronavirus/county-seizes-property-from-l-a-church-challenging-coronavirus-restrictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County is seeking to crack down on a church that is challenging local worship restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Urgent' request sent to states in push for vaccine delivery by Nov. 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/coronavirus/article245406245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't call me actress, says Cate Blanchett...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dont-call-actress-says-cate-142120984.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood star Cate Blanchett said Wednesday that she would rather be called an actor rather than an actress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Germany has evidence Putin critic Navalny was poisoned with Novichok...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200902130810-fo6ui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY-GERMANY (URGENT):Germany has evidence Putin critic Navalny was poisoned with Novichok</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Perceptions of White-Black Relations Sink to New Low...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/318851/perceptions-white-black-relations-sink-new-low.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' perceptions of relations between White and Black Americans are the lowest Gallup has recorded, with less than half now calling them good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain on barbells: Can strength training improve mood?</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/lifestyle/article/Your-brain-on-barbells-Can-strength-training-15536965.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise changed my life. It managed to do what medication alone couldn't: put a dagger into my depression.  I've struggled with depressive illness since childhood, and throughout the years, my brain and body have often felt like a one-man clinical trial for every antidepressant that came to the market. Prozac? Been there! Luvox? Done that! Effexor? Check! Paxil, Wellbutrin, Lexapro, Zoloft? Check . . . check . . . check . . . and check-a-rooni!  Although mood-stabilizing pill packs have entered and exited my life with varying degrees of success over the past 30 years, one treatment option has remained a constant, reliable, no-fail mood booster throughout the decades. That would be exercise. But not just any exercise. Not the elliptical. Not spin class. Not the recumbent bike nor the rowing machine. In fact, it's not aerobic exercise at all, which has been most commonly linked to a reduction in depressive illness.  It's strength training - the muscle-building, body-toning and sometimes grunt-inducing workout - that has helped transform my chronic mental illness into better mental health. In fact, once I began a regular regimen of resistance training, the positive shift in my mood, my confidence and my self-image was so pronounced that I switched careers.  I left my work in the social service field to become a personal trainer and eventually a college professor of fitness and health promotion. Whether lecturing students, speaking to audiences or coaching clients, encouraging others to strength train for better mental health has become my mantra, my message and my life mission.  But I'm not basing this message on my firsthand experience alone. New research is validating what I feel every time I pump iron: peace of mind and a sense of achievement.  The impact of resistance training on emotional disorders is an emerging area...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking Study Discovers Honeybee Venom Kills Breast Cancer Cells In Mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/honeybee-venom-kills-breast-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In just 20 minutes, melittin breaks down the chemical messages breast cancer cells transmits to trigger both cell growth and cell division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE NAP: Pelosi as acting president...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/pelosi-president-election-college-janurary-results-judge-andrew-napolitano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., become president if there is no election result by January?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES Draws Up Electric Maybach to Defend Luxury Position...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/mercedes-mulls-electric-maybach-to-help-defend-luxury-position</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercedes Draws UpÂ Electric Maybach to Defend Luxury Position</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: How Musk Made $88 Billion During Historic Economic Crash...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/09/elon-musk-net-worth-gain-100-billion-tesla/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk is only $10 billion away from Bill Gates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branson Airline Saved as Court Ruling Caps Race Against Clock...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/branson-airline-saved-court-ruling-130437257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Richard Branson’s Virgin empire has faced many challenges in its five-decade history, from high-profile legal clashes with British Airways and failed bids to run the U.K. national lottery to abortive forays into vodka, cola and bridal wear.The setbacks have been so numerous that overcoming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Police Searching For Man Giving 'Covid Hugs' To WALMART Shoppers...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/09/01/covid-hugs-springfield-suspect-walmart-shoppers-woman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The search continues for a man giving "Covid Hugs" to Walmart shoppers in western Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/After-the-Massachusetts-Senate-race-it-will-be-15536766.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were two big races in Democratic politics in Massachusetts on Tuesday, and neither...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics of White House trade adviser draw new scrutiny as some of his pandemic moves unravel...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Tactics-of-fiery-White-House-trade-adviser-draw-15536821.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Amid the Trump administration's troubled response to the coronavirus pandemic, senior White House aide Peter Navarro has refashioned himself as a powerful government purchasing chief, operating far beyond his original role as an adviser on trade policy.  But U.S. officials say the abrasive figure's shortcomings as a manager could influence how well prepared the United States is for a second wave of coronavirus infections expected this fall.  Navarro's harsh manner and disregard for protocol have alienated numerous colleagues, corporate executives and prominent Republicans. In a previously undisclosed incident, the White House Counsel's Office in 2018 investigated Navarro's behavior in response to repeated complaints and found he routinely had been verbally abusive toward others. Navarro narrowly avoided losing his job, but the abuse has continued as the White House has grappled with the pandemic, multiple administration officials said.  On Monday, the administration terminated one contract that Navarro had directly negotiated - for 42,900 Philips ventilators. A Department of Health and Human Services spokesperson said the cancellation was "subject to internal HHS investigation and legal review." The contract had been criticized by a House oversight subcommittee, which concluded that the government had overpaid for the ventilators by $500 million.  The cancellation came after another transaction Navarro championed, a government loan to fund Kodak's transformation into a drugmaker, unraveled and became embroiled in a securities investigation. The watchdog panel says it is broadening its inquiry to examine all of Navarro's deals.  Navarro remains unbowed, scorning critics inside and outside the White House as disloyal and leaning heavily on his one true ally: President Donald Trump. The trade specialist's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Food Banks Being Overwhelmed by Worst Crisis Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2020-hunger-minnesota-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If I die, I die': Star QB fine with getting virus...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/02/kirk-cousins-is-fine-with-getting-coronavirus-if-i-die-i-die/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vikings quarterback Kirk Cousins does not believe masks work and says that he is at peace with the thought of contracting COVID-19. “If I die, I die,” Cousins said on Spotify’s “10 Questions&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jet pack at LAX? Maybe...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jet-pack-lax-maybe-jet-100547576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone with a jet pack really could have been soaring above Los Angeles International Airport over the weekend, giving pilots a scare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Flares in New Hot Spots as Americans Let Guard Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/covid-flares-in-new-u-s-hot-spots-as-americans-let-guard-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid Flares in New U.S. Hot Spots as Americans Let Guard Down</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMORGAN: Markets Positioning for Inconclusive Result...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jpmorgan-says-key-markets-brace-054551945.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Key U.S. markets now appear to be pricing in the risk of a delayed or inconclusive result from the upcoming presidential election, according to fresh analysis from JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co.Pricing for volatility protection in interest rates -- where investors trade and hedge bond exposure through</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Higher Than Numbers Say?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/02/inflation-is-higher-than-the-numbers-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest inflation statistics say prices have risen by only 1 percent over the past year. But there’s something wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nobody Likes Snitching': Rules Against Parties Dividing Campuses...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/02/college-students-told-to-report-covid-parties-ask-to-snitch-or-not-to-snitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looked to be a typical college party: a small group of students crammed in a kitchenette, cheering on as</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
