<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Sextortion' study: Men at higher risk for online blackmail in pandemic than women...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Health_News/2022/01/31/sextortion-online-blackmail-men-pandemic-study/1201643641232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men have been twice as likely as women to fall victim to online blackmail since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic, a study published Monday by the journal Victims &amp; Offenders found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis Spokesperson Defends Governor For Not Condemning...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/desantis-spokesperson-defends-governor-for-not-condemning-group-of-nazis-do-we-even-know-theyre-nazis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ron DeSantis’ spokesperson, Christina Pushaw, defended the Florida governor for not condemning a group of Nazis demonstrating in Orlando over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom spotted maskless at 49ers-Rams game despite stadium mandates...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/gavin-newsom-eric-garcetti-maskless-magic-johnson-rams-game-photo/11525649/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom and Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti are facing criticism after being spotted at the LA Rams, 49ers game without their face masks on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employees quit when bar promotes 'catch the virus' show...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/coronavirus/article257863643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Come see the show, maybe catch the virus, or just stay home and whine. Tickets 10 bucks or 6 with proof of omicron positive test. Have you had enough???”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Jew is the devil': Neo-Nazis rally in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/article-694960</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER files lawsuit against German online reporting rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/reuters/article-10460519/Twitter-files-lawsuit-against-German-online-reporting-rule.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN, Jan 31 (Reuters) - Twitter has taken legal action against a rule, coming into force in Germany from Tuesday, that obliges social media firms to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butterfly sanctuary closes after QAnon believers say it's involved in sex trafficking...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/national-butterfly-center-closed-sex-trafficking-qanon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Butterfly Center temporarily closing after being inundated with threats from QAnon believers who think it's a sex trafficking ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watchdog issues warning on athletes' safety...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-watchdog-issues-warning-athletes-124700405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US rights monitor raised the alarm Monday over athletes' safety at China's upcoming Winter Olympics, after the host authorities threatened "punishment" for anti-Beijing comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANDEMIC TENSIONS DEEPEN IN FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-tensions-deepen-in-florida-as-de-santis-digs-in-over-battle-with-critics-192843576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few states have received as much scrutiny throughout the pandemic as Florida, where Gov. Ron DeSantis has rejected many of the safety measures recommended by health officials while also downplaying the efficacy of vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long haul patients find hope in recovery clinics...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2022-01-haul-covid-patients-recovery-clinics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Stephanie Hedrick realized she was still suffering from shortness of breath, blurry vision and brain fog months after recovering from COVID-19, she knew she needed more help than her primary care doctor alone could provide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope praises taxes: A sign of equality, justice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pope-francis-business-religion-europe-rome-fecbe4e3032c68af15e79b621c1d0b74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis encouraged tax collectors on Monday to keep working to redistribute wealth and fund social services that help the poor, saying their efforts are a “guarantee of equality” that helps the common good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogan apologizes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/31/joe-rogan-apologizes-to-spotify-and-musicians.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rogan said he would be open to changes to the show like booking mainstream experts after having controversial ones and doing more research on certain topics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Tests Positive For COVID While Hiding Out From Truckers...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/coward-19-trudeau-tests-positive-covid-while-hiding-out-canadian-truckers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unjabbed NYPD officers set to be terminated next month...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-unvaccinated-nypd-terminated-20220131-7mjktcy3ojejde2bx5qujpaig4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers who have refused the COVID-19 vaccine have until Feb. 11 to get the shot, according to a memo sent out to NYPD sergeants by Sergeants Benevolent Association president Vincent Vallelong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminalizing free speech? Group challenges Miami Beach law used to cuff people filming cops

...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article257768808.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Worst foods for health...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/experts-the-worst-foods-for-your-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to live healthier, step away from these 10 foods and general food categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Hundreds of passengers stuck at JFK urinating in seats, having panic attacks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/31/jetblue-passengers-stranded-for-hours-at-jfk-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos erupted at New York’s JFK Airport Sunday night after hundreds of JetBlue passengers were left stranded on the tarmac for hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen seeks $50k from Musk to delete TWITTER bot tracking private jet...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-elonjet-twitter-bot-221826608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Sweeney maintains ElonJet, a tracker that tweets out when Elon Musk’s private jet takes off and lands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia DA investigating The Don asks FBI for security help...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-georgia-fb-security-help-48a4d34e5f84b7d878334b21e7fe66ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The prosecutor who's investigating whether Donald Trump and others broke the law by trying to pressure Georgia officials to overturn Joe Biden's presidential election victory is asking the FBI for security help after the former president railed against prosecutors investigating him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Failure of leadership'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/sue-grey-live-partygate-boris-26094796</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson has been given a copy of the Sue Gray report into allegations that parties took place in 10 Downing Street during the coronavirus lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew Costly Court Battle Puts Strain on Finances...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/prince-andrew-s-costly-u-s-court-battle-puts-strain-on-finances</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew’s Costly U.S. Court Battle Puts Strain on Finances</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen seeks $50k from Musk to delete TWITTER bot tracking private jet...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-elonjet-twitter-bot-221826608.html?fr=sychp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Sweeney maintains ElonJet, a tracker that tweets out when Elon Musk’s private jet takes off and lands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: One in four say violence against govt okay...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/31/1076873172/one-in-four-americans-say-violence-against-the-government-is-sometimes-okay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new survey, both liberals and conservatives agreed violent protests are sometimes justifiable. Republicans were twice as likely as Democrats to say violence is justified "right now."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's declining vax at expense of lifesaving transplant: 'I was born free, I'll die free'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-e2-80-99s-declining-a-coronavirus-vaccine-at-the-expense-of-a-lifesaving-transplant-e2-80-98i-was-born-free-i-e2-80-99ll-die-free-e2-80-99/ar-AATkeOa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next microchip crisis will be bigger?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/microchip-crisis-shortage-taiwan-tsmc-534f5cbb-e49b-4e16-8f9a-6229c08e1779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's advanced chips flow from one Taiwanese manufacturer. The U.S. wants to grow its own domestic business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spit, screens, sneakers: Rise of preacher-influencer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/jan/29/pastor-michael-todd-spit-preacher-influencer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Todd’s viral moment highlights pastors’ push to connect with an audience beyond the walls of the church</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen seeks $50k from Musk to delete TWITTER bot tracking private jet...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/jan/31/teenager-seeks-50k-delete-twitter-bot-tracking-elon-musk-private-jet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In DM exchange Tesla boss offers $5,000 for takedown but 19-year-old replies: ‘Any chance to up that to $50K?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How group of Irish fishermen forced Russian Navy into U-turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/31/europe/ireland-fishermen-russia-navy-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fishing community on the southern tip of Ireland breathed a sigh of relief this weekend after the Russian government gave in to appeals from local fishermen who said naval drills ordered by Moscow off the Irish coast could endanger their livelihoods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami's lure during Covid sends housing prices through roof...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/miamis-lure-during-covid-sends-011417547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami resident Maria Ruby learned last month that her rent will shoot up 65 percent in February. She cannot afford it and does not know where to go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Freedom Convoy' vows to stay until govt reverses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10458741/Canadian-truckers-stay-Ottawa-thousands-protestors-pledging-continue-create-chaos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ottawa truckers say there is no 'end date' in sight and plan to stay in the capital 'for as long as it takes' and until the Canadian government flips and withdraws its policy on vaccine mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVER: Finns to end restrictions next month...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-denmark-finland-32b1502ee6ff40a916485094d7d568d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Finland will end all COVID-19 restrictions next month, Prime Minister Sanna Marin said Monday. Marin said her Social Democratic-led government would negotiate with the other parties in parliament the timetable for the removal of the restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym owner who defied closures running for House seat...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/592030-new-jersey-gym-owner-who-defied-covid-closures-running-for-us-house-seat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey gym owner who became known during the pandemic for defying the state’s COVID-19 closures is running for the U.S. House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breyer retirement latest complication for Biden spending bill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/591883-breyer-retirement-latest-complication-for-biden-spending-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Stephen Breyer’s plans to retire have thrown another curveball into the winding efforts to get the cornerstone of President Biden’s agenda passed in what could be the final months Democrats have full control of Con</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don's Grip Faces New Strains...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/31/trumps-grip-on-g-o-p-faces-new-strains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About halfway into his Texas rally on Saturday evening, Donald J. Trump pivoted toward the teleprompter and away from a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA seeks NKorea talks after biggest missile test in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-za/news/other/us-seeks-north-korea-talks-after-biggest-missile-test-in-years/ar-AATjmMR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration reiterated that it’s ready to hold talks with North Korea without preconditions, a day after Kim Jong Un’s regime fired an intermediate-range ballistic missile for the first time since 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot performs 1st abdominal surgery without human help...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/robot-performs-1st-abdominal-surgery-without-human-help</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soft-tissue can be tricky to operate on — for humans or a robot — because the subtle movements in the texture are unpredictable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympians worry as 'Winter' disappears from Winter Games...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-sports-environment-and-nature-beijing-environment-db61d01a980bdbcc86252523547aaada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEAVER CREEK, Colo. (AP) — Ski racers settling into the start gate for Alpine World Cup events in the Rocky Mountains in early December squinted through sunshine that carried the temperature toward 50 degrees and glanced down at a course covered with pristine — and manufactured — snow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogan apologizes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-technology-health-business-435f6efc51f4d4c94587f1b4ffe5fbe3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Following protests of Spotify kicked off by Neil Young over the spread of COVID-19 vaccine misinformation, the music streaming service said that it will add content advisories before podcasts discussing the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson gets 'partygate' report but questions linger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-boris-johnson-health-business-europe-0cc714677ec8f8450568c872b12a9bdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Prime Minister Boris Johnson has received a long-awaited report from an investigation into lockdown-breaching government parties, the government said Monday. The Cabinet Office said senior civil servant Sue Gray “has provided an update on her investigations to the Prime Minister.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Moved to Secret Location...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/canadian-prime-minister-justin-trudeau-evacuated-as-anti-covid-trucker-protest-in-ottawa-grows </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRESH FACE SUPER BOWL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kansas-city-chiefs-cincinnati-bengals-nfl-sports-super-bowl-b7ae9ff6c7085710838e0d2a90b360c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years ago, the Cincinnati Bengals were the NFL's worst team. Now they're headed to the Super Bowl to play the Los Angeles Rams — in the Rams' home stadium. Matching the biggest comeback in an AFC championship game, the Bengals rallied from an 18-point hole to stun Kansas City 27-24 in overtime Sunday for their first trip to the big game since the 1988 season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen's Biggest Bomb: Movie Opens to Just $24,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/woody-allen-rifkins-festival-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amidst renewed scrutiny over sexual abuse allegations, Allen's newest film was released in 26 theaters this weekend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss USA 2019 dead after suicide fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4574999/miss-usa-cheslie-kryst-death-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FORMER Miss USA titleholder is dead after falling from her high-rise apartment in New York City. Police were called to Cheslie Kryst’s midtown apartment building around 7:13am. Paramedics were al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY Issues New Guidelines for Podcasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/30/spotifys-daniel-ek-panics-over-rock-star-defections-personally-there-are-plenty-of-individuals-and-views-on-spotify-that-i-disagree-with-strongly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINCINNATI TO SUPERBOWL!</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/2021-nfl-playoffs-what-we-learned-from-bengals-win-over-chiefs-in-afc-championsh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since the 1988 season, the Cincinnati Bengals are going to the Super Bowl following their overtime win against the Kansas City Chiefs in the AFC Championship Game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$15 million incentive to wait a week?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/sports/tom-brady-millions-reasons-extend-career-another-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady may be retiring after 22 seasons in the NFL with the New England Patriots and Tampa Bay Buccaneers. Even still, he’s set to be paid handsomely in the coming days.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
