<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>More Strikeouts Than Hits? Baseball's Latest Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/16/sports/baseball-mlb-strikeouts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This could be the first season in major league history to feature more strikeouts than hits, a slowdown that worries many league officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dr Bumbum' charged with murder over patient death...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/dr-bumbum-brazil-murder-plastic-surgeon-cosmetic-lilian-calixto-a8493931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operation to enlarge woman's buttocks went fatally wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Member Arrested in Sacramento...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/08/15/sacramento-man-arrested-isis-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government of Iraq has charged Omar Abdulsattar Ameen with premeditated murder that happened during an ISIS takeover of the Rawah District of the Al-Anbar Province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese sexbots flood America...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/723504/sex-robot-doll-china-company-wmdoll-moving-limbs-sales-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone stalks woman outside bedroom window...</title>
      <link>http://www.kmov.com/story/38893394/its-disgusting-surveillance-shows-drone-flying-outside-womans-window-at-night</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kmov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a disgusting invasion of privacy." An airborne intruder hovering outside her home late at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Mead Could Drop Below Critical Threshold...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/agency-says-lake-mead-could-drop-below-critical-threshold-1534374220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nevada’s Lake Mead, the biggest reservoir in the West, is on track to fall below a critical threshold in 2020 and could trigger a federal shortage declaration on the Colorado River, according to a new forecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: World Droid Conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/picture-gallery/tech/2018/08/15/robots-come-alive-beijing-world-robot-conference/999190002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visitors look at a robot making drinks during the World Robot Conference in Beijing on Aug. 15, 2018. The conference includes a conference on robotics, an exhibition and a robot competition with the participation of robotics enterprises to showcase their products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS: Marital spats cause disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/08/15/marital-rows-could-make-say-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Occasional squabbling is a normal part of marriage, but when it descends into vicious rows it can makes couples ill, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaceship may lay off Florida coast, says DISCOVERY CHANNEL treasure hunter...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/science/Alien-spaceship-may-lay-off-Florida-coast-says-Discovery-Channel-treasure-hunter_170882935</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a close encounter of the submerged kind, a Discovery Channel treasure hunter said he found what could be a massive extraterrestrial structure at the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean off the Florida co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican 'disturbing' silence on abuse cover-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvz.com/news/national-world/pressure-mounts-on-pope-francis-to-address-abuse-coverups/781898736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican has declined to respond to an explosive grand jury report detailing decades of sexual abuse and cover-ups by priests and bishops in Pennsylvania, refusing even to say whether church officials in Rome have read the damaging documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Tells Catholic Leaders: 'I Want to Kick Your Ass'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/08/15/duterte-catholic-bishops-kick-your-ass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte threatened violence against any Catholic bishop or priest present at remarks he delivered Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: Maxine Waters 'Strikes Fear in the Heart' of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/15/nancy-pelosi-maxine-waters-strikes-fear-in-the-heart-of-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) claimed on Wednesday that Rep. Maxine Waters (D-CA) “strikes fear in the heart” of President Donald Trump. | Big Government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presence of threatening humanoid improves performance...</title>
      <link>http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/08/being-watched-cranky-robot-might-help-you-focus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New study is the first to explore how robot moods affect human concentration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's largest fire ever  -- keeps growing...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-mendocino-complex-update-20180815-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the River fire is 100% contained as of Monday, the Ranch fire has consumer more than 314,000 acres and is 64% contained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Drug overdoses hit new record...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/401961-cdc-drug-overdoses-hit-new-high-in-2017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 72,000 Americans died from drug overdoses in 2017, according to preliminary data from the Centers for Disease Control and Preven</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University Installing AMAZON Alexa in Dorms...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/08/15/amazon-alexa-echo-back-to-school-dorm-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexa, do ever go to class?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space arms race...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-raises-questions-over-apos-191925908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has challenged Russia about a satellite orbiting the earth exhibiting "abnormal behaviour", raising questions about Moscow's intentions to develop space weapons. A US official said the satellite was acting suspiciously, describing its recent launch as “a very troubling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Russia testing 'killer satellite' in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/military/russia-accused-of-testing-a-killer-satellite-in-orbit/news-story/618fa3f5cf0bf28f83e0bf370f7cdd0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT’S small. It's nimble. It’s doing strange things over our heads. And Russia's new Kosmos 2521 satellite has the potential to bring the world’s economy to its knees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES: BLATANT LIES BEING TOLD ABOUT ME...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/alex-jones-its-a-blatant-lie-im-calling-for-violence-its-a-hoax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSM talking heads falsely claim Infowars 'inciting violence' against media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica farm seizures: List of whites facing expropriation...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1003985/South-Africa-farmers-white-seize-list-rural-Cyril-Ramaphosa </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH Africa's government has been accused of drawing up a list of almost 200 farms it allegedly wants to seize from white farmers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastating dolphin loss in red tide disaster...</title>
      <link>Devastating dolphin loss in red tide disaster...</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRENNAN SECURITY CLEARANCE REVOKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/15/trump-pulls-security-clearance-of-ex-cia-director-brennan-778791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Mr. Brennan’s lying and recent conduct characterized by increasingly frenzied commentary is wholly inconsistent with access to the nation’s most closely held secrets.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TRUMP SUBPOENA...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/politics/politicalheadlines/13977755-74/trumps-lawyers-prepare-to-fight-subpoena-all-the-way-to-the-supreme</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- Rudy Giuliani, President Trump's lead lawyer for the ongoing Russia probe, said Wednesday that he is still awaiting a response from Special Counsel ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JACK IN THE BOX</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/402072-the-hill-interview-twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-explains-what-got-alex-jones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey isn’t sure if the timeout given to Alex Jones will convince the right-wing conspiracy theorist to “reconsider” his social media behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every Dem in California itching to run for prez vs. Donald...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/We-can-t-resist-Ranking-the-CA-Democrats-who-13159198.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When both East Bay Rep. Eric Swalwell and billionaire San Francisco activist Tom Steyer turned up at the Iowa State Fair this month, it became official: One in every five Californians is thinking about running for president in 2020. That means it is time to take a waaay too early look at the field of Golden State Democrats sniffing a run for the White House. We asked several political consultants, Republicans and Democrats, to break down their strengths and weaknesses. We granted the operatives anonymity so they could speak freely — and not lose business should any of these candidates actually run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now 350 outlets print editorials denouncing 'dirty war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/15/trump-press-editorials-defence-fake-news-media-attacks-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participation comes after a push organized by the Boston Globe to run coordinated editorials denouncing Trump’s attacks on the media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customers threaten owners with violence -- after restaurant changes french fry cut!</title>
      <link>https://www.centralmaine.com/2018/08/14/customers-criticize-new-french-fry-cut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.centralmaine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Waterville eatery's owners say customers are unhappy with the fries and have threatened to fight them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDINAL DEFIANT: Allegations  one word against another...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/local-news/cardinal-wuerl-addresses-report-on-child-sex-abuse-by-priests-says-he-will-not-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with FOX 5, Cardinal Donald Wuerl, the Archbishop of Washington, sits down to discuss a grand jury report that alleges he systematically covered up and protected priests who sexually abused children in Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No cell service, run to find phone for 911 call...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/authorities-investigating-shark-attack-at-cape-cod-beach/22739608</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patient told first responders he was standing in the water 30 yards offshore when the shark bit him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Found lying on beach...</title>
      <link>http://www.providencejournal.com/news/20180815/swimmer-suffers-puncture-wounds-in-shark-attack-on-cape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRURO, Mass. — A man swimming off Cape Cod has been attacked by a shark and is being airlifted to a hospital.A MedFlight was called for a 61-year-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARK ATTACKS CAPE COD SURFER...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/08/15/shark-attack-truro-cape-cod-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person was attacked by a shark at a Cape Cod beach Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC shuts down Alex Jones pirate flagship radio station...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/business/austin-pirate-radio-station-flagship-for-alex-jones-faces-15k-fine/IKeK5Z5IUjegmfqznULCLN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pirate radio station that serves as controversial host Alex Jones’ Austin flagship has been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing arguments in explosive Manafort trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/15/manafort-trial-closing-arguments-778331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The competing positions were made during closing arguments in the first case brought by special counsel Robert Mueller’s Russia investigative squad to reach trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petro Crypto to become official currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1003908/venezuela-petro-cryptocurrency-latest-venezuela-economic-crisis-maduro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA is to make its homegrown cryptocurrency, the Petro, an official currency alongside the bolivar as the South American nation continues to battle hyperinflation which has left it on the brink of economic collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC subpoenas TESLA over Musk tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/sec-sends-subpoena-to-tesla-in-probe-over-musk-tweets-2018-08-15-171034414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subpoena from the Securities and Exchange Commission seeks information from each of Tesla’s directors, according to a person familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower posts 'flawed cars' details...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/15/tesla-whistleblower-tweets-details-about-flawed-cars-scrapped-parts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla whistleblower Martin Tripp is tweeting internal emails, photos and vehicle identification numbers that he says are evidence of deeply flawed manufacturing practices at Tesla's battery factory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER Losses Continue in March Toward an IPO...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/15/technology/ubers-losses-continue-in-march-toward-initial-public-offering.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber’s latest quarterly results indicate little change to its financial trajectory under Dara Khosrowshahi, who took over a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMERICAN HISTORY X' Director Casts ROBOT As Lead Actor...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/filmmaker-tony-kaye-robot-lead-actor-2nd-born-1202445941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: As the advancement of technology continues to replace the need for human labor, American History X director Tony Kaye is undertaking a new — and maybe controversial — step in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Emergency Crews Rush As 20+ Overdose In CT Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhregister.com/news/article/Crews-on-scene-of-multiple-reported-overdoses-on-13157824.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW HAVEN, Conn. - More than 20 people overdosed on the Green Wednesday as emergency crews raced to save lives there and around the city and one man was arrested as a "person of interest" in the case, police said Wednesday. The man, whom investigators identified only as a person "believed to be connected to at least some of the overdoses," was found in possession of drugs, police said. The man was out on parole when he was arrested Wednesday and is "known" to police, Police Chief Anthony Campbell said. As many as 39 people have overdosed since Tuesday evening from what is believed to be the synthetic cannabinoid K2 laced with Fentanyl, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA contractor faces 'longest sentence ever' for media leaks...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/georgia-woman-facing-longest-sentence-for-leaking-to-media-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5atlanta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say a Georgia woman who pleaded guilty to mailing a secret U.S. report to a news organization faces the &amp;quot;longest sentence&amp;quot; ever for a federal crime involving leaks to the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO TRIBUNE publishes op-ed slamming Trump 'written by dog'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/402032-chicago-tribune-columnists-dog-writes-op-ed-slamming-trump-for-omarosa-comment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago Tribune on Wednesday ran an op-ed “written” by humor columnist Rex Huppke’s pet dog, Zoe, tearing into President Trump for using “dog” as an insult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA PAPER PLEADS WITH PELOSI: FORGET SPEAKERSHIP!</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/opinion/editorials/article216743495.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic Party cannot be seen as the party of Nancy Pelosi and win in November. The San Francisco Democrat must put her party and her country ahead of her personal ambition and declare that she will not seek to become speaker again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tick epidemic threatens to spread to USA from Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-care/new-tick-causes-epidemic-rocky-mountain-spotted-fever-n901046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brown dog tick is more likely to bite people and spread the often fatal bacterial infection, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady's lost contact lens found 28-years later -- in eyelid!</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/63333-contact-lens-eyelid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly three decades ago, a 14-year-old in the United Kingdom got hit in the eye during a game of badminton and lost her contact lens. Here's where it turned up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeons remove 87 nails from inside man...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/15/chinese-man-swallows-87-nails-7-push-pins/998137002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 25-year-old from southern China ate 87 metal nails and 7 push pins early August. Doctors removed the items in a four-hour surgery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker back in court, this time over 'gender transition' cake refusal...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedenverchannel.com/news/local-news/owner-of-masterpiece-cakeshop-files-lawsuit-against-governor-other-state-officials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedenverchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of Masterpiece Cakeshop filed a federal lawsuit Tuesday against state officials, claiming they have doubled down on their anti-religious hostility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifeguards link drownings to parents distracted by mobile...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/15/german-lifeguards-warn-children-drowning-parents-increasingly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children are being endangered by their parents&amp;rsquo; obssession with smartphones, lifeguards in Germany have warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VATICAN 'NO COMMENT' ON PA PREDATOR PRIESTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/15/us/pennsylvania-catholic-sex-abuse-vatican/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican has declined to respond to an explosive grand jury report detailing decades of sexual abuse and cover-ups by priests and bishops in Pennsylvania, refusing even to say whether church officials in Rome have read the damaging documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phones transform bedrooms into no-sex zones...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/15/phones-turn-bedrooms-a-no-sex-zone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly three-quarters of Americans who live with their spouse or partner bring their mobile phone to bed with them. And it’s taking a toll on relationships. A new study examined what couples really…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO GETS READY: AMERICA NEVER THAT GREAT!</title>
      <link>https://www.lohud.com/story/news/politics/albany/2018/08/15/knocking-trump-cuomo-criticized-saying-america-never-great/1000315002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lohud.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then Cuomo was stung by his own comments when he said, "We’re not going to make America great again. It was never that great."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DARES TO RUN...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/13/trump-dares-ny-gov-cuomo-to-run-against-him-in-2020-says-anybody-that-runs-against-trump-suffers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump, speaking at a fundraiser Monday with New York Republicans, dared Democratic Gov. Andrew Cuomo to run against him for president in 2020, with Trump saying he welcomes the challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Lula to register as presidential candidate from jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-politics-lula/brazils-lula-to-register-as-presidential-candidate-from-jail-idUSKBN1L01M8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imprisoned former President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva on Wednesday will be registered as a candidate for this year's presidential election despite his 12-year sentence for corruption and facing several more graft trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Need A Job? Get A Tattoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/looking-for-work-tattoo-could-help/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's no longer taboo to have a tattoo. More companies are shedding their prejudice against employees and job candidates coming in with tattoos, a smart move that's giving them a competitive edge over offices that still discriminate, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81 degree ocean water likely sets Calif. record...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/highest-Pacifica-ocean-temperature-California-13152086.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sea-surface temperature of 81.3 degrees was recorded off the coast of San Diego last Thursday, and researchers believe this could be the highest temperature ever measured in California waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA cops investigate $98,000 ramen heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/georgia-police-investigating-000-ramen-noodles-heist/f91vElO0V9ERAbtDnNGaOP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fayette County officials have confirmed reports regarding a $98,000 ramen noodle heist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parolees Ready to Vote in NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/parolees-ready-to-vote-in-upcoming-new-york-primary-1534349497</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 27,000 parolees will be newly eligible to vote in New York state’s primary next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents call NETFLIX 'DESIRE' child porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/allthemoms/2018/08/15/netflix-film-desire-accused-showing-child-porn/995953002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parents group wants Netflix to pull "Desire." The film's director said it's fiction and how you think of it depends "on your level of depravity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020: Cuomo Slams USA; 'Was Never That Great'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/cuomo-slams-maga-slogan-america-never-great/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D.) slammed President Donald Trump's "Make America Great Again" slogan on Wednesday, saying the country was never that great in the past anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC subpoenas TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/15/sec-has-reportedly-served-tesla-with-a-subpoena-after-elon-musks-take.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blasts SUN SENTINEL for publishing confidential info on Parkland shooting...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/parkland/florida-school-shooting/fl-florida-school-shooting-contempt-hearing-20180814-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broward Circuit Judge Elizabeth Scherer holds a pre-trial hearing in the Parkland shooting case. On the agenda: Whether the Sun Sentinel should be held in contempt for disclosing full contents of a school district report on shooter Nikolas Cruz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER 'TIMEOUT' TO CHANGE BEHAVIOR</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-alex-jones-election-security-regrets-n900931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We can’t build a service that is subjective just to the whims of what we personally believe,” Dorsey told NBC News’ Lester Holt in an exclusive interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANS WINS IN VT...</title>
      <link>https://www.burlingtonfreepress.com/story/news/politics/2018/08/14/vermont-primary-christine-hallquist-wins-democratic-primary-phil-scott-republican/991259002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.burlingtonfreepress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christine Hallquist is a step closer to being the country's first transgender governor, while Phil Scott edged out Keith Stern in the GOP primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After straws, balloons get more scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/71082d3bb77e44a59408a69bc58caf89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Now that plastic straws may be headed for extinction, could Americans' love of balloons be deflated?        The joyous celebration of releasing balloons int</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER CEO: I PUT ALEX JONES IN 'TIMEOUT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nightly-news/video/exclusive-twitter-ceo-on-alex-jones-timeout-1299513411754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with NBC News’ Lester Holt, Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey addresses the decision to temporarily restrict the Twitter account of Alex Jones, the controversial conspiracy theorist and radio host. See more of the interview tonight on NBC Nightly News With Lester Holt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany creates 3rd gender identity: 'Diverse'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c6ede6b6eb3c43c29626e9f3671538f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's Cabinet on Wednesday approved a third gender option for official records that will allow people to be registered as "diverse," complying with a ruling from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help wanted: Cannabis budtenders, edibles chefs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/money/2018/08/15/help-wanted-cannabis-budtenders-edibles-chefs/793897002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannabis companies in Ohio are seeking a slew of new employees with cannabis-specific skill sets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin crash prompts suicide concerns...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-market-crash-prompts-suicide-concerns-135248250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current crypto correction is so bad that people posted suicide hotline numbers on Reddit's bitcoin forum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC chief plays to tiny audience at mall -- empty seats in front row!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/photo-dnc-tom-perez-plays-to-handful-of-voters-at-shopping-mall-empty-seats-in-front-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats claim they have the enthusiasm edge heading into the November midterm election, but an appearance today by DNC Chairman Tom Perez may leave many wondering if that’s true. Perez appeared at Plaza Fiesta, an “indoor Latin shopping mall” in Atlanta, stumping on behalf of gubernatorial candidate Stacey Abrams. DNC Chair Tom Perez is here …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Cities where middle class can no longer afford home...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/real-estate/2018/08/15/cities-where-middle-class-can-no-longer-afford-home-prices/37105219/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, families that pay more than 30% of their incomes on housing are considered cost burdened and may have difficulty affording rent as well as other necessities, such as food, clothing, transportation, and medical care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lena Dunham marks 9 month hysterectomy anniversary with nude pics...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/15/lena-dunham-marks-9-month-anniversary-of-her-hysterectomy-with-naked-pictures-7843847/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress called the day a 'bittersweet' occasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Black Americans not buying Omarosa's turn...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8f6c754ff73443c5b539adf76c4cf25d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For years, Omarosa Manigault Newman stood at Donald Trump's side, making her deeply unpopular with African-Americans who see her as a sellout for aligning hersel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church helped accused get DISNEY job...</title>
      <link>https://www.theintelligencer.com/news/crime/article/Church-helped-former-priest-accused-of-abuse-get-13158081.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theintelligencer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) - A grand jury report into child sexual abuse in Roman Catholic dioceses in Pennsylvania says church officials gave a former priest a positive reference to work at Disney World, even though they'd fielded at least one complaint about him sexually abusing a boy. The ex-priest, Edward Ganster, went on to work at Disney World. He died in 2014. The report cites a letter Allentown's bishop wrote to Orlando's bishop in the late 1980s while Ganster was on sick leave at a Catholic mental health hospital. He said Ganster's problems were "partially sexual" and that he couldn't reassign him. The report says a monsignor separately told Ganster he was sure the diocese would give him a positive reference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selling fake social media popularity is very big business...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/14/selling-fake-social-media-popularity-is-a-very-big-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internet has brought new meaning to the old adage, “Don’t believe everything you read.” From fake news and fake Twitter accounts to fake Instagram followers and fake Amazon reviews, the online …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE DOC READY TO SCORCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/michael-moore-f-k-hope-seriously-f-k-hope-trump-will-be-last-president-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-Trump filmmaker Michael Moore (Screenshot) “F—k hope,” because it’s “the lazy way out,” liberal activist filmmaker Michael Moore says in an interview promoting his new anti-Trump film, “Fahrenheit 11/9,” which opens in theaters on September 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Agents 'Sickened' By Containers With Tea, Soap; Hazmat Team Brought In...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/08/14/mysterious-liquids-make-tsa-officers-ill-at-orlando-international-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials at Orlando International Airport say four security officers fell ill after checking the contents of oversized containers holding unknown liquids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weed-killing chemical linked to cancer found in children's breakfast foods...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/glyphosate-roundup-chemical-found-in-childrens-breakfast-foods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;31 out of 45 tested products had glyphosate levels higher than what some scientists consider safe for children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant Reality Star Found Dead on Street Without Pants...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2018/08/14/lyric-mchenry-found-dead-on-new-york-sidewalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 26-year-old produced and co-starred on the series "EJNYC."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Russian satellite's behaviour raises alarm in US...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-45194333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official says "there is no way to verify" what object is and whether or not it may pose a danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oral sex, then holy water...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/report-pennsylvania-priests-abused-over-1-000-children-042935265.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "real number" of abused children and abusive priests might be higher since some secret church records were lost and some victims never came forward, the grand jury said. U.S. bishops adopted sweeping reforms in 2002 when clergy abuse became a national crisis for the church, including stricter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unwanted dogs left on own in Iowa forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/15/57-unwanted-dogs-dumped-iowa-forest/995933002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 30 dogs were found in an south-central Iowa forest after they were left there by owners who didn't want them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves Accuser Shopping Tell-All Memoir...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/leslie-moonves-accuser-christine-peters-shopping-tell-all-memoir-1134765 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say the 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days' producer is pitching a memoir titled 'Hollywood Granola: My Life With Nuts and Flakes,' which will chronicle a "cautionary tale about the hard work behind the scenes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman born in 1905 oldest living person in USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article216678160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Hester Ford was researching her year of birth with her family, she came across census data that might indicate Ford might have been born in 1904, making her 114 years old and the oldest living person in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studios Gamble on Franco, Affleck Projects Post-#MeToo Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/studios-gamble-james-franco-casey-affleck-projects-metoo-claims-1134941 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many of Hollywood’s accused men aren't finding new work easily, some are keeping the jobs they have — which brings unique risks for their business partners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARREY RETURNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/jim-carreys-reluctant-return-hollywood-1134623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first extensive profile in years, the one-time $20 million-a-movie star and current political cartoonist opens up about his disappearance, his personal pain, his outrage and why he's returning to the spotlight with Showtime's 'Kidding': "My plan was not to join Hollywood. It was to destroy it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's hottest export? Sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/aug/15/americas-hottest-export-sperm-fertility</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American and a Danish company dominate the global sperm market – and both claim their supply is biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Republican Seats Join Toss Up Column?</title>
      <link>https://www.cookpolitical.com/analysis/house/house-overview/house-three-more-gop-seats-join-toss-column</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cookpolitical.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Republicans, the 2018 House playing field is a lot like a game of Whack-a-Mole: everywhere they turn, new problems keep popping up in surprising places. In January, we rated 20 GOP-held seats as Toss Ups or worse, including three leaning towards Democrats. With today's changes, we now rate 37 GOP-held seats as Toss Ups or worse, including ten leaning towards Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT: Retail sales increase strongly...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/15/us-retail-sales-july-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. retail sales were forecast to edged up 0.1 percent in July, after climbing 0.5 percent a month earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night of firsts as Dems pick diverse slate of nominees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c134320bf194096a66d93616e0b0680/Night-of-firsts-as-Democrats-pick-diverse-slate-of-nominees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — In a night of firsts, Democrats in Vermont's primary chose the nation's first transgender gubernatorial nominee. In Minnesota, they picked a woman who would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where does pay go furthest?  Duluth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/where-in-the-u-s-does-your-pay-go-furthest-try-duluth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to where you live, big salaries don't always deliver the biggest bang for your buck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals scrap surgeries, Venezuelans forgo showers as taps run dry...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180815120014-zxwh0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-WATER/ (PIX, TV):Hospitals scrap surgeries, Venezuelans forgo showers as taps run dry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muja the alligator still alive and snapping in his 80s...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180815110007-tdpgs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SERBIA-ALIGATOR/ (PIX, TV):Muja the alligator still alive and snapping in his 80s at Belgrade Zoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: More than 600 birds removed from home...</title>
      <link>https://myfox28columbus.com/news/local/columbus-humane-closes-tuesday-to-handle-large-animal-cruelty-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;myfox28columbus.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Columbus Humane was closed Tuesday to handle a large animal cruelty investigation involving around 600 birds at a home.The organization said all animal support center appointments will continue, but new adoption pickups will need to be rescheduled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden under doctor's orders not to travel...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/news/joe-biden-falls-ill-wont-campaign-for-dems-at-illinois-state-fair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president had been scheduled to take part in Thursday’s Illinois State Fair Democrat Day to help bolster support for state candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Punk Rock Frontman Jumps Off Stage, Attacks Trump Supporter In Middle Of Concert...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/08/14/social-distortion-lead-singer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Hildebrand of Galt says the attack happened at a Social Distortion concert at the Ace of Spades in Midtown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive candidates bounce back in key Midwest races...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/progressive-candidates-bounce-back-gop-eyes-midwest-races/story?id=57183800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates in Minnesota and Vermont made history Tuesday night, while a former GOP presidential candidate's comeback bid fell short in a key gubernatorial race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somali-American nears new historic mark with primary win...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/somali-american-nears-new-historic-mark-with-primary-win/490894121/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's first Somali-American state legislator is poised to set the same historic mark in Congress after winning a crowded Democratic primary in Minnesota to replace Rep. Keith Ellison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing arguments in explosive Manafort trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/lawyers-begin-closing-arguments-explosive-manafort-trial-055211909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers will begin closing arguments Wednesday in the explosive trial of former Donald Trump campaign chief Paul Manafort, after which the veteran political operative's fate will rest with the jury. After hearing some 20 witnesses for prosecutors describe how Manafort allegedly evaded taxes on millions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Twelve Apostles' help migrants cross Mexico...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180815-twelve-apostles-help-migrants-cross-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buddhist monk master resigns after sexual misconduct allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-harassment-religion/buddhist-monk-master-in-china-resigns-after-sexual-misconduct-allegations-idUSKBN1L00HR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of China's highest-ranking Buddhist monks quit as the head of the country's Buddhist association on Wednesday after facing a government investigation over accusations of sexual misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Probe Seen Pushing Past Trump-Demanded September 1 Deadline...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/15/mueller-probe-seen-pushing-past-trump-demanded-sept-1-deadline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller Probe Seen Pushing Past Trump-Demanded September 1 Deadline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ dominance of gossip dwindles...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/08/15/harvey-levin-is-casting-the-tmz-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Levin Is Casting the TMZ Primary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUTERTE: Thinking of stepping down because I'm tired...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/15/philippine-president-duterte-won-t-stop-talking-about-quitting </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines' Duterte Won't Stop Talking About Quitting</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
