<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Progressive groups unhappy...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/10/progressive-groups-unhappy-articles-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With House Democrats days away from voting on articles of impeachment, at least one progressive group that has spent months advocating for that outcome is disappointed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ambush'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/active-shooter-situation-in-jersey-city-sources-say/2238983/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One police officer was shot in the head and at least two others hurt during what a law enforcement source described as an ambush active shooter situation at a bodega in Jersey City Tuesday according to a senior law enforcement official and local authorities Every public city school was locked down as multiple local state and federal teams responded The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG intensifies investigation into NRA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/new-york-attorney-general-intensifies-investigation-nra-n1099106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Attorney General Letitia James issued a new, wide-ranging subpoena in the probe, a person familiar with the document told NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 police officers shot as gunmen open fire in Jersey City... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/hudson/2019/12/one-police-officer-shot-as-gunman-open-fires-on-mlk-drive-in-jersey-city.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two gunmen are firing upon police and people from a building on Martin Luther King Drive near Bidwell Avenue, injuring at least one police officer Tuesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-top Mexican cop charged with protecting El Chapo's cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/former-top-mexican-cop-charged-protecting-el-chapo-s-cartel-n1099081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Genaro Garcia Luna was charged with accepting millions of dollars in bribes in exchange for providing protection to the Sinaloa Cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG:  Trump would 'eat alive' the other candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2019/12/10/amanpour-bloomberg-impeachment.cnn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg tells Christiane Amanpour at the Madrid climate summit, "I would vote for impeachment," but argues Trump would "eat alive" Bloomberg's rivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Bloomberg widely unpopular following campaign launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Michael-Bloomberg-is-widely-unpopular-following-14895801.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Electability is a central pillar of former New York Mayor Michael Bloomberg's newly launched presidential campaign, but a poll released Tuesday finds he is deeply unpopular with voters nationwide.  A Monmouth University poll found about twice as many registered voters rated Bloomberg negatively as positively -- 54% unfavorable, 26% favorable. That margin was significantly worse than for five other Democratic candidates, as well as for President Trump. That same measure hampered Hillary Clinton's campaign in 2016.  Bloomberg garnered 5% support nationally for the Democratic nomination, narrowly higher than some other recent polls.He was in fifth place behind former vice president Joe Biden (26%) and Sens. Bernie Sanders of Vermont (21%) and Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts (17%). Bloomberg's support is within the margin of error of South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg at 8%, Sen. Amy Klobuchar of Minnesota at 4%, businessman Andrew Yang at 3% and Sen. Corey Booker of New Jersey at 2%.  Yet the negative favorability ratings are a sign Bloomberg may struggle to grow his support among both among Democrats the broader electorate. Since its launch last month, his campaign has spent more money on ads than all the top-polling Democrats combined and is simultaneously building out ground operations in 27 states.  "Bloomberg said he got into this race because he wants to defeat Trump, but his campaign kicks off with even lower ratings than the incumbent," said Monmouth polling director Patrick Murray. "That is not the most auspicious start, but views of Bloomberg are not as deeply held as they are for Trump, so he has room to shift those opinions,"  The Monmouth poll found leading Democratic candidates also have net negative images but by smaller margins than Bloomberg. Biden was rated favorably by 43% of all registered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE unveils hijab...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktuu.com/content/news/New-Nike-swimwear-line-includes-swim-hijab-566028361.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktuu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The collection “brings performance innovation to modest swimwear.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belichick denies involvement...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28265914/patriots-bill-belichick-denies-involvement-videographer-caught-taping-bengals-sideline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots coach Bill Belichick said he "didn't have anything at all to do" with the team's videographer who was caught taping the Cincinnati sideline during Sunday's game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team admits crew 'inappropriately filmed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/patriots-admit-that-their-video-crew-inappropriately-filmed-the-field-during-bengals-game-on-sunday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots respond to allegations that they were filming the Bengals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour tries to stage late comeback...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uks-labour-seizes-healthcare-scandal-ahead-election-113022838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK opposition Labour party sought Tuesday to exploit the ruling Conservatives' weakness on healthcare and divert attention from its own mixed message on Brexit two days before Britons head to the polls. "It's abysmal out there," Jonathan Ashworth said in a recording published by a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure to release footage...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/12/10/patriots-spygate-ii-need-to-see-video-footage-goodell-bengals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone is already firing off hot takes about the Patriots and the latest videotaping controversy. For this one to get cleared up, we're going to need to see that footage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr cites 'gross abuses'... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/barr-thinks-fbi-may-have-acted-bad-faith-probing-trump-n1098986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think our nation was turned on its head for 3 years based on a bogus narrative," said the attorney general in an exclusive interview with Pete Williams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE accused of monitoring employee text messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/10/apple-accused-of-monitoring-employee-text-messages-in-lawsuit-against-ex-chip-exec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is suing its former chip architect over claims he breached his contract by heading up a new server chip company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump launches broadside against his FBI director...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-launches-broadside-against-fbi-director-141815566.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump renewed his war against his own security establishment Tuesday with a broadside against the "attitude" of FBI Director Christopher Wray. Trump accused Wray of downplaying the findings of a report issued Monday into the FBI's opening of an investigation into Russian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rights activists warn on weakening encryption...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rights-activists-warn-weakening-encryption-150704001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 activist organizations, security experts and industry groups warned Tuesday against efforts to force tech companies to weaken encryption, saying any such requirement would help hackers, criminals and authoritarian governments. The warning came in a letter to top law enforcement officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Faces 3rd Election in Less Than Year...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israeli-lawmakers-submit-bill-3rd-155705426.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- With no end to Israel’s political crisis in sight, a group of lawmakers has submitted a bill to disband parliament and hold a third election in less than a year on March 2.Debate on the bill is to begin on Wednesday morning, hours ahead of a midnight deadline for parliament to find a lawmaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi announces agreement on new NAFTA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-democrats-plan-usmca-vote-151732148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Democrats embraced the U.S.-Mexico-Canada trade agreement after securing key revisions and announced plans to vote on the deal next week, putting President Donald Trump closer to a political win as he heads into the 2020 election.Speaker Nancy Pelosi praised the changes her House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Calls Greta Thunberg a Brat in Latest Celebrity Insult...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-calls-greta-thunberg-brat-160510584.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Brazil’s President Jair Bolsonaro described activist Greta Thunberg as a “brat” in his latest attack on celebrity environmentalists concerned about the deforestation of the Amazon rainforest.Questioned about the recent killing of two indigenous leaders -- the subject of a Facebook post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerologists Overjoyed As Final Full Moon Of Decade Peaks On 12/12 -- At 12:12!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/12/10/final-full-moon-decade-12-12-at-1212/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last full moon of the decade could have special significance if you are into numerology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUTTIGIEG PAYS WOMEN MORE THAN MEN...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/10/buttigieg-campaign-pay-gender/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - 2020 presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg's traveling press secretary confirmed Tuesday that the Buttigieg campaign pays women more than men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70 Pounds Of Pot, Prescription Meds, Metal-Piercing Bullets...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/12/09/on-board-juice-wrlds-plane-pounds-of-pot-prescription-meds-no-one-claims-cargo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to the cannabis, authorities also discovered  six prescription bottles of liquid codeine, three firearms, and metal piercing bullets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors of volcanic eruption describe horror...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2538d26bd96f1f835b83ffc378c7ecd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHAKATANE, New Zealand (AP) — Survivors of a powerful volcanic eruption in New Zealand ran into the sea to escape the scalding steam and ash and emerged covered in burns, say those who first...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS CHARGE TRUMP WITH ABUSE OF POWER, OBSTRUCTION OF CONGRESS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb81279725b6f810d5792502254f2f88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats announced two articles of impeachment Tuesday against President Donald Trump — abuse of power and obstruction of Congress — pushing toward historic votes over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris keeps it on Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2897c3fc8b6856537a7627160178b6fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — With two days until Britain's election, Prime Minister Boris Johnson's final push to drive home his key message about Brexit was overshadowed Tuesday by criticism of his ham-fisted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold War redux? U.S. to hold largest Europe exercises in 25 years...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191210155102-ybdw1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-NATO/:Cold War redux? U.S. to hold largest Europe exercises in 25 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women under 35 run Finland as world's youngest leader takes office...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191210134211-jlo58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twelve ministers in the new cabinet are women and just seven are men</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Hillary top choice of Dem voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/9/hillary-clinton-emerges-top-choice-democratic-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s not running for president — yet — but Hillary Clinton was the top choice for Democratic voters in the Harvard-Harris national poll released last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASTWOOD'S 'RICHARD JEWELL' FACES BOYCOTT OVER 'SEXIST' DEPICTION OF REPORTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/calls-to-boycott-richard-jewell-movie-intensify/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Please do not pay to see movies that feature fictional female journalists who sleep with with sources for a story," Slate staff writer Mark Joseph Stern tweets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT TO PARTICIPATE IN SENATE TRIAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment-whitehouse/trump-to-address-impeachment-charges-in-u-s-senate-trial-white-house-idUSKBN1YE1VH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will address the two "baseless" impeachment cha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of Epic Boxoffice Bomb: Animated Pic Cost $75M, Opens to $656K...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/playmobil-box-office-5-tickets-couldnt-save-pic-disaster-1261121</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not even $5 tickets could save STXfilms’ animated pic, which is being called the biggest test to date of variable pricing by U.S. movie theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Tells Barr It Won't Open Up Encrypted Messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/facebook-encryption-stays-bill-barr-letter-whatsapp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People’s private messages would be less secure and the real winners would be anyone seeking to take advantage of that weakened security,” the company wrote to leaders in the US, UK, and Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida congressman 22nd Republican lawmaker to announce retirement...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/473838-gops-yoho-announces-retirement-from-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Ted Yoho (R-Fla.) announced he will not seek re-election on Tuesday, citing his pledge to only serve four terms in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Stories Had Biggest Reach: Seen, Read or Heard in 2019...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/12/10/analyzing-what-news-voters-saw-read-or-heard-in-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of death, destruction and historic inside-the-Beltway developments were most likely to break through to voters in 2019, a year that saw the deadly Hurricane Dorian, mass shootings across the nation, the longest government shutdown in U.S. history and two major investigations into President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi announces agreement on new NAFTA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4266ab9cf1179ab8edd191bd7ecf702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi on Tuesday announced agreement on a modified North American trade pact, handing President Donald Trump a major Capitol Hill win on the same day...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXXON prevails in 'climate change' lawsuit...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191210145422-vm3uu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit said that Exxon caused investors to lose up to $1.6 billion by falsely telling them it had properly evaluated the impact of future climate regulations on its business</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyme Disease Growing Public Health Issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-12-10/lyme-disease-diagnoses-grow-in-private-insurance-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: NARCISSISM DECLINES AS WE AGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7776563/Narcissism-declines-age-study-suggests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The older you get, the more you think about the world that you may leave behind, is the conclusion of a new American study, which found a link between age and narcissistic characteristics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the lonely people: More feel disconnected than ever before...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/10/health/loneliness-future-increase-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any loneliness "epidemic" is due to our increasingly aging population, according to two new studies, but that doesn't mean we should stop the fight against the trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FULL HOUSE VOTE NEXT WEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/10/house-democrats-announce-articles-of-impeachment-against-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee plans to vote on the articles this week, sending it to the full House for a final vote in the chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci: 'Trump fatigue' could help Bloomberg beat him in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/473801-scaramucci-bloomberg-would-beat-trump-in-2020-if-former-mayor-wins-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci on Tuesday cited "Trump fatigue" as one reason he thought former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg could defeat President Trump in 2020 if he is able to se</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen runaway found 'camping' inside BED, BATH &amp; BEYOND...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article238192914.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT BLASTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/trump-blasts-fbi-director-wray-backing-ig-report-2016-campaign-n1098841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"With that kind of attitude, he will never be able to fix the FBI," the president tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bright orb hovers above Arizona; 'Dropping things'...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/region-southeast-valley/mesa/mysterious-lights-hovering-over-mesa-skies-puzzles-residents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mysterious lights hovering above the east Valley have many wondering if we've had a close encounter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French pension strikes expand, police gird for new protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2f1bed7d85c7e2686e08baa938532a55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French airport employees, teachers and other workers joined nationwide strikes Tuesday as unions cranked up pressure on the government to scrap upcoming changes to the country's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINLAND:  PRIME MINISTER AT 34!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191210115123-z5rqm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINLAND-GOVERNMENT/ (URGENT):Finland's parliament approves world's youngest prime minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Social credit score': China set to roll out 'Orwellian' mass surveillance tool...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/9/social-credit-system-china-mass-surveillance-tool-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is developing a new high-tech system of mass surveillance and coercion aimed suppressing political dissent among its 1.4 billion people, while forcing American and Western businesses to conform to the government’s communist policies if they want to operate there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St Fear Gauge Acting Up. That Could Signal Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/news/wallstreet-trade-index-america-investors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy on phone records intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/473769-controversy-on-phone-records-intensifies-amid-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republicans are escalating their feud with Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff, accusing the California Democrat of carrying out a “smear campaign” against his GOP counterpart, Rep. Devin Nunes (Calif.), by publishing his phone records in the panel’s sweeping impeachment report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000-Year-Old Plan to Erase Debts Is Hot Topic Now in America...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-000-old-plan-erase-100000406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Apple Podcast, Spotify or Pocket Cast.In ancient Babylon, a newly enthroned king would declare a jubilee, wiping out the population’s debts. In modern America, a faint echo of that idea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memo in 1990s pollution case shows Warren in action as corporate consultant...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Memo-in-1990s-pollution-case-shows-Elizabeth-14894375.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The memo from then-Professor Elizabeth Warren was written on Harvard University law school letterhead, a symbol of gravitas for a scholar renowned as a champion for consumers victimized by predatory banks and other big businesses.  But on this occasion, Warren was not arguing on behalf of vulnerable families, nor was she offering the sort of stinging rebuke of corporate greed that would later define her political career. Rather, Warren was representing a large development company that was trying to avoid having to clean up a toxic waste site.  The memo, which Warren wrote in 1996, used legalistic and often dense language to argue that businesses faced the "risk of the unknown" from a growing threat of lawsuits, and that defended the company's right to "maximize its returns to its unpaid creditors and to survive as an employer."  "Environmental claims, product liability claims, and mass tort claims, for which we have currently only seen the tip of the iceberg, are multiplying against American businesses," wrote Warren, who, according to her campaign, was arguing that a different company should bear the cleanup costs.  The eight-page memo, which has not previously been reported, offers a rare glimpse of Warren in action during her past work as a corporate consultant - one whose arguments were at times out of step with the liberal presidential campaign she is running today.  Warren's compensation in the 1996 case was included in a summary released by her campaign late Sunday night showing that she had been paid about $2 million as a legal consultant during her time as a professor, most of it between 1995 and 2009.  But Warren, who has released 11 years of tax returns, has not disclosed her tax records from most of that time period. And her campaign has provided few details about her private legal business beyond short...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOBBS:  IT'S A WHITEWASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/lou-dobbs-doj-ig-report-a-whitewash-shows-the-deep-states-awesome-control-of-our-permanent-bureaucracy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Business' Lou Dobbs today reacted to the DOJ inspector general report by calling it "long-delayed and hardly worth the wait."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dozen feared dead, many missing in volcano blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7772591/White-Island-volcano-New-Zealands-eruption-leaves-dozens-Australians-feared-missing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 20 Australians including a Sydney family-of-four and a newlywed couple are listed as missing by the New Zealand Red Cross in the wake of the deadly White Island volcano eruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'Social Credit System' Used to Blacklist Foreign Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/12/09/china-uses-social-credit-system-control-domestic-foreign-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bloomberg News report on Sunday described how Communist China uses its “social credit system” to control not just citizens but corporations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWSUIT THREAT...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/clint-eastwood-lawsuit-richard-jewell-movie-warner-bros-atlanta-journal-constitution-1202805069/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros is more than willing to take on one of America’s largest newspapers over claims that portion of the Clint Eastwood directed Richard Jewell movie are defamatory. “The film is based on a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI DIRECTOR DEFENDS...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fbi-director-chris-wray-reacts-doj-watchdog-report/story?id=67605418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI Director Christopher Wray offered mixed reactions to a Justice Department watchdog report that uncovered "serious performance failures."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THEY CAN'T AGREE ON ANYTHING</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191209222918-j9it6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV):UPDATE 8-As Democrats close in on impeachment charges, Republicans cry foul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crossfire Hurricane' Turns Tornado...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/In-opening-Trump-campaign-investigation-FBI-felt-14894307.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The FBI had barely closed a politically volcanic investigation into Secretary of State Hillary Clinton's use of a private email server when it got a troubling tip about her rival's presidential campaign.  On July 28, 2016, the bureau received information from an Australian diplomat, who said a Donald Trump campaign aide had "suggested the Trump team had received some kind of suggestion from Russia" that Moscow could anonymously release damaging information about Clinton, according to the long-awaited Justice Department inspector general's report released Monday.  The tip, vague as it was, shook senior FBI officials, who were already investigating suspected Russian interference in the 2016 campaign, including the theft of emails from the Democratic National Committee. Three days later, the FBI took the momentous decision to open a counterintelligence investigation of a presidential campaign, as the election season entered the home stretch.  Almost ever since, the origin of that investigation has been a lens through which Trump's most ardent supporters and critics see his entire presidency. To the former camp, it is the original sin of a Deep State determined to prevent Trump's election on the basis of slim, if not outright fabricated evidence. To Trump's opponents, the investigation was the only possible response to the threat of a foreign adversary compromising the Republican presidential nominee's campaign.  The 434-page report by Inspector General Michael Horowitz will not settle the feud. It finds that the FBI's investigation, dubbed Crossfire Hurricane, was sufficiently predicated and largely confirms previous findings about the origins of the probe by special counsel Robert Mueller.  But it also questions officials' investigative decisions, notably about how they decided to secretly monitor the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetics-Based Dating App?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/epstein-funded-scientist-george-church-is-creating-a-genetics-based-dating-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard professor George Church says he wants to eliminate genetic diseases, but critics find his idea chilling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ON TO THE NEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/09/us/politics/trump-ig-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the time the Justice Department inspector general’s report was released, the president and his supporters had moved on in their effort to convince Americans of the enemies arrayed against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THEY CAN'T AGREE ON ANYTHING</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnn-analyst-calls-out-gop-conduct-at-hearing-didnt-even-defend-trump-just-played-game-of-distraction-and-disinformation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN Legal Analyst Susan Hennessey calls out GOP conduct at impeachment hearing: The Republicans played a 'game of distraction and, frankly, disinformation'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military bases increase security after shootings in Hawaii, Florida...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/473735-military-bases-increase-security-after-shootings-on-hawaii-and-florida-bases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Military bases are stepping up security following two shootings within the past two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR:  MY IMPEACHMENT WAS BETTER...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/473708-chris-wallace-allegations-against-trump-far-broader-than-the-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Chris Wallace said Monday that the House impeachment inquiry includes "far broader" allegations against President Trump than were levied against former President Clinton, pointing out that the Democrats' case is based on matters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Watchdog Forces Barr To Scramble...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/muckraker/how-doj-watchdog-forced-barr-to-scramble-to-undermine-trump-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Bill Barr scrambled on Monday to keep a main anti-DOJ conspiracy theory going, after Justice Department Inspector General...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia reacts with anger after doping ban from Olympics, World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/russia-faces-sporting-ban-wada-meets-095603606--oly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Anti-Doping Agency on Monday banned Russia for four years from major global sporting events including the 2020 Tokyo Olympics and the 2022 World Cup in Qatar over manipulated doping data, prompting an angry response from President Vladimir Putin. WADA&amp;#39;s executive committee, meeting in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Moves to Center...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boris-johnson-bad-day-health-195000630.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It was the kind of moment Boris Johnson has spent the entire U.K. election campaign trying to avoid. Confronted with a picture of a sick 4-year-old forced to sleep on the floor of a British hospital because of a shortage of beds, the prime minister looked away and tried to change the subject.As</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL worker swung machete at drive-through customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/news/20191209/taco-bell-worker-swung-machete-at-drive-through-customer-austin-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee at a South Austin Taco Bell is accused of swinging a machete at a customer in the drive-through lane over the weekend, according to court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY:  Truth is finally out... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-james-comey-the-truth-is-finally-out-the-fbi-fulfilled-its-mission/ar-BBY08vk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents were confiscating drugs and guns from luggage when rapper Juice Wrld suffered seizure...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-juice-wrld-guards-arrested-20191209-sfhqe3cns5hsffhxskrhqfagl4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As authorities were going through his and his entourage’s luggage, the rapper “began convulsing (and) going into a seizure,” sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government deficit spikes another 12%... </title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/473755-deficit-spikes-12-percent-in-first-two-months-of-fiscal-year-cbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy on hospital floor dominates campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6742889e9f1c0b8652d06ba94563864</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A 4-year-old boy in a Spider-Man top lying on a hospital floor took center stage Monday in Britain's election campaign, as the opposition painted his plight as a symptom of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain faces most history-shaping election since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7c2df941c2e2b3648f552efd2f2d0ca4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain is facing the most testing and significant period in its modern history since World War II. The polarized electorate now has a critical choice to make -- but it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops that defied Maduro have fled Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/779a723625d58303b7beff55ed85c4f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — For seven nerve-wracking months, they slept through the day in cramped quarters on cold floors, while spending their nights in prayer, keeping fit with dumbbells made from water jugs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned baby giraffe befriended by dog in Africa dies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c7b10c3cdcb9bab7711a1c8adef27bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — A baby giraffe that was befriended by a dog after he was abandoned in the wild has died, a South African animal orphanage said Friday. “Our team is heartbroken,” the orphanage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Argument Over Impeachment Turned Violent...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/impeachment-battery-bust-750138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 9--An argument about the impeachment hearings targeting Donald Trump turned violent Friday evening when a man allegedly shoved his 60-year-old girlfriend to the ground in the couple’s Florid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-BOEING manager says he warned company of problems prior to 737 crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/former-boeing-manager-says-he-warned-company-problems-prior-737-n1098536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"For the first time in my life, I’m sorry to say that I’m hesitant about putting my family on a Boeing airplane," Ed Pierson wrote to a company executive before the first tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ERS Player Likes, Retweets Own Highlights -- During Game...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/2019/12/09/49ers-emmanuel-sanders-liked-retweeted-own-highlights-during-game-saints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco 49ers wide receiver Emmanuel Sanders is happy the team is playing at a high level. [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk whacks traffic pylon in 'Cybertruck'; Runs red light?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/elon-musk-tesla-cybertruck-video-driving/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the video where Tesla's CEO may have run a red light and check out the shocking amount of body roll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegan influencer eats meat for 30 days, says now feels healthier...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/09/vegan-influencer-eats-meat-for-30-days-shocks-fans-by-saying-shes-healthier-than-shes-felt-in-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, that’s a big change. A formerly vegan influencer revealed to her fans that she spent 30 days eating nothing but meat and animal products. She also revealed that the new diet had some surprisi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 2 women's trip to Florida strip club sparked constitutional bout...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/orange-county/os-ne-rachels-human-rights-ordinance-20191209-4greouwqafbx7nqi7k67zf7h3q-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On her weekly trips to an Orlando strip club, Brittney Smith noticed that one of the dancers looked very familiar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENGALS:  NFL looking into if PATS taped sideline...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28261318/bengals-nfl-looking-patriots-taped-sideline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cincinnati Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Monday that the NFL is investigating whether the New England Patriots were videotaping in the press box Sunday's game against the Cleveland Browns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK govt criticized for hiding details of AMAZON data deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/alexa-what-is-transparency-government-criticised-for-hiding-details-of-amazon-data-deal-11882241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health Secretary Matt Hancock signed the deal giving Amazon access to NHS data, but the NHS is refusing to reveal on what terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents Trashed Clinton as 'Criminal', Celebrated Trump Winning Election...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/09/fbi-agent-new-jobs-2016-election-trump-hillary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the day after the 2016 election, a pro-Trump FBI agent texted another, saying that &amp;quot;shit just got real.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
