<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>S Korea's next leader to abandon Blue House for new office...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seoul-south-korea-666c4751dab0bc6fac9b1bf748c8bf32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — South Korea’s incoming president said Sunday he will abandon the mountainside presidential palace of Blue House and establish his office at the Defense Ministry compound in central Seoul to better communicate with the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK:  People will riot if another full lockdown is enforced, top doctor warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10631269/People-riot-lockdown-enforced-doctor-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Roger Kirby, president of the Royal Society of Medicine, said the public would not tolerate being deprived of their liberty on such a scale again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye  pulled from Grammys lineup over 'concerning online behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/music/news/kanye-west-grammys-concerning-online-behavior-1235209759/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West has been barred from performing at the Grammy Awards due to his “concerning online behavior,” a rep for the artist confirms to Variety. Reps for the Recording Academy and CBS, which pres…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN GOES HYPERSONIC</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/zelensky-calls-fresh-talks-russia-052632840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine called on China on Saturday to join the West in condemning "Russian barbarism", as Moscow claimed it had struck a Ukrainian arms depot with hypersonic missiles in what would be the first use in combat of the next-generation weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official invites Biden to Kyiv next week 'if he is brave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10631455/Ukrainian-official-invites-Biden-Kyiv-week-brave.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zelensky's chief diplomatic adviser Ihor Zhovka said 'one should not be afraid to [travel to Kyiv] if you are brave'. He said Zelensky is seeking Biden's help with facilitiating Ukraine's weapons acquisiton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House considered sending gas cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-democrats-gas-prices-inflation-russia-sanctions-2e647ba7-116d-4a49-b3a4-3cad156c1148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea died quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Transgender swimmer finishes last in final college race...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/transgender-swimmer-makes-final-bid-182804467.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transgender swimmer Lia Thomas ended her controversial college swimming career with a last place finish in the final of the 100-yard freestyle at the US collegiate champsionships on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow ridicules idea that cosmonauts wore yellow in support of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-ridicules-idea-cosmonauts-wore-151014565.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Sometimes yellow is just yellow," Roscosmos's press service said on its Telegram channel. "The flight suits of the new crew are made in the colours of the emblem of the Bauman Moscow State Technical University, which all three cosmonauts graduated from ... To see the Ukrainian flag everywhere and in everything is crazy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlike Trump, Biden Has Stock Market Far Down His Priority List...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unlike-trump-biden-stock-market-170000174.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Even investors with a lot at stake tend to agree: The stock market shouldn’t be a president’s top priority, especially when issues like war, blistering inflation and a pandemic are in play. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Russia Denies Cosmonauts’ Colors Signal SupportRussia Says It Used Hypersonic ‘Kinzhal’ Missiles to AttackBiden Warned Xi of ‘Consequences’ for Backing Russia in WarUkraine Update: Zelenskiy Says Talks Are Russia’s ‘Only Chance’Biden Team Hardens View of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolution brewing in Moscow?</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/putin-panicking-over-revolution-moscow-26508643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson said failure to support Ukraine now would result in a "new age of intimidation across eastern Europe from the Baltic to the Black Sea"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE sued by Black ex-employee over 'racially biased' culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/google-sued-by-black-ex-employee-over-e2-80-98racially-biased-e2-80-99-culture/ar-AAVfJAN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil bans TELEGRAM messaging service in crackdown on 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/brazil-bans-telegram-messaging-service-in-crackdown-on-e2-80-98fake-news-e2-80-99/ar-AAVfsMm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The push to shut Telegram in Brazil is part of wide-reaching efforts to combat misinformation and falsehoods about the country’s electoral system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAT team enforces emergency curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article259474324.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Miami Beach are saying a “silent prayer” as large spring break crowds once again pack South Beach a year after revelers overwhelmed the city and led police to call in a SWAT team to enforce its emergency curfew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Truckers Could Replace 500,000 Jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/self-driving-trucks-could-replace-90-of-long-haul-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot Truckers CouldÂ Replace 500K U.S. Jobs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwhelmed prosecutors quitting in tears amid staffing crisis, NYC district attorneys say...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/overwhelmed-prosecutors-quitting-tears-amid-231200659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Underpaid prosecutors overwhelmed by a mammoth backlog of cases are quitting in droves when their work is needed more than ever, the city’s district attorneys told the City Council on Friday. “Former staffers cited the responsibilities of discovery, managing the backlog of cases, and increased night and weekend shifts among the reasons why they leave,” Bronx District Attorney Darcel Clark told ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Scott says Supreme Court vote on Judge Jackson won't be based on skin color...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article259547289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee is scheduled to start Monday the first of several confirmation hearings for Supreme Court nominee Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO wants to avoid getting dragged into  war  -- by mistake...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/europe/2022-03-18/nato-avoid-war-russia-5389776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military commanders from NATO countries are working the phones with their Russian counterparts to make sure the U.S. and its allies don’t get dragged into a war over a misunderstanding on the Ukrainian border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Russians breaking through digital iron curtain -- leading to fights with friends and family...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/some-russians-are-breaking-through-putin-e2-80-99s-digital-iron-curtain-e2-80-94-leading-to-fights-with-friends-and-family/ar-AAVfYwb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney World criticized over 'racist' performance by Texas high school at Magic Kingdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/disney-world-criticized-over-racist-performance-by-texas-high-school-at-magic-kingdom/ar-AAVfxPG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives have scored big in Philly politics. Here comes establishment pushback...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/progressives-have-scored-big-in-philly-politics-here-comes-the-establishment-pushback/ar-AAVe3PH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa caucuses could lose their top status. Jimmy Carter put them on the map...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Iowa-caucuses-could-lose-their-top-status-Jimmy-17013513.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-shot presidential candidate arrived in Le Mars, Iowa, brimming with a confidence...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELEGRAM booms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/telegram-booms-russias-digital-landscape-044602058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Telegram messaging app has become a go-to platform since Russia's invasion of Ukraine, despite concerns over its data security and defenses against misinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly find shelter in subways...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/elderly-ukrainians-shelter-metro-carriages-102912348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is not clear what makes Valentyna Katkova cry more: illness and old age, or the fact that she now lives in a Kyiv subway car, fleeing Russian bombing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother of Chicago twins who helped take down 'El Chapo' admits to burying millions in drug proceeds under porch...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brother-chicago-twins-helped-down-181200879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Chicago twins Pedro and Margarito Flores were just 16 when their older brother Armando was arrested in the late 1990s for selling narcotics out of a Cicero auto dealership. Armando was later sentenced to five years in federal prison, and his absence created a vacuum for his younger brothers to fill. Within a few years, the twins had risen to the highest levels of Chicago’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 American Marines killed during  exercise in Norway...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/4-american-marines-killed-during-123117908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Jonas Gahr Stoere tweeted that the plane crash occurred overnight while troops were participating in the NATO Cold Response exercise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the transfer of foreign military equipment to Ukrainian soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/europe/2022-03-18/secret-transfer-military-equipment-ukrainian-soldiers-5390190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were no passport officers on the dirt road, no customs lane, no signs marking this isolated patch of farmland for what it has become: a clandestine gateway for military supplies entering Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERLIN:  Ukrainian Jews find refuge in what was once Europe's 'center of darkness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/purim-in-berlin-ukrainian-jews-find-refuge-in-what-was-once-europe-s-center-of-darkness/ar-AAVg20g?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin rallies Russians forced to attend by employers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-channels-hitler-sinister-new-26505434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian president gave a pro-war speech in front of tens of thousands of “Z” flag-waving supporters at a Moscow stadium, which has now been compared to Hitler's speeches in Nazi Germany</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN USES HYPERSONIC MISSILES</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-putin-uses-deadly-hypersonic-26506222</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadly conflict in Ukraine has taken a sinister turn as Russia's leader Vladimir Putin has decided to unleash hypersonic missiles for the first time as he continues his invasion</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
