<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scooter Critics Rage Against Machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/scooter-critics-rage-against-the-machines-11555844400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber and Lyft have dipped their toes into the scooter-sharing business, but they may be cannibalizing their ride-sharing core.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd attacks leader of Turkish opposition party...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-election-attack/leader-of-turkish-opposition-party-safe-after-crowd-attacks-him-idUSKCN1RX0CO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of Turkey's main opposition party was attacked by several shouti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope during Easter vigil: Reject 'glitter of wealth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/20/pope-easter-vatican-glitter-wealth-1283780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Sin seduces; it promises things easy and quick, prosperity and success, but leaves behind only solitude and death,” he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For millennials, climate change clock ticks louder than biological one...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/some-millennials-climate-change-clock-ticks-louder-biological-one-n993331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I had this internal struggle: ‘Do I really want to bring a child into this world?’” a Seattle 29-year-old said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Methodists edge toward breakup over LGBT policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/religion/united-methodists-edge-toward-breakup-over-lgbt-policies-n996741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under one scenario, many centrists and liberals would leave en masse to form a new denomination — a potentially complex endeavor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage after protesters urge police suicides...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d1114da81614882907167a924463937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — With French police suicides on the rise, officials are expressing shock and anger after some yellow vest protesters encouraged police to kill themselves. Radical protesters have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broke Roger Stone Speaking for Money at Strip Club...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/broke-roger-stone-is-speaking-for-money-at-a-strip-club</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s pal is destitute paying to defend against charges he lied about WikiLeaks. Now he’s being hounded by an antifa who doesn't want him and the Proud Boys in town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden camera found in women's bathroom aboard Navy ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/military/hidden-camera-found-women-s-bathroom-aboard-navy-ship-n996446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Navy spokesperson confirmed that NCIS is investigating the device found aboard the USS Arlington, currently in port in Greece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher charged with hiring hitman to kill student after molestation accusation...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksdk.com/article/news/investigations/teacher-charged-with-hiring-hitman-to-kill-student-after-molestation-accusation-pleads-not-guilty/63-c5eeab38-7825-41b7-b969-2907ab1d1f1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksdk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A St. Louis teacher with HIV is accused of taking a student out of class and molesting him. Three years later, police say the teacher tried to hire a hit man to kill the child and his family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts killing music or just wasting our time?</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/entertainment/article/Are-podcasts-killing-music-or-just-wasting-our-13775490.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm about to kick a hornet's nest - and if this were a podcast, you would now hear the crunch of a boot perforating a hive, followed by the intensifying hum of inconvenienced hornets. But, fortunately, this isn't a podcast, so my punt shall remain silent, and here it is: I'm against podcasts.  I think they're tedious and samey and sedative, and when I'm feeling especially cranky, I consider them an enemy of music. Most podcasts are conversations for people to eavesdrop on - recorded talk that precludes real-life talk about real life with zombie talk about podcasts. Also, I like music. With all of the world's unheard songs beckoning us with their endless mystery, why would anyone choose to waste their precious listening hours on a podcast?  Asking that question makes me feel very alone. In a March cover story, New York Magazine called the podcast "the most significant and exciting cultural innovation of the new century," offering lots of boffo numbers to back it up. First, there were those 340 million downloads of "Serial," the true-crime investigative blockbuster that made "podcast" a household word back in 2014. Then there was that $230 million transaction in February, when Spotify bought the podcast network Gimlet Media, foreshadowing juicier deals to come. And now there are well over a half-million podcasts currently in circulation, with new ones sprouting each day.  This is a serious new form, and it's generating serious money - so instead of treating podcasts as a convenient way to feel smarter, let's take them seriously. Let's measure their worth by truly listening.  Like it or not, they're invading a soundworld near you. The marquee names of podcasting - "Pod Save America," "The Joe Budden Podcast," "Terrible, Thanks for Asking" and many others - are currently appearing on actual marquees, bringing their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atheist prayers can be barred by House chaplain...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/hoh/house-chaplain-not-allow-atheist-prayers-federal-appeals-court-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House of Representatives chaplain scored a legal victory when a federal appeals court ruled he could bar an atheist from offering a secular prayer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulance that hit pothole may have saved patient's life...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/ambulance-hitting-pothole-may-have-saved-patient-s-life-doctors-say/27215034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The force of striking the pothole seemed to reset the man's rapid heartbeat to a normal rhythm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico warns of 'deep concern' over armed groups on U.S. border...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-mexico-border/mexico-warns-of-deep-concern-over-armed-groups-on-u-s-border-idUSKCN1RW0N6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico said on Saturday it had "deep concern" about armed groups that ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger attacks zoo keeper after 'error' brought two together...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kansas-zoo-idUSKCN1RW0J7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare Sumatran tiger attacked a worker at the Topeka Zoo in Kansas on Saturday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia orders urgent review after spate of dingo attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190421-australia-orders-urgent-review-after-spate-dingo-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia orders urgent review after spate of dingo attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke seen for miles as SPACEX Crew Dragon suffers anomaly at Cape Canaveral...</title>
      <link>https://www.floridatoday.com/story/tech/science/space/2019/04/20/smoke-seen-miles-spacex-crew-dragon-suffers-anomaly-cape-canaveral/3531086002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.floridatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SpaceX Crew Dragon capsule suffered an anomaly during a routine test fire at Cape Canaveral Air Force Station, the 45th Space Wing confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Umpire body slams fan who runs on baseball field...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8da832aede36492185ed2b53a6da4518</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — When a fan ran on the field during the Blue Jays-Athletics game, he got tossed by umpire Jeff Nelson. Quite literally, actually. Nelson put a swift end to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVT SHUTS SOCIAL MEDIA SITES...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2019-04-21/sri-lanka-government-declares-curfew-shuts-down-access-to-major-social-media-sites</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400+ INJURED...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8907637/sri-lanka-colombo-easter-tourists-seven-dead-bombs-death-toll-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITS are believed to be among 156 killed in an Easter Sunday terror attack on eight churches and five-star hotels in Sri Lanka today. Nearly 500 are thought to have been injured when blasts ripped…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 EXPLOSIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2019/apr/21/sri-lanka-explosions-dozens-killed-and-hundreds-injured-in-church-and-hotel-blasts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many more injured as explosions hit three hotels and three churches in and around Colombo as well as at Batticaloa in the east of the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates demur on pursuing Trump post-White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/news/nationworld/ct-2020-democratic-presidential-hopefuls-trump-investigations-20190420-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democratic contenders for president aren't saying whether they would re-open investigations into Trump if they were to oust him in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100+ DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/six-explosions-hit-sri-lanka-on-easter-sunday-11699701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 100 people have been killed and more than 400 injured following six simultaneous blasts across Sri Lanka, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASTER SUNDAY ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8907637/colombo-attacks-explosions-sri-lanka-hotels-churches-easter-sunday-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPLOSIONS ripped through three five-star hotels and three churches in Sri Lanka today, reportedly killing 52 and injuring 280 others. Tourists are feared to be among those hurt after blasts at the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI ARRESTS LEADER OF GROUP STOPPING ILLEGALS IN NEW MEXICO</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-militia/fbi-arrests-leader-of-armed-group-stopping-migrants-in-new-mexico-idUSKCN1RW0O5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI on Saturday said it had arrested Larry Hopkins, the leader of an armed g...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds hurt as blasts hit Sri Lanka churches, hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-6944119/Hundreds-hurt-blasts-hit-Sri-Lanka-churches-hotels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A string of blasts hit high-end hotels and churches in Sri Lanka on Sunday, injuring hundreds of people as worshippers attended Easter services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump brushes off Romney criticism, points to loss in 2012...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-brushes-off-romneys-criticism-232500380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. Mitt Romney says he's "sickened" by the dishonesty the Russia investigation found in the Trump White House, but the president fires back that Romney should have put the same energy into running for president in 2012 that the Utah Republican has tapped in criticizing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Buttigieg has been surprise of Dem field. Where does he go next? </title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Buttigieg-has-been-the-surprise-of-the-Democratic-13782776.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Bend, Indiana Mayor Pete Buttigieg is on a trajectory that few people would have imagined when he first formed his presidential exploratory committee. His poise and thoughtfulness have produced accolades on Twitter and cable TV that must make him blush at times. But his performance has made him the surprise factor in the Democratic nomination race.  What happens as the campaign moves ahead is the interesting question. History is an uncertain guide but still worth examining as Buttigieg tries to capitalize on the attention he has gotten. Is he a genuine breakthrough candidate, whose rise to prominence shatters both barriers and expectations? Or is he like some candidates of the past, who found a following within a segment of their party's electorate - or the attention of the media - but could not move beyond it?  Several past candidates come to mind in trying to assess the Buttigieg phenomenon. One is Barack Obama. Another is former New Jersey senator Bill Bradley. A third is former Arizona governor Bruce Babbitt. All had their moments. All were the subject of favorable and sometimes gushing media coverage. Only Obama went on to become both his party's nominee and president of the United States.  Obama is the candidate anyone like Buttigieg would like to become: a history-maker, an outsider who shook the system, a political meteor who flashed across the nation's screens but didn't burn out. Obama's 2004 keynote speech to the Democratic National Convention turned him into an overnight political celebrity. By the time he announced his candidacy for president more than two years later (and after election to the U.S. Senate), he was already destined to become the most serious challenger to Hillary Clinton for the 2008 Democratic nomination.  Buttigieg's rise has been far more condensed - and limited. He formed his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest unsolved mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/04/20/mueller-report-left-some-perplexing-trump-russia-questions-unanswered/3521806002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mueller's report was brimming with details about Donald Trump's White House but it left some of the probe's most perplexing questions unanswered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Armed civilians detaining migrants at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/04/19/united-constitutional-patroits-armed-group-detaining-migrants-texas-nm-border/3523457002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Constitutional Patriots is patrolling the border area, armed with weapons and searching for migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLEFACEBOOKAMAZONAPPLE employees donating to Warren -- even though she wants to break up big tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/04/19/elizabeth-warren-president-tech-campaign-donations-berine-sanders-kamala-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren is getting some surprising financial support from the employees of the big tech companies she wants to slice and dice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest anger burns in France, fueled by Notre Dame fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fd877004c7b942568fe8d95a1229e180</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French yellow vest protesters set fires Saturday along a march through Paris to drive home their message to a government they believe is ignoring the poor: that rebuilding the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real reasons why New Yorkers fleeing city...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/20/the-real-reasons-why-new-yorkers-are-fleeing-the-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;True story: My wife and I both are former residents of New York City, and on a recent business trip there she was taking a nostalgic walk through the Upper West Side on a lovely fall day, talking t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna 'MEDELLIN' Flops...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/04/19/pop-charts-madonnas-comeback-fizzles-as-medellin-with-columbian-singer-maluma-flops-on-itunes-gets-no-streaming-love-on-spotify</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna had a big build up for “Medellin” single this past Wednesday. She premiered it at noon with Zane Lowe on Apple’s Beats 1 Radio like it was the second coming. The song turn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal dispute drove end of probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.oakridger.com/zz/news/20190420/how-legal-dispute-drove-end-of-special-counsels-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oakridger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel ended his investigation last month, pointedly choosing not to reach a conclusion about whether the president had obstructed justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Venezuela in flames, ChinaRussia seeking claims in rubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-soured-relations-in-Latin-America-China-13782596.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Venezuela in flames, China and Russia are seeking claims in the rubble.  But the United States has been caught flat-footed, and the Pentagon is struggling to develop ways to blunt the countries' influence in Latin America since President Donald Trump has antagonized and distanced himself from nations in the Western Hemisphere.  Defense officials have sought non-force options to deter China and Russia in Venezuela, CNN reported this week, through a mix of humanitarian missions and more training in Latin America led by U.S. Southern Command, the Pentagon arm that oversees a sixth of the world's land mass.  Yet experts said those efforts and others are in opposition to pressure and rhetoric from the White House, which has made significant demands to Latin American nations to curb migration and drug trafficking without offering much in return - all while ceding influence and support that Russia, and particularly China, have been happy to take over.  "The Trump administration's policy has supercharged China's increased presence in the region," said Benjamin Gedan, former National Security Council official under the Obama administration and a senior adviser to the Latin American program at the Wilson Center, a Washington think tank. "It's entirely counterproductive."  For years, China and Russia have sought more influence in the Western Hemisphere, but are increasingly emboldened to bolster their economic and security positions in South America, Central America and the Caribbean.  China has pledged to invest $250 billion there and reach half a trillion dollars in trade, while Russia has taken root to antagonize the United States and demonstrate its might. Both have invested billions in Venezuela, though some experts have questioned Russia's true prominence and focus on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOTAL BULLSH*T'</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cf496df553ea4b15a232c5adaa1a2936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is lashing out at current and former aides who cooperated with special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation, insisting the deeply unflattering picture...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake news? Mueller isn't buying it...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/06c88719c3634e66a15adbbc658978b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump and his team love to deride unfavorable stories as "fake news," but it's clear from Robert Mueller's report that the special counsel isn't buying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't Afford Surgery? In China, Millions Chip In Half Penny to Cover You...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cant-afford-surgery-in-china-millions-chip-in-half-a-penny-to-cover-you-11555772400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a girl in Shanghai suffered brain damage after falling off a bunk bed, millions of strangers across China helped foot her surgical bills. Crowdfunded medical coverage, offered by fintech startups, could fill gaps in the country’s health insurance sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 1 In 5 Children Suffers From Mental Health Disorder...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/one-in-five-children-suffers-from-mental-health-disorder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in five children suffer from a mental health disorder -- with notable increases in depression and anxiety over the past 30 years -- yet less than one-third have had contact with a mental healthcare provider, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists create 'living' machines that eat, grow -- and evolve...</title>
      <link>https://thenextweb.com/robots/2019/04/19/cornell-scientists-create-living-machines-that-eat-grow-and-evolve/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenextweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The field of robotics is going through a renaissance thanks to advances in machine learning and sensor technology. Each generation of robot is engineered with greater mechanical complexity and smarter operating software than the last. But what if, instead of painstakingly designing and engineering a robot, you could just tear open a packet of primordial …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome for migrants cools in Mexican town weary of caravans...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190420145232-6ogk1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO (PIX, TV):Welcome for migrants cools in Mexican town weary of caravans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Church' to offer 'miracle cure' despite FDA warnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/apr/19/church-group-to-hold-washington-event-despite-fda-warnings-against-miracle-cure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group to hold ‘effective alternative healing’ event in Washington state in which they peddle a ‘sacrament’ known to be industrial cleaner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are worst 25 jobs in America?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/04/20/the-worst-jobs-in-america/39364439/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dislike your job? These 25 are considered the worst occupations in the U.S. for factors such as lack of job security, danger, low pay and stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot anchor in Russia sparks 'propaganda' controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/russian-news-anchor-robot-sparks-propaganda-controversy-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian news channel has reportedly started using a robot to anchor some of its newscast - but not everyone is impressed. ‘Alex,’ which was built by and based on Promobot co-founder Alexei Yuzhakov, has started reporting stories on Rossiya 24 about agriculture and nuclear technology among other topics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 campaign trail runs through churches in SCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e3cd6d9a08c94ca59a1a427e6517cfd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) — By now, most Democratic presidential candidates have polished their stump speeches. But when they're in South Carolina, they may need to add in a sermon. In a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 things media got wrong...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/19/top-10-things-the-media-got-wrong-about-collusion-and-obstruction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prestige press has some explaining to do — for subjecting the nation to a long, cruel ordeal named “collusion” and “obstruction.” Almost two years and millions of column inches later, special c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving? The Kids Are So Over It...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/driving-the-kids-are-so-over-it-11555732810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a challenge for Detroit, teens put off getting their licenses and buying cars. About a quarter of 16-year-olds had a driver’s license in 2017, a sharp decline from nearly half in 1983.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Tom Ford, Fragrant Vegan Vampire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/20/style/tom-ford-maureen-dowd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a designer known for sex and excess became a devoted family man — and C.F.D.A. chief!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Should White Man Be Face of Dem Party?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/should-a-white-man-be-the-face-of-the-democratic-party-in-2020/ar-BBW7KnG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious life of James McCord, Watergate burglar whose death went unnoticed for 2 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/obituaries/la-me-james-mccord-watergate-breakin-dead-20190419-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As shadowy in death and he was in life, James McCord died at 93 — two years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Power Gets Booster Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/presidential-power-gets-a-booster-shot-no-matter-mueller-s-view</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential Power Gets a Booster Shot, No Matter Mueller's View</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand marijuana festival has visitors on a high...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thailand-marijuana-festival-visitors-high-083609076.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Buddhist monk fishes out a vial of cannabis oil from his robe and puts a drop under his tongue -- one of many people flocking to a weed festival in northeastern Thailand, where excitement is building over a medical marijuana boom. Thailand became the first country in Southeast Asia to legalise marijuana</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Pressured...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pelosi-pressured-progressives-demand-impeachment-80000574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin pop has US grooving more and more in Spanish...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/latin-pop-us-grooving-more-more-spanish-010456904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just two years after the lilting mega-hit "Despacito" captivated the globe, Latin stars are cementing their place in the US mainstream, moving beyond scoring a one-off smash to headline festivals and permeate the charts. An unprecedented number of Spanish-language acts are performing at this</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
