<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside secretive Silicon Valley group funneling cash to Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/1/6/21046631/mind-the-gap-silicon-valley-democratic-donors-stanford</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a reason you haven’t heard of Mind the Gap: Its "raison d’être is stealth."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arlington National Cemetery on alert after 'hit list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10682307/security-ramps-up-across-major-us-cities-hotspots-strike-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US cities and tourist hotspots are on high alert after Iran threatened revenge for the US strike that killed General Qasem Soleimani. Chad Wolf, acting secretary of the US Department of Homeland Se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamaworld hates Bernie -- and has no idea how to stop him...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/obamaworld-hates-bernie-sandersand-has-no-idea-how-to-stop-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most striking response to an ascendant Sanders is the lack of one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bed Bugs Released In WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/01/05/police-investigating-after-bed-bugs-found-at-local-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Walmart in Pennsylvania is facing a bedbug infestation after someone released the parasitic insects in a men's changing room, state police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused cannibal eats testicles of his GRINDR date...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article238998043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi Consulate in Detroit to open for condolences in Soleimani death...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/01/06/condolences-qassem-soleimani-iraqi-consulate-southfield/2822725001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consulate said it'sÂ open to people who want to offer their sympathy on Tuesday and Wednesday from 2-5 p.m.Â at the consulate building in Southfield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dentist accused of setting girl's mouth on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/lawsuit-nevada-dentist-set-5-year-old-girls-mouth-on-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parents of a 5-year-old girl say a Las Vegas dentist set their daughter's mouth on fire as she underwent a routine dental procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors Fed Up With MCDONALD'S Blasting Bagpipe Sounds To Keep Homeless Away...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/03/bagpipes-blasting-broadway-mcdonalds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People living in Midtown Sacramento are getting an earful from a nearby McDonald's that's reportedly blasting bagpipe music nonstop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEINSTEIN INDICTED IN LA</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/01/06/harvey-weinstein-indicted-in-los-angeles-on-sex-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA prosecutors are planning a Monday news conference to announce the charges at 2 p.m. New York time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will he be subpoenaed?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bolton-prepared-testify-trump-impeachment-trial-subpoenaed/story?id=68097771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's former national security adviser, John Bolton, said Monday he was willing to testify in a Senate impeachment trial if subpoenaed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Tells Defense to 'Leave the Witnesses Alone' in Public Statements...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/harvey-weinstein-trial-judge-tells-defense-to-leave-the-witnesses-alone-in-public-statements/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's going to be hard enough to get a fair and impartial jury," Judge James Burke says in courtroom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural wonder Punta Ventana collapses... </title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/article238996843.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIAL STARTS WITH FIREWORKS</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-fireworks-rosanna-arquette-rose-mcgowan-1202822314/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even before a jury has been selected, the first day of Harvey Weinstein’s criminal trial for rape saw legal and cultural explosions going off inside and outside a Manhattan courtroom this morning. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE WOMAN WHO CAN SAVE HARVEY</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-lawyers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the months since his initial arrest, the disgraced producer’s case has seen multiple delays, shifting charges, and a tabloid-ready turnover of defense attorneys. In interviews, the team that will take him to trial explains their case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the moody, meowing robot cat waiter...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2020/01/06/ces-2020-meet-moody-meowing-robot-cat-waiter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A food-ferrying robot cat with attitude has been revealed at the CES 2020 tech expo in Las Vegas as a solution to understaffed restaurants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE AUTOPSY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-autopsy-a-closer-look-60-minutes-2020-01-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 Minutes has obtained the photographs from inside the convicted sex offender's cell and during his autopsy. They shed new light on —and possibly raise more questions about — his death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland grapples with assisted suicide for prisoners...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/switzerland-grapples-assisted-suicide-prisoners-154459161.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A request by a convict behind bars for life is testing Switzerland's support for assisted suicide, raising complex questions over whether ill prisoners can seek help to end their own lives. The unprecedented case has exposed a legal vacuum in the country which has long been at the forefront of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS will hire Mike McCarthy to replace Garrett...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/01/06/report-mike-mccarthy-to-become-cowboys-new-head-coach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to multiple reports, former Green Bay Packers coach Mike McCarthy has agreed to become the Dallas Cowboys' new coach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of the sex toys...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2020/01/05/ces-sex-toys-2020-tech-show-lora-dicarlo/2808571001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After taking away an award for a "pleasure tech" product Lora DiCarlo's Osé, CES organizers reversed course and invited sex tech companies to exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey back with walker...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/celebrities/2020/01/06/harvey-weinstein-sex-crime-trial-day-1-new-york-city/2777110001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein's sex-crimes trial, the first celebrity #MeToo case to open in a criminal court, began with outstanding motions before jury selection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The very real scenario of protracted, 'bizarro world' primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/06/democrats-post-super-tuesday-scramble-093743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dynamics have changed so much that states voting after Super Tuesday are suddenly taking on new prominence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France warns USA against digital tax retaliation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/476900-france-wants-us-against-digital-tax-retaliation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's top finance minister on Monday warned U.S. officials against implementing tariffs or other measures aimed at harming the French economy, a month after U.S. officials proposed steep duties on French exports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Judy will join Bloomberg on campaign trail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/476867-judge-judy-rules-in-favor-of-mike-bloomberg-will-join-him-on-campaign-trail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Americans trust her than any of the Supreme Court justices; her working class, racially diverse audience are the kind of voters Democrats need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraft's nightmare scenario...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/06/robert-krafts-nightmare-tom-brady-scenario-very-much-in-play/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Kraft has a suggestion for Tom Brady about his increasingly uncertain future in New England. “My hope and prayer is number one, he play for the Patriots. Or number two, he retires,&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/pr2020006006/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People who second-guess selves make worse decisions...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/People-who-second-guess-themselves-make-worse-14952495.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Trust your gut." It's a cliche we've all heard (and probably even expressed at one time or another), an exhortation to not overthink decisions in realms as diverse as business, sports, dating and politics.  But is it actually good advice?  In a new paper published in the Journal of Behavioral and Experimental Economics, a trio of British economists applied some brain power to the question of gut feelings and found that people who second-guess themselves make considerably worse decisions than those who stick with instinct. The researchers focused on prediction accuracy in sports betting but said their findings would apply in any realm where people have to make educated guesses about the future.  The economists gathered data on 150 users of a popular sports betting and prediction website. This was a representative sample of a subset of bettors vying to predict outcomes for all 380 soccer matches in the English Premiere League during the 2017/2018 season.  The final data set consisted of 57,000 individual predictions, each consisting of a user's best guess of the final score of a given match. Users were allowed to issue score predictions and to revise those score predictions up to the minute the match started.  Revisions were infrequent: 6 percent of the predictions changed - with the typical user revising 15 out of 380 predictions - and most of those occurred within minutes of the initial forecast. The authors speculate that in such cases, users typed in a prediction and looked up some relevant information on the match before quickly changing their mind. But there also were a number of instances involving large segments of time - days, even weeks - between prediction and revision; such betters waited nearly two days, on average, to switch gears.  The researchers specifically wanted to know whether the revised predictions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Million-strong' homage for general brings Tehran to standstill...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/million-strong-homage-general-brings-tehran-standstill-092004063.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downtown Tehran was brought to a standstill Monday as mourners flooded the Iranian capital to pay an emotional homage to Qasem Soleimani, the "heroic" general killed in a US strike. Soleimani, one of Iran's most popular public figures, was killed in a US drone strike on Friday near Baghdad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meant to cripple Iran's clout, strike unites its allies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/meant-cripple-irans-clout-us-strike-unites-allies-130629301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US killing of Iranian general Qasem Soleimani was meant to cripple Tehran's clout in the Middle East, but analysts see the allies of the Islamic Republic closing rank instead. As the head of the Iranian Revolutionary Guards' Quds Force, Soleimani oversaw Tehran's interventions in regional</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.7-mag quake rocks Puerto Rico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3281a57a610c3fabbc65817e59f79633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — A 5.8-magnitude quake hit Puerto Rico before dawn Monday, unleashing small landslides, causing power outages and severely cracking some homes. It was one of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Khamenei shows general's death is personal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14792cc1d7f73ffec8f8c425b73b44fb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — In a rare display of emotion from the typically reserved and measured supreme leader of Iran, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei cried openly Monday at the funeral of slain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 'artificial human'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/samsung-neon-heres-when-well-get-details-on-the-mysterious-ai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "artificial human" company has a booth at Sunday's CES Unveiled, but it isn't actually showing its technology. And it won't be a part of Samsung's keynote Monday, either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: House to vote on resolution limiting Trump actions against Iran...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/476881-pelosi-house-to-vote-on-resolution-limiting-trumps-actions-against-iran</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House will vote on a resolution limiting President Trump’s military actions toward Iran following his decision to launch a drone strike that killed a top Iranian commander, Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 200 Arrested For Deliberately Starting Blazes...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/01/06/nearly-200-people-arrested-across-australia-for-deliberately-starting-bushfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet media &amp; celebrities continue to blame</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aliens exist and could already be on earth, first British astronaut says...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/aliens-exist-and-could-already-be-on-earth-first-british-astronaut-says-11901994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Helen Sharman says "there's no two ways" that aliens exist and that it's possible "we simply can't see them".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil $70...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oil-set-bumpy-week-u-170315364.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Oil extended its dramatic surge, surpassing $70 a barrel in London for the first time since September, as Middle East tensions flared after the U.S. assassinated one of Iran’s most powerful generals.Futures jumped by another 1.4% on Monday as the U.S. State Department warned of a “heightened</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireballs 'like hurricane'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200106075221-fw5na</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTRALIA- BUSHFIRES/COBARGO (TV):Fireballs 'like a hurricane' bring death and devastation in Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coincidence that fake news law applied to politicians, Singapore minister says...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200106074420-ku0rh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE-FAKE NEWS/:Coincidence that fake news law applied to politicians, Singapore minister says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland to introduce four-day working week and six-hour days...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10679311/finland-introduce-four-day-working-week-six-hour-days-prime-minister-sanna-marin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINLAND is introducing a FOUR-DAY working week and SIX-HOUR days under a massive reform by the world’s youngest prime minister, Sanna Marin. The 34-year-old’s reform will let workers spend mo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor 'Soldier' Out for Justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/harvey-weinstein-trial-meet-prosecutor-soldier-justice-1266403</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan Assistant District Attorney Joan  Illuzzi-Orbon may not yet be a household name, but she’s a deft lawyer with a record of high-profile convictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIC TRIAL KICKS OFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/harvey-weinstein-trial-why-a-culture-secrecy-extends-courtroom-1266394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite (or because of) intense media coverage, Judge  James  Burke is keeping many of the high profile criminal proceeding’s most pressing questions — including witness names and allegations — on lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'KILL ME'</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ricky-gervais-attacks-woke-hollywood-and-shreds-apple-disney-and-amazon-in-savage-golden-globes-monologue-2020-01-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It didn’t take long for the notorious pot-stirrer and five-time host to draw gasps at the 77th annual Golden Globes on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GET DRUNK, TAKE YOUR DRUGS'</title>
      <link>https://www.eonline.com/ap/news/1108373/ricky-gervais-truly-didn-t-care-as-he-hosted-the-2020-golden-globes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aside from a scathing monologue, Ricky Gervais mostly stayed in the sidelines as he hosted the 2020 Golden Globes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Gets Wiped Out...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/77-golden-globe-awards-show-review-ricky-gervais-1917-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-succession-fleabag-1202821358/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the eve of the start of Harvey Weinstein’s rape trial, there were literally no bombshells tonight on the Golden Globes. Bombshell star Charlize Theron lost out on a Best Actress – Dr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GET DRUNK, TAKE YOUR DRUGS'</title>
      <link>https://drudgereport.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'KNOW NOTHING OF REAL WORLD'</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ricky-gervais-golden-globes-monologue-mocks-hollywoods-jeffrey-epstein-ties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back for the fifth time, Ricky Gervais opened the 2020 Golden Globes by roasting the hell out of the Hollywood crowd in attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICKY TELLS HOLLYWOOD 'F OFF'</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/ricky-gervais-golden-globes-monologue-gets-political-1266308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During his monologue, the 'Office' creator also took shots at Felicity Huffman and Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBES 2020... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9146ceebd39493cc6c0fe3a8ff587d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on on the 77th annual Golden Globe Awards honoring achievements in television and film and being presented Sunday at the Beverly Hilton in Beverly Hills,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubles down on striking cultural sites...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8d3385ab6c29c3da3ab9b081bae53884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump insisted Sunday that Iranian cultural sites were fair game for the U.S. military, dismissing concerns within his own administration that doing so would...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOWA POLL:  Sanders, Biden, Buttigieg Tied...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/iowa-poll-shows-sanders-biden-buttigieg-tied-campaign-update/ar-BBYDlYE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL PRICE SPIKES</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-continue-to-rise-us-stock-futures-retreat-as-mideast-tensions-remain-high-2020-01-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices rose more than 1% in late Sunday trading, continuing their surge in the wake of last week’s killing of Iranian Gen. Qassem Soleimani in a U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2020-golden-globes-winners-full-list-updating-live-1265577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime's 'The Loudest Voice' and Hulu's 'Ramy' picked up early wins on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens sanctions ON IRAQ 'like they've never seen before'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/06/trump-threatens-to-slap-sanctions-on-iraq-like-theyve-never-seen-before.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His remarks come after the Iraqi parliament passed a resolution calling for the government to expel foreign troops from the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS Officially Moving On From Garrett...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/cowboys-part-ways-coach-garrett-missing-nfl-playoffs-002340374--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dallas Cowboys made it official Sunday, confirming they are parting ways with head coach Jason Garrett a week after their NFL season ended short of the playoffs. Team owner Jerry Jones confirmed the widely expected news in an official statement. &amp;quot;We are extremely grateful to Jason Garrett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Cyber Attack on Billionaire Adelson Provides Lesson...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iran-cyber-attack-billionaire-adelson-170413240.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the U.S. awaits possible retribution over a recent airstrike that killed a top general, there’s at least one American businessman who can attest, in detail, to what happened after he provoked Iran.In October 2013, Sheldon Adelson, the casino magnate and prominent supporter of conservative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Climbs to Highest Level Since 2013...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-climbs-highest-level-since-230920306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Gold surged to the highest level in more than six years as rising tensions in the Middle East stoked demand for haven assets. Palladium also extended gains to an all-time high.Iran’s government said it would no longer abide by any limits on its enrichment of uranium following the killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE QUESTIONS RAISED IN CONTROVERSIAL DEATH OF JEFFREY EPSTEIN; GUARD WHO FOUND HIM HAS YET TO BE INTERVIEWED BY INVESTIGATORS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/did-jeffrey-epstein-kill-himself-60-minutes-investigates-2020-01-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein was a convicted sex offender and a wealthy financier with powerful friends. 60 Minutes examines the circumstances surrounding his death in a Manhattan federal jail cell. Warning: This report contains graphic images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Bloomberg pops to third place in Dem race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/476689-bloomberg-rises-to-third-place-alongside-warren-in-national-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg saw a 6-point bump in the latest Hill-HarrisX survey of the Democratic presidential primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More rockets hit near US embassy in Baghdad...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/least-two-rockets-hit-near-us-embassy-baghdad-000726339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baghdad (AFP) - Two rockets hit near the US embassy in Iraq's capital Sunday, witnesses told AFP, hours after the ambassador was summoned over a US strike that killed top Iraqi and Iranian commanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv a target...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-ex-guards-chief-vows-turn-tel-aviv-212430978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former head of Iran's Revolutionary Guards threatened on Sunday to turn the Israeli cities of Haifa and Tel Aviv "to dust" if the US attacks targets in Iran. "If America takes any measures after our military response, we will turn Tel Aviv and Haifa to dust," Mohsen Rezai,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Activates Terrorism Alert Network... </title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/homeland-security-issues-terrorism-alert-after-soleimani-strike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security issued a new terrorism alert Saturday evening following the assassination this week of top Iranian military leader Qassem Soleimani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS Officially Moving On From Garrett...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/01/05/jason-garrett-no-longer-cowboys-head-coach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a week of will they or won't they, the Dallas Cowboys have made their final decision and are officially moving on from head coach Jason Garrett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES On High Alert...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/golden-globes-security-iran-tensions-soleimani-death-donald-trump-nbc-1202820982/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of Donald Trump’s drone strike on Iran’s top general Qasem Soleimani just days ago, safety concerns and security are high at today’s Golden Globes, very high. “We are …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On short notice, fast-response force flies to Mideast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9b7169d2cf472b8f643ecd69b47730a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT BRAGG, N.C. (AP) — Being a U.S. soldier in a fast-response force sometimes means being sent halfway across the world within a day, leaving no time to say goodbye to those staying behind....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
