<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Merkel's 'crown princess' seeks to chart own path...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190115-merkels-crown-princess-seeks-chart-own-path</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel's 'crown princess' seeks to chart own path</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian temple trailblazer beaten by mother-in-law...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190115-indian-temple-trailblazer-beaten-mother-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian temple trailblazer beaten by mother-in-law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Asks State Firms to Avoid Travel to America and Its Allies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/china-said-to-ask-state-firms-to-avoid-travel-to-u-s-allies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China also advised extra precautions to protect their devices in the U.S. and its allies if there arises a need to travel.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump's side, Border Patrol union leader in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/eb348270991d4d238e6aa83f18930263</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Brandon Judd, president of the union that represents thousands of border patrol agents, has flipped the axiom that there are no winners in a government shutdown. His proximity to President Donald Trump has elevated the union leader's profile while burnishing the image of the U.S. Border Patrol, a backwater in prior administrations when compared to other federal law enforcement agencies like the FBI and Secret Service. At the same time, Judd, president of the National Border Patrol Council, has helped to validate Trump's fiery immigration rhetoric and affirm his conviction that a wall at the southern border is urgently needed to stop what they've described as a humanitarian crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carol Channing, iconic Broadway star of 'HELLO, DOLLY!', dies at 97...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/51d9bd38bc0b48e598f2372983a261e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Carol Channing, the lanky, ebullient musical comedy star who delighted American audiences over almost 5,000 performances as the scheming Dolly Levi in "Hello, Dolly" on Broadway and beyond, has died. She was 97. Publicist B. Harlan Boll said Channing died of natural causes at 12:31 a.m. Tuesday in Rancho Mirage, California. Boll says she had twice suffered strokes in the last year. Besides "Hello, Dolly," Channing starred in other Broadway shows, but none with equal magnetism. She often appeared on television and in nightclubs, for a time partnering with George Burns in Las Vegas and a national tour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's domestic spy agency to investigate far-right AfD: newspaper...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190115115341-xmig0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-POLITICS/AFD (URGENT):Germany's domestic spy agency to investigate far-right AfD -newspaper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Hondurans set off toward USA in new caravan...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190115044000-9lp3o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last October, another migrants caravan left Honduras made up of men, women and children, mostly claiming that they were fleeing entrenched poverty and gangland violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germinates first lunar seed?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jan/15/china-germinates-first-seed-on-moon-cotton-shoot-change-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small cotton shoot is growing onboard Chang’e 4 lunar lander, scientists confirm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers forced to CRAWL on street after 'failing to hit annual targets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6593631/Staff-forced-CRAWL-street-failing-hit-annual-targets.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The staff, all female, were on their hands and knees as they made their way through the busy traffic of Tengzhou, eastern China, yesterday afternoon. Police soon arrived and stopped the punishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can U.S. Make Employees Work Without Pay? Judge Could Force Hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/can-u-s-make-staff-work-without-pay-judge-could-force-its-hand#gs.UiI7JWfi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can U.S. Make Staff Work Without Pay? Judge Could Force Its Hand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 2nd-deadliest Ebola outbreak reaches 600 confirmed cases...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/worlds-2nd-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-reaches-600-confirmed/story?id=60383138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second-largest, second-deadliest Ebola outbreak in history has reached 600 confirmed cases in five months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran fails to launch satellite into orbit after ignoring warnings from US...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/iran-satellite-launch-ballistic-missile-nuclear-warheads-un-payam-doosti-a8728246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACKLASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/newsbeat-46874617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video about toxic masculinity, bullying and men's behaviour sparks outrage online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President rebuffed request for Mueller interview in recent weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/politics/trump-interview-mueller-request/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's legal team rebuffed special counsel Robert Mueller's request in recent weeks for an in-person session with Trump to ask follow-up questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Star With Worst Shooting Season in NBA History...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/russell-westbrook-worst-nba-shooter-11547488655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russell Westbrook is on pace for the lowest 3-point shooting percentage ever among high-volume shooters. He keeps shooting anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT D-DAY!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8194676/theresa-may-second-vote-brexit-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May will try to force a second vote on her Brexit deal despite facing a catastrophic defeat on it, allies have revealed. It has emerged that the PM has been given fresh hope of eventual suc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD Debuts Most-Powerful MUSTANG Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/jan/14/the-mature-stoner-why-are-so-many-seniors-smoking-weed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older people are the fastest-growing group of cannabis users, as stigma fades and some seek an alternative to prescription drugs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says 'completely mischaracterized'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/01/rep-steve-king-releases-statement-debunks-new-york-times-report-and-outrageous-accusations-of-racism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking just one joint enough to change brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/legal-pot/even-little-marijuana-may-change-teen-brain-study-finds-n958536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say even one or two joints cause changes in areas of the brain involved in emotion-related processing, learning and forming memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opposition gambling all on young, untested activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Venezuela-s-opposition-is-gambling-it-all-on-a-13532833.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a week ago, few outside of Venezuela knew of Juan Guaidó. But the 35-year-old industrial engineer has suddenly emerged as a cause celebre, heralded by global leaders for his challenge to the near-total power of President Nicolás Maduro. Following May elections internationally derided as a fraudulent power grab, Maduro was sworn in for a new six-year term Thursday. One day later, Guaidó - the new head of the opposition-controlled National Assembly - took a step Venezuelan critics had long considered too dangerous:Invoking articles in the constitution that allow the head of the assembly to assume national leadership if a "usurper" takes office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVT PARALYZED</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-and-lawmakers-paralyzed-over-shutdown-as-13533754.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's dismissals of his own party's calls for compromise and his seeming indifference to shuttered federal agencies left the snowbound capital paralyzed Monday, with lawmakers in both parties scrambling to jump-start talks but increasingly uncertain about Trump's interest in ending the longest government shutdown in history. "I did reject it," Trump told reporters, when asked about a suggestion by Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., to temporarily reopen the government while continuing negotiations over money for a wall along the U.S.-Mexico border. "I'm not interested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic blast to hit KC for AFC championship game...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/nfl/story/arctic-blast-due-to-hit-kc-for-afc-championship-game-011419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Break out the parkas for Sunday night's AFC title game at Arrowhead Stadium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: Feds Can't Force To Unlock Phone With Finger, Face...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2019/01/14/feds-cant-force-you-to-unlock-your-iphone-with-finger-or-face-judge-rules/#4c236ac842b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops can't just hold an iPhone up to a suspect's face to search it, judge rules. It could be a landmark decision in modern privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Striking Teachers March in L.A...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/education/2019/01/14/photos-thousands-of-l-a-teachers-march-on-strike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educators and parents wearing ponchos and rain boots and carrying umbrellas gathered downtown to march from City Hall to district headquarters in the pouring rain, pressing for higher pay and smaller class sizes that the district says could bankrupt the school system with 640,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems zero in on Trump and Russia...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/425289-dems-zero-in-on-trump-and-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats vowed to introduce tough oversight of President Trump if they won back the House majority, and they are signaling a new aggressiveness to meet their promises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg's 'WEST SIDE STORY' Finds Its Cast... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/steven-spielberg-west-side-story-cast-ariana-debose-david-alvarez-josh-andres-rivera-rachel-zegler-1202535002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: After auditioning more than 30K people from around the world, Steven Spielberg’s West Side Story has found its Maria in fresh face 17-year old New Jersey High School student Rachel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Company known for deep cost-cutting offers to buy GANNETT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cce61bd08b664e39a7f39fdd6cb819b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A hedge fund-backed bid to buy Gannett Co., the publisher of USA Today and several other major dailies, is renewing fears of consolidation and job losses — as well as a decline in the quantity and quality of news coverage — in the already battered newspaper industry. MNG Enterprises, better known as Digital First Media, offered $1.36 billion on Monday for Gannett, saying in a letter that it can run the company more profitably via tight cost controls and consolidation of operations such as printing and administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIANT FOOD to place robotic assistants inside all 172 stores...</title>
      <link>http://www.wfmz.com/news/berks/giant-food-stores-to-use-in-store-robots-at-all-locations/975253313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GIANT food stores will begin introducing a new robotic assistant to all of its 172 stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez freaking out media. And it's working for her...</title>
      <link>http://www.heraldnews.com/opinion/20190114/opinion-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-is-freaking-out-media-and-its-working-for-her</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She's been on the job for less than two weeks and already has generated more national press coverage than some members of Congress get in their whole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces worst govt defeat in 95 years...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190114181416-s90vt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/VOTE (EXPLAINER, PIX, TV):EXPLAINER-What happens if PM May loses vote on her Brexit deal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christianity in Communist China: Churches close, pastors jailed, scripture rewritten...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/13/china-christians-religious-persecution-translation-bible</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Communist party is intensifying religious persecution as Christianity’s popularity grows. A new state translation of the Bible will establish a ‘correct understanding’ of the text</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Loses Committee Seats Over 'White Supremacy' Remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-republican-leaders-move-to-strip-rep-steve-king-of-his-committee-assignments-over-comments-about-white-nationalism/ar-BBSfGt2?li=AAa0dzB&amp;page=2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year-long domestic deployment of forces... </title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-military/2019/01/15/dod-extends-border-deployment-to-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Active duty troops were first sent to the border in October 2018 to secure it from an arriving caravan of migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Album tops Billboard chart --  after selling just 823 copies!</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/ny-rapper-tops-charts-less-1-000-sales-002417838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry tracker Billboard, whose chart ranks the most popular albums of the week in the United States, said Monday that A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie's album "Hoodie SZN" climbed to the top with the equivalent of 58,000 sales for the week ending January 10. The figures lay bare the ever-widening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death penalty for Canadian escalates China-Canada tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ad12b3e9cebe4c25ae1b4143bc74e347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — A Chinese court sentenced a Canadian man to death in a sudden retrial of a drug smuggling case and Beijing said that it has denied a Canadian diplomatic immunity, ratcheting up tensions since Canada's arrest of a top Chinese technology executive last month. A Chinese court in northeastern Liaoning province announced Monday that it had sentenced Robert Lloyd Schellenberg to death, reversing an earlier 2016 ruling that sentenced him to 15 years in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUTDOWN TURNS NIGHTMARE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a50e00cb683b4b9697c1c957bae39cd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The number of airport security screeners failing to show up for work around the country is soaring as the partial government shutdown goes into its fourth week. No-shows among screeners jumped Sunday and again Monday, when the Transportation Security Administration reported a national absence rate of 7.6 percent compared with 3.2 percent on a comparable day a year ago. Monday marked the first business day after screeners did not receive a paycheck for the first time since the shutdown began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon extends mission to Mexico border...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190115013923-guxn7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/PENTAGON (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Pentagon extends mission to Mexico border through September</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans strip congressman's committee assignments after 'white nationalism' comments...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/mccarthy-strips-steve-king-of-committee-assignments-after-white-supremacist-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., and House Republicans voted Monday night to strip Rep. Steve King, R-Iowa, of all of committee assignments days after he openly wondered when "white supremacist" and "white nationalism" became offensive terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems mull subpoenas for Putin meet interpreters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/politics/trump-secrecy-russia-interpreter/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers are discussing how to have the interpreter in President Donald Trump's meetings with Russian President Vladimir Putin appear before them to learn what transpired amid reports the President has worked to keep the content of his huddles with Putin a secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River of chocolate clogs highway after tanker spills...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/arizona-news/tanker-truck-carrying-40k-gallons-of-chocolate-spills-onto-i-40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk about a sweet cleanup! The Arizona Department of Public Safety says a tanker truck carrying 3,500 gallons of liquid chocolate has spilled onto the westbound lanes of Interstate 40, east of Flagstaff at milepost 211.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With staff furloughed, Trump feeds CLEMSON fast food feast...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/14/clemson-tigers-white-house-donald-trump-fast-food-buffet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's burger time for the national champs!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coast Guard sees surge in West Coast migrant intercepts...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/2019/01/14/coast-guard-working-without-pay-government-shutdown-sees-surge-west-coast-migrant-intercepts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The service is part of the U.S. military, but not paid because they are part of the Department of Homeland Security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT GREAT AGAIN:  China Trade Surplus With USA Hits Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-annual-trade-surplus-with-u-s-hits-record-despite-trumps-tariff-offensive-11547439977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s trade surplus with the U.S. hit a fresh record last year, as robust American demand for Chinese goods undercut the Trump administration’s tariff offensive aimed at narrowing the countries’ lopsided trade gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Angry EAGLES fan attacks girlfriend, puts dog in microwave...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/news/breaking/mc-pol-angry-eagles-fan-attacks-girlfriend-puts-dog-in-microwave-20190114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upset about the Eagles playoff loss on Sunday, a 31-year-old woman attacked her girlfriend inside their room at the Best Western hotel in Hanover Township, Northampton County and placed her dog inside a microwave, according to court records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Replacing 30 mins of sitting with activity lengthens life...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/health/sitting-30-minutes-exercise-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Replacing 30 minutes of sedentary time with 30 minutes of physical activity at a light intensity was associated with a 17% lower risk of early death in a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL LOWEST IN YEAR</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_jan14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bolsonaro is Hitler!' Nicolas exclaims...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-brazil/bolsonaro-is-hitler-venezuelas-maduro-exclaims-amid-brazil-spat-idUSKCN1P82FJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro on Monday called Brazilian President Jair Bo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House mulls wooing moderate Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/14/trump-on-declaring-national-emergency-im-not-looking-to-do-that-1098886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unlikely, however, that members in either party would split with leadership as the fight for Trump's border wall stretches into its 24th day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal charity accused of secretly killing dogs to increase flow of donations...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/care-south-korea-dog-meat-charity-killing-animals-coexistence-animal-rights-on-earth-park-soyeon-a8726821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans now more likely to die from opioids than car accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/americans-more-likely-to-die-from-accidental-opioid-overdose-than-in-a-car-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the National Safety Council sheds light on the most common causes of accidental death in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA Proposes More Commercial Drone Operations at Night, Over People...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/faa-proposes-more-commercial-drone-operations-at-night-and-over-people-11547495257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal air-safety regulators for the first time proposed allowing small drones to routinely fly over crowds of people and at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Fund Known for 'Milking' Newspapers Takes Aim at GANNETT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-14/hedge-fund-known-for-milking-newspapers-takes-aim-at-gannett</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver Strips Down to Bra as Stolen Car Pursuit Comes to Bizarre End in LA...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/01/14/authorities-in-pursuit-of-vehicle-in-southeast-l-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman stripped down to her bra and undershorts before being taken into custody in South Los Angeles after an hourlong chase came to a bizarre end on a rainy Monday morning. Authorities were chasing the suspected stolen silver Kia sedan, which was carjacked at gunpoint on Saturday, according to Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department Deputy Charles Moore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2019/01/14/shutdown-tsa-shortages-airport-delays/2569551002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travel troubles from the government shutdown continue to mount, with some airports closing select security checkpoints to handle staffing shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Checkpoints Close at Dulles...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/TSA-Closes-Some-Security-Checkpoints-at-Dulles-Amid-Staff-Absences-504319511.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam-powered spaceship could cruise cosmos indefinitely...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/steam-powered-spaceship-could-cruise-cosmos-indefinitely-without-running-out-ncna958486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say the microwave-sized craft would suck its watery fuel right out of the asteroids, planets and moons it's exploring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next American Car Recession Already Started...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-13/the-next-american-car-recession-has-already-started</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish police arrest 182 people at illegal cockfight...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190114-spanish-police-arrest-182-people-illegal-cockfight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spanish police arrest 182 people at illegal cockfight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INSTAGRAM Effect' Forces Travel Destinations To Limit Tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90291704/these-5-travel-destinations-are-fighting-back-against-the-instagram-effect-on-tourism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers are all headed to the same places in pursuit of selfies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon shipping jumbo cell to Gitmo for al-Qaeda trial from hospital bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/sns-tns-bc-guantanamo-cell-20190114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUANTANAMO BAY NAVY BASE, Cuba The Pentagon is shipping a handicapped-accessible cell big enough to accommodate a hospital bed and wheelchair that, in a first,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacist flyers posted outside Myrtle Beach newspaper, TV station...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/south-carolina/article224502495.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriot Front, known as a white supremacist organization, posted flyers outside The Sun News newspaper in Myrtle Beach. The group formed out of the Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville, VA in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: TV News Reporter Attacked While Broadcasting Live...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/01/13/reporter-attacked-live-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone attacked the reporter while she was live on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror as spiders 'rain' from sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8187625/spiders-rain-sky-brazil-web/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILLING footage has emerged appearing to show hundreds of spiders raining down from the sky in Brazil. A young boy who filmed the incredible moment said it left him “stunned and scared” as the ara…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA secretly takes nuke material out of Africa -- with Beijing's help...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/news/pentagon-congress/2019/01/14/how-the-us-and-china-collaborated-to-get-nuclear-material-out-of-nigeria-and-away-from-terrorist-groups/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense News reveals how an international team was given 24 hours to extract radioactive material from an African country in the throws of battling Boko Haram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect Shot, 2 Women Freed After Hostage Situation At UPS...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/01/14/active-shooter-nj-ups-facility-gloucester-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At around 8:30 a.m., the SWAT team was activated to head to the UPS warehouse on the 200 block of Birch Creek Road in Logan Township.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milan sends signal with feminine touch on menswear...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/62ed11fe32484a0b9d7f1b43ae2828d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Milan menswear designers are sending clear signals for next fall and winter: Feminine touches are not only acceptable, they are necessary. During three days of Milan Fashion Week previews focused on menswear, collections featured shiny and sheer textiles, sequined garments, lace and scoop necks. The trend to feminize the male wardrobe could be interpreted as encouragement for getting in touch with a female side or as an explicit sign of solidarity after a year when the sexual harassment and assault of women became a global theme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Sheriffs Flee ICE Program as Small Counties Join Trump's Deportation Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/01/14/urban-sheriffs-flee-ice-program-as-small-counties-join-trumps-deportation-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as dozens of smaller counties join President Trump’s call for sheriffs to help with deportations at local jails, larger urban counties have been dropping out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report 'almost certain to be anti-climactic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/abcs-jon-karl-people-close-to-mueller-say-his-report-certain-to-be-anti-climactic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'ROE V. WADE' Film Features Jon Voight as Supreme Court Justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/roe-v-wade-film-features-jon-voight-as-a-supreme-court-justice-1175537</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film was shot in secret and some teaser video will be shown at a pro-life rally in Washington this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Rand Paul going to Canada for surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/14/rand-paul-neighbor-attack-senator-have-surgery-canada/2568200002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After being attacked by his neighbor in 2017, Kentucky Sen. Rand Paul will have hernia surgery in Canada</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD:  Probe Tactic Pioneered By J. Edgar Hoover...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/14/the-fbis-investigation-of-trump-as-a-national-security-threat-is-itself-a-serious-danger-but-j-edgar-hoover-pioneered-the-tactic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did the FBI investigate Trump due to disagreements with his policy views on Russia? If so, it would not be the first time the bureau abused its powers this way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Pelosi Locked in Their First Battle. Neither Can Afford to Lose...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/magazine/europe/?_=1475028507366page%2F6page%2F6page%2F13page%2F9page%2F11page%2F14page%2F5page%2F7page%2F7page%2F8page%2F3page%2F14page%2F6page%2F4page%2F7page%2F2page%2F3page%2F11page%2F3page%2F2page%2F7page%2F7page%2F2%5C%27+%2F%2A+or+%2A%2FaND+3%3D3+%2B+1+--+oR+3%3D2+%2B+1page%2F11page%2F9page%2F21page%2F21page%2F17page/3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Staffing Shortages Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tsa-staffing-shortages-spread-amid-government-shutdown-11547471790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houston’s George Bush Intercontinental Airport is the latest U.S. airport to confront staffing shortfalls amid the partial government shutdown, closing one of its security checkpoints due to a lack of TSA officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 HOURS: May could be out if she loses Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8191144/gareth-johnson-quit-brexit-theresa-may-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANOTHER member of Theresa May’s government has quit today, 24 hours ahead of the crunch vote on her deal. Assistant Tory whip Gareth Johnson threw in the towel this afternoon as the PM battle…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Want to Run on Issues. But Does Beating Trump Matter Most?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/14/us/politics/democratic-candidates-issues-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major question in the coming Democratic primary is which candidate will be the best antidote to Trump and Trumpism. Liberals may want to apply policy litmus tests. Moderates may just want a winner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landing on dark side of moon was faked?</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/chinese-landing-dark-side-moon-13855050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott C. Waring believes he’s spotted a ‘stage prop line’ in a photo of the Jade Rabbit rover</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court filing in Manafort case shows Mueller's intense focus on Russia contacts... </title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-paul-manafort-russian-contacts-20190113-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New revelations about Paul Manafort's interactions with a Russian associate while he was leading President Donald Trump's campaign provide a window into how</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD Debuts Most-Powerful MUSTANG Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/ford-debuts-most-powerful-mustang-ever-2020-ford-shelby-gt500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-performance Mustang variant comes with a supercharged 5.2-liter V8 and more than 700 horsepower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta airport: More than 1 hour of waiting at checkpoints...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a50e00cb683b4b9697c1c957bae39cd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — It was taking more than an hour for passengers to get through domestic checkpoints at the world's busiest airport in Atlanta on Monday, the first business day after security screeners missed paychecks for the first time due to partial government shutdown. No-shows among screeners across the nation soared Monday morning, with a national rate of 7.6 unscheduled absences Monday morning, a Transportation Security Administration spokesman said. That compares to 3.2 percent for this time one year ago, TSA spokesman Thomas Kelly said in a statement to The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosenstein working on plan to make it easier for DOJ to spy on journalists...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/425189-rosenstein-doj-exploring-ways-to-more-easily-spy-on-journalists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The department may revise the rules for obtaining journalists' records in part because of a massive increase in criminal leak investigations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Teachers Go On Strike For First Time In 30 Years... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/14/first-day-strike-austin-beutner-exclusive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Classes at all LAUSD schools begin at 8 a.m. as usual, but picketing is scheduled to start at 7:30 a.m. State preschool sites, however, will be closed and early education centers will be open only for students with special needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER warns conservative author his book violates Pakistan law...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/twitter-warns-conservative-author-his-book-violates-pakistan-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter is warning it may censor content by Western users that the social giant deems a violation of Pakistan law. Russian-born Canadian columnist Jamie Glazov explained the situation on The Glazov Gang, an online talk show. ﻿ “Ladies and gentlemen, a very interesting world we’re entering now. Twitter has recently warned me that a post …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLETTE Ad Challenges Men to Shave Their Toxic Masculinity...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/p-g-challenges-men-to-shave-their-toxic-masculinity-in-gillette-ad-11547467200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gillette addresses ‘toxic masculinity’ in a new digital ad campaign aimed at men, the latest message from an advertiser attempting to change societal norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of Porn's Julian Assange...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-rise-and-fall-of-porns-julian-assange</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donny Long ran Porn Wikileaks, which terrorized adult actors and outed ‘crossover’ performers. Then he fled the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPERHUMAN babies?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/752949/stephen-hawking-designer-baby-crispr-he-jiankui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Debated Whether Trump Was Following Putin 'Directions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/politics/trump-fbi-debate-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the chaotic aftermath at the FBI following Director James Comey's firing, a half-dozen senior FBI officials huddled to set in motion the momentous move to open an investigation into President Donald Trump that included trying to understand why he was acting in ways that seemed to benefit Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish Mayor Dies After Stabbed In Heart On Stage At Charity Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fc1f50c3b8964efabf012002f712bfa6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — The popular liberal mayor of the Polish port city of Gdansk died on Monday after he was stabbed during a charity event the evening before by an ex-convict who stormed onstage and said it was revenge against a political party the politician once belonged to. Pawel Adamowicz, 53, died as a result of wounds to the heart and abdomen in spite of efforts to save him that involved a five-hour operation and blood transfusions, Health Minister Lukasz Szumowski said. "The fight for his life has been lost," Szumowski said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5 most likely impeachment scenarios...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/817163/5-most-likely-trump-impeachment-scenarios</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats' favorite subject, ranked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Father of DNA' Stripped of Honors Over Race Comments...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/father-of-dna-james-watson-stripped-of-accolades-in-ugly-racism-row</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acclaimed Nobel Prize-winning scientist James Watson will be forever remembered as one of the 'fathers of DNA'. But also as something much worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris Opera drops star dancer after homophobic rant...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190114-paris-opera-drops-star-dancer-after-homophobic-rant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris Opera drops star dancer after homophobic rant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to Build Conscious Robots Using Insect Brains?</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/darpa-wants-conscious-robots-insect-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Even small insects have subjective experiences, the first step towards a concept of 'consciousness.'"</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
