<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>INVESTORS TAKING ON HUGE RISKS...</title>
      <link>https://news.google.com/articles/CBMiP2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZ0LmNvbS9jb250ZW50LzMyZTAwMGNmLWM5NWEtNDk0MC04OTg1LWY2N2NhNjE3MGFlONIBP2h0dHBzOi8vYW1wLmZ0LmNvbS9jb250ZW50LzMyZTAwMGNmLWM5NWEtNDk0MC04OTg1LWY2N2NhNjE3MGFlOA?hl=en-US&amp;gl=US&amp;ceid=US%3Aen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comprehensive up-to-date news coverage, aggregated from sources all over the world by Google News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Derby Winner Medina Spirit Dies During Workout...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/12/06/medina-spirit-kentucky-derby-winner-failed-drug-test-dies-workout-santa-anita-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medina Spirit reportedly died suddenly while on the track. The 3-year-old throughbred won the Kentucky Derby in May, came in second in the Breeders’ Cup Classic and third in the Preakness Stakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIAGRA cuts risk of Alzheimer's by 69%...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4216281/viagra-cuts-risk-alzheimers-prescribed-beat-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAKING Viagra slashes Alzheimer’s risk by two-thirds, research suggests. Scientists claim the love drug may help boost brain health and cut levels of toxic proteins that trigger dementia. Experts a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media venture under scrutiny by market regulators...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-elections-media-social-media-donald-trump-ba09954162b8309419134d7e2488a52e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Regulators are looking into the deal that would bring Donald Trump's new social media company to the stock market, one that has attracted both legions of fans of the former president and people looking to make a quick profit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tapper to get Prime Time?</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/jake-tapper-to-replace-chris-cuomo-primetime-cnn-andrew-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources tell Radar Jake had been pushing for the job behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk accused of manipulating search results to bury whistleblower story...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/economy/musk-accused-of-manipulating-search-results-to-bury-whistleblower-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla founder Elon Musk faces accusations that he used Twitter to obfuscate news that the Securities and Exchange Commission is investigating his company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE ANTI-LOCKDOWN RIOTS SWEEP EUROPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4210241/anti-lockdown-marches-europe-covid-christmas-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-LOCKDOWN riots erupted today in Belgium as protests sweep across Europe over fears Christmas could be cancelled due to Covid. Six people were hospitalised including two police officers while 2…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second accuser testifies...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211206154013-8n4cy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-GHISLAINE MAXWELL/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Maxwell accuser testifies she had sexual contact with Epstein at 17</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Enters Bear Market Following Report of SEC Probe...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-track-enter-bear-market-154538370.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tesla Inc.’s selloff intensified Monday following a report that regulators opened an investigation into the electric-vehicle company, briefly pushing the stock to its biggest four-day decline since March.Most Read from BloombergThe Hot New Trend For Hedge Funds Is—Finally—Female FoundersAutomating the War on Noise PollutionEven in the Metaverse, Not All Identities Are Created Equal‘Ghost Signs’ Haunt London’s Reviving NeighborhoodsMeet the New Climate Refugee in Town: CoyotesThe s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Chaos In The Loop Leads To Shooting, Beatings; 21 Arrested...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/12/05/loop-chaos-arrests-flash-mob-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens flooded the streets near Millennium Park in a similar sight to last summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer at therapy farm dies after rammed by sheep...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-massachusetts-animals-sheep-d62de90ca2125e8ae22e68803994c205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOLTON, Mass. (AP) — A 73-year-old volunteer at a Massachusetts animal therapy farm died over the weekend after she was repeatedly rammed by a sheep, police said. Kim Taylor, of Wellesley, was caring for livestock in a pen alone at about 9 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rife' cocaine use reported in UK Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98rife-e2-80-99-cocaine-use-reported-in-uk-parliament-e2-80-94-just-as-boris-johnson-announces-crackdown-on-drug-crime/ar-AARwHDF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Fires 200 For Missing Deadline...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/12/06/umass-memorial-health-covid-vaccine-mandate-firings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 200 UMass Memorial employees are out of a job because they missed the health care system's COVID vaccination deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger, Alarm After Follow-Home Burglaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jackie-avant-death-raises-alarm-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When it starts happening in Trousdale Estates and Hancock Park, we're in trouble," said radio station owner and Avant family friend Tavis Smiley</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials debate changing definition of 'fully vaccinated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/is-it-time-to-change-the-definition-of-fully-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been more than six months since many Americans finished their vaccination course against COVID-19; statistically, their immunity is waning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How side-effect database sowed doubt in shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/health-care/2021/12/06/how-a-vaccine-side-effect-database-sowed-doubt-in-vaccinations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Midway into the pandemic, University of Alabama epidemiologist Bertha Hidalgo realized her COVID communication strategy needed a makeover. She was skipping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don draws attention with admission he 'fired Comey'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/584470-trump-draws-attention-with-admission-he-fired-comey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump is drawing attention after giving an interview in which he admitted to firing ex-FBI Director James Comey and suggested that doing so allowed him to remain in office for four years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gum Reduces Transmission?</title>
      <link>https://scitechdaily.com/chewing-gum-developed-that-could-reduce-covid-transmission-laced-with-protein-that-traps-the-sars-cov-2-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scitechdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A chewing gum laced with a plant-grown protein serves as a “trap” for the SARS-CoV-2 virus, reducing viral load in saliva and potentially tamping down transmission, according to a new study. The work, led by Henry Daniell at Penn’s School of Dental Medicine and performed in collaboration with sci</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second accuser called to testify...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211206145439-zrj1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-GHISLAINE MAXWELL/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Second Ghislaine Maxwell accuser called to testify at sex abuse trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smollett trial to resume with defense possibly calling him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/jussie-smollett-trial-resumes-chicago-3860a3e677b22f4da2233d333df7dabd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — After two brothers spent hours telling a jury how Jussie Smollett paid them to carry out a fake racist and anti-gay attack on himself in downtown Chicago, the big question when the actor’s trial resumes Monday will be whether he will tell his side of the story .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next smartphone might have camera that's always watching...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/your-next-smartphone-might-have-a-camera-that-e2-80-99s-always-watching/ar-AARwjKv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black couple says appraiser lowballed them. So, they 'whitewashed' home and say value shot up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/a-black-couple-says-an-appraiser-lowballed-them-so-they-whitewashed-their-home-and-say-the-value-shot-up/ar-AARwbJG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin calls ties with USA 'lamentable'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211206120656-ud5gn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/KREMLIN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Kremlin calls U.S.-Russia ties ' quite lamentable' on eve of Putin-Biden call</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People Who Meditate Have Better Focus, Sleep, Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/meditation-better-focus-sleep-mental-health-apps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The self-care tools they’ve found most beneficial for achieving this include meditation apps (52%), in-person therapy (45%), and virtual therapy (43%).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists bask on battlefield as drug gangs fight over Mexican resort town...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tourists-bask-battlefield-drug-gangs-100051334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tulum, jewel of the Mayan Riviera, risks emulating Acapulco, another once glamorous resort now overwhelmed by violence Members of the national guard patrol Playa Pescadores in Tulum. Photograph: Artur Widak/NurPhoto/Rex/Shutterstock Bright yellow police tape fluttered in the breeze outside a restaurant just off the main strip in the Mexican resort town of Tulum, as the lights of a nearby police truck flashed blue and red. Troops in camouflage fatigues stood guard outside the deserted late-night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Robbers Hit Home During Holiday Party...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/12/05/exclusive-armed-robbers-hit-palisades-home-during-holiday-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the bulk of partygoers were in the backyard, the suspects entered the home and robbed two guests inside the house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's New Moon Landing Schedule Escalates Race With USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/china-s-new-moon-landing-schedule-escalates-race-with-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s New Moon Landing Schedule Escalates Race With U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Workers Shrug Off Omicron as More Return to Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/city-of-london-workers-shrug-off-omicron-as-more-return-to-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City of London Workers Shrug Off Omicron as More Return to Work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Has Blood Pressure Rising? You're Not Alone...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/the-pandemic-has-your-blood-pressure-rising-youre-not-alone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year was a tough one. Americans grappled with a global pandemic, the loss of loved ones, lockdowns that splintered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partners or Partners in Crime? Maxwell-Epstein Bond Key to Case...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/partners-or-partners-in-crime-maxwell-epstein-bond-is-key-to-her-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Visoski, the silver-haired pilot who flew Jeffrey Epstein and his prominent friends all over the world, believed Ghislaine Maxwell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside TESLA as Musk Pushed Unflinching Vision for Self-Driving Cars...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/inside-tesla-as-elon-musk-pushed-an-unflinching-vision-for-self-driving-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. Elon Musk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How TIKTOK Reads Mind...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/how-tiktok-reads-your-mind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are four main goals for TikTok’s algorithm: 用户价值, 用户价值 (长期), 作者价值, and 平台价值, which the company translates as “user</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight wolves poisoned in Oregon, stumping police and renewing calls for protections...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Eight-wolves-have-been-poisoned-in-Oregon-16677692.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oregon authorities are seeking help after the state's dwindling gray wolf population was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems plot escape from Biden poll woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/06/democrats-biden-polling-woes-523719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party's own polling has the president in the red. Lawmakers know they need to get better at selling his agenda to avert midterm disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven days: Following Trump's reckless coronavirus trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Seven-days-Following-Trump-s-reckless-16676950.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When he first learned he had tested positive for the coronavirus, President Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonds' Faith in Fed Set For Biggest Test Since '80s...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bond-market-s-faith-in-fed-set-for-biggest-test-since-the-1980s-1.1691116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bond traders’ faith in the Federal Reserve’s power to curb inflation is about to face its biggest test in four decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing attacks potential diplomatic boycott of Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-sports-boycotts-beijing-2020-tokyo-olympics-7727b98d708447ae24457d910a8f1ae8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China on Monday threatened to take “firm countermeasures” if the U.S. proceeds with a diplomatic boycott of February’s Beijing Winter Olympic Games. Foreign Ministry spokesperson Zhao Lijian accused U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unvaxxed Italians face new restrictions as holidays near...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-milan-894002a958b201b5ac255152294d3fa3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Italy is making life more uncomfortable for unvaccinated people this holiday season, excluding them from indoor restaurants, theaters and museums starting Monday to reduce the spread of coronavirus and encourage vaccine skeptics to get their shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Tells USA to look in 'Mirror' Before Accusing Kremlin of Aggression...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/ukraine-russia-vladimir-putin-joe-biden-anthony-blinken-invasion-1656092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian foreign affair's spokeswoman Maria Zakharova referred to NATO campaigns in Iraq, Libya and Syria and Yugoslavia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of young adults obese or overweight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/over-half-of-young-adults-are-obese-or-overweight-study-says/ar-AARtSVq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Congressman's gun-toting family Christmas photo sparks outrage days after school shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gop-congressman-e2-80-99s-gun-toting-family-christmas-photo-sparks-outrage-days-after-school-shooting/ar-AARuSV1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB DOLE DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/05/politics/bob-dole-dies/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dole, a Republican Party stalwart and presidential hopeful who espoused a brand of plain-spoken conservatism as one of Washington's most recognizable political figures throughout the latter half of the 20th century, died Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise ship with at least 17 virus cases aboard docks in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Cruise-ship-with-at-least-17-coronavirus-cases-16678395.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Norwegian Cruise Line ship docked in New Orleans over the weekend with at least 17...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock to Crypto Daredevils Joins List of Scary Market Omens...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/shock-to-crypto-daredevils-joins-list-of-scary-omens-in-markets-1.1691526</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brutal bout of selling that wiped billions of dollars from profitless growth companies, IPO stocks and SPACs has now caught up with Bitcoin, further stressing risk tolerances and brokerage balances among small-time traders.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
