<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Air pollution the 'new tobacco,' warns WHO head...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/oct/27/air-pollution-is-the-new-tobacco-warns-who-head</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Simple act of breathing is killing 7 million people a year and harming billions more, but ‘a smog of complacency pervades the planet’, says Dr Tedros Adhanom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid Granted Visa...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paularmstrongtech/2018/10/27/ai-humanoid-sophia-is-granted-first-ever-robot-visa-speaks-with-president/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's first ever visa was just issued to a robot in the Caucasus but there's more going on that will shape the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy Flashes Signs It's Downhill From Here...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-economy-flashes-signs-its-downhill-from-here-1540656002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private analysts and the Federal Reserve say a slowdown is looming. Though few believe a recession is near, a slowdown in growth would have far-reaching implications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New spotlight on embattled Andy Lack...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/megyn-kelly-debacle-puts-new-spotlight-on-embattled-nbc-news-honcho-andy-lack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly’s disastrous tenure at NBC News is coming to an end as her low-rated “Megyn Kelly Today” was canceled Friday on the heels of backlash after she questioned if “blackface” is racist. Now the pressure is one NBC News chairman Andy Lack, who handed Kelly a bank-breaking, three-year contract worth $69 million in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warning: 'We are preparing for war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1037059/Russia-INF-treaty-world-war-3-Donald-Trump-Vladimir-Putin-Mikhail-Gorbachev-US-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LEADING Russian official has warned that Russia is preparing for war in the wake of the US’s unilateral withdrawal from the Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty (INF), in a sign of growing tensions between the two foes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida wipeout?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/26/trump-florida-senate-2018-senate-governor-941802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is mounting an 11th-hour effort to head off high-profile losses for governor and Senate in his adopted home state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuPaul brings drag queens out of the closet...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-icon-rupaul-brings-drag-queens-closet-011058843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long kept within the confines of gay bars, drag queen culture is spreading like wildfire in the United States, propelled by the most famous of them all, RuPaul and his cult television show. "I wouldn't have predicted this even five years ago," says Raymond Alvarez, one of those attending</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Gunman opens fire at Pittsburgh synagogue... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/breaking-pittsburgh-synagogue-shooting-gunman-13489212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tree of Life Congregation Synagogue in Wilkins Avenue has been sealed off by police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai rappers cause stir with anti-junta lyrics...</title>
      <link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/world/2018/10/27/thai-rappers-cause-stir-with-anti-junta-lyrics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freemalaysiatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative criticism through music and arts has been harder to control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control of Senate may hinge on Mississippi runoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/control-u-senate-may-hinge-possible-mississippi-runoff-102220038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Republicans and two Democrats are contesting a special election to serve out the remainder of retired Republican Senator Thad Cochran's term. Under state law, if no one gets 50 percent of the vote, the top two candidates regardless of party affiliation will go to a Nov. 27 runoff. "Mississippi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romans protest at eternal decline of Italian capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-rome-protests/romans-protest-at-eternal-decline-of-italian-capital-idUSKCN1N10GO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several thousand people protested in front of Rome City Hall on Saturday to deno...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots -- to make robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-abb-robots/robots-to-make-robots-at-abbs-new-150-million-factory-in-china-idUSKCN1N109X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots will make robots at a new ABB factory in China, which the Swiss engineeri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus kills 8th child at facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/eighth-child-s-death-reported-new-jersey-rehabilitation-facility-n925131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I am calling on the Wanaque Center to take immediate appropriate measures to address this tragic situation," said legislative leader Craig J. Coughlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's 'Tropical Trump' poised to win presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/bolsonaro-brazils-tropical-trump-poised-win-presidency-051840854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes called a "Tropical Trump" for his politically incorrect vitriol, Brazilian far-right presidential candidate and heavy favorite Jair Bolsonaro has successfully played to an electorate disgusted with politics as usual. Bolsonaro, 63, has built an image as a political outsider ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Best Shot in 30 Years to Turn Arizona Blue...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/democrats-get-best-shot-in-30-years-to-put-blue-stamp-on-arizona#gs.fLGvjT0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Get Best Shot in 30 Years to Put Blue Stamp on Arizona</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Faces Next Test of Authority in German Regional Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/merkel-faces-next-test-of-her-authority-in-german-regional-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel Faces Next Test of Her Authority in German Regional Vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your DNA Is Out There. Want Law Enforcement Using It?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/your-dna-is-out-there-do-you-want-law-enforcement-using-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your DNA Is Out There. Do You Want Law Enforcement Using It?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surreal World: TV Delves Into Paranoia, Anxiety, Misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-surreal-world-tv-delves-into-paranoia-anxiety-and-misinformation-1540645108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New TV dramas like “Homecoming,” “Maniac” and “Legion” are exploring the issues unsettling society with characters who struggle to maintain a grip on reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Workers Fume Over Payouts After Misconduct Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/google-workers-fume-over-executives-payouts-after-sexual-misconduct-claims/17949270/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — At Google’s weekly staff meeting Thursday, the top question employees voted to ask Larry Page, a co-founder, and Sundar Pichai, the chief executive, was one about sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Faces Deepening Criminal Probe Over Production Figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tesla-faces-deepening-criminal-probe-over-whether-it-misstated-production-figures-1540576636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla, with a fresh civil fraud settlement now behind it, faces a new legal problem: a deepening criminal investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail Bombs, Other Threats Have Wealthy Cranking Up Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/27/us/terror-private-security-bodyguard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrities and the rich are creating a boom in demand for bodyguards, drivers and similar amenities. Not everyone has that luxury, of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan Could Pose Public Health Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/10/26/medical-expert-migrant-caravan-could-pose-public-health-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Jane Orient, executive director of the Association of American Physicians and Surgeons, said migrants could bring diseases to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'could tone up' rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/413418-trump-rejects-calls-to-temper-rhetoric-i-think-ive-been-toned-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday rejected calls to temper his political rhetoric in the aftermath of a nationwide bomb scare involving many prominent Democrats with whom he has traded barbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly Crash at NBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/-megyn-kelly-today-is-canceled-as-the-nbc-host-negotiates-an-exit/17948668/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four days that sank Megyn Kelly and sparked a vicious standoff inside NBC News began with a simple, cheery welcome to her “Today” show audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he 'could tone up' rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-says-he-could-tone-rhetoric-after-mail-bomb-arrest-n925106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: With a mail bomb suspect in custody, Trump finds himself in a political box of his own making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama rips Trump, GOP in fiery speeches for Midwest Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/06ec76cf0cf14a4fa0cc5aeefdf7ba82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Former President Barack Obama criticized President Donald Trump's tenure in office Friday in fiery speeches in Milwaukee and Detroit that took aim at him and other Republicans for "making stuff up." The speeches were among Obama's sharpest and most direct takedowns of Trump's presidency, although the former president was careful to not mention Trump by name. He said the "character of our country is on the ballot" in the first midterm election since Trump took office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOT HIM</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/26/suspected-mail-bomber-found-a-father-in-trump-former-lawyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspected Florida mail bomber is a lost and “sick individual’ who estranged himself from his family but eventually “found a father” in President Trump, his family’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High, naked woman tried to bite off man's genitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.wwaytv3.com/2018/10/25/police-naked-woman-tries-to-bite-off-mans-genitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wwaytv3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in South Carolina are investigating after a man says a naked woman tried to bite his genitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raged On Social Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mail-bomb-suspect-displayed-rage-love-trump-social-media-pages-175126009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook accounts, a LinkedIn account, and a Twitter page appear to belong to mail-bomb suspect Cesar Altieri Sayoc, and the postings appear to be from an ardent supporter of President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu pays surprise visit to Oman...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israels-netanyahu-pays-surprise-visit-134816654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Friday returned from an unannounced visit to Oman, the two countries confirmed, meeting the Gulf state's leader in the first visit of its kind in over 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Jewish community leader resigns after impostor claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/german-jewish-community-leader-resigns-impostor-claims-170839800.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A prominent Jewish community leader in northern Germany is stepping down from his post after reports that he may have lied about his roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scare rattles those touched by past political violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/bomb-scare-rattles-those-touched-101545908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — No one has been hurt or killed. But the wave of mail bombs targeting prominent Democrats this week has angered and dismayed some of the people affected personally by past acts of political violence in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immersive Haunted Houses Mean More Guest Thrills, More Zombie Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-immersive-haunted-houses-mean-more-thrills-for-guestsmore-rules-for-zombies-1540584863</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chain-saw maniacs must show some restraint. ‘Putting someone against a wall by their shoulders’ is okay but no touching torsos; ‘Go away, monster.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Catholic Diocese whistleblower to appear on '60 MINUTES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wivb.com/news/local-news/buffalo-catholic-diocese-whistleblower-to-appear-on-60-minutes-this-sunday/1550307259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wivb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Siobhan O'Connor, Malone's former executive assistant, will speak to 60 Minutes this Sunday night at 7 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Brazil Poised to Elect 'Tropical Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/a/brazil-poised-to-elect-a-tropical-trump/4630123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Riding a wave of voter resentment, Congressman Jair Bolsonaro has surged in popularity by embracing anti-establishment stance and combative demeanor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER caravan forms...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/10/26/migrants-guatemala-border-another-caravan-us-takes-shape/1771797002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the bridge connecting Guatemala and Mexico closed, migrants said they planned to cross en masse the river that dividesÂ the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear plant workers told to 'take cover immediately' over incident with uranium tunnels...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7591972/nuclear-plant-workers-sent-take-cover-immediately-alert-over-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORKERS at a nuclear plant in the US have been told to “take cover immediately” following an incident involving plutonium and uranium tunnels. A text message alert was sent to workers a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  GOOGLE Earth blind spot over military base may be hiding crashed UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7585911/google-earth-blind-spot-over-experimental-military-base-may-be-where-us-government-hides-crashed-ufos-defence-insider-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Google Earth blind spot over an experimental military base in Nevada may have been used to cover up a “super secret location” where the US government kept crashed UFOs, a defence in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside bizarre Venezuelan 'gangster god' shrines where desperate families pray for protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7572207/venezuelan-gangster-shrines-families-pay-protection-caracas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT the heart of the city with the highest murder rate in the world is a “holy temple” dedicated to the gangsters behind the killings. The Santos Malandros (Holy Thugs) shrine in Venezue…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America ready for wave of socialists?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/oct/26/america-midterms-democrats-socialism-bernie-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A slew of leftwing Democrats are running in the midterms – but some believe it’s too soon for a full-scale embrace of progressive ideas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Implosion: Ugly, Dramatic, Inevitable...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/megyn-kellys-nbc-career-implosion-ugly-dramatic-and-inevitable </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly is out at NBC News, following her ‘blackface’ remarks. Next, a negotiation around a multimillion-dollar payout and what could be a long search for a new employer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town hunts mystery serial rabbit killer; 100 victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/26/french-town-hunts-mystery-serial-rabbit-killer-100-pets-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A serial killer of rabbits has struck fear into the hearts of the people of a picturesque French village on the north Brittany coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/latest-news/article220671715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Florida man from Aventura has been arrested at a Plantation AutoZone in connection to the string of suspected explosive packages sent to prominent Democrats and critics of President Donald Trump this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron-Less CAVS Tickets: $2...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/extra-mustard/2018/10/26/friday-hot-clicks-cleveland-cavaliers-nets-lebron-james-tickets-prices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You could get into this week’s Nets-Cavs game practically for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSFT Overtakes AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-microsoft-amazon-com/microsoft-overtakes-amazon-as-second-most-valuable-u-s-company-idUSKCN1N02FQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft Corp regained its spot as the second most valuable U.S. company on Fri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fingerprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-packages/fingerprint-dna-lead-to-florida-mans-arrest-in-bombs-sent-to-trump-critics-idUSKCN1MZ1CP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man suspected of sending at least 14 bombs to prominent critics of U.S. Presid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Inquiry Into What Went Wrong in Moonves Era Hits Snags...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/26/business/media/les-moonves-investigation-cbs.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President hails quick arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-hails-quick-arrest-pipe-bomb-suspect-vows-swift-certain-n924871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We must show the world we are united in peace and harmony," Trump said at a White House event held shortly after an arrest was made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOT HIM</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/suspicious-package-addressed-sen-cory-booker-found-florida-n924776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Packages addressed to Sen. Corey Booker, former National Intelligence Director James Clapper, Sen. Kamala Harris and billionaire Tom Steyer were discovered Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comets, asteroids spreading life across galaxy?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/comets-asteroids-may-be-spreading-life-across-galaxy-ncna924916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are germs from outer space the source of life on Earth?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military energy drink obsession contributing to PTSD...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2018/10/26/the-militarys-obsession-with-energy-drinks-is-contributing-to-ptsd-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatened to Bomb in 2002...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/broward/article220672300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cesar Sayoc, an Aventura man arrested in connection with the mail pipe bombs sent to prominent critics of President Donald Trump, is a businessman with a long criminal history in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT:   Bombs Slowing Republican 'Momentum' in Midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-unfortunate-that-bomb-stuff-has-slowed-republican-momentum-going-into-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO to Staff All Sex Scenes With Intimacy Coordinator...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/hbo-staff-all-sex-scenes-intimacy-coordinator-1155204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After piloting the practice on 'The Deuce,' the cable network will be enlisting a professional to ensure standards and prevent abuse during all sexual scenes on-set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime and crisis turn Caracas streets dark and deserted...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181026-crime-crisis-turn-caracas-streets-dark-deserted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 years on, German far right seeks to rehabilitate Empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181026-100-years-german-far-right-seeks-rehabilitate-empire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defaming Mohammad not free speech, European court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/defaming-muhammad-does-not-fall-under-purview-of-free-speech-european-court-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The freedom of speech does not extend to include defaming the prophet of Islam, the European Court of Human rights ruled Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin invited to DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/vladimir-putin-invited-to-washington-in-early-2019-john-bolton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin has been invited to visit Washington, D.C.  in early 2019, according to President Trump’s National Security Adviser Amb. John Bolton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smart city' dream becomes privacy nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/10/26/sidewalk-labs-ann-cavoukian-smart-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran boats harass US ship with CENTCOM commander aboard...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/10/26/two-iranian-fast-boats-approach-us-warship-while-centcom-commander-on-board/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Essex is hauling U.S. Marines and F-35Bs with the 13th MEU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto tops $70 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2018-elections/2018/10/26/beto-orourke-tops-70-million-outpacing-cruz-2-1-texas-race-hits-100-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- The cost of a U.S. Senate seat from Texas has never been higher, and Rep. Beto O'Rourke's insurgent bid to topple Sen. Ted Cruz has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: NBC Sat On Info That Undermined Kavanaugh Accusers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/37637/nbc-sat-information-undermined-brett-kavanaugh-ashe-schow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In yet another stunning display of media bias, NBC now acknowledges that it had information that undermined the credibility of some of the women who accused the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man caught trying to steal Magna Carta with hammer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/738821/magna-carta-salisbury-cathedral-attempted-theft-hammer-uk-latest-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOT COMING BACK TO FOXNEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6321805/Megyn-Kellys-past-employer-squashes-rumors-return-Fox-News.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumors of a possible return to Fox News were firmly shot down by a high-level source at her former network , who told DailyMail.com that Kelly 'is not coming back to any of the Fox News platforms.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodybuilding, Native American Florida strip-club worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6321331/Suspected-mail-bomber-identified-Cesar-Altier-Sayoc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cesar Altier Sayoc was taken into custody on Friday morning in Plantation, Florida in connection with the 12 suspicious packages that have been discovered this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing #MeToo card?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6320437/Black-employees-NBC-hurt-Megyn-Kelly-playing-MeToo-card-collect-69M-payout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Her blackface comments were bad but falsely playing the gender card is the worst form of white privilege I have ever seen,' said one employee at the network in response to Megyn Kelly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE COULD BE IN MAIL</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6319391/FBI-warns-pipe-bombs-mail-MAGAbomber-sent-10-South-Florida.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI Assistant Director William Sweeney warned the 'American public to remain vigilant' as more devices could be found and they should be considered dangerous as investigation continues.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: You CAN booze away troubles...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6316275/Alcohol-helps-remember-good-times-not-bad-ones-study-says.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study from Brown University has found alcohol affects a gene making you only remember good times. But addiction experts warn that you should not drink to forget your troubles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESSIONS:  'PARTISAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/clintons-obama-suspicious-packages/h_8e80e624a4a7ff77ee6dc5a82b5963d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When asked why bomb suspect Cesar Sayoc was targeting Democrats, Attorney General Jeff Sessions replied, "I don't know. Other than what you might normally expect. He may have been -- he appears to be partisan but that will be determined by the facts as the case goes forward. I'm not able to comment on that."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New travel ban?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/25/politics/trump-travel-ban-mexico/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is considering a travel ban-like executive action that would block certain asylum seekers at the Mexican border, the San Francisco Chronicle reported Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI reviewing TESLA production numbers as part of criminal probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/26/tesla-faces-criminal-probe-over-allegedly-misstating-production-numbers-and-misleading-investors-wsj.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents are reviewing Tesla's stated Model 3 numbers dating back to early 2017, the Journal reports, citing unnamed sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCTOBER WITCH:  STOCKS IN CORRECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/26/stock-market-us-futures-show-drop-for-dow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell sharply on Friday as investors slogged through another volatile session on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch could pull off amazing coup: Buying FOX regional sports networks back at discount...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/26/rupert-murdoch-may-buy-back-fox-sports-networks-from-disney.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"New Fox" may end up buying back the 22 regional sports networks "Old Fox" sold to Disney earlier this year. Those networks are a declining asset that's still worth more to Fox than anybody else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP: 3.5%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/26/first-read-on-us-q3-2018-gross-domestic-product.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy grows at a faster-than-expected rate in the third quarter as inflation was kept in check and consumer spending surged, according to Commerce Department data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts cable network in 3 AM tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/politics/2018/10/26/tweet-trump-claims-being-blamed-for-mail-bombs/V2M5BfZEBICFITOq6Lm5bP/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump called a series of attempted attacks targeting prominent critics of his administration “this ‘bomb’ stuff” in a tweet Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Sentiment Cools...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-s-consumer-sentiment-cools-on-buying-conditions-for-durables</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. consumer confidence in October was slightly weaker than forecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vanessa Trump details powder experience...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/vanessa-trump-details-powder-experience-1540584158-dc15bcca-e83b-42ef-9829-d10d471906c3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attack on the Trump family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte crowd chants 'CNN SUCKS' before rally...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/jeffzeleny/status/1055926687983120384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Here at the Bojangles Coliseum in Charlotte, the crowd is already warming up the “CNN Sucks” chant - two hours before tonight’s rally.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network unveils plan to replace...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/10/26/nbc-unveils-plan-to-replace-megyn-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An insider told us Kelly’s staff of nearly 200 will continue working at the 9 a.m. hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Steroid problem'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/26/suspected-mail-bomber-was-a-stripper-with-a-steroid-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida man charged with sending at least 13 mail bombs was a fitness-obsessed male stripper who dreamt of becoming a professional wrestler, according to a new report Friday. Cesar Sayoc Jr. tr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmented reality porn stars coming to living room...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/25/augmented-reality-porn-stars-are-coming-to-a-living-room-near-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was only a matter of time: Adult entertainment studio Naughty America released one of the industry’s very first XXX-rated augmented reality (AR) apps for Android phones this week, which promises…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MAGA BOMBER' SUSPECT IN CUSTODY</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/10/26/11th-suspicious-package-found-at-florida-mail-facility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities have arrested a man in Plantation in connection to a series of package bombs that have been sent to top Democrats and President Trump critics, according to CBS News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSPECT'S TRUMPMOBILE... </title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/10/26/suspected-maga-bomber-idd-as-native-american-trump-supporter-cesar-sayoc-56-8079040/?ito=article.desktop.share.top.twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sayoc, of Fort Lauderdale, is belived to have been arrested in Plantation, a suburb of Miami, Florida, Friday on suspicion of sending 12 pipe bombs to top Democrats and high-profile figures critical of Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors to start prescribing museum visits...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-10-canadian-doctors-museum.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Canadian doctors are to begin prescribing trips to an art gallery to help patients suffering a range of ailments become a picture of health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP CRAP CRASH...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/snap-stock-earnings-set-to-plunge-to-a-record-low-2018-10-1027659323</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Voters Report Machines Changing Votes...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/10/25/tarrant-county-voters-straight-party-option/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tarrant County Elections Administrator Heider Garcia said voters need to leave the wheel alone and give the machine a few moments to load the next page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Loner' with long arrest record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf86a256719b422eb656e5cb5854e04d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Cesar Sayoc is an amateur body builder and former male stripper, a loner with a long arrest record who showed little interest in politics until Donald Trump came along. On Friday, he was identified by authorities as the Florida man who put pipe bombs in small manila envelopes, affixed six stamps and sent them to some of Trump's most prominent critics. Records show Sayoc, 56, of Aventura, has a history of financial problems and extensive record of past arrests, including a stint served on probation for making a bomb threat. He was born in New York City and attended college in North Carolina before moving to the Miami suburbs in the late 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish schools cancel LGBT tolerance day under govt pressure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/adf839c37719411e80a97a22eb936be7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Several schools in Poland have canceled activities promoting tolerance for gays and lesbians following government pressure and threats in some places. More than 200 schools had planned to take part in "Rainbow Friday," an anti-discrimination event that a civic rights group, the Campaign Against Homophobia, had promoted in hopes of building greater acceptance for LGBT students. Private broadcaster TVN reported that some schools pulled out of the event following an outcry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodwill workers find original 1774 'rebel' newspaper...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0be8910e4060486ca2f8f93d70f738d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELLMAWR, N.J. (AP) — A quick eye by Goodwill workers in southern New Jersey turned up framed pages from an original 1774 Philadelphia newspaper with an iconic "Unite or Die" snake design on the masthead. The frayed Dec. 28, 1774, edition of the "Pennsylvania Journal and the Weekly Advertiser" boasts three items signed by John Hancock, then president of the Provincial Congress, who pleads for the Colonies to fight back "enemies" trying to divide them. A jumble of small advertisements offer rewards for a lost horse or runaway apprentice, while another insists the poster will no longer pay his "misbehav(ing)" wife's debts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracked using cell phone...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/explosive-device-maxine-waters-la-similar-obama-clinton/story?id=58737042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cesar Sayoc, 56, faces 48 years in prison for the charges, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Gillum jump started progressive movement...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-florida-governors-race-20181025-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How Andrew Gillum rose from obscurity to become the exemplar for national progressives building a case that the path left is the only promising path back to the White House for Democrats. What happens if he wins the governor's race there?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EYE ON THE GAVEL...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-midterm-nancy-pelosi-20181026-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apart from President Trump, no one may be more responsible if Democrats win back control of the House — or fail to do so. At age 78, and signaling an end to her historic leadership, the San Francisco lawmaker shows no sign of slowing down as she works to check a president she sees as dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat on Stone...</title>
      <link>http://www.fltimes.com/tns/national/for-years-trump-adviser-roger-stone-loved-notoriety-now-he/article_163dcaa4-7baf-59b3-9736-83db2d279e82.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POMPANO BEACH, Fla. —The sun had set outside the banquet room when Roger Stone took the stage, a pale blue handkerchief sprouting from the chest pocket of his double-breasted gray</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW IT'S THIRTEEN PACKAGES...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/10/26/kamala-harris-suspicious-package-sacramento/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sacramento County Sheriff's Department confirms that they are investigating a suspicious package at a post office, but will not confirm who it's addressed to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Loses $14,000,000,000?</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/10/26/amazon-stock-jeff-bezos-wealth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following disappointing revenue in Amazon's third quarter.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
