<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Loses $13.5 Billion After AMAZON Disappointment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/jeff-bezos-loses-135-billion-after-amazon-disappointment/ar-AAMKy55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc.’s weaker-than-expected second-quarter results has sent its founder’s fortune tumbling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway requires shot, covering for all shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210730-new-york-s-broadway-mandates-vaccines-masks-for-all-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's Broadway mandates vaccines, masks for all shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 47% of Republicans say time will come 'to take law into own hands'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/565610-47-percent-of-republicans-say-time-will-come-to-take-the-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 47 percent of Republicans believe that a time will come when “patriotic Americans have to take the law into their own hands,” according to a George Washington University</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Everyone Obsessed With Bezos Face?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-everyone-obsessed-jeff-bezos-082628628.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastJeff Bezos’ face looks, well, different lately: his lips are plumped up to near-Kardashian proportions, and his cheeks look more full, as if someone used Facetune to expand his face and head.It is unknown if Bezos has had work of any kind done. If he has, there’s no shame—unlike, his critics would say, union-busting, tax evasion, and shooting yourself into space while the rest of the world crumbles. And so many were quick to take to TikTok and so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaxed, waxed, but definitely not relaxed: Welcome to pandemic swerve...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaxed-waxed-but-definitely-not-relaxed-welcome-to-the-pandemic-swerve/ar-AAMK67j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delta variant rudely interrupts an optimistic summer with the realization that this ordeal is far from over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate moves to legalize pot at federal level. What are chances?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/senate-moves-to-legalize-pot-at-federal-level-what-are-the-chances/ar-AAMHopd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposed bill puts forth restorative justice measures, taxes marijuana and lays a framework for regulation. But it is unlikely to pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Brawl Between Homeless Erupts On Venice Boardwalk...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/caught-on-video-brawl-on-venice-beach-boardwalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cellphone video shows an all-out brawl between what appears to be at least three homeless men on the Venice Beach Boardwalk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Attempt To Test Air Force Hypersonic Weapon Fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41761/air-forces-fails-in-second-attempt-to-conduct-a-test-flight-of-its-first-hypersonic-missile</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The missile's rocket booster failed to ignite after separating from the B-52 carrying it, but the Air Force says it still gained valuable test data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA being overrun by freaky 'penis snakes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3379278/us-overrun-freaky-penis-snake-slither-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US faces being overrun by strange-looking “penis snakes” that appear to have slithered up from the Amazon. Caecilians can grow up to 32 inches long and one was found in a Miami canal in Novembe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Living Past 100 Lies In Gut?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/centenarians-gut-bacteria-live-longer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery could lead to yogurts and other probiotic foods that increase longevity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did bogus tale of U.S.-backed drug raids help set plot in motion?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/investigations/article253121148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A month before the assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moïse, two South Florida men turned up at an unusual meeting in the Caribbean nation, according to information presented to a Haitian prosecutor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key inflation indicator fastest gain since 1991...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/key-inflation-indicator-up-3point5percent-year-over-year-in-june-vs-3point6percent-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inflation indicator that the Fed uses as its key guide rose 3.5% in June, a sharp acceleration that was nonetheless right around expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million infected daily?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/dr-scott-gottlieb-estimates-up-to-1-million-americans-infected-with-covid-daily-as-delta-spreads.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I wouldn't be surprised if, on the whole, we're infecting up to a million people a day right now," Dr. Scott Gottlieb told CNBC on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unvaxxed athlete slammed for bareface...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/olympics/1003188/unvaccinated-us-swimmer-slammed-for-going-maskless-at-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'War Has Changed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/cdc-warns-internal-document-war-has-changed-coronavirus-n1275478</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccines continue to be effective, particularly at preventing severe disease, according to the document. But they may not be as good at preventing infection or transmission of the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brits outraged by U.S. cartoon depicting royal family as egotistical tea drinkers controlled by mafia boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brits-outraged-by-us-cartoon-depicting-royal-family-as-egotistical-tea-drinkers-controlled-by-mafia-boss/ar-AAMKm9z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The HBO Max series has been slammed by critics in Britain as "wrong" and "disgusting."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Deep new history of TESLA takes shine off Musk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/review-deep-history-tesla-takes-130057001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The polarizing founder shows up a lot in 'Power Play,' Tim Higgins' Tesla history — but usually in the role of a dramatic foil who will be overtaken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic police dogs: Useful hounds or dehumanizing machines?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/robotic-police-dogs-e32e371e8776b8565f1a0f6491e55c29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — If you’re homeless and looking for temporary shelter in Hawaii’s capital, expect a visit from a robotic police dog that will scan your eye to make sure you don’t have a fever. That’s just one of the ways public safety agencies are starting to use Spot, the best-known of a new commercial category of robots that trot around with animal-like agility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Front-line workers in FL say surge 'feels like impending storm'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/frontline-workers-florida-current-covid-19-surge-feels/story?id=79151882</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"In early July, we were down to 12 COVID-19 patients in the hospital, and today we have 80."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trolls targeting trans Olympian...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210730-online-trolls-targeting-transgender-olympian-kiwi-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online trolls targeting transgender Olympian: Kiwi official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYDNEY READIES FOR ARMY</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210730053158-jwg5n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 3,TV,PIX):UPDATE 3-Sydney readies for the army as lockdown fails to squash Delta outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After mudslide, priest gets narcos' help to build new town...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-caribbean-f0306dc68771d5166f918e863de6f185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION SAN FRANCISCO DE ASIS, Honduras (AP) — First came Hurricane Eta. Then, Hurricane Iota, unleashing rains of biblical proportions on the hillside community of La Reina. As Iota hammered La Reina for four days, residents kept watch on the mountain above their 300 homes for signs that they should flee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship tied to Israeli billionaire attacked off Oman, 2 killed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ship-israeli-billionaire-oman-c43203ff0262ba2c4bfafb31cc42fa50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — An oil tanker linked to an Israeli billionaire reportedly came under attack off the coast of Oman in the Arabian Sea, authorities said Friday, an assault that killed two crew members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese athletes face Chinese nationalists' wrath after beating at Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/30/china/china-japan-olympics-online-abuse-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of Japan's victorious Olympic athletes have been subjected to a storm of online abuse from Chinese nationalists following the defeat of their Team China opponents in Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They Thought I Was Dead': Haitian President's Widow Recounts Assassination...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/30/they-thought-i-was-dead-haitian-presidents-widow-recounts-assassination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — With her elbow shattered by gunfire and her mouth full of blood, the first lady of Haiti lay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qaddafi Son Alive. And Wants to Take Libya Back...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/30/qaddafis-son-is-alive-and-he-wants-to-take-libya-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. Ten years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Covid With a Vengeance' Consumes Politics...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/30/covid-with-a-vengeance-consumes-u-s-politics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American political system has come down with a case of long Covid. In Washington and the states, and in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angst grips America's most liberal city...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/equilibrium-sustainability/565550-rapid-change-churns-seattle-creating-political-turmoil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — America’s most liberal city stands at an uneasy crossroads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump takes punches from Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/565499-trump-takes-two-punches-from-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been a tough week for former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court finds AI systems can be recognized under patent law...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jul/30/im-sorry-dave-im-afraid-i-invented-that-australian-court-finds-ai-systems-can-be-recognised-under-patent-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal court judge says allowing artificial intelligence systems, as well as humans, to be inventors is ‘consistent with promoting innovation’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic leads to another summer of anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-pandemic-leads-to-another-summer-of-anger/ar-AAMJ4EM </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother bear rushed woman snapping photo of cubs. Now, parkgoer facing federal charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-mother-bear-rushed-a-woman-snapping-a-photo-of-her-cubs-now-the-parkgoer-is-facing-federal-charges/ar-AAMJHgf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators found that she had posted photos of the bears on her Facebook page with the caption “absolutely floored by the beauty of this place.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Trump follow pledge to donate last 6 months of presidential pay? It's mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/did-trump-follow-his-pledge-to-donate-the-last-6-months-of-his-presidential-pay-it-e2-80-99s-a-mystery/ar-AAMJQ0B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump never announced a recipient of the final $220,000 of his salary. His post-presidential office has not said where it went.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Internal Report Calls Delta Variant as Contagious as Chickenpox...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/30/c-d-c-internal-report-calls-delta-variant-as-contagious-as-chickenpox/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delta variant is much more contagious, more likely to break through protections afforded by the vaccines and may cause</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Considers Closing NYC Tourist Hot Spot After 14-Year-Old Leaps to Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/billionaire-developer-stephen-ross-mulls-closing-nyc-hot-spot-the-vessel-after-14-year-old-leaps-to-his-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We thought we did everything that would really prevent this,” said Stephen Ross, developer of the Manhattan neighborhood where the attraction sits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVIDED STATES OF AMERICA:  Texas Gov. Abbott issues executive order prohibiting cities from requiring masks and vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Texas-Gov-Abbott-issues-executive-order-16350969.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott, a Republican, on Thursday signed an executive order prohibiting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILITARY 'MANDATORY INJECTIONS'</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2021/07/29/biden-orders-military-move-toward-mandatory-covid-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden said making the vaccines mandatory is important because troops often serve in places where vaccination rates are low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As violent crimes surge, Californians' faith in gun control slips in new poll...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/violent-crimes-surge-californians-faith-120044493.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new UC Berkeley Institute of Governmental Studies poll co-sponsored by the Los Angeles Times found that 56% of the state's voters surveyed believe stronger laws restricting the sale and possession of guns help make their communities safer, but the number is down from 60% who felt that way three years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling mysterious mutations...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/unraveling-the-mysterious-mutations-that-make-delta-the-most-transmissible-covid-virus-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are trying to piece together why the delta variant so readily infects unvaccinated Americans, spewing 1,000 times more virus particles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN MASK BACK ON</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-joe-biden-business-health-travel-a1670ffa08f1f2eab42c675d99f1d9ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden on Thursday announced sweeping new pandemic requirements aimed at boosting vaccination rates for millions of federal workers and contractors as he lamented the “American tragedy” of rising-yet-preventable deaths among the unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to release 'smart glasses' to record EVERYTHING...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3375994/facebook-smart-glasses-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK CEO Mark Zuckerberg has announced that its Ray Ban smart glasses will be the company’s next product to launch. Zuckerberg made the comment during Facebook’s second quarter earnings c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAILER:  GAGA GOES 'GUCCI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/29/lady-gaga-sizzles-and-aims-for-another-oscar-nomination-in-house-of-gucci</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MGM is really hitting for the fences with “House of Gucci.” Lady Gaga and Adam Driver sizzle in the trailer for the Ridley Scott movie coming in November. Um, this means that Ridley Sco…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significance of 'breakthrough' infections remains unclear; CDC hides data...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Experts-ask-to-see-data-behind-new-policy-16347545.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - New recommendations from federal health officials this week on when...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNFRIENDLY SKIES:  Flight attendants dealing with unruly passengers at unprecedented rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/flight-attendant-harassment-bc32953f-79f0-4103-aea7-1a94e2524521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flight attendants are experiencing passenger abuse - including urination, name-calling, and being followed off of planes - at unprecedented rates this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World races to contain Delta variant...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/world-races-contain-delta-variant-014314177.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governments around the world on Thursday raced to head off a surge in coronavirus cases driven by the Delta variant, with US President Joe Biden offering new incentives to vaccine holdouts and Israel authorizing booster shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Schools Mandate Weekly Testing For Students, Teachers...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/lausd-require-students-covid-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Unified School District announced Thursday it would require all students and employees returning for in-person instruction to participate in weekly COVID testing regardless of vaccination status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP Trails Forecast Even as Consumer Spending Surges...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-gdp-trails-forecast-even-123834932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. growth missed forecasts in the second quarter as the effects of supply-chain constraints reverberated through the economy and took the shine off one of the biggest gains in consumer spending in decades.Gross domestic product expanded at a 6.5% annualized rate following a revised 6.3% pace in the first quarter, the Commerce Department’s preliminary estimate showed Thursday.The report underscores the robust bounce back in household demand as well as the challenges companies are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom's wine shop broken into -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/crime/article/Gavin-Newsom-San-Francisco-wine-shop-break-in-16349766.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson said what's happening is similar to other local businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy sailor charged for starting fire that destroyed $3B warship...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/07/29/navy-charges-bonhomme-richard-sailor-in-devastating-2020-fire-of-amphibious-assault-ship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This post has been updated with additional details of the sailor accused of starting the fire aboard the former Bonhomme Richard (LHA-6). The Navy has filed charges against a sailor for allegedly deliberately starting a fire last year that quickly spread and consumed much of the interior of amphibious assault ship USS Bonhomme Richard (LHD-6), the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD Has Worst Debut Ever...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/robinhood-flirts-worst-debut-ever-172454124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Robinhood Markets Inc. wanted to make history with its initial public offering, and now it has -- for the wrong reason.Shares in the broker behind the meme-stock revolution fell 8.4% below the IPO price in the company’s first trading session. That’s the worst debut on record among 51 U.S. firms that raised as much cash as Robinhood or more, according to data compiled by Bloomberg.It dethroned the 2007 IPO by another brokerage, MF Global Holdings Ltd., as the worst debut among qual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decision followed 'stunning findings' from Cape Cod beach outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/cdc-mask-decision-stunning-findings-cape-cod-beach/story?id=79148102</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC's mask decision followed stunning findings from a Cape Cod beach outbreak. The viral load of vaccinated beachgoers changed what we know about the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILITARY MULLS 'MANDATORY INJECTIONS'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9841073/Biden-tells-states-offer-100-vaccination-bribes-tells-military-look-mandatory-jabs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is launching a tough new approach on the COVID pandemic amid rising infections, and will require federal employees to attest to getting a vaccine or submit to testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School debate erupts anew weeks before classes resume...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210729162204-5lf2x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-SCHOOLS (PIX):U.S. school masks debate erupts anew weeks before classes resume</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden undergoing procedure to remove object from her foot...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/565519-jill-biden-undergoing-procedure-to-remove-object-from-her-foot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First lady Jill Biden will undergo a procedure on Thursday to remove an object from her left foot, her office announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian fixed kayak with condom, threw up and won...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/29/olympics-2020-jess-fox-won-kayak-gold-thanks-to-condom-fix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian canoeing legend Jess Fox won a gold medal in resourcefulness at the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research looks for Covid tie to later Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-coronavirus-pandemic-d8fbdcb7fd099e2416d0b15d99bc564c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are trying to unravel why some COVID-19 survivors suffer “brain fog” and other problems that can last for months, and new findings suggest some worrisome overlaps with Alzheimer’s disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN CALLS FOR VAX PAYMENTS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/565492-biden-calls-on-states-to-offer-100-vaccine-incentives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden on Thursday called on state and local governments to use funds from his $1.9 trillion American Rescue Plan to offer $100 payments to individuals in order to incentivize coronavirus vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKOLA Founder Pleads Not Guilty To Fraud, Freed On $100 Million Bail...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanponciano/2021/07/29/billionaire-nikola-founder-trevor-milton-pleads-not-guilty-to-criminal-fraud-charges-freed-on-100-million-bail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of the electric truck maker plunged 9% after the charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NPR Ethics Policy:  OK For Journalists To Demonstrate...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/publiceditor/2021/07/29/1021802098/new-npr-ethics-policy-its-ok-for-journalists-to-demonstrate-sometimes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NPR opens the door for journalists to publicly advocate for fairness, justice and other human values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return Of Long Lines: 'Crazy' Wait Times At FL Testing Sites...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/south-florida-covid-test-sites-long-lines-cases-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long lines for coronavirus tests are back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson Sues DISNEY Over 'BLACK WIDOW' Streaming Release...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/scarlett-johansson-walt-disney-co-black-widow-lawsuit-1234802440/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scarlett Johansson filed a lawsuit on Thursday against The Walt Disney Co., claiming that the studio breached her contract by releasing the Marvel movie Black Widow on Disney+ at the same time it w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:   If you don't fall asleep, there's plenty to look at...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/07/jungle-cruise-disney-review/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s how to drag a 20-minute theme-park ride into nearly two hours of cinematic tedium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Woman Found Beheaded On MN Sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/suspect-arrested-after-woman-found-stabbed-to-death-on-shakopee-sidewalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An arrest has been made after a woman was found beheaded on a Shakopee sidewalk Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Chasing Extra Vaccine Dose, While Scientists Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-are-chasing-extra-vaccine-shots-while-scientists-debate/ar-AAMI68p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many scientists say that vaccinated people probably won’t need booster shots anytime soon. Some are getting them anyway. They are going to local pharmacies, other states or even other countries — anywhere where there is no record of them having been vaccinated — to get extra doses out of concern about the Delta variant or because they are worried their protection may be wearing off. The news on Thursday that Israel would give them to some older...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major universities have more diversity staff than history professors...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/john-s-2/2021/07/28/diversity-bloat-many-major-universities-have-more-diversity-staff-than-history-professors-n405278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"legislators should consider reducing and restructuring DEI staffs"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military looks for secret to GPS-free navigation in bird's eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/07/28/military-funded-research-looks-for-the-secret-gps-free-navigation-in-a-birds-eye/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers can synthesize DNA that could be used for future navigation applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman With Only J.D. Salinger Recording To Burn It...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/woman-only-known-recording-j-125755616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woman with only known recording of J.D. Salinger's voice to have tape burned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police ordered to arrest bareface...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/capitol-police-ordered-arrest-staff-visitors-not-wearing-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Capitol Police were ordered to start arresting visitors and staff who refuse to wear a mask on the House side of the Capitol complex starting Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Cardinal charged with sexually assaulting teen...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2021/07/ex-cardinal-mccarrick-charged-with-sexually-assaulting-teen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Cardinal Theodore McCarrick, who was defrocked after a Vatican investigation confirmed he had sexually molested adults and children, is charged with sexually assaulting a teenage boy during a Massachusetts wedding reception in the 1970s, court records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL QB Says He Only Jabbed After Pressure From League: 'They'll Make Your Life Miserable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/nfl-qb-says-he-only-got-vaccinated-because-of-league-pressure-if-you-dont-fall-in-line-theyll-make-your-life-miserable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;85 percent of NFL players have reportedly received at least one dose of the Covid-19 vaccine, but a hesitancy lingers among the remaining 15 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Forces soldier drowns in Key West pool during underwater combat training...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9839637/Special-Forces-soldier-drowns-underwater-combat-training.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday, a Green Beret drowned in a pool at the Special Forces Underwater Operations School in Key West, Florida, during a conditioning exercise on Tuesday,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feelings Of Deja Vu Growing Amid More Mandates, Return Of Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/amid-covid-setbacks-and-mask-mandates-some-feeling-sense-of-deja-vu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City restaurateur Danny Meyer, behind hot spots including Union Square Cafe and Gramercy Tavern, is requiring all staffers and diners inside his restaurants to be vaccinated, starting Sept. 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prolonged shaking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-alaska-hawaii-tsunamis-2a5af8987548ead7182d21f87cca7557</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PERRYVILLE, Alaska (AP) — A powerful earthquake which struck just off Alaska’s southern coast caused prolonged shaking and prompted tsunami warnings that sent people scrambling for shelters. Residents reported only minor damage, but officials said that could change after sunrise and people get a better look.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
