<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China Covid death toll could be 17,000% higher than admitted..</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4470802/chinas-virus-death-toll-higher-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA’S coronavirus death toll could actually be a staggering 17,000 per cent higher than admitted in a shocking cover-up, an analyst has claimed. It’s feared the country’s true C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The story of how Doomsday Clock began ticking 75 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/story-doomsday-clock-began-ticking-144100844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Martyl Langsdorf designed just one magazine cover, but it has had considerable staying power. A prolific painter of abstract and figurative canvases, she was commissioned 75 years ago by the scientists who built the atomic bomb that ended World War II. By 1947 the Cold War was on, and they wanted to alert Americans to the danger of a nuclear confrontation with the Soviet Union. They ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celine Dion cancels remaining tour dates due to 'persistent' medical issues...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/music/celine-dion-cancels-remaining-north-american-tour-dates-due-to-health-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celine Dion has canceled her remaining North American tour dates due to 'persistent' medical issues that prevent her from performing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift away from daily case counts has begun...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2022/01/15/news/nation/a-shift-away-from-daily-covid-case-counts-has-begun-joam40zk0w/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epidemiologists caution that the numbers should be relied on only as broad indicators of the velocity and direction of the disease’s transmission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As nations decide to live with virus, experts warn of surrendering too soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-nations-decide-to-live-with-the-virus-some-16778094.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nations around the planet are making a subtle but consequential pivot in their war...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin sworn into office...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/glenn-youngkin-first-republican-to-win-statewide-in-virginia-since-2009-sworn-into-office/ar-AASOgaW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT restaurant opening in New York will serve up status with side of seafood...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/an-nft-restaurant-opening-in-new-york-will-serve-up-status-with-a-side-of-seafood/ar-AASOGzx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew accuser seeks testimony from British nightclub witness...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220115-prince-andrew-accuser-seeks-testimony-from-british-nightclub-witness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Prince Andrew's sexual assault accuser want to question a woman who they say saw him in a London nightclub with a "young girl," US court documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUVRE Blasts Le Pen Video as French Presidential Race Heats Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/louvre-blasts-le-pen-video-as-french-presidential-race-heats-up-1.1708074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s crowded presidential campaign is getting more heated ahead of the April elections, and now even the Louvre, one of the country’s most recognizable symbols, is caught in the fray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of migrants set off in Honduras in first caravan of '22...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220115161035-eytnw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CENTAM:Hundreds of U.S.-bound migrants set off in Honduras in first caravan of 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safer gun?: 'Smart' pistols debut...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-01-safer-gun-smart-pistols.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Smart" pistols designed to limit who can shoot them are poised to hit the booming US firearm market this year, taking aim at spiking gun deaths as federal lawmakers remain deadlocked on any new restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass Trials in Cuba Deepen Harshest Crackdown in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/14/mass-trials-in-cuba-deepen-its-harshest-crackdown-in-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detained protesters in Cuba could get up to 30 years in prison as they face the largest and most punitive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Did We Get So 'Cringe'?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2022/01/cringe-culture-everywhere/621272/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early cringe culture was about empathy and secondhand embarrassment. Today, being “cringe” is a serious infraction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there second act ahead?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/As-Biden-ends-his-first-year-amid-many-16778070.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Nearing the first anniversary of his swearing in, President Joe Biden has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decaying 122-year-old San Fran home sells for $2m at auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/14/san-francisco-victorian-home-2-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price tag on the roughly 2,000 sq ft Victorian, called ‘the worst house on the best block’, was the outcome of overbidding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music catalogs fetching huge deals. Are they overvalued?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/music-catalogs-fetching-huge-deals-140011619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Songwriters like Bruce Springsteen, John Legend and Bob Dylan are cashing in on the growing demand for popular songwriting catalogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA BEACHES CLOSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/tsunami-warning-issued-for-california-coast-beaches-closed-waves-expected/ar-AASOpSX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST COAST TSUNAMI THREAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10405333/Tongans-flee-lives-tsunami-smashes-island-nation-underwater-volcano-erupts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia is the fifth nation to issue a tsunami warning after an undersea volcano in the Pacific Ocean caused havoc in Tonga, with the dangerous waves due to affect Australia from 9.45pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAVES IN HAWAII...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/15/asia/tsunami-warning-tonga-volcano-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tsunami has hit Tonga's largest island, Tongatapu, and reportedly sent waves flooding into the capital after an underwater volcano in the South Pacific exploded in a violent eruption on Saturday, sending a cloud of ash and gas steam into the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONGA TAKES HIT...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2022-01-15-tsunami-hawaii-california-alaska-tonga-fiji-volcano-eruption</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a developing story. Please check back for updates. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How diplomats commit crazy crimes living abroad -- and get away with it...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/15/how-diplomatic-immunity-lets-envoys-get-away-with-crazy-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are around 100,000 foreign diplomats, including their dependents, currently living in the US — and some have broken local laws and faced zero consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Gay Cruise Keep 5,500 People Safe Amid Covid?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/14/can-a-gay-cruise-keep-5500-people-safe-amid-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Omicron variant of the coronavirus continues to surge onboard cruise ships, forcing several cruise lines to cancel and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEVER-ENDING: Expect more worrisome variants, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-pandemics-dc99bc9f769dd6d7cb669e3d185c6261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready to learn more Greek letters. Scientists warn that omicron’s whirlwind advance practically ensures it won’t be the last version of the coronavirus to worry the world. Every infection provides a chance for the virus to mutate, and omicron has an edge over its predecessors: It spreads way faster despite emerging on a planet with a stronger patchwork of immunity from vaccines and prior illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal risks in sedition conspiracy case against Oath Keepers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-riots-conspiracy-indictments-b846daef24d854ed267c509e758164db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seditious conspiracy case against members and associates of the far-right Oath Keepers militia group marks the boldest attempt so far by the government to prosecute those who attacked the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican midterm dilemma: How closely to align with him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arizona-donald-trump-campaigns-presidential-elections-elections-be1c94516de16d480870ea8f46e0f35b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former President Donald Trump is stepping up his election-year effort to dominate the Republican Party with a Saturday rally in Arizona in which he plans to castigate anyone who dares to question his lie that the 2020 presidential election was stolen, likely including the state’s GOP governor, Doug Ducey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest in Vienna against mandatory vaccination...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220115151003-w4ya8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRIA (PIX):Thousands protest in Vienna against mandatory vaccination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Politics Making Americans Sick, Literally...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/american-politics-feel-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1 in 20 even say thinking about and discussing politics leaves them feeling suicidal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brought to Brink by Vengeful Aide He Crossed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/boris-johnson-brought-to-brink-by-the-vengeful-aide-he-crossed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson Brought to Brink by the Vengeful Aide He Crossed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers stuck at sea after NORWEGIAN cancels cruise mid-voyage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/ports-waterways/589881-passengers-stuck-at-sea-after-norwegian-cancels-cruise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers aboard a Norwegian cruise ship are stuck at sea this week after the cruise line decided to cancel the cruise mid-voyage due to COVID-19 concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Enthusiasts Meet Their Match: Angry Gamers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/15/crypto-enthusiasts-meet-their-match-angry-gamers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — For years, Christian Lantz has played S.T.A.L.K.E.R., a first-person shooter game set in a post-apocalyptic Ukraine that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRECTV drops OAN in blow to conservative channel...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/mystery-surrounds-decision-directv-drop-one-america-news-network-its-lineup-1669743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OANN has positioned itself as rightward of Fox News. However, the network has been accused of running "disinformation campaigns."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French fashion brand under fire for photo shoot involving indigenous women in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-fashion-brand-under-fire-191846818.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - A production team from the popular French fashion label Sézane landed in Oaxaca earlier this month to photograph their new collection, drawing on the vibrant colors and patterns created by local artisans in southern Mexico. But a video from one of those shoots, involving an indigenous Mexican woman, has drawn widespread criticism, including from the Mexican government, which has launched an investigation into the incident.Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcano erupts in Pacific, West Coast under tsunami advisory...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-environment-and-nature-new-zealand-tonga-d434936e25079859df8261780976def8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — An undersea volcano erupted in spectacular fashion near the Pacific nation of Tonga on Saturday, sending large tsunami waves crashing across the shore and people rushing to higher ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students stage walkouts to protest in-person classes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/omicron-fuels-surge-us-students-stage-walkouts-protest-in-person-classes-2022-01-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of students in Boston and Chicago walked out of classes on Friday in protests demanding a switch to remote learning as a surge in COVID-19 cases fueled by the Omicron variant disrupted efforts at returning to in-person education around the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peak TV boom; Record 559 scripted shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/peak-tv-scripted-series-all-time-high-2021-1235075677/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual estimate of shows from FX jumps by 13 percent after a one-year dip in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America registers record cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.anews.com.tr/world/2022/01/14/latin-america-registers-record-daily-covid-19-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.anews.com.tr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin America registers record daily COVID-19 cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/johnschreiber/status/1481770722271760384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery shortages deepen as pandemic dries supplies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-grocery-shortages-deepen-pandemic-180518711.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High demand for groceries combined with soaring freight costs and Omicron-related labor shortages are creating a new round of backlogs at processed food and fresh produce companies, leading to empty supermarket shelves at major retailers across the United States. Growers of perishable produce across the West Coast are paying nearly triple pre-pandemic trucking rates to ship things like lettuce and berries before they spoil. Shay Myers, CEO of Owyhee Produce, which grows onions, watermelons and asparagus along the border of Idaho and Oregon, said he has been holding off shipping onions to retail distributors until freight costs go down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Thieves loot freight trains in Los Angeles with impunity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thieves-loot-freight-trains-los-214224509.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of freight cars are broken into every day on Los Angeles's railways by thieves who take advantage of the trains' stops to loot packages bought online, leaving thousands of gutted boxes and products that will never reach their destinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-media-ukraine-vladimir-putin-f24e6bd400e20d7890daff371cd80eb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. intelligence officials have determined a Russian effort is underway to create a pretext for its troops to further invade Ukraine, and Moscow has already prepositioned operatives to conduct “a false-flag operation” in eastern Ukraine, according to the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Backs Off Race-Based Treatment After Legal Threat...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/coronavirus/hospital-system-backs-off-race-based-treatment-policy-after-legal-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the largest hospital systems in the United States gave race more weight than diabetes, obesity, asthma, and hypertension combined in its allocation scheme for COVID treatments, only to reverse the policy after threats of legal action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN: Djokovic detained ahead of Australia visa hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/asia/live-news/novak-djokovic-australia-visa-ruling-01-14-22/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Novak Djokovic is being detained ahead of a court hearing on his case to stay in the country and play at the Australian Open. Follow here for live updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines OK first religious exemptions for shot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-us-marine-corps-1fb313feafcd36a7d621ba152cab3eb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. Marine Corps has approved its first two COVID-19 vaccine exemptions based on religious reasons, something no other military service has done so far. The two exemptions are the first to be approved by the Corps in 10 years, the Marines said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surges in 44 states now slowing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10403061/Covid-surges-44-states-slowing-experts-predict-cases-coming-weeks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Omicron variant is showing more signs that it is starting to burn out this week, as the rate of case growth is slowing in 44 U.S. states as of most recent reported data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson's 'wine time Fridays' -- staff drinks EVERY week during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/boris-johnsons-wine-time-fridays-25951853</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Downing Street held yet MORE parties throughout the Covid pandemic with events taking place every Friday as Prime Minister Boris Johnson encouraged staff to "let off steam" even though indoor socialising was strictly banned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin Finally Hands Over Phone To Police...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/01/alec-baldwin-fatal-shooting-rust-phone-police-search-warrant-1234913061/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weeks after a search warrant was issued for Alec Baldwin’s cell phone, the Rust star has given the device to police for their probe into the fatal shooting of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Airs McCarthy Saying The Don Admitted Responsibility for Capitol Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/we-have-the-receipts-cnn-airs-tape-of-kevin-mccarthy-saying-trump-admitted-bearing-some-responsibility-for-capitol-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN digs up tape of Kevin McCarthy saying Trump admitted bearing some responsibility for Capitol attack day after attempting 'revisionist history'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL's extraordinary grip on media diet...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nfl-covid-viewership-ratings-11b58e14-c3d2-400d-b9d6-e48db8934d0b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viewership for the regular season is up 10% from last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage piles up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-lifestyle-recycling-louisville-102ea8cdc6a38f01a54816d9f0780aa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — The omicron variant is sickening so many sanitation workers around the U.S. that some cities have had to delay or suspend garbage or recycling pickup, angering residents shocked that governments can’t perform this most basic of functions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston students endure frigid temps thanks to open-window policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/children-bundle-up-for-class-due-to-boston-public-schools-open-window-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The policy has triggered outrage from some parents, who see the abundance of Covid caution to the point that kids are freezing in class as a hindrance to learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/14/which-states-are-the-freest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our liberties have taken a beating in recent years, accelerated by governments' enthusiasm for leveraging COVID-19 as an excuse for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Trans Movement Not About Rights Anymore...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/the-trans-movement-is-not-about-rights-67e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's about a cultural revolution and the abolition of biological sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence shows appears in throat first...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/throat-swab-home-covid-test-rcna12096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throat swabs with at-home Covid tests are not currently recommended in addition to nasal swabs despite mounting pressure, but the FDA says the research isn't there yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Benioff is transforming TIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/marc-benioff-time-magazine-salesforce-c4298c2a-3fb2-4068-bb69-3d9ee59e08ac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He's kept pushing us to get out of the boxes we were in," Time editor-in-chief Edward Felsenthal said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
