<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Man hit strip club, bought LAMBORGHINI with coronavirus aid. Received 9 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-texas-man-hit-the-strip-club-and-bought-a-lamborghini-with-coronavirus-aid-he-received-9-years-in-prison/ar-AARixeQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Troubled' Mennonite boys were trafficked, forced into physical labor, and abused at farm, suit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/pennsylvania/mennonite-church-liberty-ridge-farm-abuse-20211130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two former residents claim the Eastern Pennsylvania Mennonite Church and Liberty Ridge Farm violated federal laws against human trafficking, racketeering, and forced labor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mom told son to back out of frat boxing match. He died days after 'Fight Night'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-mom-told-her-son-to-back-out-of-a-16662189.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcer revved up the crowd with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices peak?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/30/home-price-hikes-slow-down-according-to-sp-case-shiller.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home prices are still higher than a year ago, but the gains are now decelerating for the first time since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confessions of prolific serial killer have LA detectives chasing ghosts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/confessions-prolific-serial-killer-left-130015414.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Little confessed to killing 93 women across the U.S. Nearly a third of those admissions are uncorroborated, and most of those are in L.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our Money Has No Value': Frustration Rises in Turkey at Lira Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/our-money-has-no-value-frustration-rises-in-turkey-at-lira-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL — Lines outside bread stores and gas stations; farmers defaulting on loans; impromptu street demonstrations. The signs of economic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Pandemic Changed Where Californians Live...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/how-covid-19-has-changed-where-californians-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the earliest days of the pandemic, we’ve been hearing about Californians abandoning their usual way of life for greener,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling mass rallies planned...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/29/dueling-mass-rallies-planned-supreme-court-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expect plenty of opinions Wednesday at the Supreme Court when crowds of demonstrators converge for rallies timed to oral arguments on a Mississippi abortion law that could upend Roe v. Wade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right figure Zemmour announces presidential run to 'save' France...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211130114609-3zt61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-ELECTION/ZEMMOUR (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Far-right figure Zemmour announces presidential run to 'save' France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fattest Profits Since 1950 Debunk Inflation Story Spun by CEOs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fattest-profits-since-1950-debunk-120000558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In the second year of a pandemic that began by wiping out 20 million jobs, American workers are doing surprisingly well. It’s just that American business is doing even better. Most Read from BloombergChina Cash Flowed Through Congo Bank to Former President’s Cronies‘Pension Poachers’ Are Targeting America’s Elderly VeteransReliving the New York Subway Map DebateIn the past two quarters, U.S. corporations outside of the finance industry posted their fattest margins since 1950 -- on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In shadow of TX gas drilling sites, health fears escalate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-environment-and-nature-texas-asthma-ae7e3b327293247642c99d8126c8f12d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARLINGTON, Texas (AP) — At a playground outside a North Texas day care center, giggling preschoolers chase each other into a playhouse. Toddlers scoot by on tricycles. A boy cries as a teacher helps him negotiate over a toy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger tries to wave down plane at LAX; Cops tackle on tarmac...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4172026/woman-apprehended-at-lax-after-running-on-tarmac/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLICE have apprehended a woman who allegedly tried to run out on the tarmac at Los Angeles International Airport. The woman apparently tried to wave at a plane, according to an eyewitness. A video…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Good As Original?</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/west-side-story-2021-movie-reviews-preview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The early reactions to West Side Story are in!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Teens Getting Six Figures to Quit High School for Basketball...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/the-teenagers-getting-six-figures-to-quit-high-school-for-basketball/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jalen Lewis liked high school, and why not? At 6-foot-9, with a bird’s nest of hair on top, he was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Injection Sites for Drug Users to Open in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/supervised-injection-sites-for-drug-users-to-open-in-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an attempt to curb a surge in overdose deaths caused by increasingly potent street drugs, New York City will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In China, TESLA Is Catfish, and Turns Auto Companies Into Sharks...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/in-china-tesla-is-a-catfish-and-turns-auto-companies-into-sharks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-two years ago, Liu Siong Song built machines to help factories make cheap toys and watches. Then he made them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell sex abuse trial to resume with Epstein pilot's testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/maxwell-sex-abuse-trial-resume-with-epstein-pilots-testimony-2021-11-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell's criminal sex abuse trial was set to enter its second day on Tuesday, with prosecutors expected to question a longtime pilot of the deceased financier Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WEST SIDE STORY' First Reactions: 'Top-Tier Spielberg,' Zegler Star Shines Bright...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2021/11/west-side-story-first-reactions-steven-spielberg-musical-1234682024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Spielberg’s musical has finally screened, and ecstatic first reactions are pouring in: “Everyone is at the top of their game.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Spectacular'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/west-side-story-first-reactions-praise-steven-spielberg-1235121757/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first reactions to 20th Century Studios’ “West Side Story” are beginning to pour in following the film’s premiere in New York City on Monday evening. Those who attended …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Jan. 6 panel set for faceoff... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/583492-trump-jan-6-panel-are-set-for-tuesday-faceoff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump and the Jan. 6 select committee will face off in court on Tuesday over whether he can use executive privilege claims to block lawmakers from obtaining extensive internal White House records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boebert, Omar fight leaves Republicans scrambling...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/583500-boebert-and-omar-fight-leaves-gop-scrambling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is grappling with yet another fight between a far-right Republican and a member of the progressive “squad” — this time Reps. Lauren Boebert (R-Colo.) and Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow war in space heating up fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/11/30/space-race-china-david-thompson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space Force general: China and Russia are attacking U.S. space assets “every day.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex shops offer Brazil Evangelicals taste of heaven...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211130-sex-shops-offer-brazil-evangelicals-a-taste-of-heaven</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes, she disguises her merchandise as medication. Others, as a bakery delivery. Whatever the packaging, Andrea dos Anjos knows discretion is key when Brazil's emerging Evangelical sex shops sen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right pundit Zemmour launches bid for French presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20211130-far-right-pundit-eric-zemmour-announces-2022-bid-for-french-presidency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French far-right commentator Eric Zemmour on Tuesday announced he will be running in the 2022 presidential election, joining a crowded field of candidates aiming to unseat President Emmanuel Macron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS BUILD 'LIVING' ROBOTS THAT REPRODUCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10254773/Scientists-build-living-robots-reproduce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tiny 'living machines' aren't traditional robots, nor a species of animal, but living, programmable organisms. They were created by Tufts University and University of Vermont scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson's house raided by LA police...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/11/29/marilyn-manson-house-raided-los-angeles-county-sheriff-sexual-assault-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson's home was raided by L.A. County Sheriff's detectives as part of a sexual assault investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  CHRIS MUST EXIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/11/fire-chris-cuomo/620835/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New revelations show the CNN anchor betrayed his obligation to his viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor: 'Secret plan' for hate crime on himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jussie-smollett-had-a-secret-plan-for-hate-crime-on-himself-prosecutor-says-as-trial-begins/ar-AARhb8X?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces uncertain threat as evolving pandemic tests nation's patience...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/biden-faces-uncertain-threat-with-omicron-variant-as-evolving-pandemic-tests-nation-s-patience/ar-AARgkEC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayors scramble for face time with Buttigieg with billions of infrastructure dollars at stake...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article256078832.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The competition started months before the infrastructure bill even passed, but now it’s kicked into high gear, with city leaders crafting ambitious plans in hopes of securing a windfall of federal funds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan hits new record for hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/agriculture/michigan-hits-new-record-for-adult-covid-19-hospitalizations-80-of-beds-full/article_87a6731a-09f6-59f5-8370-af5589ad681b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan reached a new record of adults hospitalized with COVID-19 on Monday with 4,181 hospitalized with confirmed cases of the virus, the most since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He sued SeaWorld to liberate the whales. Then he started getting postcards from them...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/column-one-sued-seaworld-liberate-130034325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten years after a legal activist filed a lawsuit for orcas held in captivity, he began receiving postcards from them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZOOM EARTH</title>
      <link>https://zoom.earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;zoom.earth&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;View LIVE satellite images, rain radar, and animated wind speed maps. Track the latest hurricanes, wildfires and weather in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY ROE MAY GO!</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/05/why-its-unlikely-democrats-would-pack-the-supreme-court-even-if-roe-were-overturned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Where does it stop? Democrats add three seats; Republicans add four more. Pretty soon you have a 100-person unelected third-chamber of the legislature.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETS ON CRYPTO FUTURE</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/fintech/jack-dorsey-bitcoin-crypto-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The departure of @jack from Twitter may have seemed sudden, but it reflects his obsession with bitcoin, an interest that’s been building for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lorne Michaels, 77,  still lives for Saturday night...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/lorne-michaels-still-lives-for-saturday-night/ar-AARgSAU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New opioids, more powerful than fentanyl, discovered in DC amid deadly wave of overdoses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/new-opioids-more-powerful-than-fentanyl-are-discovered-in-dc-amid-deadly-wave-of-overdoses/ar-AARgxFB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Fails to Halt Art Basel Miami as People Crave Normalcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/omicron-fails-to-halt-art-basel-miami-as-people-crave-normalcy/ar-AARgxAx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutations alarm scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/omicron-mutations-alarm-scientists-but-new-variant-first-must-prove-it-can-outcompete-delta/ar-AARhgqb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLIONAIRE OUT AT  TROUBLED SOCIAL</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4167154/jack-dorsey-step-down-twitter-ceo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACK Dorsey announced on Monday that he will step down as Twitter’s CEO today. Parag Agrawal, the current Chief Technology Officer at Twitter, is set to replace the tech giant, who faced a st…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'COMPANY BEFORE EGO'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-as-twitter-ceo-cnbc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey is resigning from the platform he co-founded, CNBC reported Monday. Dorsey confirmed his resignation in a tweet. Sources told CNBC’s David Faber that Dorsey, a Twitter founder who now serves as its chief executive, is expected to announce he will be stepping down “in the near term.” Faber said he did not […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military readying 'Plan B' if Iran nuke talks fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-news/israeli-military-readying-for-plan-b-if-iran-nuclear-talks-fail-687220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER JACK STEPS DOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-is-expected-to-step-down-sources-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Dorsey was serving as both the CEO of Twitter and Square, his digital payments company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine sex trafficking trial begins...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-nyc-trial-starts-17f7c28591c1f32c802f3b7bc413bfe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ghislaine Maxwell and Jeffrey Epstein were “partners in crime” in the sexual abuse of teenage girls, a prosecutor said Monday, while Maxwell’s lawyers said she was being made a scapegoat for a man’s bad behavior as the British socialite’s sex trafficking trial got underway in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Six-Foot Rule' Doesn't Protect...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/6-foot-rule-doesnt-protect-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The policy could have been set anywhere between three to 10 feet, depending on the risk tolerance of the local public health authority putting out the mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another House retirement spells even more trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/29/politics/suozzi-retirement-2022-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, New York Democratic Rep. Tom Suozzi announced he plans to leave his 3rd District seat behind to run for governor in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METS Agree To Record $130M Contract Over 3 Years With Aging Ace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/max-scherzer-mets-agree-to-record-contract-as-right-hander-signs-three-year-130-million-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mets appear to be adding Scherzer to a rotation that already includes Jacob deGrom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradley Cooper reveals he 'got held up at KNIFEPOINT' in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4170028/bradley-cooper-held-up-knifepoint-nyc-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRADLEY Cooper revealed he was “held up at knifepoint” in New York City while on his way to pick up his daughter Lea, 4, from school. While detailing the traumatic experience, the 46-year-old actor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most infectious yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/29/1059861661/the-omicron-variant-may-be-the-most-infectious-one-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in South Africa say preliminary data suggests the omicron coronavirus variant is already widespread across southern Africa — and this happened in a very short period of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Done as Full-Time Golfer...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/29/tiger-woods-reveals-future-golf-plans-after-scary-car-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods is done as a full-time golfer, but says he is channeling Ben Hogan in his eventual return to the links.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGER TALKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.golfdigest.com/story/tiger-woods-exclusive-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.golfdigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with Golf Digest, Tiger Woods opens up about a painful year, a possible return to golf, and son Charlie's progress as a player.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWELL:  Complicates inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/fed-chair-powell-says-omicron-variant-poses-risk-to-economy-complicates-inflation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed Chair Jerome Powell believes that the omicron variant of Covid-19 and a recent rise in coronavirus cases pose a threat to the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schoolgirl Outfits, Gifts to Teens, Abuse 'Every Day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/schoolgirl-outfits-gifts-to-teens-sex-abuse-every-day-feds-slam-ghislaine-maxwell-on-1st-day-of-trial/ar-AARgWuB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMON &amp; SCHUSTER Lawsuit Puts Big Media on Notice...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/biden-simon-schuster-antitrust-media-strictly-business-1235120691/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration made a statement earlier this month when the Justice Department filed an antitrust lawsuit to block the $2.1 billion sale of Simon &amp; Schuster. Merrick Garland’s body bl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey decides NOT to run for Texas gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/matthew-mcconaughey-texas-governor-decision-1235051474/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar-winner has decided against challenging incumbent Greg Abbott in 2022 despite polls suggesting he would win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON workers in Alabama will get another chance to unionize...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/amazon-warehouse-workers-in-alabama-will-get-another-chance-to-vote-to-unionize.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Labor Relations Board has authorized a new union election at one of Amazon's Alabama warehouses, the labor union behind the effort said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Pushes Wildly Different Covid Messages in Same-Day Hits on FOX, CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/rep-nancy-mace-pushes-wildly-different-covid-messages-in-same-day-appearances-on-fox-and-cnn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Nancy Mace (R-SC) made waves on Sunday when discussing Covid-19 in two very different interviews - one on Fox Business Network and the other on CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omar, Boebert blast one another after tense call...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/583426-omar-boebert-blast-one-another-after-tense-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reps. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.) and Lauren Boebert (R-Colo.) clashed in what both described as a tense phone call on Monday after video surfaced of the far-right lawmaker making Islamophobic remarks about her colleague.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes set to take up all-or-nothing abortion fight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-us-supreme-court-voting-rights-samuel-alito-07ecdb3661032c4c6ececd4d07c70655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Both sides are telling the Supreme Court there's no middle ground in Wednesday's showdown over abortion. The justices can either reaffirm the constitutional right to an abortion or wipe it away altogether.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Cuomo used media sources to find info on brother's accusers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/cnn-host-chris-cuomo-used-sources-to-find-info-on-andrew-cuomo-accusers-records.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Cuomo advised a top aide to his brother Andrew Cuomo about reports that detailed alleged sexual harassment by the then-NY governor, new records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Line Up to Be Injected With Illegal 'Homemade' Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyppyy/hundreds-of-people-queue-lubeck-airport-to-receive-unauthorised-winfried-stocker-vaccine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The developer of the unauthorised vaccine is believed to be Winfried Stöcker, a German doctor who also owns an airport, and a department store that featured in “The Grand Budapest Hotel.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credible UFO Reports Ignored, Declassified Canadian Govt Docs Reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dggbx/canada-military-rcaf-ufos-sightings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike in the U.S., UFO reports in Canada pretty much get “shit-canned,” declassified files obtained by Motherboard show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch hotel saga raises quarantine questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211129-dutch-covid-hotel-saga-raises-quarantine-questions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the "Hotel Omicron" in the Netherlands, where a couple of quarantine fugitives have just discovered that you can check out any time you like, but you can't leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jesus Christ Superstar' actor, accused Capitol rioter, claimed 'divine' authority...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/29/politics/january-6-jesus-christ-superstar-sovereign-citizen/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A court hearing for a January 6 defendant quickly turned contentious Monday after an actor and Oath Keeper tried to reject the United States' authority over him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delays federal worker mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/29/politics/federal-workers-vaccine-mandate-holidays/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Office of Management and Budget is telling some agencies they can delay firing federal employees who refuse to get vaccinated until after the holidays, an official confirmed to CNN, as an "education and counseling period" continues in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urges Calm...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/biden-urges-calm-in-the-face-of-omicron-variant-a-cause-for-concern-not-a-cause-for-panic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Monday urged Americans to remain calm as the Omicron variant of Covid-19 threatens to begin a rampage across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nervous Traders Track Gauges...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nervous-traders-track-gauges-markets-164725526.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Friday’s stock-market drubbing reignited coronavirus-related fears for traders. Now, many are taking to reading charts for clues to where prices might settle. Most Read from BloombergChina Cash Flowed Through Congo Bank to Former President’s Cronies‘Pension Poachers’ Are Targeting America’s Elderly VeteransThe two key levels to watch for the S&amp;P 500 are 4,546, which represents the September high before that month’s retreat, and 4,489, which is the redrawn long-term uptrend support</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets face weeks of uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-face-weeks-uncertainty-wait-131238784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The fate of global markets now depends at least in part on laboratories around the world probing the omicron Covid-19 strain, potentially leaving investors with weeks of uncertainty in the wait for answers. Most Read from BloombergChina Cash Flowed Through Congo Bank to Former President’s Cronies‘Pension Poachers’ Are Targeting America’s Elderly VeteransThe variant detected in Africa is described as highly worrying and international travel bans are proliferating. Scientists are an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Kennedy Jr.: Fauci  'Like J. Edgar Hoover'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/11/28/robert_kennedy_jr_on_dr_fauci_like_j_edgar_hoover_carrying_water_for_the_pharmaceutical_industry.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Kennedy Jr. talked about his new book, The Real Anthony Fauci: Bill Gates, Big Pharma, and the Global War on Democracy and Public Health on the Theo Von podcast.  "Under his watch chronic disease has gone from impacting 12% of the American population to 54%. We take more pharmaceutical drugs than anybody in the world and we pay the highest prices. He has made this country a pharmaceutical nation," Kenndy said.  "If you're born after 1989, I think it is 1 in 12" with a food allergy, he said. "It is the same with all these chronic diseases that are all listed as side effects... The Moderna vaccine was completely developed by Tony Fauci. he hands it to a private group, and then they put $2 billion in federal money to allow them to develop it, and then Tony Fauci's agency keeps half the profits from the vaccine. It would be like... if EPA made half of its profits selling coal. It is the same thing. These agencies are not independent agencies, they are completely captured." "All of the other institutions of government that should stand between a greedy corporation and vulnerable child have been compromised."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC start of winter surge?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/new-york-city-may-be-at-start-of-winter-surge-of-covid-19/ar-AARebUc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS BACK ON...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/nyc-reinstitutes-covid-mask-advisory-at-all-times-indoors-regardless-of-vaccination-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City has not identified any cases of omicron so far, according to outgoing Mayor Bill de Blasio and Health Commissioner Dr. David Chokshi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover potential cause of Alzheimer's disease...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-11-scientists-potential-alzheimer-disease.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prevailing theories posit plaques in the brain cause Alzheimer's disease. New UC Riverside research instead points to cells' slowing ability to clean themselves as the likely cause of unhealthy brain buildup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia and West 'one mistake' from nuke conflict, warns admiral...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4165272/russia-nuclear-war-west-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world is “one mistake” from all-out nuclear war thanks to Vladimir Putin’s “dangerous games” in Eastern Europe, warns an ex-Navy chief. Moscow is amassing 100…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters gear up to collect signatures on Michigan petition to decide presidency by popular vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supporters-gear-up-to-collect-signatures-on-petition-to-decide-presidency-by-popular-vote/ar-AARdoC4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames shot hoarding...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/11/27/world/africa/coronavirus-omicron-africa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With countries trying to close their doors to the new coronavirus variant, southern African officials note that the West’s hoarding of vaccines helped create their struggle in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When YOU'RE the Investment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/what-happens-when-you-e2-80-99re-the-investment/ar-AARfQLY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigating antisemitic fliers left at homes in Beverly Hills...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/583334-police-investigating-antisemitic-fliers-left-at-homes-in-beverly-hills</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating antisemitic fliers that were left at homes in Beverly Hills on Sunday, hours before Hanukkah began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Archaeologists Just Find Evidence of Hanukkah Stories?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/did-archaeologists-just-evidence-hanukkah-085147411.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gil Cohen-Magen/AFP via Getty ImagesThis week marks the beginning of Hanukkah, the “festival of lights.” The holiday commemorates an event during the Maccabean revolt in the second century BCE, when the candelabrum in the Jerusalem Temple miraculously burned for eight days despite only having enough oil for one. But Hanukkah isn’t just about energy efficiency; broadly speaking it celebrates the successful struggle for Jewish independence. Now archaeologists have unearthed the charred remains of</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
