<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iawQnzy6xzg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday, November 5, 2018: RSBN's Liz Willis and James Willis will be on hand as President Donald J. Trump holds a campaign style rally at the Show Me Center ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Congress will be younger, more female and more diverse... </title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/11/05/the-next-congress-will-likely-be-younger-more-diverse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The result could be two parties whose image and ideology diverge in powerful ways ahead of the 2020 presidential race, when the increasingly white GOP could face an increasing demographic disadvant…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  LIMBAUGH, TRUMP, CAPE GIRARDEAU... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.kmov.com/news/limbaugh-hannity-to-join-trump-to-campaign-for-hawley-in/article_794ab10e-dbed-11e8-9749-7f62c21f45ca.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kmov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will make a visit to southeast Missouri on November 5, the night before voters in the Show Me State go to the polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  O'Rourke Vs. Cruz; Texas' direction at stake...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2018-elections/2018/11/05/final-sprint-beto-orourke-ted-cruz-texas-direction-stake-trump-minds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON -- With the hours ticking down before polls open on Election Day, the rivals for Texas' coveted U.S. Senate seat made a final pitch to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fractious AZ Senate race heads into final hours...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9716d587ee9a4d79b6a163d887bf5d6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLAGSTAFF, Ariz. (AP) — Republican Rep. Martha McSally barnstormed rural Arizona on Monday while Democratic Rep. Kyrsten Sinema dashed around its urban core in Phoenix as the congresswomen tried to drum up every last vote in the final day of their neck-and-neck U.S. Senate race. The candidates' itinerary and rhetoric was a microcosm of their contest, with McSally trying to keep the state's traditional GOP voters in her column while Sinema tried to cast herself as a nonpartisan problem solver only incidentally attached to the Democratic party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks controversial plan to sterilize wild horses in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/judge-blocks-controversial-plan-sterilize-wild-horses-oregon-n931681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge has temporarily blocked a controversial plan by the Interior Department that would surgically sterilize wild horses in Oregon after animal rights groups filed a lawsuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  ONLY HALF OF AMERICANS HAVE FAITH IN DEMOCRACY...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/poll-americans-faith-in-democracy-2e94a938-4365-4e80-9fb6-d9743d817710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half the country believes America is more divided today than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President regrets tone used during first 2 years...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/nation-world/trump-says-he-regrets-the-tone-he-used-during-first-2-years-in-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Sinclair Broadcast Group) - President Donald Trump said he regrets the tone he has used during his first two years in office during an exclusive interviewÂ with Sinclair Broadcast Group. Video: Sinclair Broadcast Group&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Trump said if there was anything he would try and redo it would be to soften his tone. "I would like to have a much softer tone. I feel to a certain extent I have no choice, but maybe I do," Trump said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump warns of 'fragile' victories in final midterm sprint...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/16fc64a12b3b4a8e84330b04f4d77dc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WAYNE, Ind. (AP) — In his final pitch to voters, President Donald Trump implored Republicans on Monday to help preserve "fragile" GOP victories that could be erased by Democrats as he closes out a midterm campaign that has been defined by his racially charged rhetoric, hard-line immigration moves and scattershot policy proposals. Trump's shadow has hung over the midterm elections that will determine the future of his presidency, with the monthslong fight serving as a testing ground for his nationalist appeals and the strength of the coalition that powered him to the White House two years ago. Acknowledging the stakes in the closing days of campaigning, Trump stressed to voters that everything is on the line when they go to the polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troop Deployment Rises to 8,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/more-than-4-800-troops-are-at-the-border-u-s-says-1541432248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 8,000 American troops will be sent to positions along the U.S.-Mexican border where officials say migrants and asylum seekers are most likely to try to enter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-risk strategy...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-trump-ballot-20181105-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's allies say he's on the ballot — like it or not. So he's decided to own it like few other presidents have. Win or lose, his grip on the GOP will be even tighter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER WILDCARD</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/election-day-2018-midterms-weather-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election Day is poised to bring heavy rain, strong wind gusts and even potential tornadoes to various states across the U.S. where voters will be casting their ballots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Election Needle 'Safety' Features; Nervous Reaction Worries...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/11/the-new-york-times-election-needle-is-back-with-a-few-new-safety-features</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the trauma of November 8, 2016, the Times is taking steps not to trigger its readers—even as it rolls out not one, but two midterm-election needles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercomputer mimics human brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/New-supercomputer-mimics-human-brain-researchers-say/1361541441333/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new supercomputer is able to mimic how the human brain functions, and can perform 200 quadrillion actions simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lasers could be Earth 'porch light' to attract aliens...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-laser-technology-fashioned-earth-porch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If extraterrestrial intelligence exists somewhere in our galaxy, a new MIT study proposes that laser technology on Earth could, in principle, be fashioned into something of a planetary porch light—a beacon strong enough to attract attention from as far as 20,000 light years away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama closes out by talking about himself 89x during campaign stop...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/obama-closes-out-campaign-by-talking-about-himself-89-times-during-chicago-appearance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama is ending the midterm campaign by the way he started: Talking about himself. A lot. During a Sunday appearance in Chicago, the former president referred to himself no fewer than 89 times during a roughly 46-minute speech. ﻿ “First of all, you notice my throat is a little iffy,” Obama began, lamenting about …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>101 captured Orcas, Belugas held in 'whale jail'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/05/russia-investigating-whale-jail-holding-101-captured-orcas-belugas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors are investigating whether more than 100 whales crowded into tiny enclosures on Russia's Pacific Coast are being held illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potent storm to blast eastern US...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/05/election-day-weather-forecast-big-storm-blast-eastern-us/1891149002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A potent Election Day storm is forecast to blast the eastern U.S. with rain, winds and thunderstorms. Rain tends to favor Republican candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music exec survives 200ft plunge onto jagged rocks!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7659021/music-executive-survived-200ft-plunge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOP music boss survived a 200ft plunge on to jagged rocks after he lost his footing on a clifftop. Andy Godfrey, 60, broke his back and breast bone, fractured his skull and cracked all of his rib…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For trans candidate, fight on many levels in Vermont...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/11/04/for-christine-hallquist-fight-many-levels-vermont/ha8WquAv6CaWlNnOU1UsQM/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s first transgender gubernatorial finalist is battling more than prejudice and ignorance. She’s up against the power of incumbency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crown Prince launches first Saudi nuclear plant project...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/bin-salman-launches-saudi-arabia-nuclear-plant-project-181105192827938.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman launches project to build the first nuclear research reactor in the kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pamela Anderson: #MeToo 'bore', feminism can go too far...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/05/pamela-anderson-calls-metoo-movement-a-bore-urges-common-sense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I think this feminism can go too far,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family shocked as 'dead' relative returns home months after funeral...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/05/dead-man-shocks-family-by-returning-home-two-months-after-his-funeral-8107876/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He took up a short-term job at a far away farm without telling his relatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Cars to Talk to One Another...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/nyc-cars-to-talk-to-one-another-under-traffic-safety-pilot-program-1541452455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of a $25 million pilot program, 8,000 vehicles in New York will be outfitted with special devices that can communicate with one another, as well as with roadside sensors, traffic signals and app-enabled smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic at standstill, postal worker goes rogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/article221159320.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video of a U.S. postal truck tearing down a road off a Miami highway has gone viral since a humorous Facebook page posted it last week. The clip had over 1 million views since Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka Rallies Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://fox8.com/2018/11/05/president-trump-campaigns-in-cleveland-ahead-of-election-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND-- President Donald Trump was in Cleveland on Monday as voters prepare to head to the polls. He was joined by his daughter and White House adviser Ivanka Trump and spoke about Republican candidates in the state Ohio while at the I-X Center. Trump attacked Democratic candidate for governor Richard Cordray, calling him a bad person and a disgrace, before bringing up Ohio Attorney General Mike DeWine to speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDER ARMOUR #MeToo Moment: No More Strip Clubs on Company Dime...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/under-armours-metoo-moment-no-more-strip-clubs-on-company-dime-1541450209</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under Armour employees received an email earlier this year that upended a longstanding company practice: They could no longer charge visits to strip clubs on their corporate cards. Strip-club visits were symptomatic of practices women at Under Armour found demeaning, current and former employees say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Dog Dies Trying To Protect Woman From Assault...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/05/family-dog-dies-trying-to-protect-woman-from-assault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 24-year-old man was arrested for assault and animal cruelty after he allegedly stabbed and killed a dog and injured its owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailers order trans woman to show genitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/courts/2018/11/05/dallas-jailers-ordered-transgenderwoman-show-genitals-lawsuit-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transgender woman has filed a federal lawsuit against Dallas County alleging jailers ordered her to show her genitalia to them so they could...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Handler Gets Naked to Urge America to 'Vote'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/11/05/chelsea-handler-posts-nude-video-promote-voting-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian and left-wing activist Chelsea Handler stripped nude to promote voting in Tuesday's midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsavory dilemma for NJ...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/jersey-democrats-face-unsavory-vote-dilemma-200251505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Re-electing a Democrat tainted by corruption allegations or allowing a safe seat to flip for Donald Trump? Party leaders are urging Democratic faithful to sacrifice their principles for the greater good of thrashing the Republican president at the polls and re-elect Senator Bob Menendez, who last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes decline to take on net neutrality...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/05/supreme-court-declines-to-take-on-net-neutrality-challenges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a setback for industry groups, the U.S. Supreme Court on Monday declined to hear a number of challenges to Obama-era "net neutrality" regulations that barred internet service providers from giving certain customers preferential treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting problems persist...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-election-systems-more-secure-voting-problems-persist-193214442--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday's midterm elections will mark the first nationwide voting since Russia targeted state election systems in the 2016 presidential race, with federal, state and local officials seeking to reassure the public their voting systems are secure. There have been no signs so far that Russia or any</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ deploys election monitors to 35 districts, 19 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/livecoverage/2018-midterms-live-elections-coverage-analysis/card/1541447566</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Justice Department said Monday that it will send election observers to polling stations across the country this week to ensure that federal electi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to Split HQ2 Evenly Between Two Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/amazon-plans-to-split-hq2-evenly-between-two-cities-1541446552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com plans to split its second headquarters evenly between two locations rather than picking one city for HQ2, a surprise decision that will spread the impact of a massive new office across two communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEINEKEN seals $3bn deal with top China brewer...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181105-heineken-seals-3-bn-deal-with-chinas-top-brewer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Jews contact gun-training academy after Pittsburgh attack...</title>
      <link>http://observers.france24.com/en/20181102-jews-pittsburgh-synagogue-attack-firearms-guns-training</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observers.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow international news through our Observers' amateur images and eyewitness testimony. All the content is verified and explained by our journalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine Gov Announces Move To Florida: 'No Income Tax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/11/05/lepage-says-hes-moving-to-florida-and-may-take-a-teaching-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two-term governor wouldn't say where he might teach, but he indicated he would become a Florida resident because the state has no income tax and low property taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant caravan pushes on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb335ceae7444924b97db378ed1f11b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Thousands of exhausted migrants from the Central American caravan trudged along highways Monday toward Mexico City, where officials prepared a sports stadium to accommodate them as they try to reach the U.S. border still hundreds of miles away. The first wave of more than 500 migrants spent Sunday night on concrete benches at the Jesus Martinez stadium, where they were served hot meals as authorities prepared to receive as many as 5,000 migrants from the lead caravan and several smaller ones hundreds of miles behind it. Nashieli Ramirez, ombudsman for the city's human rights commission, said the migrants would be able to stay at the stadium as long as necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller To Pick Up Pace...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/05/mueller-midterms-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speculation builds that Mueller will issue indictments soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer hunters trying to feed the hungry...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/special-reports/food-story/article221025890.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in seven Georgians struggles with hunger, and about 500,000 children are food insecure. Georgia Hunters for the Hungry provides donated venison to food pantries and soup kitchen across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICA DIVIDED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/464f27b585d34fc597884d88d8ab10af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — Michael Gregoire marched along a downtown sidewalk in the tense days before the midterm elections, waving a hand-painted sign at passing traffic: "DEFEAT REPUBLICANS 2018." "The survival of the country is going to depend on this election," he said as another man stopped for a moment to argue. The strangers faced each other from opposite edges of the great American divide, Democrat versus Republican, both convinced the election is among the most consequential in their lifetimes and that they must save the nation from the other side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With smartphones everywhere, workers baffled by work telephones...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/its-giant-and-has-like-five-million-buttons-the-office-desk-phone-wont-die-1541432514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With iPhones everywhere, workers are increasingly baffled by their telephones at work—if they can figure out how to operate them at all; the problem of ‘that curly cord.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fighter jet intercepts US Navy plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/05/politics/russian-fighter-jet-intercepts-us-navy-plane/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US Navy reconnaissance aircraft flying in international airspace over the Black Sea was intercepted by a Russian fighter jet Monday in an unsafe and unprofessional manner, according to three US defense officials and a statement from the Navy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS, NBC Pull Controversial Campaign Ad on Caravan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/05/media/nbc-trump-immigration-ad/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC and Fox News said in separate statements on Monday that their networks will no longer air the Trump campaign's racist anti-immigrant advertisement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis tied to serious diabetes complications...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cannabis-tied-serious-type-1-diabetes-complications-172010645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers surveyed 450 patients with type 1 diabetes in Colorado, where cannabis is legal for medical and recreational use. Compared to nonusers, cannabis users had about twice the risk of experiencing a serious complication known as diabetic ketoacidosis, which develops when blood sugar is elevated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left Eyes Dozen New Govs...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/the-run/articles/2018-11-05/election-2018-democrats-eye-a-dozen-governors-races</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S sent worker home for being late -- so he robbed another MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article221136825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Gomez-Beltran, 19, is charged with robbery after deputies in San Antonio say he robbed another McDonald’s after the location he worked at sent him home for being late for work on his first day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE enlists NASA to help it prove quantum supremacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612381/google-has-enlisted-nasa-to-help-it-prove-quantum-supremacy-within-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The firm will pit its Bristlecone quantum processor against a classical supercomputer early next year and see which comes out on top.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail bomb suspect's mother wants country, Trump to tone down rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/raised-mother-mail-bombing-suspect-cesar-sayoc-wrote/story?id=58963938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madeline Sayoc said her son has been "ill for a long time" and asked politicians to refrain from using rhetoric to incite violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE VERDICT</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-democrats-frenzied-final-push-ahead-us-elections-224442883.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's whirlwind campaign hits three states Monday in the final effort to stop Democrats from breaking his Republicans' stranglehold on Congress in midterms elections seen as a referendum on the most divisive US president in decades. Trump is not on the ballot in the midterms, which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT DEADLINE LOOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2018/11/05/brexit-where-negotiations-stand-deal-deadline-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the March 2019 deadline for Brexit looming, Prime Minister Theresa May will have to clinch a deal -- or not -- with the EU soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Time to learn to get along with robot co-workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/business/2018/11/04/hey-robot-that-report-ready/LrGEKOLaBJB50MA8tzTXbP/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Machines will inevitably displace some workers, but they will also increasingly be working alongside us, elevating humans into higher-level roles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election test: Movement or moment...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-supporters-elections-battle-vision-america-111050368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He is putting people back to work," said Barbara Peacock, 58, a retired postal worker from Macon, Georgia, as she perused Trump 2020 merchandise. "He is telling it like it is." At rallies overflowing with red-hatted, mostly white supporters in conservative pockets of the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuses Israel of failed cyber attack...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/iran-accuses-israel-failed-cyber-attack-132934741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's telecommunications minister accused Israel on Monday of a new cyber attack on its telecommunications infrastructure, and vowed to respond with legal action. This followed comments from another official last week that Iran had uncovered a new generation of Stuxnet, a virus which was used against</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot economy is cold comfort in tight races...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/hot-economy-cold-comfort-republicans-tight-u-races-130526395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead, the retired teacher says she is "at a loss" deciding who she will vote for in this week's election because of Trump's "deplorable" character. "After this, I might just be a plain old independent." Trump has wagered big that a nearly $1.8-trillion blast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLSTERS CLUELESS?</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/us-politics/la-na-pol-usc-latimes-poll-20181105-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final results from the USC-Los Angeles Times tracking poll show Democrats continuing to hold a hefty lead in voter preferences for Congress. But what are the X factors that could upset expectations for the race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Burst of Polio-Like Cases in Children Alarms Doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/another-burst-of-polio-like-cases-in-children-alarms-doctors-1541432122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The condition, known as AFM, has jumped onto the national radar. Researchers are struggling to explain its third nationwide peak since 2014, and families are trying to provide hope to children hit with the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of seats remain empty as NFL season enters second half...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2018/11/04/weak-9-thousands-of-empty-seats-remain-as-nfl-starts-second-half-of-the-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the National Football League now entering the second half of the 2018 season, some teams are still not drawing fans to the stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 MILLION ALREADY VOTED IN TX...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6e7994936094d9ba46baa1510cad6b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Republican Sen. Ted Cruz and Democratic Congressman Beto O'Rourke are working their way home at the end of one of the most closely watched races of the 2018 midterms. Cruz's last rally Monday is set near his hometown of Houston. O'Rourke is heading to El Paso to finish an underdog campaign that drew national attention and took him through each of Texas' 254 counties. Polls show a surprisingly tight race in Texas heading into Tuesday's midterm elections. It's the most competitive U.S. Senate race in a generation in Texas, where Democrats have been shut out of statewide office since the 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran president warns of 'war situation' as sanctions resume...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4e22aa017d524490af8ed2b3dfca13f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran greeted the re-imposition of U.S. sanctions on Monday with air defense drills and a statement from President Hassan Rouhani that the nation faces a "war situation," raising Mideast tensions as America's maximalist approach to the Islamic Republic takes hold. The sanctions end all economic benefits America had granted Tehran for its 2015 nuclear deal with world powers, though Iran for now continues to abide by the accord that saw it limit its enrichment of uranium. While at the moment not threatening to resume higher enrichment, Iranian officials in recent months have made a point to warn the controversial process could resume at any time, faster than before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICA DIVIDED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/45c16428c1ea41a9b7f7e087498d312e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The day of reckoning for American politics has nearly arrived. Voters on Tuesday will decide the $5 billion debate between President Donald Trump's take-no-prisoner politics and the Democratic Party's super-charged campaign to end the GOP's monopoly in Washington and statehouses across the nation. There are indications that an oft-discussed "blue wave" may help Democrats seize control of at least one chamber of Congress. But two years after an election that proved polls and prognosticators wrong, nothing is certain on the eve of the first nationwide elections of the Trump presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCK OFF:  FACEBOOK feature could suggest friends by TRACKING who you stand near...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7664071/facebook-track-feature-creepy-patent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK has invented a creepy system that suggests new friends based on who you’ve stood near to. The social network could use the feature to match you up with people on the train, in your o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO:  House Republicans in panic mode...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/04/trump-2018-elections-midterms-republicans-immigration-960748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worries deepen that Trump's charged immigration rhetoric will cost the GOP more seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Pulls Controversial Trump Campaign Ad on Caravan...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/nbcuniversal-trump-campaign-ad-sunday-night-football-1203019655/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBCUniversal is pulling a controversial Trump campaign commercial from rotation on its networks after the ad sparked criticism while appearing during “Sunday Night Football.” Both Judd …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the police droids...</title>
      <link>https://www.deccanchronicle.com/nation/current-affairs/051118/rise-of-the-police-robots.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deccanchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hyderabad has launched the country’s first smart policing robot called the smart Robocop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial begins for cartel kingpin...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181105-usa-justice-massive-drug-trafficking-trial-begins-el-chapo-joaquin-guzman-new-york-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman goes on trial in New York on Monday, accused of running the world’s biggest drug cartel and spending a quarter of a century smuggling more than 155 tons of cocaine into the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make-or-break program sends pandas back into wild in bid to prevent extinction...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/china-s-make-or-break-program-sends-pandas-back-into/article_249a17ae-9db1-5473-ad62-e2d062b27e97.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING — The panda cub snuffles, stretches out a tiny paw and snuggles with his mother, Cao Cao. She stirs, sniffs him gently and gives him a lick as they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Partner Consolidates Empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/billionaire-partner-of-imprisoned-el-chapo-consolidates-empire#gs.zcTk1u4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Partner of Imprisoned El Chapo Consolidates Empire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polio-like illness on rise again. But why?</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/health/polio-like-acute-flaccid-myelitis-virus-cdc-chop-20181105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far this year, 72 children have suffered from sudden muscle weakness or paralysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami runs out of ballots!</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/election/article221127195.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Printers fail at the North Miami early-voting site, causing long lines, voters reporting waits topping three hours, and poll workers briefly running out of ballots for nearby precincts. Miami-Dade seeing record early voting for a mid-term election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems betting Gillum historic candidacy can change Florida electorate...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/5/18052008/florida-governor-andrew-gillum-demographics-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why Democrats are growing more optimistic that the blue wave will sweep Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxer, 49, Dies After Knockout Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.boxingscene.com/boxer-49-years-old-passes-away-knockout-loss--133416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boxingscene.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian boxer Christian Daghio, who was very popular in Thailand after moving there a decade ago, has passed away at the age of 49-years-old after suffering a bad knockout loss at the hands of Don Pareuang in twelfth round of their bout for the vacant WBC Asian Boxing Council silver light heavyweight title.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK SHIFTS 9 TO DEMS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/414863-cook-political-report-shifts-10-house-race-ratings-one-day-before-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nonpartisan Cook Political Report shifted 9 House races toward Democrats in a new forecast published Monday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Sets Another NFL Record After Out-Dueling Rodgers On Sunday Night Football...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/05/tom-brady-sets-new-nfl-record-passing-peyton-manning-most-all-time-yards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another week, another all-time NFL record for Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: iPhone Owners Happier, Have More Money, Friends Than ANDROID Users...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-iphone-owners-happier-more-money-friends-android/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are iPhones better than Android phones? That's a question many technophiles could spend hours debating, but a new study shows you may be better off just being an iPhone owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm donor fathers 24 kids in 12 months...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7612979/i-sold-my-sperm-for-quick-cash-when-i-was-skint-now-ive-got-24-kids-meet-the-57-year-old-sperm-donor-who-believes-he-could-have-hundreds-of-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEN Peter Ellenstein received a Facebook message from a young woman he didn’t recognise in 2016, he did not expect to open it and find out she was his daughter. Nor could he have possibly im…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll crush replicas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/740553/sex-doll-replicas-crush-copies-women-they-fancy-video-real</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOWE'S to close 51 stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/lowes-to-close-51-stores-including-20-in-the-us-2018-11-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intruder tried to break in to embassy to kidnap Assange, claims legal team...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6353833/Break-attempt-Julian-Assanges-residence-Ecuadorian-Embassy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WikiLeaks founder (pictured) was woken up in the night after an alleged intruder attempted to enter a window at the front of the embassy building in Knightsbridge, west London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stockman believes 40% market downturn he's long predicted has finally arrived...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/03/david-stockman-epic-downturn-is-here-brace-for-40percent-market-plunge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Reagan's OMB director warns a recession is closing in on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Administration prepares for massive shake-up after midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-administration-prepares-for-massive-13362905.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Trump administration is bracing for a massive staff shake-up in the weeks following the midterm elections, as the fates of a number of Cabinet secretaries and top White House aides are increasingly uncertain heading into a potentially perilous time for President Donald Trump. Some embattled officials, including Attorney General Jeff Sessions, are expected to be fired or actively pushed out by Trump after months of bitter recriminations. Others, like Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen, may leave amid a mutual recognition that their relationship with the president has become too strained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Bomber Makes Provocative Flyover Of U.S. Command Ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-03/russian-bomber-conducts-provocative-flyover-us-command-ship-during-trident-juncture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish Nurse Who Treated Synagogue Shooter Opens Up...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/11/04/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooting-jewish-nurse-treated-robert-bowers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jewish nurse who treated Pittsburgh synagogue shooting suspect Robert Bowers when he arrived at the hospital is telling his side of the story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy told to clean room shoots grandmother, kills self...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/southwest-valley-breaking/2018/11/04/mcso-11-year-old-shoots-grandmother-yvonne-woodard-before-killing-self/1886514002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An MCSO spokesman said 65-year-old Yvonne Woodard had asked the grandson to clean his room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another SoCal home-price boom cooling. Crash looming?</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-housing-busts-20181104-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The housing market is slowing down, leading many would-be buyers to ponder if a crash is on the horizon. The history of Southern California housing booms is that they build steadily and end suddenly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pow! 'Good Guy' Superheroes Engage In More Violence Than Evil Enemies...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/superheroes-engage-more-violence-than-evil-enemies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your favorite superheroes may put their lives on the line to rid the world of evil, but they might not be the great role models for young children that they're often made out to be, it seems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOM FORD manager said she 'needed sex for breakfast, lunch and dinner': suit...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/04/tom-ford-manager-said-she-needed-sex-for-breakfast-lunch-and-dinner-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seamstress for famed fashion designer Tom Ford says one of her bosses over-shared about her favorite accessory — sex toys — while boasting that she “needed sex for breakfast, lunch and dinner.” Y…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I killed soccer star and cut off genitals for raping wife'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/04/i-mutilated-nearly-beheaded-soccer-star-for-raping-my-wife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The businessman who allegedly killed Brazilian soccer player Daniel Correa Freitas says he did so after finding the midfielder in his underwear trying to rape his wife. The Sao Paulo star’s b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Boogeyman May Come for Bonds, Not Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/market-boogeyman-may-come-for-bonds-not-stocks-1541419320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Risk-parity funds are often cited as culprits during stock selloffs like the recent one. In this case, though, the worry should be in bonds, not stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Georgia, 11th-hour daggers over voting system...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/business/technology/article221117220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest indication of poor management of Georgia's secretary of state's office, run by Republican gubernatorial candidate Brian Kemp, follows a citizen's tip that the voter registration system used for Tuesday's election may be vulnerable to hackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Rouhani Promises Iran Will 'Break' New U.S. Sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/iranian-president-promises-to-break-new-u-s-sanctions-1541413178 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani vowed that his country would resist tough new U.S. sanctions on Iran’s oil and banks, as Tehran braced for a new era of political and economic isolation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancels production boost...</title>
      <link>https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Companies/Apple-cancels-production-boost-for-budget-iPhone-XR-sources</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;asia.nikkei.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dimmer outlook for new model contrasts with extra orders for older versions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTIES BRACE FOR SURPRISES</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/midterm-campaign-down-to-wire-as-two-parties-brace-for-surprises#gs.uoc8cNY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A split verdict would hand the House to Democrats, leave Republicans holding onto or expanding their Senate majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Citizens Replacing Teens at Fast-Food Joints...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/senior-citizens-are-replacing-teenagers-at-fast-food-joints</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Citizens Are Replacing Teenagers atÂ Fast-Food Joints</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diddy to headline Gillum rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/414828-diddy-to-headline-gillum-rally-monday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean "Diddy" Combs will headline a rally for Andrew Gillum's Florida governor campaign midnight Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top Senate seats most likely to flip...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/414658-the-top-senate-seats-most-likely-to-flip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans believe they are on the cusp of increasing their majority in the midterm elections despite historic headwinds that seem likely to cost the GOP control of the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. Emerges as GOP 'Relief Pitcher'...</title>
      <link>https://lasvegasnews.media/donald-trump-jr-emerges-as-the-g-o-p-relief-pitcher-of-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lasvegasnews.media&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force falcon expected to recover from 'life-threatening' injuries after West Point prank...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/military/west-point-apologizes-for-falcon-s-injuries-air-force-academy/article_5e36d640-e070-11e8-8c47-97fe443c471f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army’s military academy issued an apology Sunday for an apparent prank in which a live Air Force mascot falcon was abducted and injured ahead of this weekend’s Army-Air Force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Farrakhan Leads 'Death to America' Chant in Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.algemeiner.com/2018/11/04/renowned-antisemite-louis-farrakhan-chants-death-to-america-on-solidarity-trip-to-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.algemeiner.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Midterm like no other in generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/This-midterm-election-is-like-no-other-in-a-13362028.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday's midterm election is about many things. It's about health care and immigration. It's about the economy. It's about power and who will hold it, both in Washington and in the states. Above all, it's about something more elemental: what kind of country Americans see today and want to see in the future. That makes these midterms unlike any in the recent past. Talk to voters almost anywhere about what this election means to them, and the answer almost invariably involves personal feelings about President Donald Trump and perceptions about the overall state of the country. This debate about America's divisions has been underway for some time, but Trump has raised the emotional level to something not seen before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influx of tech companies pushes Bay Area residents to breaking point...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-East-Palo-Alto-the-influx-of-tech-companies-13361661.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST PALO ALTO, Calif. - This poor city is surrounded by the temples of the new American economy that has, in nearly every way imaginable, passed it by. Just outside the northern city limit, Facebook is expanding the blocks-long headquarters it built seven years ago. Google's offices sit just outside the southern edge, and just a few miles to the west, Stanford University stands as the rich proving ground of the economy's future. Amazon just moved in. Only a small fraction of jobs in those companies go to those who live in this city of 30,000 people, one of the region's few whose population is majority minority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experiment plays music -- to cheese -- to improve taste...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.ch/20181102/swiss-cheese-maker-experiments-with-music-to-increase-taste-led-zeppelin-a-tribe-called-quest-emmental-bern-university</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When searching a fromagerie for the perfect chunk of cheddar or parmesan, cheese aficionados have probably never grilled vendors over what kind of music was played to their cheeses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants camped at border worry caravans will shut them out...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f4d231f3a56c4156a06650245215f92d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MATAMOROS, Mexico (AP) — Waiting on the southern end of a bridge that leads to the United States, Humberto Alvarez Gonzalez warily follows the progress of the caravan winding through Mexico with the goal of reaching the border. Alvarez and about two dozen other people are waiting in Matamoros, across the Rio Grande from Brownsville, Texas, because U.S. customs officers say there's no space to process them. They sleep on cots near the bridge and rely on donors who bring them food and clothing. Some have waited for two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Buffett takes musical shots at Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-wpb-buffett-political-rally-20181103-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida music legend Jimmy Buffett supported the Sunshine State’s Democratic ticket in West Palm Beach Saturday, performing a free concert and changing lyrics to take shots at Gov. Rick Scott and President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Marchers Chant 'Death To America' On Sanctions Eve...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-oil-sanctions-iranian-marchers-chant-death-to-america-on-eve-of-us-oil-sanctions-1942828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Iranians chanting "Death to America" rallied on Sunday to mark the anniversary of the seizure of the U.S. Embassy during the 1979 Islamic Revolution and the imminent reimposition of U.S. sanctions on Iran's oil sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate: 'Demanding apology culture' not healthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/dan-crenshaw-doesnt-think-snls-pete-davidson-owes-him-an-apology-we-dont-need-to-be-outwardly-outraged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
