<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro's erratic behavior making his military backers nervous...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/bolsonaro-s-erratic-behavior-is-making-his-military-backers-nervous/story-M672ojEcMf5rchNTHh6AzH.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over a third of Bolsonaro’s cabinet hails from the military, which now plays a greater role in government than at any other time since Brazil’s brutal dictatorship ended in the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT plan for preserving union: Drive Trump out by driving him nuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/The-Lincoln-Project-s-plan-for-preserving-the-15451080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your house is on fire. Do you care who the firemen are?  That is a central question of the 2020 election. Donald Trump has managed to do one thing no other president has done: Bring Republicans and Democrats, conservatives and progressives, boomers and millennials together in unprecedented numbers to try to defeat him in November. For Americans who believe the president is a raging threat to democracy, purity tests are out. Results are in.  Which explains the spectacular rise of the Lincoln Project, a group of Republican Never Trumpers who have moved rent free into the president's head. Their viral videos and tweets mocking his leadership, his intelligence and his patriotism - aimed both at Republican voters who are waveringand Trump himself - have attracted millions of dollars, via donors from both parties. More than 10,000 people showed up for a virtual town hall last month. Lifelong Democrats are organizing fundraisers for the project.  The "Mourning in America" ad attacks Trump's mismanagement of the coronavirus outbreak. "#TrumpIsNotWell" questions his mental and physical fitness. "Bounty" asks why Trump won't confront Vladimir Putin about U.S. intelligence reports that Russia offered bounties for the killing of American soldiers in Afghanistan.  The ads are slick, scathing and more shocking than anything Joe Biden's official campaign has produced. The newest release, "Wake Up," is a dark comic satire about a coma victim hearing about Trump's last three years. "Republicans, we need to wake up. This guy was in a coma. What's your excuse?"  "Donald Trump is so completely at odds with every institution in America and so completely at odds with anything that the Republican Party allegedly stood for: the rule of law, constitutional fealty, institutions, norms, traditions, all of those things are out the window," says...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Ellen telling execs she's had enough, ready to quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8581717/Ellen-DeGeneres-telling-executives-shes-ready-call-quits.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com can reveal that the host is telling executives at Telepictures and Warner Bros that she has had enough and wants to walk away from the show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Trump says he will ban TIKTOK through executive action...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/31/trump-says-he-will-ban-tiktok-through-executive-action-as-soon-as-saturday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Friday told reporters he will act as soon as Saturday to ban Chinese-owned video app TikTok from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Ply With Alternatives to Kamala...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/democrats-ply-biden-with-alternatives-to-harris-for-running-mate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Ply Biden With Alternatives to Harris for Running Mate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coin Shortages Causing Liquidity Crisis at Laundromats...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/coin-shortage-u-s-laundromats-are-running-out-of-quarters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coin Shortages Are Causing a Liquidity Crisis at Laundromats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors ask for Depardieu rape case to be reopened...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/prosecutors-ask-depardieu-rape-case-reopened-102455010.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris prosecutors said Saturday they had asked for an investigation into rape allegations against French actor Gerard Depardieu to be reopened after an earlier probe was dropped last year. An actress in her 20s accuses Depardieu of assaulting and raping her in his Paris home in August 2018. After she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia preparing mass vaccination for October...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801080054-o9lpq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RUSSIA-VACCINE (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Russia preparing mass vaccination against coronavirus for October</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hear What Was Once Impossible? Musk's Mysterious Brain Chip...</title>
      <link>https://www.techtimes.com/articles/251499/20200801/elon-musks-mysterious-neuralink-chip-could-apparently-make-you-hear-things-that-were-impossible-to-hear-before.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What sounds exactly?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data isn't just being collected from phone. It's being used to score you...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/opinion/article/Data-isn-t-just-being-collected-from-your-phone-15449776.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operating in the shadows of the online marketplace, specialized tech companies you've likely never heard of are tapping vast troves of our personal data to generate secret "surveillance scores" - digital mug shots of millions of Americans - that supposedly predict our future behavior. The firms sell their scoring services to major businesses across the U.S. economy.  People with low scores can suffer harsh consequences.  CoreLogic and TransUnion say that scores they peddle to landlords can predict whether a potential tenant will pay the rent on time, be able to "absorb rent increases," or break a lease. Large employers use HireVue, a firm that generates an "employability" score about candidates by analyzing "tens of thousands of factors," including a person's facial expressions and voice intonations. Other employers use Cornerstone's score, which considers where a job prospect lives and which web browser they use to judge how successful they will be at a job.  Brand-name retailers purchase "risk scores" from Retail Equation to help make judgments about whether consumers commit fraud when they return goods for refunds. Players in the gig economy use outside firms such as Sift to score consumers' "overall trustworthiness." Wireless customers predicted to be less profitable are sometimes forced to endure longer customer service hold times.  Auto insurers raise premiums based on scores calculated using information from smartphone apps that track driving styles. Large analytics firms monitor whether we are likely to take our medication based on our propensity to refill our prescriptions; pharmaceutical companies, health-care providers and insurance companies can use those scores to, among other things, "match the right patient investment level to the right patients."  Surveillance scoring is the product of two trends. First...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASHES BAHAMAS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hurricane-isaias-strengthens-slightly-bears-084643752.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isaias was carrying top sustained winds of 85 mph (140 kph) and was located about 80 miles (125 km) south-southeast of the Bahamas capital Nassau at 5 a.m. (0900 GMT) heading northwest, the National Hurricane Center said. Its center was approaching Andros Island in the Bahamas and was due to pass over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest in Berlin against virus restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ef70c1af702b89c23e71fcd843e63293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Thousands of protesters against German coronavirus restrictions converged Saturday in Berlin for a demonstration proclaiming “the end of the pandemic” has arrived just as authorities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver Stone thinks he would be 'vilified' if he tried to make his films today amid 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-8579055/Oliver-Stone-thinks-villified-tried-make-films-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Oliver Stone revealed in a recent interview that he thinks he would be 'vilified' if his were released today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 25,000 deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801004545-71yqc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-JULY (UPDATE 1, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 1-U.S. records over 25,000 coronavirus deaths in July</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida record high for fourth straight day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801002615-f2jqo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-RECORDS (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-California, Florida report record increases in COVID-19 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico eclipses Britain with third highest death toll...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200801001214-yr80u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/LATAM (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-Mexico eclipses Britain with third highest coronavirus death toll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JmLUULS9ja8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts do NOT ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Acted Like the Virus Had Gone. Now It's Spread Everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/japan-acted-like-the-virus-had-gone-now-it-e2-80-99s-spread-everywhere/ar-BB17qNQd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland Security' had access to messages from Portland protesters, document shows... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/DHS-had-access-to-messages-from-Portland-15450458.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Department of Homeland Security official told a Senate committee earlier this month that the department had not collected, exploited or analyzed information from the electronic devices or accounts of protesters in Portland, Ore.  But an internal DHS document obtained by The Washington Post shows the department did have access to protesters' electronic messages and that their conversations were written up in an "intelligence report" that was disseminated to federal law enforcement agencies, including the FBI, as well as state and local governments.  In a letter sent Friday, Democratic members of the Senate Intelligence Committee asked Brian Murphy, acting DHS undersecretary for intelligence and analysis, about statements he made to committee staff on July 23 regarding the department's intelligence activities in Portland.  "You stated that I &amp; A [the intelligence and analysis office] had neither collected nor exploited or analyzed information obtained from the devices or accounts of protesters or detainees. Please confirm," the senators wrote.  A DHS Open Source Intelligence Report dated six days before Murphy's briefing to the committee shows that the I &amp; A office analyzed messages that protesters exchanged on the Telegram messaging app. They discussed which routes to take during marches and how to avoid the police.  The report describes the messages as "likely Portland-based encrypted messaging app users discuss TTPs [tactics, techniques and procedures] to evade law enforcement when being pursued." It also states that the information came from "a Telegram chat room," which it described as "an instant messaging service."  It's not clear how DHS obtained the messages and whether an informant or undercover officer had access to the Telegram group. Some officials familiar with the report, who spoke on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovered Bolsonaro says nothing to fear...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/recovered-virus-bolsonaro-says-nothing-fear-001111535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh off a bout of COVID-19, President Jair Bolsonaro said Friday nearly everyone will probably end up catching the new coronavirus, urging Brazilians to "face up to it" and saying there was nothing to fear. "I'm in the high-risk group," the 65-year-old president told journalists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Jumbo Jets Are Heading for the Boneyard...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-jumbo-jets-heading-boneyard-000002240.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The queens of the skies have fallen on hard times.As Covid-19 has frozen the international travel on which they once thrived, double-decker, four-engine planes like the Airbus SE A380 and Boeing Co. 747 are more likely to be found in storage than soaring through the skies.Carriers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNHAM:  MY COVID HELL...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/lena-dunham-talks-covid-19-on-instagram-1203001407/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add Lena Dunham to the growing list of celebrities who have contracted COVID-19. The Girls creator and star shared on Instagram that she contracted the virus in mid-March. Her “Covid Story,” as she…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. outlook revised to negative from stable by FITCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/united-states-outlook-revised-to-negative-from-stable-by-fitch/ar-BB17qy05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden likely to name his running mate in second week of August... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-likely-to-name-his-running-mate-in-second-15450249.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden will most likely announce his running mate in the second week of August, again breaking a self-imposed deadline for unveiling the choice, according to two people familiar with his plans.  Biden, the presumptive Democratic presidential nominee, initially said he'd select his running mate by Aug. 1. Then on Tuesday, he told reporters that he intended to make up his mind by the end of the first week of August, which would be Aug. 8.  "I'm going to have a choice in the first week in August," he said, "and I promise I'll let you know when I do."  But Friday, two people familiar with Biden's vice-presidential search process said the announcement is not likely to come next week.  There are political reasons for Biden to unveil the pick relatively shortly before the Aug. 17 kickoff of the Democratic National Convention, since that timing could add some excitement to the gathering while minimizing the opportunity for Republican attacks. Some Biden allies have been urging him to make the announcement around Aug. 10.  The former vice president has said he will pick a woman to be his running mate. He's also said that he's vetting four Black women for the role, and those close to the campaign say the list includes Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif.; former national security adviser Susan Rice; Rep. Karen Bass, D-Calif.; and Rep. Val Demings, D-Fla. Sen. Tammy Duckworth, D-Ill., confirmed Thursday that she's been vetted.  Others believed to be in contention are Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., who has become an informal economic policy adviser to Biden in recent months, and Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer.  Making the announcement just a few days before the convention would allow Biden to build buzz for the party's quadrennial meeting, with less time for the Trump campaign to define...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major League Baseball Tells Players Union Season Is On Brink... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/31/mlb-facing-shutdown-if-coronavirus-spread-cant-be-contained/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commissioner Rob Manfred reached out Friday to union executive director Tony Clark to urge that a redoubling of efforts to adhere to COVID-19 safety and health protocols is necessary or shutting do…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight still missing after US Marine amphibious vehicle sinks... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eight-still-missing-us-marine-amphibious-vehicle-sinks-232242800.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight military personnel remained missing at sea Friday nearly a full day after a US Marine amphibious assault vehicle sank in deep water off the California coast during training exercises. Officials at Camp Pendleton in southern California said that one of eight Marines rescued in the mishap off the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dershowitz Goes To War With CBS Over Connections...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-alan-dershowitz-good-fight-lawsuit-viacomcbs-1203001249/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite having the Oscar-winning Reversal of Fortune made from his book of the same name, it seems Alan Dershowitz this week had the difference between fact and fiction painstakingly explained to h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden likely to name his running mate in second week of August... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/biden-likely-to-name-his-running-mate-in-second-week-of-august/2020/07/31/38dd92c2-d366-11ea-9038-af089b63ac21_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden first said he would reveal his pick by Aug. 1, then by Aug. 8. Now the announcement is likely to come later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Murdoch Resigns From NEWSCORP Board...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/james-murdoch-resigns-from-news-corp-board-over-editorial-disagreements</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Mr. Murdoch informed the Company that his resignation was due to disagreements over certain editorial content,” a statement said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JULY WORST MONTH FOR COVID HOSPITALIZATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1289327679666188288?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many People Hospitalized? Who Knows?</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/how-many-people-in-the-us-are-hospitalized-with-covid-19-who-knows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration told hospitals to stop reporting data to the CDC, and report it to HHS instead. Vice President Mike Pence said the information would continue to be released publicly. It hasn’t worked out as promised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi duels with White House as unemployment aid set to expire...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/31/white-house-democrats-unemployment-benefits-389540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negotiators remain at an impasse over a massive coronavirus relief package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burns, bloody wounds, broken bones: Injuries mount at Portland protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2020/07/burns-bloody-wounds-broken-bones-injuries-mount-at-portland-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weeks of restive demonstrations in Portland are leaving an indelible mark on protesters as the nightly cries against police violence and racism have often ended with an aggressive show of force by local and federal officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia patients to be sent to giant convention center...</title>
      <link>https://www.onlineathens.com/news/20200731/rsquosurge-bedsrsquo-virus-patients-to-be-sent-to-giant-georgia-convention-center</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — One of the nation's largest convention centers will reopen on Monday with "surge beds" to treat COVID-19 patients as critical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Murdoch Resigns From NEWSCORP Board...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/james-murdoch-resigns-news-corp-board-citing-disagreements-editorial-content-1305446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mogul sent a letter of resignation on Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future FITBIT? 'Drawn-On-Skin' Electronics...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/future-fitbit-drawn-on-skin-electronics-may-be-breakthrough-for-health-tech-industry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have developed a way to attach electronics to patients' skin. The innovative health technology is simply drawn on skin using a pen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax concerns worrying medical professionals...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/07/31/covid-19-vaccine-amazingly-close-why-am-i-so-worried/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The work to develop a Covid-19 vaccine has been impressive. But we don't need just any vaccine: we deserve one that's been proven to be safe and effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASS BUZZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/31/politics/joe-biden-running-mate/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden heads into the weekend weighing the biggest decision of his presidential campaign so far, and people close to the process tell CNN that the former vice president is believed to have now begun to narrow his personal shortlist of potential running mates to a handful of women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobbying intensifies among VP candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/nation-world/ct-nw-nyt-joe-biden-vp-choice-20200731-f54rxsdqxna4dkldadrfordymm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has entered the final stage of his deliberations about choosing a running mate as he prepares to talk one-on-one with the finalists next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camp Took Almost Every Precaution. Majority of Kids Still Got It...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-summer-camp-took-almost-every-precaution-the-majority-of-kids-still-got-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 76 percent of young campers who were tested came back positive—an ominous sign as schools push to reopen by the fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now wants EARLY election?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-makes-ominous-prediction-while-raging-against-mail-vote-this-is-going-to-be-the-greatest-election-disaster-in-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Actually, The Washington Post wrote a great article, of all groups," Trump said on Friday. "A week ago, The Washington Post wrote a great article that this is a disaster. This is going</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court overturns Boston Marathon bomber's death sentence...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2020/07/31/federal-appeals-court-overturns-boston-marathon-bomber-dzhokhar-tsarnaevs-death-sentence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen accused of being 'mastermind' behind TWITTER hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/hillsborough-county/tampa-teen-accused-of-being-mastermind-behind-twitter-hack-that-targeted-high-profile-accounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tampa teenager is in jail, accused of being the “mastermind” behind a hack on the social media website Twitter that caused limited access to the site and high-profile accounts, accord…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX set to bring NASA astronauts home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/31/tech/nasa-spacex-crew-dragon-mission-preview-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA astronauts Robert Behnken and Douglas Hurley, the first-ever astronauts to travel into orbit aboard a commercially developed spacecraft, are aiming to return to Earth this weekend — if an incoming hurricane doesn't delay those plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reopenings linked to politics not public health...</title>
      <link>https://www.brookings.edu/blog/brown-center-chalkboard/2020/07/29/school-reopening-plans-linked-to-politics-rather-than-public-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.brookings.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is partisanship playing a role in school reopening?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Warning Signs...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/31/gov-murphy-puts-new-jersey-on-notice-warns-residents-to-heed-coronavirus-guidelines-as-cases-spike-the-alarms-are-going-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey remains among the states with the lowest coronavirus positivity rates, but Gov. Phil Murphy said Friday that may change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer road trip? Quarantines crimping travelers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ee83aefdc086c7cc6710adc71a20774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Families trying to squeeze in a summer vacation before school starts better do some homework on COVID-19 restrictions before loading up the minivan. The web of state...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient didn't recognize body after double transplant...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/COVID-patient-didn-t-recognize-body-after-double-15447359.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) - A Chicago woman who last month became the nation's first COVID-19 patient to undergo a double lung transplant said Thursday that she woke up days later, unaware about the surgery and unable to "recognize my body."  Mayra Ramirez said that before she fell ill she was an independent, active person who moved from North Carolina to Chicago in 2014 to work as a paralegal. She said she had an autoimmune condition, but was otherwise healthy. She had gone on a three-mile run shortly before becoming ill and heading for the hospital.  "I was told to hurry up (and) change," she said. "I was asked who would be making my medical decisions for me. That's when I told them it would be my mother and eldest sister who all live in North Carolina. I only had a couple minutes to contact them to let them know what was going on before I was intubated."  Ramirez, 28, spoke to the media on Thursday alongside Brian Kuhns, 62, of Lake Zurich, Illinois, who followed her as the second U.S. coronavirus patient to undergo a double transplant.  Ramirez underwent the lung transplant on June 5 at Northwestern Memorial Hospital in Chicago. She didn't wake up until mid-June.  "I looked at myself and couldn't recognize my body," she said. "I didn't have the cognitive ability to process what was going on. All I knew was that I wanted water."  Dr. Ankit Bharat, chief of thoracic surgery and surgical director of the Northwestern Medicine Lung Transplant Program, said Ramirez, who was on a ventilator, fought for her life for six weeks, with the virus completely destroying her lungs. Doctors would call Nohemi Romero, her mother in North Carolina, with updates.  Ramirez, sitting next to her mother during a news conference at the hospital, said her family made the trip to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Insiders Say Entertainment Boss Fostered Toxic Culture, Under Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/nbc-insiders-say-entertainment-boss-fostered-toxic-culture-under-investigation-1305307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former employees allege that NBC Entertainment chairman Paul Telegdy engaged in racist, sexist and homophobic behavior: "It was par for the course."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Order China's BYTEDANCE to Sell TIKTOK U.S. Operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-07-31/trump-to-order-china-s-bytedance-to-sell-tiktok-u-s-operations-kdaib6eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Republicans wants rapid testing available -- at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/510000-gop-leaders-wants-to-make-rapid-testing-available-at-capitol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) said he is looking at options for Republicans to bring rapid testing to the Capitol that would be offered to members in both parties along with staff and reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors could lose hearing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/31/covid-19-survivors-may-lose-hearing-sense-of-smell-and-taste/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has already been established that some coronavirus survivors lose their sense of smell and taste — but doctors in Britain now warn that they can also lose their hearing, according to a report. E…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds to Seize Bolton Book Profits Without Trial?</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/us-seeks-to-seize-john-bolton-book-profits-without-a-trial/article_7670200f-2ea8-56d8-955a-a4e465390bc8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government asked a federal judge in Washington to rule in its favor without a trial as it seeks to seize the proceeds from former national security adviser John</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron salutes Kaepernick for inspiring NBA National Anthem demonstration...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/LeBron-James-salutes-Colin-Kaepernick-for-15448572.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KISSIMMEE, Fla. - After kneeling during the national anthem on the opening night of the NBA's bubble restart, LeBron James dedicated the coordinated social justice demonstration to former NFL quarterback Colin Kaepernick.  James, who led the Los Angeles Lakers past the Clippers at 103-101 at The Arena at Disney World on Thursday, said that Kaepernick "taught me a lot" about the protest issue. Kaepernick, once a star quarterback with the San Francisco 49ers, has not played in the NFL since he began protesting police brutality by taking a knee during the national anthem in 2016.  "I hope we made Kaep proud," James said. "I hope we continue to make Kaep proud every single day. I hope I make him proud on how I live my life, not only out on the basketball floor but off the floor."  The Lakers and Clippers donned "Black Lives Matter" shirts and locked arms before their contest in a unified demonstration. Every player on both teams participated, as did the coaches and referees. A similar demonstration took place involving members of the Utah Jazz and New Orleans Pelicans earlier Thursday.  The 35-year-old James, who has been outspoken on political issues dating back to Trayvon Martin and Eric Garner, called for the Louisville police officers who shot Breonna Taylor to be arrested last week. After praising Rep. John Lewis recently for teaching him to "never be afraid of conflict, good conflict, positive conflict that can create change," James said he appreciated Kaepernick's willingness to take a polarizing stand and to clearly state his motives, even when critics suggested that kneeling was disrespectful to the military or un-American.  "Kaep was someone who stood up when times weren't comfortable, when people didn't understand, when people refused to listen to what he was saying," James said. "If you go back and listen to his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers make wills, retire, plan strikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2020/jul/31/teachers-school-reopening-in-person-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educators, worried about the potentially deadly risks they are being forced to take, say proper protections have not been implemented</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Sentiment Sinks into Deep Funk...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2020/07/31/summertime-blues-u-s-consumer-sentiment-sinks-deeper-into-coronavirus-resurgence-funk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer sentiment continued to slide downward in late July, with both the current conditions and expectations gauges declining. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH EAST COAST</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/isaias-explodes-into-hurricane-to-eye-us-east-coast/786335</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director Alan Parker dead...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/alan-parker-dies-director-of-bugsy-malone-midnight-express-evita-was-76-1203000762/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Alan Parker, a towering figure in the UK industry, passed away this morning following a lengthy illness, the British Film Institute has confirmed. He was 76. Two-time Oscar nominee Parker…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced microchip to revolutionize commercial, weapons tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/30/tachyum-prodigy-universal-processor-microchip-revo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An energy-efficient microchip under development combines different types of processors into one chip and is expected to revolutionize commercial and defense technology, the advanced semiconductor’s inventor says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: 'NO END IN SIGHT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1233195/fauci-covid-continue-for-some-time-disagreement-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTHONY Fauci said the COVID-19 crisis will “continue for some time” in latest disagreement with Trump, who said it would “disappear.” On Friday, Fauci, CDC boss Robert Redf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICH GET RICHER DURING COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1232880/amazon-facebook-apple-profit-coronavirus-quarter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON sales have jumped by 40 percent, Facebook’s profit has increased by 98 percent and Apple has posted more than $11billion profit in the last quarter. The companies have all seen a rise …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Algorithms Struggle to Detect Faces Under Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/07/facial-recognition-algorithms-struggle-detect-faces-under-masks-nist-study-finds/167303/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Halts Ad Spending While It Reviews Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-campaign-halts-ad-spending-while-it-reviews-strategy/ar-BB17q4ET</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Owners Leaning on Credit Cards to Survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/small-business-owners-are-leaning-on-credit-cards-to-survive/ar-BB17q2Mg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 men killed, woman injured in baseball bat attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2020/07/31/2-men-killed-woman-injured-in-baseball-bat-attack-at-windermere-home-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were beaten to death and a woman was seriously injured late Thursday during an attack at a home in a gated Windermere community while a 10-year-old boy called authorities while hiding in a bathroom, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH EAST COAST</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/isaias-explodes-into-hurricane-to-eye-us-east-coast/785580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Street Corners Overflowing With Garbage After Sanitation Dept Budget Slashed...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/trash-collection-nyc-sanitation-department-budget-cuts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sanitation commissioner says curbside collection service has stayed the same, but people are leaving out more trash than usual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deal with it'... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deal-epstein-told-maxwell-unsealed-emails-150325713.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York court has unsealed emails revealing that disgraced late financier Jeffrey Epstein tried to reassure accused sex trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell by telling her she had "done nothing wrong." "You have done nothing wrong and I would urge you to start acting like it," Epstein</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to invest $10 billion in space-based internet system...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-invest-10-bn-space-based-internet-system-143020830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon says it will invest $10 billion for its planned space-based internet delivery system after winning US regulatory approval to deploy more than 3,000 low-orbit satellites. The US tech giant said on Thursday it is moving forward with its Project Kuiper, one of several systems planned to bring internet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAHAMAS BRACES...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200731144415-rvcis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-ISAIAS/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Hurricane Isaias heads toward Florida with 75-mph winds -Hurricane Center</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami-Dade Mayor Urges Residents To Prep For Hurricane; All COVID-19 Testing Sites Shut Down...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/31/miami-dade-mayor-carlos-gimenez-urges-residents-prepare-impacts-hurricane-isaias/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami-Dade is preparing for possible impacts from Hurricane Isaias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President faces rare rebuke from GOP for floating election delay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08c1c9bb58ecb5392e2e59a4161233b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump repeatedly tests the Republican Party's limits on issues including race, trade and immigration. Now he has struck a boundary. GOP officials from New...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPECTED CAT 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/weather/hurricane/fl-hurricane-isaias-florida-update-20200731-5g7pveljzjdcppbzmd64s35jim-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hurricane watch was issued for part of the South Florida coast, as Hurricane Isaias was projected to reach Category 2 strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partisan clash at start of hearing with Fauci...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-usa-fauci/partisan-clash-at-start-of-u-s-house-coronavirus-hearing-with-fauci-idUSKCN24W1GS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressional Republicans and Democrats clashed about whether the Trump administration had a national strategy to respond to the coronavirus pandemic at the start of a hearing featuring Dr. Anthony Fauci, the United States' top infectious disease expert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist recalls most disturbing case: Yellow snake-like eyes, contorted body...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/yellow-snake-like-eyes-contorted-22439624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Reverend Bill Bean has been a practising exorcist since 2013 and told Daily Star Online about the chilling details of one particular demonic possession</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDINALS Game Postponed After 'Multiple' Players Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/cardinals-have-positive-coronavirus-tests-fridays-game-against-brewers-postponed-per-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cardinals are reportedly self-isolating at their hotel following multiple positive tests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Nevada Sportsbooks Suffer First Monthly Loss Since '13...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/general/news/nevada-sportsbooks-suffer-first-monthly-net-loss-since-2013/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nevada sportsbooks lost $483,000 in June</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida record high for fourth straight day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200731134711-omuu8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-RECORDS (URGENT):Florida reports record increase in COVID-19 deaths for fourth day in a row</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
