<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Britain secretly funded REUTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-media/britain-secretly-funded-reuters-in-1960s-and-1970s-documents-idUSKBN1ZC20H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British government secretly funded Reuters in the 1960s and 1970s at the beh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb in Van of NJ Shooting Attack Suspects Could've Killed People 5 Football Fields Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/bomb-in-van-of-nj-shooting-attack-suspects-couldve-killed-people-5-football-fields-away-officials/2259079/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. attorney in New Jersey and the head of the local FBI said Monday that the bomb found in the van of alleged domestic terrorists Francine Graham and David Anderson could have killed or maimed people up to five football fields away. They also said there was enough material in the van to make a second bomb. Four innocent…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTROS GM, Manager Suspended 1 Year for 'Cheating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28476780/sources-houston-astros-jeff-luhnow-aj-hinch-suspended-1-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astros GM Jeff Luhnow and manager AJ Hinch have been suspended for one year after an MLB investigation found the team used technology to cheat during its World Series-winning 2017 season, it was announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How High Schooler Uses Online Trick To Scoop CNN...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/01/11/dublin-teens-url-sleuthing-trick-scoops-cnns-iowa-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN unveiled a much-anticipated Iowa Democratic primary poll, but Dublin High School senior Arjav Rawal had already done it for them, tweeting out the numbers 20 minutes earlier. How?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Entertainment, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE SAYS A WOMAN CAN'T WIN?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/13/politics/bernie-sanders-elizabeth-warren-meeting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stakes were high when Bernie Sanders and Elizabeth Warren met at Warren's apartment in Washington, DC, one evening in December 2018. The longtime friends knew that they could soon be running against each other for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Yoga instructor punched, kicked man for using phone during 'ONCE UPON TIME IN HOLLYWOOD' screening...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/once-upon-an-assault-287569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANUARY 13--An Iowa yoga instructor allegedly pummeled a fellow moviegoer whose use of a phone during a showing of “Once Upon a Time in Hollywood” was purportedly responsible for “ruining the film” f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD'S CHEAPEST MAN:  Bezos gives Oz fire victims just $690,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/249608/jeff-bezos-slammed-for-giving-australia-fire-victims-just-690000-the-same-as-you-giving-0-0006-of-your-salary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON billionaire Jeff Bezos has been slammed for donating a tiny fraction of his mega-wealth to the Australian bush fire fund. The uber-rich tech tycoon has pledged $690,000 ($1m Aus) to the reli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight polls, impeachment, billionaire wild cards: Uncertainty reigns in  2020 Dem race...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/tight-polls-impeachment-billionaire-wild-cards-uncertainty-reigns-in-the-2020-democratic-race/ar-BBYUr9K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein spy says he's not sorry for secretly trailing 91 Hollywood figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7881959/Harvey-Weinstein-SPY-says-hes-not-sorry-trailing-91-Hollywood-figures-including-Rose-McGowan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seth Freedman, left, worked for private intelligence agency Black Cube. They were hired by Weinstein, right with accuser McGowan, in July 2017 to look into 'a plot against him'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stadium Ran Out Of Fireworks During Scoring Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/chiefs-run-out-of-fireworks-at-arrowhead-stadium-during-51-point-scoring-blitz-in-playoff-win-over-texans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was so much Kansas City offense that Arrowhead couldn't keep up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/av/stories-51061969/hired-by-weinstein-to-spy-on-celebrities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spy posed as a journalist to extract information from Hollywood stars for Weinstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royals present united front...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/queen-gathers-royals-crisis-meeting-prince-harry-055916398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry and his brother Prince William put on a united front as they were summoned to showdown talks Monday on Harry's future after he and his wife Meghan unilaterally announced they were quitting as front-line British royalty. William, 37, and 35-year-old Harry formed a close bond following</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Denies Gun Confiscation Request For First Time Under Red Flag Law In Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/12/colorado-judge-red-flag-confiscation-request/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, a judge has denied a request to take away a man's guns under Colorado's new red flag law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court refuses to 'Free the Nipple' in topless women case...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113140914-x3iun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TOPLESS (PIX):U.S. Supreme Court refuses to 'Free the Nipple' in topless women case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumbling volcano shuts down Philippine capital...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113050635-e0zn3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands evacuated as seismologists warn that a hazardous eruption could happen any time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass Panic: It's Not Clear That Colorado's Mystery Drones Even Exist...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/pkeb9k/mass-panic-its-not-clear-that-colorados-mystery-drones-even-exist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drone hobbyists say the media and the FAA regularly uses drone panic to enact strict regulations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women Scored Record 31% of All Contenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/oscars-2020-women-record-31-percent-nominations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;65 of the 209 nominees this year were women despite leaving out "Little Women" filmmaker Greta Gerwig</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: William Barr, President's Sword and Shield...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2020/01/20/william-barr-trumps-sword-and-shield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Attorney General’s mission to maximize executive power and protect the Presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Nets Blast Trump with 93% Neg News...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/rich-noyes/2020/01/13/tvs-trump-news-three-fourths-impeachment-and-93-negative</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first 100 days since House Democrats began their impeachment push, ABC, CBS and NBC have aggressively aided the effort. An MRC analysis finds the Big Three evening newscasts battered the President with 93% negative coverage and promoted impeachment at the expense of nearly all other Trump news. At the same time, the broadcast networks donated at least 124 hours of wall-to-wall live coverage as they pre-empted regular programming in favor of House Democrat-led impeachment activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX LEADS ALL STUDIOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/oscars-netflix-leads-all-hollywood-studios-24-nominations-1268945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Disney empire picked up 23 nods, while Sony makes a huge comeback with 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will alleged CIA misbehavior set Assange free?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/477939-will-cia-misbehavior-set-julian-assange-free</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The behavior of UC Global and the CIA seems indistinguishable from the government’s behavior in the Ellsberg case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: ESPN Planning 'Historic' Offer for Tony Romo; Between $10-14M?</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/report-espn-to-make-cbs-tony-romo-a-historic-offer-to-join-its-nfl-coverage-033157777.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Romo was an instant star at CBS, and ESPN reportedly wants him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker suspends... </title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/sen-cory-booker-suspends-presidential-campaign/story?id=67472609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Cory Booker ends presidential campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You Need a Boat.' Water Main Break Floods NYC Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/boat-water-main-break-floods-135547858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water main break flooded streets on Manhattan&amp;#39;s Upper West Side near Lincoln Center and hampered subway service during the Monday morning rush hour. The Fire Department of New York responded to the flooding around 5 a.m. near Broadway and West 62nd Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANDERS SURGES</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/13/sanders-progressives-flock-warren-098065</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consolidation of left-wing support is a remarkable turnaround for Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen hosts royal family summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7879471/Deeply-Hurt-Queen-gathers-Royals-Megxit-crisis-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of Sussex wants his 93-year-old grandmother, father and brother to let him and his wife keep their royal titles while living in Canada while grabbing 'financial independence'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabbing spree in Colorado Springs leaves 8 injured... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/13/us/colorado-springs-stabbings/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man allegedly stabbed eight people at several locations in Colorado Springs, Colorado, early Monday morning in what police said was a random spree of violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Teases Talking Car...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/13/elon-musk-teases-a-new-talking-car-feature-for-tesla.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a clip Musk shared on Twitter, a Model 3 rolls by as the speakers play, "Well don't just stand there staring. Hop in."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suddenly, Eruptions Across Globe...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/why-are-volcanoes-all-over-the-globe-suddenly-shooting-giant-clouds-of-ash-miles-into-the-air</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There certainly hasn't been a lack of seismic activity so far in 2020.  Just a few days ago, I wrote about the horrific earthquake swarm that Puerto Rico is currently experiencing.  More than 1,000 earthquakes have rattled Puerto Rico so far, and as you will see below, it was just hit by another ver</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPLETE LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/oscar-nominations-2020-the-complete-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 92nd Academy Awards take place on Feb. 9</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE NIRO, J.LO SHUT OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/01/13/updating-oscar-nominations-snubs-include-jlo-for-hustlers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2020 Oscar nominations are here. Snubs  include Jennifer Lopez for “Hustlers.” Eddie Murphy for “Dolemite” and everything for that movie. But I’m really shocked th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts leading trial, but this woman is shaping it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/13/john-roberts-senate-impeachment-whisperer-098050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first female Senate parliamentarian will be advising the chief justice on how to address arcane procedural questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PARASITE' MAKES HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/parasite-oscar-nominations-best-picture-international-film-1203464351/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Parasite” made history on Monday, becoming the first South Korean movie to be nominated for best picture and best international film. Given South Korea’s rich film history, it&amp;#8…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNUBS, SURPRISES...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/2020-oscar-nominations-snubs-surprises-jennifer-lopez-robert-de-niro-awkwafina-women-directors-1202828716/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Similar to last year, the 92nd Academy Awards will be going hostless on February 9, but this morning’s Oscar nominations certainly had their fair share of unexpected disclosure for Hollywood’s bigg…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' LEADS OSCAR NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/907139138b9271a3cfb4637e4e2f4334</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Phillips’ much-debated supervillain origin story and R-rated box-office smash “Joker” topped all films with 11 Academy Awards nominations, while Martin Scorsese’s elegiac crime epic “The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: OSCAR NOMINATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BEho_CNX43s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 92nd Oscar nominations are almost here! Join us live on Monday, January 13, at 5:18am PT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could A Pill Replace Exercise? </title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sestrin-could-pill-replace-exercise-protein-mimics-effects-of-working-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds the naturally occurring protein Sestrin appears to mimic the effects of exercise on both flies and mice in clinical trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Republican case for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/The-Republican-case-for-Biden-14970558.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It isn't easy to support a Democrat after an attachment to Republican politics that began when I watched the 1992 GOP convention at age 12. Eventually I worked on Capitol Hill as a Republican senior counsel for the House Financial Services Committee, where I helped conduct oversight of the Obama administration. I worked on the presidential campaigns of John McCain, Mitt Romney and Marco Rubio, and even worked for the Trump transition team in 2016 as an economic adviser.  But I'm happy to urge my fellow Republicans to back Joe Biden for president. If you're a Republican living in an open-primary state, help him get the Democratic nomination. Once he has it, vote for him in November.  Plenty of Republicans see President Donald Trump's moral and political failures clearly. About 10 percentof Republican voters believe that Trump should be removed from office. Those voters will be up for grabs in the 2020 election. They should be relieved that Biden is the Democratic front-runner right now.  For one thing, Biden surely would score high on the "have a beer with the guy" electability test. Biden doesn't even drink beer, or any alcohol, but he's still able to inspire a sense of collegial good feeling. I saw as much at the November 2006Return Day ceremony, a post-election tradition in Sussex County, Delaware, when politicians from both sides gather and literally bury a hatchet to symbolize goodwill. Lots of beer is consumed on Return Day, but one of the most convivial participants I saw was the teetotal Biden. Washington could use a few more old-school politicians who understand that spirit of bipartisanship.  For some Democrats, the idea of wooing dissatisfied Republicans is nauseating. Yet the best outcome for the country may require the left-of-center to find common ground with the right-of-center, especially on trade,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soleimani killing authorized seven months ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/trump-authorized-soleimani-s-killing-7-months-ago-conditions-n1113271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The timing raises new questions about the Trump administration's stated justification for taking out the top Iranian general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle Age Misery Peaks at Age of 47.2, Economist Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/middle-age-misery-peaks-at-age-of-47-2-economist-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Middle Age Misery Peaks at Age of 47.2, Economist Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Expands Robotic Workforce to 650 Additional Stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/walmart-expands-its-robotic-workforce-to-650-additional-stores</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart Expands Its Robotic Workforce to 650 Additional Stores</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to Face Unprecedented Protests During India Trip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-bezos-face-unprecedented-protests-095958681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Amazon.com Inc. founder Jeff Bezos is likely to be greeted by an unprecedented show of opposition during his short India visit this week, after thousands of small-time local retailers pledged to protest its pricing and exclusive-selling practices.The Amazon chief executive is slated to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese woman with mystery virus quarantined in Thailand...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113103056-2bhmv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/PNEUMONIA-THAILAND:Chinese woman with mystery virus quarantined in Thailand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight for Bolton testimony echoes Lewinsky...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113102655-ka82i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-CLINTON (PIX):Trump impeachment trial fight for Bolton testimony echoes Monica Lewinsky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders Says He'd Consider Releasing List of Supreme Court Picks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/bernie-sanders-says-hed-consider-releasing-list-of-supreme-court-picks/ar-BBYTNpb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biblical prophecy 'fulfilled' as floodwater 'flows from Jerusalem into Dead Sea'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/biblical-prophecy-fulfilled-floodwater-flows-21269525</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some have bizarrely claimed that a Bible prophecy in the Book of Ezekiel – one of the major prophetic books in the Old Testament – has been fulfilled after footage emerged of floodwater appearing to flow eastwards from Jerusalem towards the Dead Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters disrupt Pete rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/477928-protesters-interrupt-buttigieg-at-iowa-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters with a local Black Lives Matter group disrupted an event being held in Des Moines, Iowa, by South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg (D) on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In McGahn Case, an Epic Constitutional Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/01/13/in-mcgahn-case-an-epic-constitutional-showdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — “Has there ever been,” the judge asked, “an instance of such broad-scale defiance of a congressional request for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Iranian security forces fire live ammunition to disperse protesters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b5f51dc8712b6fcddc2010bbd9de31f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iranian security forces fired both live ammunition and tear gas to disperse demonstrators protesting against the Islamic Republic's initial denial that it shot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PACKERS SILENCE SEAHAWKS.... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001096372/article/packers-top-seahawks-to-advance-to-nfc-championship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been four years but the Green Bay Packers are one win away from the Super Bowl, beating the Seattle Seahawks at Lambeau Field to earn a spot against the 49ers in the NFC Championship game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo Plans Dinner With Tech Leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pompeo-plans-dinner-tech-leaders-225938488.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Secretary of State Michael Pompeo is planning to attend a private dinner on Monday with tech leaders including Oracle Corp.’s Larry Ellison, according to people familiar with the matter. The dinner, which will be held in San Francisco, comes as tensions between the U.S. and Iran run high</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNING!</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Weeks-before-Iowa-caucuses-Sanders-goes-on-the-14970045.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARSHALLTOWN, Iowa - Sen. Bernie Sanders' presidential campaign has suddenly gone on the attack as he seeks to secure an opening victory in the early February caucuses, engaging in a rare dispute with Sen. Elizabeth Warren, tussling with former vice president Joe Biden and drawing an insult from President Donald Trump.  Although Sanders, I-Vt., mostly had resisted comparing himself with other candidates, over the weekend, his surrogates and aides intensified their attacks on Biden, targeting his past positions on racial issues and his vote to sanction the Iraq War.  At the same time, his campaign went after Warren, D-Mass., with whom Sanders has shared a nonaggression pact for much of the primary season. A script first reported by Politico told Sanders' volunteers to tell voters they called on Sanders' behalf who had indicated support for her that Warren's popularity was limited to the rich and educated - effectively denigrating her electability.  Both candidates struck back either personally or through their own surrogates on Sunday.  Warren told reporters in Iowa that she was "disappointed" with Sanders' campaign script painting her as an elitist. She used the opportunity to warn about "factionalism" that led to Democrats losing the White House in 2016, a reference to the belief by many Democrats that Sanders and his supporters failed to sufficiently support Hillary Clinton against Donald Trump.  "I hope Bernie reconsiders and turns his campaign in a different direction," Warren added.  Trump put an exclamation point on the Democratic infighting, calling the senator "Crazy Bernie Sanders" in a tweet and telling his followers to "stay tuned." A Trump campaign aide said to expect the president to mount a full-throttle attack on Sanders in the coming days.  Sanders'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell walks tightrope...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/McConnell-walks-impeachment-tightrope-14969962.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLORENCE, Ky. - It is not easy these days to lose as a Republican running in ruby-red Kentucky. But that is what happened here in November in the governor's race, when the caustic incumbent managed to alienate enough of his base to fall just short.  This year, another polarizing and unpopular Republican will be up for reelection in the Bluegrass State. But Mitch McConnell has at least one key advantage that former governor Matt Bevin did not: As perhaps the most powerful man on Capitol Hill, he is positioned to drive a stake through efforts to oust a Republican who remains indisputably admired among Kentucky voters: President Donald Trump.  The Senate majority leader's insistence that he will coordinate Trump's impeachment trial with the White House - and that he has no intention of being impartial - has provoked howls of protest from Democrats. On Sunday, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., accused McConnell of orchestrating a "coverup" of Trump's actions.  It has also prompted speculation that he could jeopardize his slender majority by exposing Republicans in swing or Democratic-leaning states to accusations that they went along with a rigged process running counter to the Constitution.  But here in Kentucky, it just looks like savvy politics.  The 77-year-old is expected to face a vigorous challenge in November from a decorated Marine fighter pilot with a record of big-dollar fundraising. Yet McConnell has shown an unerring instinct for self-preservation across six Senate terms and a record stint as Republican leader.  Analysts say his impeachment strategy is just more evidence that he is playing to win.  "It's the safest move he could make," said Ryan Salzman, a politics professor at Northern Kentucky University. "Anything that even appears he's going against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO POPES:  Benedict defends priestly celibacy as Francis considers changes...</title>
      <link>https://www.ncronline.org/news/vatican/surprise-benedict-openly-defends-clerical-celibacy-francis-considers-married-priests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ncronline.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retired Pope Benedict XVI has coauthored a new book defending the Catholic Church's practice of a celibate priesthood, in a shocking move that comes as Pope Francis is considering the possibility of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data operation targeting women voters amid warning signs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-data-operation-is-targeting-women-voters-amid-warning-signs/ar-BBYSDhl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False alarm sets off nuclear scare in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/false-alarm-sets-off-nuclear-scare-canada-011722234.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alert signaling an incident at a major nuclear power plant near Toronto in Canada was sent in error to millions of residents Sunday, causing a scare and prompting calls for an investigation. The emergency alert went out shortly before 7:30 am (1230 GMT). About an hour later, the Ontario Power Generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan Collapses, Dies At RAVENS During Game...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/01/12/fan-collapses-at-mt-bank-stadium-dies-during-ravens-titans-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man collapsed in the upper deck of M&amp;T Bank Stadium during the Ravens-Titans playoff game Saturday night and died, the Ravens confirmed Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen prepares for royal family summit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/608f7b86ada84876a40389c94f449109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Ensconced with aides at her royal retreat, Britain's Queen Elizabeth II prepared Sunday for a crisis family meeting to work out a future for Prince Harry and his wife, Meghan, after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN SHOWS TEETH</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200112223314-3co2t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/SANDERS (PIX):Warren, Sanders campaigns spar in rare show of discord between progressive Democratic contenders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small but dangerous: Volcano spews ash over Philippine capital... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200112170703-wipui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands evacuated amid warnings of a possible explosive eruption and volcanic tsunami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' Declining Fortunes as 'SKYWALKER' Way Behind Last 2 Films...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/01/12/star-wars-declining-fortunes-as-skywalker-nears-billion-dollars-but-way-behind-last-2-films</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Star Wars” is shrinking at the box office. “The Rise of Skywalker” is nearing $1 billion worldwide, but it’s way behind the previous installments. “The Force Aw…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She's not my mom!' Child's sign in car window alarms drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article239219423.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's toilet tirades...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/flushing-10-times-what-s-really-behind-trump-s-tirades-n1111691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal regulations on water use in bathrooms and kitchens have caught the president's ire. Some conservatives have long held a grudge about the restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren finally shows teeth...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/warren-disappointed-sanders-reportedly-sending-his-volunteers-out-trash-me-n1114241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Bernie knows me and has known me for a long time," Warren told NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edelman arrested in Beverly Hills...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/new-england-patriots-star-julian-edelman-arrested-vandalism-beverly-hills-n1114236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England wide receiver was arrested after he allegedly jumped on the hood of a vehicle and caused damage Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Unhinged passenger charges cockpit, attacks cops, flight attendant...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article239217193.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost No Chance of a Recession This Year, Experts Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/why-markets-will-gain-despite-looming-risks-barrons-roundtable-panelists-say-51578707631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors entered 2020 with the financial markets heading higher and a lot of optimism about the economy. Here’s what our 10 panelists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Greenlights 'SILENCE OF THE LAMBS' Series...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/silence-lambs-spinoff-clarice-a-go-at-cbs-1268773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drama hails from 'Star Trek' franchise captain Alex Kurtzman and received a big commitment from the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAHOMES MANIA! QB Tosses 5 TDs As CHIEFS Truimph...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/texans-vs-chiefs-score-patrick-mahomes-throws-five-tds-kansas-city-scores-41-unanswered-in-comeback-rout/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not even a 24-point lead was safe for Houston at Arrowhead Stadium on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grisham unleashes on former press secretaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/press-secretaries-white-house-briefings-8776f868-e14b-462e-bf86-bea299d9c170.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump White House has not held a traditional press briefing since March 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Promos Encourage Super Bowl Viewers to Call in Sick the Next Day...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/fox-super-bowl-promos-super-monday-nfl-1203464151/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox wants you to stay home the day after the Super Bowl. As part of its marketing strategy for the big game, the network has launched a new on-air campaign touting “Super Monday” — a da…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tries to ease Iowans' concerns about electability...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/warren-tries-ease-iowans-concerns-211135966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren barnstormed across Iowa this weekend, seeking to put to rest questions about her electability and her ability to build a coalition to defeat Donald Trump.With less than a month before the Feb. 3 Iowa Caucuses, the Massachusetts senator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1917' FILLS THEATERS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/box-office-1917-star-wars-rise-of-skywalker-like-a-boss-1202826743/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4th Update, Sunday AM writethru final with chart: After Saturday AM update It’s another win for original movies, and this time around with a fresh face cast, as Amblin/New Republic/Universal&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense chief admits he 'didn't see' evidence for Trump claim that Iran planned embassy attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5a168a5d8f560e928f3924f7af10f1d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Defense Secretary Mark Esper explicitly said Sunday that he had seen no hard evidence that four American embassies had been under possible threat when President Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Pelosi square off ahead of impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/526fb7e868e0bf03c73937a03f61efbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump and Speaker Nancy Pelosi squared off Sunday ahead of his impeachment trial, as she said senators will “pay a price” for blocking new witnesses and he...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
