<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Artist who created 'paint-by-numbers' dead at 93...</title>
      <link>https://www.toledoblade.com/a-e/art/2019/04/04/toledo-artist-dan-robbins-created-paint-by-numbers-pictures-dies-obituary/stories/20190404145</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An artist who created the first paint-by-numbers pictures and helped turn the kits into an American sensation during the 1950s has died. Dan Robbins, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEALs lawyered up during war crimes case, then prosecutors went after counsel...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2019/04/04/seals-lawyered-up-during-war-crimes-case-then-prosecutors-went-after-their-lawyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NCIS files and legal motions outline a complex war crimes case against two SEALs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba cuts newspaper size, circulation due to paper scarcity...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-cuba-economy-shortages/cuba-cuts-newspaper-size-due-to-paper-scarcity-as-shortages-bite-idUKKCN1RG2WJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba says a paper shortage is forcing it to cut back on pages and circulation at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What will MSNBC do without Special Counsel?</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/153435/msnbcs-wild-ride</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to Trump and the Russia investigation, the liberal network is booming. But is it selling its viewers a conspiratorial fantasy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly plan to open supervised injection site despite federal suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/philadelphia-plans-to-open-supervised-opioid-injection-facility-despite-federal-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the plan for what is known as a safe injection site has garnered local support, the city now finds itself in a major legal fight with the federal government. The Justice Department sued, arguing that the facility — the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico latest to join national popular vote compact...</title>
      <link>https://www.santafenewmexican.com/news/legislature/bill-backing-presidential-popular-vote-gets-gov-lujan-grisham-s/article_99d7f14a-6536-5b86-9c07-49eb7ef54fb9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.santafenewmexican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Bill 55 allows New Mexico to join a compact of states that would allocate their electors in a presidential campaign to the candidate that wins the most votes nationally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTEL 6 to pay for sharing guest info with ICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.king5.com/article/news/local/motel-6-to-pay-12-million-after-sharing-guest-info-with-ice/281-2afefa9b-f364-48db-8d66-9d17d8e1e30c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.king5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 2018 investigation by the Attorney General's Office found Motel 6 locations, including seven in Washington, shared guests’ personal information with ICE agents without the guests’ consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $1,000,000,000 ask: Trump goes big on re-elect fundraising...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/015974755b7842e2819cd98deae78763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is well on his way to raising the $1 billion his campaign believes it will take for him to win another term in the White House, building a fundraising...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Halperin Comes Out of #MeToo Hiding, Weighs In...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mark-halperin-comes-out-of-metoo-hiding-to-weigh-in-on-bidens-creepy-touching</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two years after being fired over sexual-harassment claims, the ex-pundit resurfaced for a chat and apologized again before opining on the ex-veep’s own creepy behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45-year-old elephant on death row gets execution stay...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2019-04-04/judge-grants-stay-of-execution-to-45-year-old-problem-elephant-on-death-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats -- know their own names...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/clever-kitty-cats-know-their-names-doc-1fd46z1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama silently standing behind Biden, associates say...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/437460-obama-is-quiet-as-biden-comes-under-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Joe Biden’s allies raced to defend the former vice president in the face of a mounting political crisis, one voice has remained silent: former President Barack Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swallowing partner's semen can help have baby, scientists claim...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/04/04/women-want-baby-start-swallowing-partners-semen-scientists-claim-9110233/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It turns out that ingesting men's sexual emissions could help to prevent miscarriages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruelty charges for evicted man who abandoned FISH!</title>
      <link>http://www.wect.com/2019/04/03/man-accused-abandoning-pet-fish-faces-animal-cruelty-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wect.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Hanover County man was arrested on animal cruelty charges after he allegedly failed to provide fresh water and food to his pet fish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Woman who fell from Vegas roller coaster 'double amputee'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/the-strip/woman-who-fell-from-las-vegas-roller-coaster-is-double-amputee-1633357/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman who fell last month from a Circus Circus Adventuredome roller coaster is a “double amputee,” according to records obtained by the Las Vegas Review-Journal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prank petition seeking permission to use N-word sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/socal/daily-pilot/news/tn-dpt-me-marina-high-petition-20190403-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Marina High School students circulated a petition asking students of color for permission to use the N-word as an April Fool's joke gone wrong, according to the Huntington Beach Union High School District board president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTER: Congressman Apologized For Shoving Me...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/reporter-rep-don-young-apologized-for-shoving-me</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Don Young (R-AK) on Thursday called reporter Melanie Zanona of Politico to apologize for shoving her earlier in the day,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporations, special interests wrote bills. Politicians introduced them. 10,000 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/investigations/2019/04/03/abortion-gun-laws-stand-your-ground-model-bills-conservatives-liberal-corporate-influence-lobbyists/3162173002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle school teacher says pressured into student sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article228810694.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dimon Decided Not To Run...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/04/jamie-dimon-weighed-a-2020-presidential-run-sources-say-heres-why-he-decided-against-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Republican nomination unavailable and the leftward lean of the Democratic party making the election of a Wall Street tycoon unlikely, Dimon begrudgingly decided against running, sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD secret standoff weapon: Simple length of rope...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9919831195cd4980960fd86c524360c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The New York Police Department has all the latest crime-fighting tools: body cameras, algorithms, even drones. But it is now widely deploying a far simpler technology, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man admits ghost did not plant meth in home...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/ghost/meth-ghost-cleared-285430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who surmised that a ghost may have planted methamphetamine in his Louisiana home eventually admitted that he, and not an otherworldly force, was responsible for the drug being in his residence,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS REMAINS WORLD'S RICHEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/jeff-bezos-keeping-75-of-couples-amazon-stock-in-divorce-all-voting-rights-11554399197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. Chief Executive Jeff Bezos will retain 75% of the shares that he owns with his wife, MacKenzie Bezos, and have voting control over the remaining shares she owns in the company, Ms. Bezos said on Twitter Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four-legged prehistoric whale fossil found...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190404-four-legged-prehistoric-whale-fossil-found-peru</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four-legged prehistoric whale fossil found in Peru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF KEEPS WASHPOST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/04/mackenzie-bezos-to-keep-25-percent-of-couples-amazon-stock-after-finalizing-divorce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MacKenzie Bezos announces on Twitter that she and Jeff Bezos have completed the process of dissolving their marriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nadler Briefs Top Dem Donors on Trump Investigations...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/liberal-dark-money-group-to-receive-private-briefing-from-house-dem-jerrold-nadler/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN—The largest donors on the left will be given a private briefing on investigations into President Donald Trump by Rep. Jerrold Nadler (N.Y.)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backs off threat to close border...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/04/trump-backs-off-threat-to-close-the-southern-border-1255926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump eased off his threat to shut down the U.S.-Mexico border, instead giving Mexico a “one-year warning” and threatening to first impose auto tariffs before closing the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skateboarders vandalize gravesites of President Ford, First Lady...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/gravesites-of-gerald-ford-betty-ford-vandalized-in-michigan-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Michigan are asking for help after two people were captured on camera defacing the gravesites of former President Gerald R. Ford and former First Lady Betty Ford last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid rising anxiety, colleges tell students OK to fail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c6bde0dd123a4b81a2388d3c28830a24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALTHAM, Mass. (AP) — Bentley University has plenty of success stories among its faculty and alumni. But one recent evening, the school invited students to hear about the failures. Speaking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia stakes hold on Arctic with military base...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/44c182c68f85475bb828942b53042b19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEVERNY KLEVER MILITARY BASE, Russia (AP) — Missile launchers ply icy roads and air defense systems point menacingly into the sky at this Arctic military outpost, a key vantage point for Russia to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to end Yemen war, rebuffing President...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/263d2069e3a0450b9f6329d01004de0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House on Thursday voted to end American involvement in the Yemen war, rebuffing the Trump administration's support for the military campaign led by Saudi Arabia. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS FALL TO 49-YEAR LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/04/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing applications for unemployment benefits dropped to a more than 49-year low last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormons repeal ban on baptisms for children of gay parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona/2019/04/04/mormon-church-repeals-ban-baptisms-children-gay-parents/3364524002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints is repealing rules that banned baptisms for kids of gay parents and made gay marriage worthy of expulsion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran MLB Umpire Under Fire Over Tempter Tantrums, Antagonizing Players, Blown Calls...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/04/04/mlb-has-to-discipline-umpire-ron-kulpa-incident-astros-aj-hinch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran MLB umpire Ron Kulpa is a fellow who had himself a temper tantrum on Wednesday evening in Arlington, Texas. And he ought to be forced to pay for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULLER REPORT MORE DAMAGING THAN REVEALED?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/some-on-muellers-team-see-their-findings-as-more-damaging-for-trump-than-barr-revealed/ar-BBVB0HE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Human dog' who has never felt like a man eats pet food and barks at friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/human-pup-who-never-felt-14235958</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaz James, 37, from Salford, Greater Manchester, carries items with his teeth and snacks on Bonios</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain damage caused by alcohol carries on for six weeks after stop drinking...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6886057/Disturbing-scans-reveal-brain-damage-caused-alcohol-carries-SIX-WEEKS.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers working in Germany and Spain did scans on the brains of 90 alcoholics and 36 non-drinkers to find those who drank alcohol had less electrical activity even weeks after abstaining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROWING SECURITY CONCERNS</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/An-intruder-brought-malware-to-Mar-a-Lago-which-13738350.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidents used to vacation in seclusion - at a ranch in Texas or a beach house in Hawaii. Screening their visitors was relatively simple: The only people who came were friends and staff.  President Donald Trump has added vast new complications by choosing to spend his weekends with his customers.  Trump stays at the Mar-a-Lago Club, a busy beachfront resort where his quarters are a short distance from the pool, the ballroom and the "six star" seafood buffet. That decision - to use his Palm Beach, Florida, club as both a presidential retreat and a moneymaking resort - brings hundreds of members, overnight guests and partygoing strangers into the president's "Winter White House" every weekend.  To protect the president, that requires the Secret Service to screen hundreds of would-be visitors against preapproved lists.  But to protect his business, it has also required the Secret Service to defer to Mar-a-Lago staffers and allow in some visitors who are not on the list.  Last weekend, that complex system of lists and exceptions broke down.  When a visitor approached the club, officers found she was not on the approved list - but let her in anyway after a Mar-a-Lago staffer suggested she might be the relative of a club member.  The woman, identified as Yujing Zhang, a Chinese national, was later arrested inside the club's main building. Authorities said she was carrying four cellphones, a laptop and a thumb drive with malicious software.  "I'm surprised that she got in. But then again, I'm not surprised," said Shannon Donnelly, the longtime society columnist for the Palm Beach Daily News who has covered Mar-a-Lago for years.  She described a situation in which the Secret Service is dealing with two missions, to keep the president safe and to keep his customers happy.  "It's bound...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK:   Dems 2020 Field Full of Unelectable Nonentities...</title>
      <link>https://amgreatness.com/2019/04/03/democrats-in-2020-unelectable-nonentities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;amgreatness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is uproariously entertaining to see the scurryings of the innumerable host of Democratic presidential candidates in what is already more of a lottery than a quest for the nomination of a great party to the world’s greatest office. The Gadarene stampede to (and over) the edge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS -- Opening Stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/sears-after-years-of-closures-is-opening-stores-again-11554379761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears plans to open three stores in May in an attempt to reclaim shoppers after closing hundreds of locations in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>African Child Brides Sold on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/child-brides-in-africa-are-advertised-on-facebook-and-sold-to-old-men</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one Nigerian community, illiterate fathers have learned from their sons that Facebook is a good way to let buyers know their daughters are for sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Revolutionary War hero actually WOMAN?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6884677/Researchers-claim-war-hero-Casimir-Pulaski-biologically-female.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Georgia Southern University say they made the discovery about General Casimir Pulaski after years of research examining the general's remains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to launch thousands of satellites into orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/04/amazon-project-kuiper-broadband-internet-small-satellite-network.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon is planning to build a network of more than 3,000 satellites federal filings reveal, in an ambitious attempt to provide global internet access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF: Monopolistic Power Growing Around World...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/monopolistic-power-is-growing-around-the-world-01554378608</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite declining competition, the IMF cautions against drastic action designed to curb or break up big companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA tests set for border?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/dna-tests-could-be-key-to-ice-verifying-immigrant-families-at-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government has adopted a DNA testing system that would allow border officials to assess within two hours whether immigrants claiming to be in the same family are telling the truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Gorillas Gather Around, Groom Bodies Of Deceased...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gorillas-gather-around-grooms-bodies-deceased/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research shows that death appears to be a profound experience for gorillas. The apes often gather around the bodies of dead individuals, touching and grooming them, which the observers warn could cause the spread of contagious diseases like Ebola.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient teeth hint at mysterious human relative...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/04/ancient-teeth-hint-at-mysterious-human-relative/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The find adds to a growing number of fossils from China that don't fit neatly in the existing human family tree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crying 'Socialism' is Tired...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/pete-buttigieg-says-crying-socialism-is-tired-obamacare-was-a-conservative-idea-which-they-called-socialist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic bees set to invade International Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/space-station-to-take-delivery-of-flying-astrobee-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitaltrends.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There'll be a couple of bees buzzing about the International Space Station in a few weeks' time. OK, they're not real bees, but instead "Astrobees.” Designed by NASA, the compact flying robots are capable of performing routine chores so the crew can focus more on its research activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimon rips socialism...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/04/dimon-defends-capitalism-socialism-inevitably-produces-stagnation-corruption-and-often-worse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dimon in his annual letter acknowledged there are flaws with capitalism and that it should be combined with a strong social safety net.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Claims Fall to 49-Year Low, Below ALL Forecasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-s-jobless-claims-fall-to-49-year-low-below-all-forecasts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jobless claims decreased to 202,000 in the week ended March 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Median list price for house reaches record $300,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/04/04/expensive-homes-sale-flood-market-inflating-listing-prices/3357094002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The median asking price for a U.S. home hit $300,000 for the first time on record, according to March housing data from Realtor.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin were tricked into planting British flag on moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8787751/neil-armstrong-buzz-aldrin-plant-british-flag-moon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRITISH engineer has finally revealed how he tricked astronauts Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin into planting a Union Flag on the moon. Keith Wright, from Nottingham, was based at the Kennedy Spac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey previews new song...</title>
      <link>https://www.thefader.com/2019/04/03/lana-del-rey-previews-new-song-on-instagram-fast-cars-norman-rockwell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thefader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lana Del Rey offers a snippet of yet another track, possibly from her new album Norman Fucking Rockwell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharia law plunges Brunei gay community into fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/se-asia/sharia-law-plunges-brunei-gay-community-into-fear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANDAR SERI BEGAWAN, BRUNEI (AFP) - Transgender woman Zoella Zayce fled her native Brunei last year as the country shifted towards hardline Islam, and thinks more of the LGBT community will follow after the death penalty for gay sex was introduced.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX fires up Mars spaceship for first time, rattling homes for miles around...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/spacex-test-hopper-starhopper-first-raptor-engine-static-fire-2019-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX founder Elon Musk said his rocket company successfully fired up "Starshopper" for the first time. The vehicle is an early prototype of a Mars spaceship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ramos calls for open borders: 'Nobody can stop them'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/03/jorge-ramos-amnesty-for-illegals-migrants-nothing-we-can-do-to-stop-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Univision anchor Jorge Ramos said on Tuesday evening that he believes the solution to the migrant crisis at U.S.-Mexico border is to just legalize illegal immigrants because “nobody can really stop them” from entering the United States. | Politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As sun sets, Caracas empties...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dec789ddf6a4446181fba3eb9730e3db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — When the sun goes down in Venezuela's capital of Caracas, the once-thriving metropolis empties under darkness. Many street lights don't work. Residents avoid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One in five people eating selves to early death...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/04/03/unhealthy-diet-killing-millions-around-world-lancet-study/3339934002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people are dying from poor diets packed with sodium and lacking in whole grains and fruits, according to a study published in The Lancet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diseases surge as health system languishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Diseases-surge-in-Venezuela-as-health-system-13740280.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's health system is in "utter collapse," according to a report, including the exponential spread of vaccine-preventable diseases such as measles and diphtheria and "dramatic surges" in infectious diseases such as malaria and tuberculosis.  The report, to be released Thursday by Human Rights Watch and the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health, is among the few that has sought to quantify Venezuela's misery, as the country has ceased releasing health and nutrition data and retaliated against those who did.  Based on interviews with doctors and other health personnel in Venezuela, conducted by telephone and online; refugees in Colombia and Brazil, including health care professionals; and representatives of humanitarian and international organizations, the report concludes that the United Nations should take the lead providing aid.  It calls on U.N. Secretary General António Guterres to spearhead efforts to declare a complex humanitarian emergency, an official designation that would trigger a major, comprehensive effort under U.N. auspices and unlock the mobilization of international resources.  Humanitarian aid to Venezuela has been slow, compared with the need, because of the intransigence of President Nicolás Maduro - who has blamed deprivations on U.S. sanctions and refused to allow anything beyond a trickle of assistance to enter the country - and the reluctance of some donors to allow assistance to be distributed by the Maduro government.  A U.N. declaration, the reports' authors say, would put Guterres in a position to press Maduro to allow U.N. agencies to lead and implement a large-scale humanitarian response aid.  Guterres has said the United Nations should not join any of the groups of nations promoting various political solutions to the Venezuelan crisis. They include the Lima Group of 14...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles cases soar across USA: 'Getting worse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/apr/03/us-sees-more-measles-reports-in-first-three-months-of-2019-than-in-all-of-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country sees more cases in first three months of 2019 than in all of last year, CDC says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to tropical prison that some don't want to leave...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190404-welcome-tropical-prison-dont-want-leave</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the tropical prison that some don't want to leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: West Virginians lead nation in TV watching...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/71e31af0f4cf40f0864d0208b560e431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — A study by Verizon says that West Virginians watch more television than people in any other state in the country. The report came out Wednesday and used data from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accusations pile up...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/437301-three-more-women-come-forward-with-allegations-against-biden-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three additional women came forward on Wednesday to say former Vice President Joe Biden touched them in ways that made them uncomfortable shortly after Biden, in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deified as voice of his generation, Kurt Cobain lives...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deified-voice-generation-kurt-cobain-lives-013200884.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades after Kurt Cobain's guttural rasp seduced Generation X from its collective bedroom and into the post-punk clubs of 1990s Seattle, the late Nirvana frontman remains a talisman for the young and disaffected the world over. It is a quarter-century on Friday since grunge's reluctant poster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela says more Russian troops could arrive...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190404095809-d5vel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/USA-RUSSIA-MILITARY (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Venezuelan deputy minister says more Russian troops could arrive - Interfax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin 'planted British flag on moon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/04/03/neil-armstrong-buzz-aldrin-planted-british-flag-moon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British engineer has claimed that a Union Flag was planted on the moon by an unwitting Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland Basic Income Experiment Shows Recipients Happier, More Secure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/finland-basic-income-experiment-shows-082142474.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unemployed people derive significant psychological benefits from receiving a fixed amount of financial support from the state, according to a landmark experiment into basic income in Finland that highlights the disadvantages of the country’s existing means-tested system. Initial results of the two-year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROVE:  DON'T COUNT HIM OUT!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/dont-count-joe-biden-out-11554332499</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He could well become president—but first he’s going to have to stop apologizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS NOT defeated as terrorists re-grouping in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8787169/isis-not-been-defeated-terror-group-regrouping-syria-plotting-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS the world has been celebrating the fall of ISIS, the terror group has been re-grouping in Syria, according to reports. US-backed Syrian fighters were still battling ISIS jihadis in eastern Syria…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Democratic Party Radicalizing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/04/progressivism-making-democrats/586372/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extremism isn’t just affecting the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterintelligence probe of Chinese activity focuses on Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article228783369.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax hike on gasoline?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article228794204.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEYSER:  Judge Uncle Joe on the real issues...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/03/the-bonkers-assault-on-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creepy, handsy Uncle Joe Biden, who had the temerity to hug, kiss and space-invade a smattering of unsuspecting women and girls — some of whom dug it while a few felt “uncomfortable,’’ if not exact…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women divided...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/a7f42e9fdfe745b9a247ca563831819b/he-hugs-everybody-women-divided-over-defense-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — It's simply a "human touch." He's a "warm, affectionate person." ''He hugs everybody."In the days since allegations surfaced of uninvited touching on the part of Joe Biden, several women in politics and beyond have been coming to his defense, vouching for his character and saying it was merely his old-fashioned tactile style at issue — nothing intentional, and certainly nothing sexual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Silent As Former VP Feels Heat...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/obama-silent-on-biden-as-former-vp-feels-heat-over-allegations-of-inappropriate-touching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama has remained silent on the allegations of inappropriate touching against his vice president and close friend Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis Ford Coppola Ready To Make 'MEGALOPOLIS';  Eyeing Cast...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/francis-ford-coppola-megalopolis-directing-this-year-1202588167/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: On the eve of his 80th birthday, Francis Ford Coppola is ready to embark on one of his dream projects. He plans to direct Megalopolis, a sprawling film as ambitious as Apocalypse Now, th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men shoot each other with rifle to test bulletproof vest...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/arkansas-idiots-670389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 3--Two Arkansas men took turns shooting one another while wearing a bulletproof vest, according to police who arrested the pair for felony assault. As detailed in a probable cause affidavit, Ch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialists Surge To Victories In Chicago City Council...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/04/03/socialism-chicago-alderman-city-council/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A total of five democratic socialists, and possibly a sixth, won races for alderman either in February or in Tuesday's runoff elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As arms sales surge, Swiss confront EU gun law demand tension...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.ch/20190403/swiss-love-of-guns-to-be-tested-in-upcoming-referendum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland, where gun culture has deep roots, has managed to avoid the charged national debates over firearm ownership that have consumed other countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>280 arrested in ICE raid at TX tech biz...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/immigration/2019/04/03/ice-operation-underway-allen-technology-refurbishing-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officials are detaining people at an Allen technology business today.The operation is underway at CVE...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-deal Brexit outlawed as May faces fury...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/03/uk/brexit-no-deal-bill-yvette-cooper-theresa-may-gbr-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK lawmakers have finally agreed on something related to Brexit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of 1 vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/jeremy-corbyn-brexit-talks-with-theresa-may-useful-but-inconclusive-11683506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It follows talks between Theresa May and Jeremy Corbyn to try to find a possible compromise Brexit deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ways and Means chair asks IRS for POTUS tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/house-democrats-treasury-trumps-tax-returns/story?id=62150855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats have sent their long-anticipated request to the IRS for President Trump’s tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher fired over leaked topless selfie plans to sue school, claims gender discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/society/teacher-fired-over-topless-selfie-to-sue-school-district/5230173/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A middle school math teacher from Long Island is planning to sue her former school district after she was fired, she alleges, for a topless selfie.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
