<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Attacks on Jewish community on rise long before Colleyville...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/attacks-on-americas-jewish-community-on-the-rise-long-before-colleyville-experts-say/ar-AASRg9r?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLACEBO Are Done With Being Fetishised...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akv7v4/placebo-never-let-me-go-album-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were just trying to express ourselves in the way that we needed to – which was cross-dressing and wearing makeup.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 In 3 People Have Never Completed New Year's Resolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/new-years-resolution-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of 2,000 adults reveals that of those who’ve previously set New Year's resolutions, 68 percent have never fully achieved one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noem on Political Rocket Ship. Don't Rule Out Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/01/17/kristi-noem-covid-politician-527080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid made South Dakota’s governor a Republican star. What happens to a pandemic politician after the pandemic?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Obscene inequality'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/17/oxfam-on-covid-inequality-tax-rich-to-pay-for-vaccines-protect-climate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wealth of the world's ten richest men doubled from $700 billion to $1.5 trillion during the pandemic, the global charity said in a press release on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: 1,200 US flights canceled as winter storm pummels East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/17/business/winter-storm-flight-cancellations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US airlines have canceled more than 1,200 flights Monday as a powerful winter storm packing rain, sleet and snow slammed the East Coast on the holiday weekend and made travel difficult. On Sunday, roughly 3,000 flights were canceled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Americans Shift Republican...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/388781/political-party-preferences-shifted-greatly-during-2021.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the U.S. political party affiliation average for 2021 was similar to prior years, the country shifted from a nine-point Democratic preference early in the year to a five-point Republican advantage near the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsession with morning routines dates back to Ben Franklin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/our-obsession-with-morning-routines-dates-back-to-benjamin-franklin/ar-AASPK1Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves snatching French bulldogs across USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-thieves-snatching-french-bulldogs-054130034.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two thieves who brutally robbed 27-year-old Marieke Bayens at gunpoint on a California street were not after her purse -- or her. They wanted the little dog at the end of her leash: Merlyn, a French bulldog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida looms large in Republican 2024 primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/589649-florida-looms-large-in-republican-2024-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is emerging as the epicenter of the early fight for the GOP presidential nomination as speculation grows about the possibility of as many as four Republicans from the Sunshine State pursuing the party's nod in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GO PACK DJOKOVIC; DEPORTED FROM OZ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-novak-djokovic-sports-entertainment-health-d736b70771525c190c1c58bb447b6b95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Novak Djokovic arrived early Monday in Dubai after his deportation from Australia over its required COVID-19 vaccination ended the No. 1-ranked men's tennis player's hopes of defending his Australian Open title.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran-backed Houthi rebels launch 'kamikaze drone' attack on Abu Dhabi...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17347179/iran-houthi-rebels-drone-attack-abu-dhabi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DRONE attack on Abu Dhabi has led to three oil tankers exploding and a fire at the airport, police have said. Responsibility for the attack has been claimed by Yemen’s Iran-backed Houthi rebels w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 10 richest men see wealth double during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2022/jan/17/world-10-richest-men-see-their-wealth-double-during-covid-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oxfam calls for windfall tax as 99% of world population takes a pay cut while top 10 incomes grow by $1bn a day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside pioneering site authorized to monitor people using drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/inside-a-pioneering-us-site-authorized-to-monitor-people-using-drugs/ar-AASONZX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailblazing Arab lawmaker shakes up Israeli politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-middle-east-israel-tel-aviv-9f570e7d01677e59cba3652c07fa7c75</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Mansour Abbas broke a longstanding taboo when he led his Arab party into Israel's governing coalition last year. The bold move appears to be paying dividends. Abbas, a once obscure politician, is the linchpin of the shaky union, securing hefty budgets and favorable policies for his constituents and even winning an audience with the king of Jordan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden puzzled by drones spotted over nuke power plants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-denmark-sweden-baltic-sea-2605c0d837b2a4b5ba43e89763841afc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Swedish authorities are puzzled by reports that drones last week were seen hovering over two nuclear power plants on the country's Baltic Sea coast. Police said Sunday that preliminary investigations have been launched, adding the probes are being handled locally by investigators but they are coordinated nationally by the Swedish police’s national operational department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific volcano erupts with explosive force, heard 5,000 miles away...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/how-the-tonga-volcano-generated-a-shock-wave-around-the-world/ar-AASQ9vj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After years of threats, Congress finally unleashes subpoena power on Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/after-years-of-threats-congress-finally-unleashed-its-subpoena-power-on-silicon-valley/ar-AASMFsM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body temperature may not really gauge covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/body-temperature-may-not-be-an-effective-gauge-of-covid-19/ar-AASPuVE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit named in Tex Terror...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/texas-synagogue-hostages-e6087528c4728c418ee6872f13778b71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLLEYVILLE, Texas (AP) — A rabbi who was among four people held hostage at a Texas synagogue said Sunday that their armed captor grew “increasingly belligerent and threatening” toward the end of the 10-hour standoff, which ended with an FBI SWAT team rushing into the building and the captor's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Biden's first year, virus and disunity rage on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-one-year-07788eba2c1eb84de0edf3dbe3f2d412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — From the inaugural platform, President Joe Biden saw American sickness on two fronts — a disease of the national spirit and the one from the rampaging coronavirus — and he saw hope, because leaders always must see that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Oath Keepers and founder, Jan. 6 was weeks in making...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-oath-keepers-stewart-rhodes-0c30d5cb0724c623a27f2eb39da20285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Two days after the election on Nov. 3, 2020, the Oath Keepers were already convinced that victory had been stolen from President Donald Trump and members of the far-right militia group were making plans to march on the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wins lottery for the FOURTH time...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/money/4476369/man-wins-for-fourth-time-lottery-pennsylvania/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN has scooped $1million this month in his FOURTH lottery win since 1999 – scoring a whopping $4.6million in total. Mike “Lucky” Luciano won his latest prize from a $20 scratch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Year is It? Nearly Third of iTunes Chart Taken By Oldies...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/16/what-year-is-it-nearly-a-third-of-the-itunes-top-100-taken-by-oldies-new-releases-not-catching-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DOGS 'DULL' DESANTIS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-privately-slams-desantis-ba0ce3aa-839f-41c9-83a1-4b9dc26649d9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president is irked by the Florida governor's popularity and refusal to rule out running against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump AZ Speech Proves Shock Comic Act Has 'Jumped the Shark'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trumps-arizona-speech-proves-shock-170114287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROBYN BECK/AFP via Getty ImagesThere was a time when Donald Trump made news with his rallies—when he said things that utterly shocked us. Who could forget the firestorm he started, for example, when he went after Colin Kaepernick and other NFL players who knelt during the national anthem in 2017, or earlier that year when he called Barack Obama “the founder of ISIS”?Trump’s performance in Arizona on Saturday night—his first rally in months and his much-hyped chance to respond to the one-year ann</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From pandemic to endemic: Can 2022 succeed where 2021 failed?</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/from-pandemic-to-endemic-can-2022-succeed-where-2021-failed/articleshow/88914210.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The appetite for economically damaging lockdowns is long gone. Vaccines are protecting swathes of the population, and there is even hope that omicron, with its frenetic spread and less powerful punch, may be hastening the path to the pandemics exit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
