<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Raves blamed?</title>
      <link>https://edm.com/news/violent-crime-spikes-in-tulum-hotel-association-blames-raves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reported rise in drug demand aligns with an increase of local electronic dance music parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI emails hacked in huge breach...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4059641/fbi-hacked-spam-email-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) had its email system hacked this morning, sending out fake messages about cyberattacks. The rogue emails, sent from the FBI’s email infrastructure are said…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Caribbean jewel of Tulum deals with rapid rise in violence...</title>
      <link>https://mexiconewsdaily.com/news/analysis/caribbean-jewel-of-tulum-deals-with-rapid-rise-in-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mexiconewsdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between January and September 2021, the Quintana Roo resort town recorded 65 murders, an 80.5% increase over the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Hell: 3 In 5 Banning Unjabbed Relatives From Gatherings...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/unvaccinated-relatives-banned-holiday-family-gatherings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two-thirds of vaccinated Americans are banning unvaccinated family members from their holiday gatherings this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC chair's challenging bid to avert midterm defeat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-jaime-harrison-south-carolina-congress-elections-197d1c896908cebc6f4d8945c0b97fb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's not particularly close to the White House. He's never won statewide office or a seat in Congress. And just last year, he lost a high-profile Senate race by double digits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan thanks NBA star for support as Oz pledges help in island's defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/taiwan-thanks-nba-star-kanter-for-support-as-australia-pledges-to-help-us-in-island-e2-80-99s-defense/ar-AAQEUAS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ships Keep Coming, Pushing Port Logjam and Waits to Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/ships-keep-coming-pushing-us-port-logjam-and-waits-to-records/ar-AAQEMaZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW VARIANT IN FRANCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/new-covid-variant-found-in-france-reason-for-panic-or-not-quite-yet-684878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spike protein of the variant known as B.1.640 has some unprecedented mutations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Asghari: More Than Mr. Spears...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/13/more-than-mr-britney-spears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Sam Asghari is a nascent actor and erstwhile personal trainer. But this highly polite, handsome and friendly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants Say Belarusians Took Them to EU Border and Supplied Wire Cutters...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/13/migrants-say-belarusians-took-them-to-e-u-border-and-supplied-wire-cutters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SULAIMANIYA, Iraq — The sudden surge of migrants to Belarus from the Middle East that is now the focus of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are going to bring 100'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/lawyer-for-arbery-e2-80-99s-family-on-objection-to-black-pastors-in-court-e2-80-98we-are-going-to-bring-100-e2-80-b2/ar-AAQE66Z?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense attorney Kevin Gough raised eyebrows when he objected this week to “high-profile members of the African-American community” and specifically "Black pastors" attending the murder trial for the killing of Ahmaud Arbery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTEMPT</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/former-trump-adviser-steve-bannon-indicted-federal-grand-jury-contempt-n1283834</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The indictment is a first: No one has been prosecuted for contempt of Congress when executive privilege was asserted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For some, exile from MAGAworld is less appealing than prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-some-exile-from-trumpworld-is-less-appealing-than-prison/ar-AAQDZEK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The question is: for how many?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verhoeven Says to Stop Fearing On-Screen Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/paul-verhoeven-does-storyboards-for-sex-scenes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Verhoeven doesn’t understand why there’s such taboo around sex scenes. In fact, he says, he plans them meticulously. “If you feel, like I do, that one of the most important things in life is sexuality, then I don’t know why there would be a problem to show sexuality,” the Basic Instinct director told MovieMaker. […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online slots players say company refusing to pay jackpots...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/online-slots-players-say-company-refusing-to-pay-jackpots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania woman is suing the manufacturer of a popular online slots game, claiming it wrongly refused to pay her a $100,000 jackpot due to “a bug” in the product. She's not alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANNON INDICTED, AGAIN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/12/politics/steve-bannon-indicted/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal grand jury has returned an indictment against former Donald Trump adviser Steve Bannon for contempt of Congress, the Justice Department announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD NUMBER  QUIT JOBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/12/economy/job-openings-quits-september/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record 4.4 million Americans quit their jobs in September as the sheer volume of available jobs is empowering workers to have their pick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends threats to 'hang' Pence...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-hang-mike-pence-january-6-audio-4f147245-becf-4766-ac60-7acece6862be.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"[W]ell, the people were very angry."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGGEST SHOW ON CABLE SINCE 2017...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/yellowstone-season-4-premiere-draws-12-7-million-total-viewers-in-live3-1234873188/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nielsen Live+3 ratings numbers are in, and Yellowstone has smashed more of its own records. Sunday night’s Season 4 premiere drew 12.7 million total viewers across Paramount Network and t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY FREE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/britney-spears-conservatorship-hearing-termination-1234873024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 13 years, #FreeBritney is now more than just a hashtag. “The court agrees to the termination of the conservatorship,” Los Angeles Superior Court Judge Brenda Penny ruled Friday, i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES 2 YEARS IN JAIL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/steve-bannon-donald-trump-congress-mark-meadows-subpoenas-70fcf59323df874b4a0def1f4c1222cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Steve Bannon, a longtime ally of former President Donald Trump, was indicted Friday on two counts of criminal contempt of Congress after he defied a subpoena from the House committee investigating the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW COVID HOTSPOTS USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-colorado-united-states-michigan-public-health-f2d9ccb4092fd4651d055dbf7083f259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The contagious delta variant is driving up COVID-19 hospitalizations in the Mountain West and fueling disruptive outbreaks in the North, a worrisome sign of what could be ahead this winter in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY FREE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4055131/britney-spears-conservatorship-ends-judge-rules-pop-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’s conservatorship has finally ended after 13 years without requiring any further mental evaluation as Judge Brenda Penny ruled in favor of the pop star. Back in September, Brit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada spy service increasingly worried about violent online rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211112210312-134d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANADA-EXTREMISTS/ (PIX):Canada spy service increasingly worried about violent online rhetoric</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAIL BLAZERS CEO resigns amid workplace investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/portland-trail-blazers-ceo-chris-mcgowan-resigns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Blazers announced CEO Chris McGowan would resign effective on Nov. 26. Chief commercial officer Dewayne Hankins will take over the role of team president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY FREE...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/skbaer/britney-spears-free-conservatorship-ends</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling marks the end of what she has described as a "demoralizing" and traumatizing chapter of her life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo, married aide allegedly caught 'making out'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/12/ex-gov-cuomo-married-aide-derosa-allegedly-caught-making-out-trooper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Gov. Andrew Cuomo and his then-top aide, Melissa DeRosa, were allegedly spotted by a state police bodyguard “making out on the sidewalk like high schoolers,” The Post has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why giant companies suddenly splitting into pieces...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/12/investing/johnson-johnson-ge-toshiba-splits/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking up is the newest craze for ginormous global companies. Johnson &amp; Johnson, Toshiba and GE announced plans to split into multiple entities this week. The trend may have only just begun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINS': Andrew Sullivan says America's democracy at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/andrew-sullivan-conservatism-60-minutes-2021-11-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative author says the January 6 insurrection was a wake-up call for Americans to open their minds to compromise as the U.S. Constitution's authors intended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board president kept sensitive personal information on protesting parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/arizona-school-board-personal-information-parents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than six hundred parents in Scottsdale, Arizona, are demanding the resignation of the school board president after a shocking revelation. The president or his father appears to have kept a dossier on 47 parents who dared to speak out against his policies at school board meetings – a dossier complete with Social Security numbers, background checks, divorce decrees, mortgage documents, trade certifications, and screenshots of Facebook posts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With staff 'exhausted,' schools cancel class, return to remote learning...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/stretched-too-thin-staff-exhausted-115710003.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts worry many students will suffer if they miss classes, but say exhausted teachers need a break after helping families through the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRUDEN SUES NFL...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/11/12/jon-gruden-suing-roger-goodell-nfl-leaked-emails/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Raiders head coach Jon Gruden is going to war with the NFL. He&amp;amp;#039;s suing the NFL and Goodell over his leaked emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUTATION LINKED TO REMDESIVIR RESISTANCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mutation-linked-to-remdesivir-resistance-found-in-covid-patient/ar-AAQzvTg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resistance to Gilead Sciences Inc.’s antiviral remdesivir was found in coronavirus samples collected from an immune-compromised patient treated with the drug for a persistent Covid-19 infection, researchers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO SPIKE A 'MYSTERY'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/11/12/covid-surge-cases-trajectory-colorado-state-university/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of statisticians from Colorado State University that has spent the pandemic helping the State of Colorado forecast spikes in COVID cases says the recent surge is mysterious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Who Flew To Space With William Shatner Killed In Small Plane Crash...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/12/glen-de-vries-plane-crash-new-jersey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;De Vries flew to space last month with Jeff Bezos' company Blue Origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May lead to higher tax bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/heres-how-rising-inflation-may-lead-to-higher-tax-bills.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As inflation surges, the IRS has boosted federal income tax brackets and other provisions for 2022. However, certain fixed provisions may cause higher bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reversed Paralysis in Mice. Humans Could Be Next...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/injectable-gel-reversed-paralysis-mice-165207056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samuel I. Stupp Laboratory/Northwestern UniversityParalysis might one day be as easy to cure as a single injection of a drug, if some promising new results stand up to scrutiny. Scientists at Northwestern University reversed paralysis in mice with spinal cord injuries by injecting them with a self-assembling gel that can repair tissues.We don’t yet know if the findings, published in the journal Science, will translate over to humans. But for the nearly 1.5 million people in the U.S. living with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter arrested on suspicion of murdering mother...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Bay-Area-reporter-suspected-murder-16613055.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bay Area reporter was arrested Monday on suspicion of stabbing his 74-year-old mother...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK TROOPS DEPLOYED...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/british-troops-deployed-poland-belarus-border-migration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The troops will repair or fortify fencing rather than help police the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum computing problem rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/personal-finance/crypto/cryptocurrency-faces-a-quantum-computing-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two cutting-edge technologies that promise to revolutionize entire fields may be on a collision course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbon footprint of COP26 in Glasgow more than DOUBLE that of previous conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.scotsman.com/news/environment/cop26-carbon-footprint-of-cop26-in-glasgow-more-than-double-that-of-cop25-3453546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scotsman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carbon emissions from the Glasgow climate conference are expected to reach more than double the amount pumped into the atmosphere during the last COP, The Scotsman can reveal, with the event on track to be the most polluting summit of its kind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick bald eagles acting strangely in Maryland prompts investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/sick-bald-eagles-found-in-carroll-county-state-wildlife-officials-investigating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five bald eagles were found acting strangely and seemingly sick in northern Maryland, prompting an investigation by state wildlife officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man threatens to kill Republican congressman who voted for infrastructure bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/long-island-man-arrested-for-threatening-congressman-garbarino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long Island man has been arrested for making a death threat against a Republican congressional member who voted for the $1 trillion infrastructure package, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China slams U.S. democracy as 'game of the rich'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/china-criticizes-us-democracy-while-promoting-xis-growing-power.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remarks come as Chinese President Xi Jinping became the third leader to oversee the politically significant approval of a "historical resolution" this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would nation survive a civil war?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/11/would-america-survive-a-civil-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US army could not withstand an insurgency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKLE HAS EYE ON WHITE HOUSE?</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/meghan-markle-wins-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Meghan bestrides the world like a well-coiffed Colossus, the question isn’t whether she could run. It’s whether she’s already started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astroworld Countdown to Catastrophe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/astroworld-festival-deaths-travis-scott-entertainment-houston-music-5628f631f335ea5d182852ba0116d2cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anticipation had been building for hours, but never more than now, as the red numerals on the countdown clock disappeared and the first synthesized notes vibrated. An image of an eagle in a fireball hovered above the stage, a neon red tunnel appeared and eight towers of flames rose to the sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Drake went to strip club after Festival of Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4050746/drake-went-to-a-strip-club-day-after-deadly-astroworld/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAKE went to a strip club with his crew for a private party a day after the deadly Astroworld disaster – which saw nine killed and around 100 injured, The Sun can confirm. In deleted posts s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Committee seeks criminal charges on Meadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jan-6-committee-criminal-charges-mark-meadows-745bc38c-d99f-44e4-8ab8-aed5258bb055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the Jan. 6 committee's third threat of criminal prosecution made in recent weeks against non-cooperative witnesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Breakdown: Dry Cleaners Out Of Hangers, Silverware Shortage For Restaurants, MORE...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/11/supply-chain-impacts-cleaners-hangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supply chain crisis is impacting local businesses that you may not have expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211112143634-x47sh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPA-MIGRANTS/BELARUS-NATO (URGENT):NATO says it remains vigilant over risk of escalation at Belarus borders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER SENTIMENT 10-YEAR LOW</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-consumer-sentiment-drops-10-150000933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for the New Economy Daily newsletter, follow us @economics and subscribe to our podcast.Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesHong Kong's New Museum Tries to Please Art World — and BeijingFarmers Take on ‘Post-Apocalyptic’ Food CrisisGreece’s Popular Islands Are Crowded — With PlasticU.S. consumer sentiment unexpectedly collapsed in early November as Americans grew increasingly concerned about rising prices and the inflation</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
