<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER record month for illegal immigration...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/april-another-record-month-illegal-immigration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will it matter?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Seize 1,000 Guns from Upscale LA Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/08/us/massive-seizure-of-guns-la-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 guns were found in a home in the upscale Los Angeles neighborhood Holmby Hills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sanctuary City' Oakland Near-Broke...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/09/sanctuary-city-oakland-near-broke-will-use-gas-tax-money-to-keep-lights-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City of Oakland is in such dire financial straits that it is planning to use $2.9 million from the state gas tax to keep its lights on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Woos Silicon Valley with Five Fundraisers in Hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/09/pete-buttigieg-woos-silicon-valley-at-five-fundraisers-in-one-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Pete Buttigieg is planning five fundraisers across Silicon Vally on Friday, in an effort to bring more tech donors to his campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona tribe refuses Trump's wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2206322?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOHONO O'ODHAM NATION, Ariz. -- Verlon Jose had long vowed President Donald Trump would build a wall along his tribe's 75-mile border with Mexico only "over my dead body."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL WARMING:  Spring snowstorm breaks 117-year-old record in Minnesota...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/photos-may-storm-brings-heavy-snow-slippery-travel-to-minnesota/70008224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No prison for mother after baby dies from drug-laced breast milk...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/no-prison-for-mother-after-baby-dies-from-drug-laced-breast-milk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania mother who prosecutors say killed her 11-week-old son with a lethal mix of drugs in her breast milk is not going to prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Scholar Found Dead In Bathroom At San Francisco Airport; Languished On Floor For Day...</title>
      <link>http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/05/08/scholar-with-stanford-ties-found-dead-in-bathroom-at-sfo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of a well-respected East Asian scholar with ties to Stanford was discovered inside the Cathay Pacific Airlines lounge bathroom at San Francisco International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLIONS:  Top quant hedge fund in performance meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.fnlondon.com/articles/redemptions-hit-quant-king-aqr-in-performance-slump-20190509  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fnlondon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quantitative fund manager had a difficult 2018 and its alternative risk premia funds continue to struggle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURDOCH TAKES STAGE FOR FOX!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/rupert-and-lachlan-murdoch-kick-off-fox-investor-day-we-are-returning-to-our-roots-1202610699/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch began Fox Corp.’s investor day, appearing solo onstage to emphasize the effectiveness of the company’s evolution. The architect of the Fox empire said even before the mil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Promises Hollywood Pals He'll Undo Trump Era...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/joe-biden-hollywood-fundraiser-donald-trump-jeffrey-katzenberg-byron-allen-aubrey-plaza-pete-buttigieg-1202610619/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just over a month after Donald Trump was in town for a pricey Beverly Hills fundraiser, Joe Biden tonight told a deep-pocketed Hollywood crowd in the same neighborhood that the time for change is h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds secretly release 168,000 into communities...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/8/feds-release-168k-illegal-immigrant-family-members/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICE has already released 168,000 illegal immigrant family members into the U.S. this fiscal year, and the number is likely to surge as the border situation deteriorates, a top deportation official told Congress on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCKETMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-05-09/north-korea-launches-new-missiles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TWEET WIPES $2 TRILLION OFF MARKET...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9034671/trump-global-markets-tweet-china-tariffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump wiped nearly $2TRILLION off global markets with a single Twitter blast vowing to double tariffs on Chinese goods after they “broke” a crucial trade deal. The US president r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Video, Humanoid Crosses Narrow Balance Beam Like Cakewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/science/in-video-humanoid-robot-crosses-narrow-balance-beam-like-a-cakewalk-2034978</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At first glance, a humanoid robot walking between two platforms across several cinder blocks may look like a simple feat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of Spanish coins that predate Columbus found deep in Utah desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7009641/Mystery-Spanish-coins-Utah-desert-predate-Columbus-200-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spanish treasure that predates the arrival of Columbus by 200 years has been found in Utah. The two coins, minted in Madrid, were found in Glen Canyon National Recreation Area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>140 Migrants Cross into South Texas in 3 Hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/05/09/exclusive-photos-140-migrants-cross-into-south-texas-in-3-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a three-hour span Sunday, 140 Central American migrants crossed into Texas from the cartel-controlled city of Reynosa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adults spending big on video games, playing on smartphones...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-videogames/u-s-adults-are-spending-big-on-video-games-playing-mostly-on-smartphones-idUSKCN1SF1DC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average American video gamer is 33 years old, prefers to play on their smart...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey brutally beaten by rest of troop 'because can't get erection any more'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/monkey-brutally-beaten-rest-troop-15019747 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 18-year-old Barbary macaques was head of 22 other monkeys but they turned on him and killed their aging leader</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SACRIFICED SECURITY FOR CLICKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/facebook-co-founder-calls-for-break-up-of-facebook-zuckerberg-sacrificed-security-and-civility-for-clicks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Mark is a good, kind person. But I'm angry that his focus on growth led him to sacrifice security and civility for clicks."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Releasing Word Version That Makes Grammar 'Politically Correct'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/microsoft-to-release-version-of-word-that-makes-your-grammar-politically-correct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New features will screen out 'offensive' language</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST BLOOD EVER?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/entertainment/films/1124862/IT-Chapter-2-Pennywise-clown-more-shocking-Bill-Skarsgard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT: CHAPTER 2 will show the return of Pennywise to horrify the Losers’ Club as adults - and Bill Skarsgard has revealed that there are surprises in store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC Fires Radio Host Over Racist Royal Baby Tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/14223a22b5774000a507034b7c9a22c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A BBC disc jockey has been fired after using a picture of a chimpanzee in a tweet about the royal baby born to Meghan the Duchess of Sussex and her husband Prince Harry. Danny...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/video/facebook-co-founder-calls-on-government-to-break-up-tech-giant-59281989995</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Hughes, a co-founder of Facebook and former college roommate of Mark Zuckerberg, sits down for an exclusive interview with NBC’s Kate Snow to sound the alarm on the tech giant and Zuckerberg’s “staggering” world influence. The full interview airs Thursday on NBC Nightly News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple must pay $600K for removing oak tree from their property, judge rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/judge-orders-northern-california-couple-to-pay-600000-for-removing-oak-tree</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge ordered a Northern California couple this week to pay nearly $600,000 for uprooting an almost 200-year-old oak tree from their property that was protected under a conservation easement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GORE-TEX EYE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2019-gore-artificial-cornea/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Dem field will be 'winnowed out pretty quickly'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442853-biden-dem-field-will-be-winnowed-out-pretty-quickly-in-early-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden on Wednesday predicted that the vast field of Democratic presidential contenders will be “winnowed out pretty quickly” in early 2020,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little soldiers: Controversy over Russian children in WWII uniform...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/little-soldiers-controversy-over-russian-children-wwii-uniform-110757970--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When kindergarten staff told Lyubov Sobol her five-year-old daughter needed to come in wearing a miniature military uniform ahead of Russia's World War II Victory Day, she was shocked and angry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK CO-FOUNDER CALLS FOR GOVT TO BREAK UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/facebook-co-founder-says-zuckerberg-not-accountable-calls-government-break-n1003606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Hughes, who started Facebook with Mark Zuckerberg, joins a growing chorus of privacy advocates and politicians who have called for antitrust action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON accused of illegally collecting data on children...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/05/08/amazon-accused-of-using-echo-dot-kids-to-illegally-collect-data-on-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Craig Timberg | The Washington Post A coalition of 19 consumer and privacy groups plans to file a complaint Thursday alleging that Amazon’s Echo Dot Kids Edition is illegally collecting voice…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Real Estate Flippers Get Their First Taste of Losing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-09/young-real-estate-flippers-get-their-first-taste-of-losing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA FIRES AGAIN AS US ENVOY VISITS SEOUL...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a5fc6c7710604d11925251b5e5827bf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea on Thursday fired two suspected short-range missiles from the country's western area, South Korea's military said, the North's second weapons launch in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspense builds for Supreme Court moves on abortion, LGBT cases...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/442806-suspense-builds-for-supreme-court-moves-on-abortion-lgbt-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court has yet to announce whether it will take up two of this year’s most closely watched cases, fueling speculation about the justices’ closed-door deliberations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd time in 5 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/north-korea-fires-missiles-possible-launch-south-korea-today-live-updates-2019-05-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong Un regime fired short-range missiles over the weekend, and may have just done so again during senior Trump envoy's visit to South Korea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires again as US envoy visits...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-korea-fires-again-us-envoy-visits-085533782.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea welcomed a US envoy's visit to Seoul by firing at least one projectile for the second time in a week Thursday, the South's military said, as Pyongyang seeks to up the ante in deadlocked nuclear negotiations with Washington. The launch came after North Korea carried out a military</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The only way is down: Subterranean survival warning...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/only-way-down-subterranean-survival-warning-022606429--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solutions to the biggest threats facing our planet lie underground, according to experts who insist climate change, overpopulation and food shortages can all be tackled by going subterranean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK becoming digital graveyard  -- and gift to future... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2019/05/08/facebook-is-becoming-vast-digital-graveyard-gift-future/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is an astonishing repository of daily life. We can't let it disappear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump donor Cindy Yang sues MIAMI HERALD...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/news/20190508/spa-owner-turned-trump-donor-cindy-yang-sues-miami-herald-claiming-defamation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Miami Herald attorney warned in a letter to Yang's lawyer that the Trump family and associates could be summoned as witnesses in what will likely be a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT FIRES BACK:  WHAT IS TRUMP HIDING IN HIS TAX RETURNS?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/08/opinion/trump-taxes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest revelations about President Trump’s past tax reports underscore the importance of examining his more recent returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human lifespan could soon pass 100 years!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/08/techs-next-big-disruption-could-be-delaying-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the biggest investment opportunities over the next decade will be in companies working to delay human death, Bank of America says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS HOLD BARR IN CONTEMPT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d64338bc6606456d978c33f11d2cf2b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House Judiciary Committee voted Wednesday to hold Attorney General William Barr in contempt of Congress, escalating the Democrats' extraordinary legal battle with the Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside sex-crazed final weeks at elite colleges...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/08/inside-the-sex-crazed-final-weeks-at-americas-elite-colleges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Avendano, Columbia College’s 2018 senior class president, received only one piece of advice from his predecessor. “She said, ‘Your best friends are going to ask who put them down for senior sc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders 3-year-old to undergo chemo...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/noah-mcadams-chemotherapy-hearing-tampa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 3-year-old cancer patient must undergo chemotherapy over the next&amp;nbsp;28 days despite the wishes of his parents, a Tampa judge ruled Wednesday afternoon. But she did not make a decision about treatment options after that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chickenpox, measles cases among children hidden in trucks... </title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/mexican-officials-find-289-migrants-in-tractor-trailer-rigs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in the northern Mexico border state of Tamaulipas say they have detained 289 Central American migrants, including some children with measles and other illnesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia community living in fear: 2 deaths, dozens of prostitutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/2-investigates/2-deaths-dozens-of-prostitutes-and-neighbors-living-in-fear-when-will-it-end-/947280323</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DeKalb County community told Channel 2 it is watching prostitutes work, get killed and even solicit around kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Police Arrest No. 2 Leader of Opposition-Controlled Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2019-05-08/the-latest-police-take-no-2-leader-of-venezuela-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Denver decriminalizes psychedelic mushrooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/05/08/denver-psychedelic-magic-mushroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denver is poised to become the first city in the nation to effectively decriminalize psychedelic mushrooms after final ballot-counting flipped Initiative 301’s margin in favor of narrow passa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenes from new Cold War unfolding at top of world...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/2018/10/new-cold-war-brews-as-arctic-ice-melts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scenes from inside the Arctic Circle show a rapidly growing military presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First unionized presidential campaign in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/campaigns/bernie-2020-becomes-first-unionized-presidential-campaign-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders ratified a collective bargaining agreement for his presidential campaign last week, the first presidential campaign in history to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ignore International Grand Committee on 'Fake News' Request...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/mark-zuckerberg-faces-subpoena-in-canada-over-fake-news-on-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook CEO reportedly didn't respond to requests to appear before an international committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark, Sheryl face Canadian Parliament subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/facebooks-mark-zuckerberg-sheryl-sandberg-face-subpoena-from-canadian-parliament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook brass have ignored repeated requests to appear before a committee of officials from 10 nations, according to a Canadian Member of Parliament</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liz Cheney accuses Dems of helping Putin undermine democracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/gop-rep-liz-cheney-accuses-democrats-of-helping-vladimir-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Liz Cheney (R-WY) lashed out at congressional Democrats Wednesday, accusing them of "undermining our democracy and helping Vladimir Putin."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World-famous chef interrogated at LAX over duffel full of piranhas...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/food/la-fo-virgilio-martinez-central-piranhas-lax-peru-20190508-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgilio Martinez of Central in Peru successfully brought 40 frozen piranhas through LAX to cook two dinners as part of Food Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare event to bring secretive BLUE ORIGIN out of shadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/08/tech/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-rocket-company/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos may be ready to bring Blue Origin, his secretive space company, out of the shadows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk v Bezos: Military rocket rivalry may reshape national security...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1603659/elon-musk-and-jeff-bezos-wrangle-over-us-military-rockets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force has been terrible at buying rockets. The current contract battle could shape American national security— and the future of private space companies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University sprinter impaled by javelin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dawgnation.com/track/details-emerge-after-uga-sprinter-accidentally-pierced-by-javelin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dawgnation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS -- Whenever someone hears the words "pierced" and "javelin," they're left to expect the worst. But a UGA track and field athlete who recently suffered that fate apparently is going to be OK. Elija Godwin, a freshmen sprinter for the Bulldogs' men's team, was seriously injured when he fell into a javelin during</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy DONKEYS Calm Students Ahead Of Finals...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/these-animals-work-miracles-therapy-donkeys-calm-college-students-ahead-final-exams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add therapy donkeys to the list of options for college students who want to lower stress levels ahead of final exams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetically engineered virus prolongs life...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/05/08/phage-therapy-how-genetically-engineered-viruses-may-have-prolonged-teens-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While phage experts were excited by the work, clinicians wonder to what extent it can be scaled up to combat the global crisis of antibiotic resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUBS investigating fan's alleged racist hand gesture...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sports/cubs/ct-spt-cubs-doug-glanville-racist-gesture-wrigley-field-20190508-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cubs are investigating an on-air incident involving a racist gesture behind NBC Sports Chicago reporter Doug Glanville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers Clone Phone Number In Elaborate YELP Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/elaborate-scheme-yelp-imposters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local police said this is an elaborate scheme they’ve never dealt with before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Producer accused of sex misconduct was fired because he's a man...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/08/news-producer-accused-of-sex-misconduct-was-fired-because-hes-a-man-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former employee at a Connecticut TV station is suing the ABC affiliate’s parent company, claiming he was singled out because he’s a man after three female colleagues accused him of sexual miscond…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA to revise sex ed guidance for teachers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6b4018eaebb49bf8ddc63aee0074182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California is close to overhauling its guidance for teaching sex education in public schools, offering teachers a framework for talking to kindergartners about gender...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore passes 'fake news' law despite fierce criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190508-singapore-passes-fake-news-law-despite-fierce-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore passes 'fake news' law despite fierce criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  NFL Network slashed; $20M cuts...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/08/nfl-network-shows-slashed-tensions-rise-after-20m-cuts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL Network is being forced to cut $20 million out of its projected budget and, in the process, already has eliminated at least five shows, including one that featured Deion Sanders, The Post h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: High Schooler Who Sued Over Chickenpox Vaccine -- Gets Chickenpox!</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/05/08/student-who-sued-over-chickenpox-policy-comes-down-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high school senior who went to court after he was barred from playing basketball because he wasn’t vaccinated against chickenpox has come down with the illness, his lawyer said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY lawmakers jump into fight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/116f602be4e34de2b73a35fe7ac02cb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York's Democrat-controlled Senate approved a bill easily Wednesday that would allow three congressional committees to get access to President Donald Trump's state tax...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Drama: Campaign Reset, Advisers Clashing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/08/us/politics/kamala-harris-2020-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the months since 20,000 people gathered to kick off her candidacy, Ms. Harris has found herself in a vise, squeezed by factions in her party and her own campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Pans Mayor Pete: 'Boring,' Low Energy...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/nbcs-craig-melvin-calls-mayor-pete-kind-of-boring/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melvin said on Wednesday that he doesn't predict South Bend mayor Pete Buttigieg's candidacy will go very far, calling him "kind of boring."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team claims unfamiliar position: Front-runner...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1a7612014544fe99a97fe57d2f04896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump spent his first campaign as an underdog, written off by the political establishment and down on his own chances on Election Night. But as he and his team...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: 850 open investigations into domestic terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/70168e7cf4d5481c8a38589bbfb40483</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The FBI has more than 850 open investigations into domestic terrorism across the country, and the threat continues to grow, top counterterrorism officials said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Miami Man Accused Of Threatening To 'Explode Jewish Community'...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/08/miami-man-accused-of-threatening-to-explode-the-jewish-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Miami man was arrested after Miami Beach police said he threatened to "explode the Jewish community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans goes through grisly castration to 'become a nullo'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9019798/nullo-removes-penis-testicles-knife-washington-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN IT worker has revealed how he hacked off his own penis and testicles with an ultra-sharp knife in a gruesome bid to become a genitalia-free “nullo.” Trent Gates, 23, from Washington DC, cut off …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China backtracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-backtracking-exclusiv/exclusive-china-backtracked-on-almost-all-aspects-of-u-s-trade-deal-sources-idUSKCN1SE0WJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diplomatic cable from Beijing arrived in Washington late on Friday night, wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders shores up superdels...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442617-sanders-shores-up-dem-superdelegate-support</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost a year after Donald Trump beat Hillary Clinton, a group of about 20 Democratic National Committee (DNC) members met on the sidelines of the committee’s meeting in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says rocket drill was in self-defense...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190508131901-o61wq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-North Korea says recent rocket drill was</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
