<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CHINA FLIES MORE WARPLANES OVER TAIWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-10-04/brazen-china-steadily-ramps-up-warplane-flights-in-taiwans-airspace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing appears to believe now is the time to test America’s resolve in support of the island nation as it boasts of its military might.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-n-c-o-m-f-o-r-t-a-b-l-e...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/tom-brady-is-hardly-ever-uncomfortable-his-return-to-new-england-was/ar-AAP7AV1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a strange night in New England, Tom Brady beat the Patriots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang leaves Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/andrew-yang-democrat-independent-voting-794f9190-ccdb-4af4-80b5-ec4df7884f88.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yang said he is "confident that no longer being a Democrat is the right thing."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Turns Negative for 2021...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-turns-negative-2021-higher-144653874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Amazon.com Inc. shares fell sharply on Monday, taking the e-commerce giant into negative territory for the year, as a sustained rise in Treasury yields is hurting the earnings outlook for companies with high valuations. Most Read from BloombergChristmas at Risk as Supply Chain ‘Disaster’ Only Gets WorseReshaped by Crisis, an ‘Anti-Biennial’ Reimagines ChicagoThis Is What Europe’s Green Future Looks LikeWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsAn Unapologetic Old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CILLIZZA:  Majority shakier than ever...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2021/10/04/politics/democrats-house-senate-2022/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sausage-making on display over the past week in Washington was bad enough for Democrats trying to preserve their wafer-thin majorities in the House and Senate next year. That all of the back and forth didn't produce any actual sausage is even worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Chatting With Strangers Improves Well-Being...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/deep-conversations-strangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people will actually benefit from having a deep and meaningful chat with someone they don't know, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING WARNS USA</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211004140105-f7yd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/USA-MINISTRY (URGENT):China says U.S. should stop supporting Taiwan separatist forces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR TREK'S Captain Kirk rocketing into space next week...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/william-shatner-star-trek-blue-origin-space-jeff-bezos-e10877d624a4cc0be9385585c2647cdd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Star Trek’s Captain Kirk is rocketing into space this month — boldly going where no other sci-fi actors have gone. Jeff Bezos’ space travel company, Blue Origin, announced Monday that William Shatner will blast off from West Texas on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil at 7-year high...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-economy-prices-opec-54c606517408481b9f99895b168a07cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — Oil prices jumped Monday after OPEC and allied oil producing countries stayed with their gradual approach to restoring output slashed during the pandemic, agreeing to add only 400,000 barrels per day in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden admin takes aim at Big Chicken. But goose might not yet be cooked...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/the-biden-administration-takes-aim-at-big-chicken-but-its-goose-might-not-yet-be-cooked/ar-AAP7g3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poultry's possible pandemic profiteering gets a close look from the Biden administration, with other big meat companies' potential antitrust infractions getting extra scrutiny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MAINLAND MUST CRUSH'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/international/patrick-goodenough/warplanes-scramble-beijing-paper-calls-taiwans-govt-evil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese warplanes operating in the skies near Taiwan in record numbers prompted a statement of concern from the State Department on Sunday, as a Chinese Communist Party media outlet hailed what it called “a clear and unmistakable declaration of China’s sovereignty over the island.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists follow Sinema into bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/immigration-activists-follow-sinema-into-bathroom-demanding-action-on-reconciliation-bill/ar-AAP711C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinema has remained one of the few Democratic holdouts on the domestic spending bill, demanding that the $3.5 trillion price tag be reduced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother and son helped steal laptop from Pelosi office on Jan. 6. They have now been charged...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-mother-and-son-helped-steal-a-laptop-from-16507387.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After breaching the Capitol and walking through the office of House Speaker Nancy Pelosi,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of states with residents facing obesity rises to 16...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/number-states-residents-facing-obesity-121749763.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 16 states, at least 35 percent of adult residents are obese, an increase from nine states two years earlier, according to new data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. In all 50 states, however, more than 20 percent of adults are obese. Although the numbers vary from state to state, the highest prevalence of obesity was found in states in the Midwest and South.Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important and interesting stories from The Washington Post. Looking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA FLIES WARPLANES OVER TAIWAN</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211004121352-8yv5l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/ (URGENT):Taiwan reports surge in Chinese aircraft in defence zone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax-the-Rich Era in Nordics Showing Signs of Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report/tax-the-rich-era-in-nordic-region-is-showing-signs-of-a-comeback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the pandemic mostly behind them, Nordic countries are placing themselves in the vanguard of global economies trying to get rich people to fund public finances more in the aftermath of the ordeal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Now Defeated Every NFL Team...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/10/04/tom-brady-win-over-patriots-beaten-every-nfl-team-brees-manning-marino/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a win over the Patriots on Sunday night, Tom Brady has now beaten everyone in the NFL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX intensely popular 'SQUID GAME' worth hype -- much deeper than chilling violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/netflix-e2-80-99s-intensely-popular-e2-80-98squid-game-e2-80-99-is-worth-the-hype-e2-80-94-and-much-deeper-than-its-chilling-violence/ar-AAP7igY </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Superstar Cities Aren't What Used to Be...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/new-york-la-and-other-superstar-cities-aren-t-what-they-used-to-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s Superstar Cities Aren’t What They Used to Be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decade after Jobs' death, has APPLE traded magic for profit?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/decade-jobs-death-apple-traded-013632107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten years after Apple founder Steve Jobs' death, the firm has grown into a colossus of devices and services that is the world's most valuable company, but the tech legend's diehard fans lament its lost aura of revolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia test fires sub-launched hypersonic missile for first time...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211004064956-qrwkc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-MISSILES/ (TV):Russia test fires submarine-launched hypersonic Tsirkon missile for first time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prophet Muhammad Cartoonist Death Sparks Homicide Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/death-of-swedish-cartoonist-investigated-as-negligent-homicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prophet Muhammad Cartoonist Death Sparks Swedish Homicide Probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THREE-Day Work Week? Startup Experiments to Draw Talent...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/three-day-week-one-startup-093000327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A shortage of technology talent has Indian companies offering sweeteners like more vacation time and gender-neutral parental leave as they compete for graduates and professionals. One Bangalore startup is trying a more dramatic solution: a three-day work week.Fintech company Slice is offering new hires a three-day week with salary at 80% of the going market rate. This is a win-win approach that frees the workers to pursue other passions or interests -- or other gigs -- while still</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangland Murders Forcing Israel to Breaking Point...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/gangland-murders-forcing-israel-breaking-085940851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amhad Gharabli/GettyJERUSALEM—Benjamin Netanyahu has been out of office for all of 110 days, but for Arab citizens of Israel, post-Bibiism has become the era of emancipation. Decades of Arab community leaders have failed to inspire change in the country, leading to frustration, disenchantment and a growing social chasm between the mainstream Jewish experience and minority Arab lives.Since the start of 2021, almost 100 Arab citizens of Israel have been killed in street violence made possible by y</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force's X-37B robotic space plane wings past 500 days in Earth orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/x-37b-space-plane-500-days-in-orbit-otv-6-mission</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Sprawling Use of NDAs Now Threatens to Humiliate Him...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-sprawling-ndas-now-threatens-090037278.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photo GettyFor decades, Donald Trump has treasured Non-Disclosure and Non-Disparagement Agreements, using them to prevent staff and associates from divulging information about his political and corporate empires. But a recent court judgment has called into question just how iron-clad these agreements really are, potentially exposing Trump to many of the secrets he’s worked to keep private in all facets of his life.Just last week, the Trump NDA regime suffe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary's Leader Fights Criticism in USA via Vast Influence Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/04/hungarys-leader-fights-criticism-in-u-s-via-vast-influence-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Former Vice President Mike Pence turned up in Hungary last month to speak to a conference on conservative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheers, embraces in New England return...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32334823/tampa-bay-buccaneers-tom-brady-greeted-patriots-tribute-video-brady-cheers-embraces-new-england-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots honored quarterback Tom Brady with a one-minute video of his top highlights, which sparked the rain-soaked crowd to chant Brady's name in appreciation before he led the Buccaneers on to the field for Sunday night's game at Gillette Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY BEATS BELICHICK... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-tampa-bay-buccaneers-new-england-patriots-nick-folk-6d060206412a135a8d6d181dc1b9425f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. (AP) — Tom Brady brought two decades of touchdown passes, victories and championships to New England. He returned Sunday night and reminded his former team what they’re missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FACEBOOK manager alleges social network fed Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-business-misinformation-4a3640440769d9a241c47670facac213</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A data scientist who was revealed Sunday as the Facebook whistleblower says that whenever there was a conflict between the public good and what benefited the company, the social media giant would choose its own interests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY BEATS BELICHICK... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official source for NFL news, video highlights, fantasy football, game-day coverage, schedules, stats, scores and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feuding Dems hint at compromise on Biden's embattled agenda ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/feuding-democrats-hint-at-compromise-on-biden-s-embattled-agenda/ar-AAP5WiD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive Democrats signaled Sunday they are willing to compromise to get US President Joe Biden's sweeping domestic agenda through Congress, but a tough fight lay ahead to overcome deep party divisions. Former president Donald Trump, who still wields considerable power within the Republican party, blasted the spending plan in a statement Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAIPEI PREPS FOR BATTLE</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2021-10-04/taiwan-preparing-for-war-with-china/100511294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph Wu urges Australia to increase intelligence sharing and security cooperation with Taiwan and says the island is ready to defend itself if China launches a strike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Environmental catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/massive-oil-spill-fouls-beaches-170458223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive oil spill off of Southern California is fouling beaches and forced cancellation of an air show as officials raced to minimize damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY MONEY:  Vice Chair Traded Millions Day Before Powell Emergency Pandemic Statement...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/fed-vice-chair-clarida-traded-millions-one-day-powell-emergency-pandemic-statement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest ever leak of offshore data exposes financial secrets of rich and famous...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2021/oct/03/pandora-papers-biggest-ever-leak-of-offshore-data-exposes-financial-secrets-of-rich-and-powerful</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of documents reveal offshore deals and assets of more than 100 billionaires, 30 world leaders and 300 public officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of world leaders, politicians, billionaires, celebrities, religious leaders and drug dealers... MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/key-revelations-from-the-pandora-papers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AFP) - An investigation based on one of the biggest ever leaks of financial documents on Sunday (Oct 3) exposed a hidden world of shielded wealth belonging to hundreds of politicians and billionaires.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN and FOXNEWS Air Opposite Mandate Coverage -- At  EXACT Same Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-dan-abrams-mocks-dramatically-different-vax-mandate-coverage-on-cnn-and-fox-news-and-we-wonder-why-were-so-divided/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the "Mediaite Moments" segment of his new show, Dan Abrams flipped between CNN and Fox News to contrast their coverage of Covid vaccine mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA heading into new era of high inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-could-be-heading-into-an-era-of-high-inflation-that-produces-paltry-or-even-negative-real-returns-on-safe-assets-analyst-warns-11633016799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High inflation in the U.S. could last for an entire decade -- creating paltry inflation-adjusted returns on safe assets like Treasury bonds and weakening the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Egyptian killer whale with legs identified as new species...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/ancient-egyptian-killer-whale-with-legs-identified-as-new-species-680848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newly-discovered species of killer whale, dubbed Phiomicetus anubis, most likely roamed the Earth's oceans during the Eocene Period, around 56 to 34 million years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's Monte Carlo mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Secret-money-swanky-real-estate-and-a-Monte-16506084.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONACO - The apartment hangs over the blue waters of the Mediterranean beneath the Monte...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key findings...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Key-findings-from-the-Pandora-Papers-investigation-16506082.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pandora Papers is an investigation based on more than 11.9 million documents...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead birds, fish wash on beaches...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-california-wildlife-wetlands-oil-spills-05cbeb962f42ae50590715fb3546d56c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON BEACH, Calif. (AP) — Crude was no longer leaking from a Southern California pipeline believed to be the source of a massive oil spill that closed miles of popular beaches on Sunday, according to the head of the company that owns the facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Cops Plea In Dipping Sauce Rage Case...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/dipping-sauce-plea-105827</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 1--The McDonald's customer who called in a bomb threat to an Iowa restaurant because he did not receive dipping sauces with his 30-piece Chicken McNuggets order has pleaded guilty to a harass</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
