<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Harvard Hurts Asian Americans With 'Personal Rating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/justice-department-says-harvard-hurts-asian-americans-admissions-prospects-with-personal-rating-1535637680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department says Harvard University puts Asian-American applicants at a disadvantage through the school’s use of a subjective “personal rating.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi terrorist-turned-politician says worked with Iran to kill Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/josh-rogin/wp/2018/08/30/iraqi-terrorist-turned-politician-told-u-s-interrogators-he-worked-with-iran-to-kill-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly released interrogation reports shed new light on an old foe of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAPCHAT sorry that map called NYC 'Jewtropolis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7135583/snapchat-jewtropolis-snap-maps-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snapchat has apologised for a major gaffe that labelled New York City “Jewtropolis” on Snap Maps, leading users to blast it as “racist”. But the blunder – which is impacting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper blames tariffs for layoffs -- but reductions likely remain as tariffs overturned..</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/business/Tariffs-on-Canadian-newsprint-are-overturned_171322528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The International Trade Commission on Wednesday overturned a Trump administration decision to impose tariffs on Canadian newsprint, saying that U.S. paper producers are not harmed by new</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETA Pushes Memorial For LOBSTERS Killed In Crash...</title>
      <link>https://wgme.com/news/local/maine-dot-denies-request-from-peta-to-put-up-memorial-for-lobsters-killed-in-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK (WGME) -- The Maine Department of Transportation has denied a request from People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals to build a 5-foot tombstone memorial where lobsters may have died after a crash on Route 1 in Brunswick last week.Brunswick Pol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top search engine sues comedian over joke...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/30/technology/baidu-sues-comedian-china/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baidu is suing a comedian, demanding damages and a public apology, after he mocked the company and its CEO on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>229k+ teens get plastic surgery, fueled by socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/should-you-let-your-teenager-get-plastic-surgery-2018-08-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Society of Plastic Surgeons released new guidance for cosmetic procedures on teens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARGENTINA CURRENCY COLLAPSES; RATES HIKED TO 60%! IMF RESCUE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/argentina-crisis-peso-crashes-to-record-low-amid-imf-plea.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Argentina is struggling to cope with yet another financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Seeks AI to Match Criminals to Biometric Database...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/08/fbi-looking-tech-foil-fingerprint-obliteration/150908/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI wants artificial intelligence tools that can ID people with burnt, cut or otherwise altered fingerprints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA freezing accounts of customers suspected of not being citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article217095125.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bank of America has been accused of asking citizenship questions and for proof of residency, then freezing customers’ accounts after failing to properly recognize their current residency status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKE NEWS... FAKE SEARCH... FAKE SOCIALS... FAKE BOOKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-tweets-fake-everything-nbc-cnn-books-google-news-8ccb6e50-24cf-47dc-b547-34b2aa8e5e9f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, books, social media and Google searches are all in his Twitter sights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO American flag?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/canadian-first-man-actor-defends-omitting-american-flag-planting-on-moon-achievement-transcended-countries-and-borders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The late Neil Armstrong’s 1969 trip to the moon may have been “one small step for man, one giant leap for mankind,” but it was also a massive achievement for the United States. One of Armstrong’s first orders of business was to proudly plant the American flag, after all. But Ryan Gosling, the Canadian actor …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Monster' lizard menacing family in backyard. Even trappers stumped...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/broward/article217507540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A six-foot Nile or Asian monitor lizard has eluded trappers from Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission and Martin County Trappers in the Davie family neighborhood of Zachary and Maria Lieberman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical depression likely to form in Atlantic over weekend...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/weather/hurricane/fl-reg-tropical-weather-aug-28-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patch of storms and clouds near the Cape Verde Islands has a 50 percent chance of becoming a tropical cyclone, say forecasters at the Miami-based National Hurricane Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call for boycott...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/404323-california-dems-call-for-boycott-of-in-n-out-after-donation-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California Democratic Party chairman is calling for a boycott of In-N-Out Burger after it was revealed this week that the fast food chain donated $25,000 to the California Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Dems Outraged As IN-N-OUT BURGER Donates To GOP...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/08/30/in-n-out-burger-republican-donation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cult fast food chain is taking sides in this year's election—or is it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy drag queen serving looks -- and country...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/navy-drag-queen-harpy-daniels-serving-looks-country-n905056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Kelley, 24, performs drag for his fellow Navy sailors while also fulfilling the role of his squadron’s administrative supervisor by day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Jr. says he'd back a new conservative social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-am-6b5b747e-4bab-4d9a-a6da-802524475400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10 stories that will drive the day, from the world’s most wired reporter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON hits $2,000 per share...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/amazon-set-to-open-above-2000-a-share-for-the-first-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a major milestone in the stock's climb to match Apple's $1 trillion market valuation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 48%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/current_events/politics/prez_track_aug30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day gas prices hit 4-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/gas-prices-remain-stuck-at-4-year-highs-for-labor-day.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national average gasoline price remains stuck around $2.85 a gallon, and analysts don't expect it to drop much this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space station 'hit by meteorite'; Depressurization...</title>
      <link>https://www.airlive.net/breaking-pressure-sensors-detected-a-depressurization-in-the-international-space-station-possibly-caused-by-a-micrometeorite-impact/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airlive.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass brawl on plane after woman starts giving lapdances...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7133571/easyjet-brawl-delayed-flight-woman-boobs-lap-dance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MASS brawl broke out on a plane after a drunk woman allegedly gave lap dances to strangers and flashed her breasts. Footage shows a group of passengers on plane from Luton to Ibiza pushing and sh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurassic Park-style cloning facility to bring extinct species back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-plans-45million-jurassic-park-13163552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin will next month unveil exact plans for the centre intended to be a "world class paleo-genetic scientific hub" in the world's coldest city, Yakutsk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists unearth site of Jesus 'water into wine' miracle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/726563/jesus-bible-miracle-site-gospel-of-john-water-wine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franken-algorithms: Deadly consequences of unpredictable code...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/aug/29/coding-algorithms-frankenalgos-program-danger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death of a woman hit by a self-driving car highlights an unfolding technological crisis, as code piled on code creates ‘a universe no one fully understands’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new normal? PWC allows new hires to work when want...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/08/30/new-normal-pwc-launches-flexi-scheme-allows-new-joiners-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accounting giant PwC has launched a new scheme that allows new employees the option to work whenever they want, and for as few or many hours as they choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer spending increases strongly; inflation rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/consumer-spending-increases-strongly-inflation-rising.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. consumer spending increased solidly in July, pointing to strong economic growth early in the third quarter, while a measure of underlying inflation hit the Federal Reserve's 2 percent target for the third time this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUTONOMOUS airships set to revolutionize policing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/726546/avalon-airships-autonomous-drones-future-policing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW TWEET STORM...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/speedreads/793295/trump-tweets-earlymorning-attacks-cnn-books-baselessly-claims-nbc-news-fudged-comey-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump went on an early-morning Twitter tirade against his favorite media punching bags Thursday, first claiming that CNN's "hatred and extreme bias" against him has "made them unable to function," and suggesting that AT&amp;T fire Jeff Zucker ("Little Jeff Z") because "his ratings suck." Trump then said NBC News was actually "the worst," predicting that NBC News Chairman Andy Lack "is about to be fired (?) for incompetence" — the rumors are actually that he's in trouble due to Matt Lauer's sexual misconduct and other #MeToo scandals — and made a curious, apparently unsubstantiated claim that NBC News "fudged" the interview where Trump admitted on national TV that he fired FBI Director James Comey because of the Russia investigation. What’s going on at @CNN is happening, to different degrees, at other networks - with @NBCNews being the worst. The good news is that Andy Lack(y) is about to be fired(?) for incompetence, and much worse. When Lester Holt got caught fudging my tape on Russia, they were hurt badly! — Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) August 30, 2018 Trump concluded by throwing "fake books" into the media bonfire and declaring that all media are the "Enemy of the People!" NBC News political director Chuck Todd seems to be subtweeting the president here, and suggesting you avert your eyes in embarrassment. I miss the days when people muttered nutty conspiracy theories to themselves while meandering down a sidewalk. Now they share it on Twitter w/millions of followers and for some reason some folks amplify it. Treat these tweets the way you’d treat the sidewalk mumbler, look away — Chuck Todd (@chucktodd) August 30, 2018 Certainly, taking the occasional break from the Twitter machine is good for everybody's mental health. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss America hopefuls arrive as pageant faces dissension...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/miss-america-hopefuls-arrive-pageant-faces-dissension-040810932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — The 51 hopefuls vying for the title of Miss America are set to arrive in Atlantic City on Thursday amid changes and internal dissension for the pageant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this a blue state? GOP governor looks unbeatable in Mass...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/blue-state-gop-governor-looks-unbeatable-mass-040622199--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — A popular Republican who seems nearly unbeatable. To his left, a pair of little-known Democratic hopefuls vying for attention and struggling to raise cash. To his right, a GOP challenger who claims the incumbent isn't nearly conservative enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How plan to save rhino left 11 dead in historic blunder...</title>
      <link>https://www.news24.com/Africa/News/how-a-plan-to-save-kenyas-rhino-left-11-dead-in-historic-blunder-20180830</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven of Kenya's precious black rhinos were transferred to a new home in what was supposed to be a routine operation in a country fabled for its conservation. But how did all of them end up dead?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK risks being dragged into war crime trials, UN warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/facebook-risks-being-dragged-war-164442838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Nations has warned Facebook that it risks being dragged into international war crimes trials for its role in future human rights violations, as it called on the social network to address hate speech more quickly. Zeid Ra'ad Al-Hussein, the UN’s human rights chief, said the company risked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Advert: Robot Life Coach...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/would-you-apply-robotics-firm-13163125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you got what it takes to guide the future race of artificially intelligent robots into our world?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV reporter shot dead in Cancun...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180830-television-reporter-killed-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry French farmers sow Chinese-owned field in investor protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180830-angry-french-farmers-sow-chinese-owned-field-investor-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China launches platform to stamp out 'online rumors'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180830063018-6rju6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-INTERNET/:China launches platform to stamp out 'online rumours'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farage for London mayor?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1010529/Nigel-Farage-London-mayor-Sadiq-Khan-Brexit-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREXIT campaigner Nigel Farage is considering a shock bid to run for mayor of London and oust Labour's Sadiq Khan from power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big Tech Swallowed Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/08/30/how-big-tech-swallowed-seattle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How Big Tech Swallowed Seattle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Number of Students Cutting Class...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/schools-crack-down-as-more-students-cut-class-1535621403</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing problem of children skipping school has districts across the country experimenting with solutions, from punishments to rewards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broken Relationship, Accusations of Emotional Abuse: Case of Keith Ellison...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/30/us/keith-elllison-karen-monahan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allegations against the high-profile progressive leader represent a potentially new chapter of the #MeToo movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALIBABA superstore: Robots, apps, conveyor belts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/inside-hema-alibabas-new-kind-of-superstore-robots-apps-and-more.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alibaba opened 65 retail stores in China in the past year. CNBC visited a location in Shanghai, which is also connected to its own robot-operated restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aftershocks of cover-up accusation felt in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://cruxnow.com/vatican/2018/08/30/aftershocks-of-cover-up-accusation-against-pope-felt-in-rome/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cruxnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the Vatican's informal policy of ignoring it, aftershocks from the bombshell accusations against Pope Francis from a former papal envoy in the United States were felt in Rome on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants bet future of TV is $10,000 massive screens with eye-popping colors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/samsung-lg-launch-8k-tvs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samsung and LG launched huge 8K televisions this week touting different screen technologies but there are many stumbling blocks to overcome before they become mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 20-Hour Flight Is Coming. Gym, Bunks, Child-Care...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/08/29/20-hour-flight-qantas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal of a nonstop flight from Sydney to London — half the way around the planet — took a leap forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC preparing for violence as confederate statue protests planned...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article217528820.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNC-Chapel Hill officials want people to avoid McCorkle Place on Thursday night as Silent Sam protesters plan a dance party and the opposing ACTBAC plans a twilight vigil for the toppled Confederate statue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS SENATE RACE TURNS NASTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2018/08/29/cant-ignore-beto-gop-tweets-mug-shot-cruz-skips-senate-votes-after-railing-august-recess</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- For anyone doubting the flurry of polls showing a neck and neck Senate race in Texas, there's fresh proof this week that Rep. Beto...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mad cow disease diagnosed in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/health/mad-cow-disease-diagnosed-in-florida-beef-cow/4088696/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USDA announces Mad cow disease diagnosed in Florida beef cow, but cow never entered food supply</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodward Book Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-takes-aim-watergate-scandal-reporter-carl-bernstein-000038865.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump took aim Wednesday at Carl Bernstein, one of the reporters who helped bring down Richard Nixon's presidency, accusing him of "making up" stories. Bernstein and Bob Woodward led the Washington Post team that investigated the 1972 break-in at the Democratic National</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina Peso Plunges to Record Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/argentinas-peso-plunges-to-record-low-1535578085 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The currency fell to a record low against the dollar Wednesday after President Mauricio Macri announced he has asked the International Monetary Fund to speed up delivery of a $50 billion bailout package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker sentenced to prison for Jennifer Lawrence nude photo theft... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/aug/29/nude-photo-hacker-prison-sentence-jennifer-lawrence-victims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Garofano, 26, one of four charged over illegal hacking of American actor and other celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Burning Man has been ruined. But it was doomed from beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/burningman/article/burning-man-terbo-ted-first-dj-electronic-playa-13188760.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For as long as Burning Man's existed, it's been ruined. The ravers ruined it for the welders. The collective-minded hippies ruined it for the anarchist ravers. Tech bros displaced the bohemians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man decapitates girlfriend after 'spoke with God'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattlepi.com/local/crime/article/Charge-Mount-Vernon-man-decapitated-girlfriend-13191736.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattlepi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When 32-year-old Timothy Hernandez's parents arrived at their Mount Vernon home after church Sunday afternoon, they found his girlfriend on the ground, with her head removed from her body and placed on the back of her torso, according to Mount Vernon police reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC preparing for violence as confederate statue protests planned...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article217528820.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNC-Chapel Hill officials want people to avoid McCorkle Place on Thursday night as Silent Sam protesters plan a dance party and the opposing ACTBAC plans a twilight vigil for the toppled Confederate statue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk repeats 'pedophile' accusations against man who's preparing to sue him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elon-musk-ignores-tesla-board-and-keeps-tweeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the entreaties of Tesla's board, Musk has kept tweeting — possibly to his detriment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three-Minute Ovation in Venice...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/first-man-standing-ovation-venice-world-premiere-1202454304/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Damien Chazelle’s taut space epic First Man was greeted with warm applause following its world premiere on the Lido tonight. Venice Film Festival guests and jurors, including Guillermo del To…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END? Assange isolation intensifies; Faces eviction...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/isolation-intensifies-wikileaks-julian-assange-faces-threat-eviction/story?id=57475632</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As his residency at the Ecuadorian Embassy in London enters its seventh year, Assange is facing a pair of converging crises that have left his allies worried.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake early-warning system sent alarm 3 seconds before Los Angeles temblor...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-quake-early-warning-20180829-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California’s nascent earthquake early-warning system had another successful run Tuesday night when a 4.4 magnitude temblor hit the La Verne area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says GOOGLE promoted Obama 'State of Unions' -- but not his...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-accuses-google-of-promoting-obamas-state-of-the-union-addresses-not-his</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump accused Google of promoting former President Obama’s State of the Union address on Google’s homepage, but not his own State of the Union in 2018 nor his speech before a joint session of Congress in February 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://onepeterfive.com/vigano-crow-truth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;onepeterfive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian reporter Aldo Maria Valli catches up with accused 'crow' Archbishop Viganò, who offers some words in his own defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil presidential hopeful: Let police kill criminals...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/brazil-presidential-hopeful-police-kill-criminals-57483440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leading candidate in Brazil's presidential election said police should be given license to kill criminals and those who do should receive medals not face prosecution. Hard-right candidate Jair Bolsonaro said in an interview Tuesday night that he would "leave good people out of range of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  'FIRST MAN' DAZZLES......</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/festivals/venice-gets-great-blasts-off-as-first-man-dazzles-and-vanessa-redgrave-charms-1202920730/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Venice Film Festival had a successful blastoff Wednesday with Damien Chazelle’s space epic “First Man,” starring Ryan Gosling as astronaut Neil Armstrong, which dazzled its first viewers and sc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOSLING BLAST OFF...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/ryan-gosling-damien-chazelle-first-man-venice-film-festival-opening-1202454004/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universal’s First Man touched down on the Lido this morning, ahead of its opening gala slot this evening that will officially kick off the 75th Venice Film Festival. In town for the movie’s maiden …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST: Trump Allies Fear Gathering Legal Storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/winter-is-coming-allies-fear-trump-isnt-prepared-for-gathering-legal-storm/2018/08/29/b07fc0a6-aba0-11e8-b1da-ff7faa680710_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has discussed adding to legal team, including possibly hiring Kushner lawyer Abbe Lowell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN: MANY 'FOOLS' IN THIS STORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-blasts-cnn-and-sloppy-carl-bernstein-over-disputed-story-caught-in-a-major-lie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernstein was one of three CNN reporters who wrote in July that the president's former lawyer, Michael Cohen was prepared to cooperate with Robert Mueller</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Star Slugger Defends Hitler INSTA Post...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/sports/2018/08/29/red-sox-s-jd-martinez-cites-support-for-second-amendment-in-defense-hitler-post.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Red Sox star J.D. Martinez stood by his controversial Hitler Instagram post Tuesday, saying he was defending the Second Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Rules Would Boost Rights of Accused of Campus Sexual Assaults...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-rules-would-boost-rights-of-those-accused-of-campus-sexual-assaults-1535582610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education Secretary Betsy DeVos is preparing to release new rules strengthening the rights of students accused of sexual assault on campus and lessen the burden placed on schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP UNLEASHES ON CARL BERNSTEIN...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/404285-trump-says-watergate-reporting-thinks-like-a-degenerate-fool</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday stepped up his personal attacks against CNN, lambasting the network and veteran journalist Carl Bernstein for a July report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller wants emails between Manafort, former lawyer...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/29/mueller-manafort-emails-lawyer-803921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney-client privilege doesn’t apply when the client enlists a lawyer’s help to commit a crime, which is what Mueller’s team says Manafort did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Woody Allen flick may never see light of day...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/08/29/latest-woody-allen-movie-may-never-see-the-light-of-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A Rainy Day in New York” wrapped filming before #MeToo refocused attention on the allegations of sexual abuse from Allen’s adopted daughter Dylan Farrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife convicted after trying to feed husband's ex-girlfriend to alligators...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/raleigh-woman-convicted-after-trying-to-feed-body-to-alligators/4067625/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amanda Smith Hayes, a North Carolina woman convicted of helping her husband dispose of his ex-girlfriend's body, has now been convicted of trying to dissolve the remains in acid and then throwing them into an alligator-infested creek.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Sleeping lady killed during homeless camp demoliton...</title>
      <link>https://www.modbee.com/news/article217453845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman sleeping in a homeless encampment in Modesto, California, was killed when she was hit by heavy machinery used by Caltrans to clean up the property, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Tests 'Unfollow' List...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/8/29/17798038/twitter-suggested-unfollow-list-test-liberal-bias-president-donald-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid claims of liberal bias from the president of the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widely Used Diabetes Drugs Cause Flesh-Eating Genital Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/29/flesh-eating-genital-infection-tied-to-rare-diabetes-drug-effect</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Widely Used Diabetes Drug Can Cause Flesh-Eating Genital Infection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheating scandal rocks Basic School for Marine Officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/08/28/land-nav-cheating-scandal-inside-the-total-meltdown-at-tbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Basic School for Marine Officers is reeling from a cheating scandal that involved six second lieutenants accused of wrongfully obtaining and sharing key grid points for the night land navigation course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller's Revenge? Won't Rule Out Going After Manafort in Third Trial...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/muellers-revenge-special-counsel-wont-rule-out-going-after-manafort-in-third-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olive oil better than Viagra, scientists suggest...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/29/olive-oil-could-better-viagra-scientists-suggest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olive oil could be better than Viagra at helping men perform in the bedroom, scientists suggest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Helps Afghanistan Fight Terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2161745/china-building-training-camp-afghanistan-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghan embassy refutes claim China is building a training camp in Wakhan Corridor and says there will be ‘no Chinese military personnel on Afghan soil’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President: 'No Reason' for Korea War Games...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/404272-trump-no-reason-for-korea-war-games-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday said there was “no reason” for joint U.S.-South Korea military exercises at the moment, citing ongoing discussions over North Korea’s nuclear program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AARON RODGERS RECORD DEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenbaypressgazette.com/story/sports/nfl/packers/2018/08/29/packers-aaron-rodgers-agrees-4-year-contract-extension/590180002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenbaypressgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Green Bay Packers will make quarterback Aaron Rodgers the highest-paid player in NFL history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Theaters Best Summer in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/29/despite-netflix-threat-hollywood-had-its-best-summer-in-decades</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite Netflix, Movie Theaters Had Best Summer in Decades</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Linebacker Admits to Insider Trading...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2018/08/29/mychal-kendricks-admission-of-insider-trading-puts-nfl-in-an-awkward-spot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Browns linebacker Mychal Kendricks admitting to insider trading and planning to plead guilty to it, many assume that the NFL will find a way to keep Kendricks off the field until he’s se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nap Breaks the New Lunch Breaks?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/are-15-nap-breaks-the-new-lunch-breaks-1535562920</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Urban ‘resting studios’ offer personal sleeping pods to weary workers looking for a midday recharge. But that’s a lot to pay for nothingness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison Staff in OH, PA Treated for Drug Exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/ohio/articles/2018-08-29/report-prison-guards-inmates-treated-for-exposure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones, stakeouts: How 'haters' pressured on Elon...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-musk-shorts/drones-and-stakeouts-how-tesla-haters-put-pressure-on-ceo-musk-idUSKCN1LE2FC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An online army of skeptics and amateur sleuths that has spent years promoting bets against Tesla Inc senses an opportunity to renew pressure on the electric carmaker after the failure of Chief Executive Elon Musk’s plan to take it private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PALIN EXCLUDED FROM MCCAIN FUNERAL</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/29/sarah-palin-loyal-running-mate-excluded-from-john-mccains-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin, who was Sen. John McCain (R-AZ)'s running mate in the 2008 presidential election, has not been invited to his funeral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Boulevard Coming to Los Angeles...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2018/08/29/la-leaders-approve-obama-boulevard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City council members approved renaming the street in a Tuesday vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON WAGES WAR VS BERNIE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/29/amazon-bernie-sanders-claims-are-inaccurate-and-misleading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a rare public response for Amazon. It has been largely silent amid repeated public attacks by President Donald Trump on the company and CEO Jeff Bezos, who also owns The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power outage leaves Venezuela capital in dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/power-outage-leaves-venezuelas-capital-dark-hour-201514846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — A major blackout has left several parts of Venezuela's capital and neighboring states in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorized horse rider new hero quiet N.J. town...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/entertainment/index.ssf/2018/08/meet_the_crazy_cranford_cowboy_motorized_horse_sco.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Bacque became a neighborhood celebrity after riding his motorized horse Charger through the streets of Cranford.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast Swelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/heat-index-us-northeast-tops-100-girl-dies-172342795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Tens of millions of people in the northeastern United States sweated in dangerously high heat Wednesday, with temperatures that felt like more than 100 degrees and prompted emergency measures including extra breaks for star players wilting at the U.S. Open tennis tournament and school</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope's Bombshell Author Says He's 'At Peace'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2018-08-29/the-latest-popes-bombshell-author-says-hes-at-peace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Detroit schools shut off ALL drinking water...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/education/2018/08/29/detroit-schools-drinking-water/1132514002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detroit Superintendent Nikolai Vitti this spring ordered testing of all schools in the district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE STOCK RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/29/us-markets-us-canada-trade-talks-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks traded slightly higher on Wednesday as trade negotiations between the U.S. and Canada resumed, while a rise in Amazon and Alphabet shares also boosted equities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outfit change for Aretha Franklin on second day of public viewing...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/08/29/outfit-change-for-aretha-franklin-on-second-day-of-public-viewing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen of Soul was decked out in a pastel blue frock and matching blue stilettos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly cost of child care for one child in San Fran: $1,955...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/mommyfiles/article/housing-expensive-childcare-cost-of-living-rent-13189388.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco not only has the most expensive rents in the country, according to a new analysis. It also has the highest cost of child care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau says NAFTA deal possible by Friday...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/29/canadas-trudeau-says-nafta-deal-possible-by-friday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said that it may be possible to reach a deal on NAFTA before U.S. President Donald Trump's Friday deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER faces losses, legal trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tabloid-kept-trump-secrets-faces-losses-legal-trouble-183801545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The National Enquirer has long explained its support for Donald Trump as a business decision based on the president's popularity among its readers. But private financial documents and circulation figures obtained by The Associated Press show that the tabloid's business was declining</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of beer, soda and coffee is colorless...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/clear-beer-dont-judge-a-drink-by-its-color-1535544000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese beverage makers are increasingly producing products that look like water but taste like other drinks, betting that consumers want the taste of Coke or beer in a healthier-looking clear liquid. Flavored, bottled water sales have more than doubled in both the U.S. and Japan in the past five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn actress waits for #MeToo; 'Treated like piece of meat'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/29/i-was-treated-like-a-piece-of-meat-adult-actress-waits-for-metoo/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jenny Blighe’s first professional porn film will be her last. What was supposed to be her “big break” in the adult film industry turned into a nightmare for Blighe, who says she was pressured to pe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane season coming to life in Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/08/29/hurricane-season-coming-life-atlantic/1132669002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sleeping giant may be about to awaken. Hurricane activity in the Atlantic is forecast to ramp up over the next couple of weeks. One storm could spin up in the Caribbean over the next couple of days and potentially impact Florida over the Labor Day weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DICK'S blames new gun policy for weak sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/dicks-says-under-armour-new-gun-sales-policy-dragged-on-results-1535565173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dick’s Sporting Goods said weaker sales of Under Armour apparel and a decision to pull back from the hunting business dragged on the retailer’s latest quarterly results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$80,000,000 -- in next 6 months!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/29/the-packers-are-paying-aaron-rodgers-80m-in-the-next-6-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Packers traded Brett Hundley, their backup quarterback, to the Seahawks on Wednesday morning. They then worked on cementing their starter for quite a long while. Green Bay and Aaron Rodgers are…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Aaron Rodgers Record Deal...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/24514088/green-bay-packers-aaron-rodgers-record-extension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record-breaking extension between the Packers and Aaron Rodgers is expected to be in place before the start of the season, a source told ESPN's Adam Schefter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  'FIRST MAN' STUNNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/first-man-venice-2018-1138214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan Gosling takes one small step for man, one giant leap for mankind in Damien Chazelle's account of the first successful manned mission to the Moon, also starring Claire Foy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE ATLANTIC RECORDS:  Porn, sex toys, cocaine...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6103869/Porn-sex-toys-cocaine-hookers-boasts-manhood-size-life-inside-80s-Atlantic-Records.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dorothy Carvello, the first female A&amp;R executive for Atlantic Records, tells of the toxic work culture in the music industry in the 80s in her new memoir,  Anything for a Hit - due September 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Secret War On Weed...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/dominicholden/trump-secret-committee-anti-marijuana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marijuana Policy Coordination Committee wants to counteract positive marijuana messages and identify problems with state legalization initiatives, according to documents obtained by BuzzFeed News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Women better drivers than men...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/women-are-better-drivers-than-men-study-finds-11484839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Male drivers seem to have more accidents than their female counterparts - costing insurers more money in claims pay-outs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
