<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>She bought dream home; 'Sovereign citizen' changed locks...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/she-bought-her-dream-home-a-sovereign-citizen-changed-the-locks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known as the Moorish sovereign citizen movement, and loosely based around a theory that Black people are foreign citizens bound only by arcane legal systems, it encourages followers to violate laws in the name of empowerment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto-Trading Hamster Performs Better Than Buffett, S&amp;P 500...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/25/1040683057/crypto-trading-hamster-goxx-warren-buffet-s-p-500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hamster named Mr. Goxx enters one of two tunnels in the his cage, which determines whether he will buy or sell. As of Friday, his portfolio is up nearly 20%, according to his Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 DEAD; 'WELL OVER' 50 HURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/amtrak-derailment-at-least-50-hurt-in-montana-official-says/ar-AAOPanm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three people were killed and 50 others were injured after an Amtrak train derailed in Montana on Saturday afternoon, setting off a frantic response by rescuers who scrambled to extricate passengers from cars, the authorities said.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most SF restaurants say mandate has sparked conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/San-Francisco-restaurants-have-seen-a-decrease-in-16480570.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One restaurant owner reported that requiring proof of vaccination has 'gone over much...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretly taping NYC visit for NETFLIX doc...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/25/prince-harry-and-meghan-markle-taping-nyc-trip-for-netflix-documentary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry and Meghan Markle have been secretly taping their NYC visit for a rumored Netflix documentary about their lives, Page Six has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch protest against vaccine pass to enter bars, restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210925123916-oqsd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NETHERLANDS-PASS (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Dutch protest against COVID-19 vaccine pass to enter bars, restaurants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School bus driver stabbed to death in front of students...</title>
      <link>https://www.tri-cityherald.com/news/local/crime/article254509112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tri-cityherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kids were safely removed from the bus and being held inside the school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Covid killed sex lives?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/sep/25/has-covid-killed-our-sex-lives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The end of lockdown was supposed to herald an explosion of pent-up desire and a bonkbuster of a summer. But it’s been way more complicated than that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's No Time to Die: But is it time to revoke James Bond's licence to kill?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/sep/25/its-no-time-to-die-but-is-it-time-to-revoke-james-bonds-licence-to-kill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1960s, 007 was a glamorous antidote to postwar austerity, but now he’s more laughable than heroic. Can the Bond brand survive, post-Brexit?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout begins for far-right trolls who trusted EPIK to keep their identities secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/fallout-begins-for-far-right-trolls-who-trusted-epik-to-keep-their-identities-secret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anonymous' massive hack of internet-services company Epik exposed previously obscure details of far-right sites and launched a race among extremism researchers to identify the hidden promoters of online hate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citizen enforcement of TX abortion ban could spread to other laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/09/23/citizen-enforcement-of-texas-abortion-ban-could-spread-to-other-laws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two state laws that restrict transgender youth also rely on private civil actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho morgues running out of space for bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/idaho-morgues-are-running-out-of-space-for-bodies-as-covid-19-deaths-mount/ar-AAOOBD3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dire situation in Idaho, one of the least vaccinated states in the country, is another grisly illustration of what happens when a state fails to contain infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amtrak train derails in remote Montana...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3734525/amtrak-train-derails-in-montana-trapped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Amtrak train derailed in Montana as shocking images revealed railroad cars detached and toppled over on Saturday. Images from the scene revealed the wreckage as unconfirmed reports of passengers…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  UNITED fined for keeping thousands of passengers trapped on planes --  for hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/united-airlines-fined-for-keeping-thousands-of-passengers-stuck-on-planes-for-hours/ar-AAONbNT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Department fined United Airlines $1.9 million for keeping thousands of passengers stuck on planes for hours. The airline said it has made investments to avoid lengthy delays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crews try to rescue passengers trapped inside'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10029033/Several-people-trapped-Amtrak-train-derails-Montana.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Amtrak train has derailed in Montana. It has been reported that several passengers are trapped inside after two cars separated from the train. This is an developing story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUG COMPANIES CASH IN ON 'BOOSTERS'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-science-health-coronavirus-vaccine-5305defac283ac5f352bc47fcb74c82b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billions more in profits are at stake for some vaccine makers as the U.S. moves toward dispensing COVID-19 booster shots to shore up Americans' protection against the virus. How much the manufacturers stand to gain depends on how big the rollout proves to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto throws shade at McConaughey...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/politics/article/Beto-O-Rourke-Texas-governor-run-McConaughey-16485628.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Texas congressman pondered McConaughey's ambiguous politics while remaining...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran and Venezuela strike oil deal amid US sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/573931-iran-and-venezuela-strike-oil-deal-amid-us-sanctions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran and Venezuela have struck an oil deal amid U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-elections-germany-angela-merkel-european-union-0203ca4281803d2d9af5e1df421a7f26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's closely fought election on Sunday will set the direction of the European Union's most populous country after 16 years under Angela Merkel, whose party is scrambling to avoid defeat by its center-left rivals after a rollercoaster campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The great sperm heist: 'They were playing with people's lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/sep/25/the-great-sperm-heist-they-were-playing-with-peoples-lives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul was in his 80s when someone called to say she was his daughter, conceived in a fertility clinic with his sperm. The only problem? He’d never donated any</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychedelic awakening led Navy SEAL on mission to save monarch butterflies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/environment/monarch-butterflies-are-wiped-combat-veterans-are-trying-rcna2200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guardian Grange aims to help veterans cope with trauma and transitioning back to civilian life. The group's first projects is to help build a butterfly preserve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Hawke 'BLACK PHONE' Next Horror Smash?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/ethan-hawke-the-black-phone-blumhouse-1235049261/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally, something scarier than the COVID-19 delta variant has come out of CinemaCon 2021. Universal Pictures unveiled a packed trailer for its upcoming Blumhouse horror thriller “The Black P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in booster guidance leads to confusion, chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/changes-in-booster-shot-guidance-leads-to-confusion-chaos-for-doctors-and-the-vaccinated/ar-AAOOsq9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confusion over boosters, which has been brewing for months, heightened over the past week as government regulators and advisers met to hash out the pros and cons of doling out third doses - and came up with different recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When FBI seizes messages from Big Tech, you may not know for years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/when-the-fbi-seizes-your-messages-from-big-tech-you-may-not-know-it-for-years/ar-AAONVgy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft, Google, Facebook and other tech firms are pressing lawmakers to enact new rules to stop prosecutors from secretly snooping on private messages, photos, search history and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junkies shoot up in broad daylight in Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/25/nyc-drug-users-shoot-up-in-broad-daylight-in-midtown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The block bordered by 35th and 36th streets, and Seventh and Eighth Avenues, is “littered with used needles, broken glass crack pipes, trash, urine, and feces.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police departments clamoring for de-escalation training...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/death-of-george-floyd-police-new-york-new-york-city-maine-a85463f8955fcf4be53e7b66287c1a87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACO, Maine (AP) — Angry over being fired, a former employee slashed the tires of his boss’ vehicle and still held the knife when police officers arrived. Three officers positioned themselves at a safe distance as the man yelled and ranted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazis still using. And making money...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-technology-sports-business-43cc5e3bc9fbdd6d2d2f425c117e4f0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — It’s the premier martial arts group in Europe for right-wing extremists. German authorities have twice banned their signature tournament. But Kampf der Nibelungen, or Battle of the Nibelungs, still thrives on Facebook, where organizers maintain multiple pages, as well as on Instagram and YouTube, which they use to spread their ideology, draw in recruits and make money through ticket sales and branded merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pill to Treat Covid 'Months Away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/daily-pill-treat-covid-could-be-just-months-away-scientists-n1279938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three promising antivirals that could prevent symptoms and limit transmission of Covid-19 are in clinical trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Germany's battle to succeed Merkel, final campaign scrambles with race up for grabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-germany-e2-80-99s-battle-to-succeed-merkel-final-campaign-scrambles-with-race-up-for-grabs/ar-AAOO3HS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even after Sunday's voting, difficult coalition talks are likely ahead to form a government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Spanish volcano eruption intensifies and suspends flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/la-palma-volcano-eruption-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eruptions on the Cumbre Vieja volcano on the Canary Island of La Palma intensifies, as flights are suspended and more evacuations are made while hot lava spews from the volcano and toxic ash blankets the surrounding area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI investigating alleged assault on Fort Bliss soldier at refugee camp...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/573901-fbi-investigating-alleged-assault-on-female-service-member-at-afghan-refugee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is investigating an alleged assault on a female service member at an Afghan refugee camp in New Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: How Thiel became most feared man in Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/25/how-peter-thiel-became-the-most-feared-man-in-silicon-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Facebook’s first president, Sean Parker, first brought Thiel into the fold as an investor in 2004, he warned Zuckerberg against the financier’s “dirty tricks.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reparations for Black Residents Gaining Steam...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/25/reparations-for-black-residents-are-becoming-a-local-issue-as-well-as-a-national-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Detroit took everything from Keith E. Williams and his family. He now wants it back. Right before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among Those Who Marched Into Capitol on Jan. 6: FBI Informant...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/25/among-those-who-marched-into-the-capitol-on-jan-6-an-f-b-i-informant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As scores of Proud Boys made their way, chanting and shouting, toward the Capitol on Jan. 6, one member of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Hospitals Face Mass Firings as Workers Spurn Vax...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/new-york-hospitals-face-possible-mass-firings-as-workers-spurn-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Buffalo, the Erie County Medical Center plans to suspend elective in-patient surgeries and not take intensive-care patients from other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitness Teachers, Plumbers Highest-Paying Jobs With No Experience Necessary...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/no-experience-highest-paying-jobs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although jobs that don't require a college education have a reputation of being low-paying, the study finds several which buck that trend significantly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces 'substantial' legal risk in Georgia case, think tank report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/politics/2021/09/24/trump-faces-substantial-legal-risk-georgia-case-think-tank-report-says/5851857001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report, written by seven legal analysts, concludes that Trump’s post-election conduct leaves him at “substantial risk of possible state charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Britain, Rising Prices and Shortages Evoke 1970s-Style Jitters...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/in-britain-rising-prices-and-shortages-evoke-1970s-style-jitters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Long lines at gas stations, rising fuel prices, empty shelves in supermarkets, and worries about runaway inflation. Britons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Afghans arrive near small Virginia town...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Thousands-of-Afghans-arrived-near-a-small-16486872.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLACKSTONE, Va. - Mayor Billy Coleburn finished his burger, pulled out his cellphone and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surveillance Apparatus That Surrounded Britney...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/the-surveillance-apparatus-that-surrounded-britney-spears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears’s father and the security firm he hired to protect her ran an intense surveillance apparatus that monitored her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Looking Anew at Carbon Tax...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/sinemas-income-tax-stance-has-democrats-looking-anew-at-a-carbon-tax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Opposition from a single moderate Democrat to corporate and income tax rate increases has revived efforts in the</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
