<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Murder Plot Claims, Dog Bite, Roger Stone: Inside FL's Craziest Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/murder-plot-claims-a-dog-bite-and-roger-stone-inside-floridas-craziest-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actions of an overly aggressive service dog named Gunner are only the latest twist in the bizarre race to represent this coastal Florida congressional district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague of 50 million cannibal crabs shuts roads in Oz...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4085287/moment-50-million-cannibal-crabs-shut-roads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the jaw-dropping moment a “biblical plague” of 50 million crabs head to the ocean to breed. The swarm of cannibalistic critters shut down roads from the jungle to the coast on C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY PLANS GAMBING FUTURE; SPORTS BETTING...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/disney-espn-sports-betting-dollars-1235048867/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that major leagues are getting on board with gambling, the family-friendly Hollywood giant is eyeing that revenue and may start with a splashy ESPN licensing deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE TAX:  New Yorkers Fume As MTA Says It's Moving Ahead With Congestion Pricing...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/congestion-pricing-new-york-city-manhattan-mta-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commuters are raising questions about the need to enact congestion pricing, the charging a hefty fee for anyone driving into Manhattan's Central Business District below 60th Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booster Shot Confusion As CA Goes Against CDC And FDA Recommendations...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/booster-shot-confusion-as-california-goes-against-current-cdc-and-fda-recommendations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the Food and Drug Administration said last month that only seniors and adults at high risk should get boosters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VAX MANDATE HANGING BY A PING-PONG</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/16/politics/vaccine-mandate-osha-lottery/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenges to the Biden administration's vaccine mandate targeting employers with more than 100 employees will be consolidated and heard by the Ohio-based 6th US Circuit Court of Appeals after it was chosen Tuesday by a ping-pong ball lottery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian cases hit record high amid quarantine for The Unjabbed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/austrian-covid-cases-hit-record-102452050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian coronavirus infections hit a new daily record on Wednesday, the third day of a lockdown for those not fully vaccinated aimed at halting the surge. Roughly 65% of Austria's population is fully vaccinated against the virus, one of the lowest rates in western Europe. Austria also has one of the highest infection rates on the continent, with a seven-day incidence https://covid19-dashboard.ages.at of 925 per 100,000 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VT has highest vaccination rate in country. So why are cases surging?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/vermont-highest-vaccination-rate-country-cases-surging/story?id=81090116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why COVID-19 cases are surging in Vermont, which is one of the most vaccinated states in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This experience broke people': Inside State amid Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/17/afghanistan-withdrawal-state-department-522705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chaos that came with ending America's longest war extended to Foggy Bottom, where staff were left with psychological scars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Will Sell Parts for Customers to Make Own Repairs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/apple-sell-spare-parts-consumers-140308622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc on Wednesday said it will for the first time start selling spare parts and tools to the general public to perform their own repairs on some iPhones and Mac computers. The self-service repair program comes after years of pressure from consumer groups have resulted in Apple providing greater access to repair manuals and genuine parts. In 2019, Apple started a program where independent repair shops can buy its parts, tools and manuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest Robbed At Gunpoint, Assaulted Outside Baltimore Church...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/priest-assaulted-robbed-at-gunpoint-outside-of-st-leos-roman-catholic-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Father Bernie Carman of St. Leo’s Roman Catholic Church has bruises and scrapes, but is doing okay tonight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Foreign' agents pitch has El Salvador civil society on edge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-united-states-nayib-bukele-el-salvador-san-salvador-fbc5b491ccbad99289719765e9a7aea1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador (AP) — El Salvador President Nayib Bukele has pitched a proposed law requiring people and organizations who receive foreign funding to register as “foreign agents,” following the lead of countries like the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Outbreak in Party Town Shows How Pandemic Could End...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/covid-outbreak-in-party-town-shows-how-the-pandemic-could-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers studying those who contracted the virus are gaining important insights into the immunity-bolstering effects of natural infection after vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'POWER OF THE DOG' review: Superb gothic western mysterious and menacing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/nov/17/the-power-of-the-dog-review-jane-campions-superb-gothic-western-is-mysterious-and-menacing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slow-burning psychodrama about two warring brothers on a ranch in 1920s Montana is one of the director’s best</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ELEPHANT WHO COULD BE A PERSON...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/11/happy-elephant-bronx-zoo-nhrp-lawsuit/620672/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most important animal-rights case of the 21st century revolves around an unlikely subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will TSA Be Ready For Thanksgiving? It's Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/suzannerowankelleher/2021/11/17/tsa-thanksgiving-mystery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the vaccine mandate deadline and Turkey Day looming, how many TSA employees are still not inoculated? The agency isn't saying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China hypersonic weapon could launch surprise nuke attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10211221/Chinas-hypersonic-space-weapons-used-launch-SURPRISE-attack-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff Gen John Hyten said China's space weapons could be used to launch a surprise attack on the US. China is thought to have carried out two tests of an orbital nuke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder Plot Claims, Dog Bite, Roger Stone: Inside FL's Craziest Race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/murder-plot-claims-dog-bite-100030816.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/Photos Getty ImagesWhen a Belgian Malinois named Gunner bit into a 9-year-old boy at a Florida fishing tournament earlier this month, it didn’t seem like the kind of incident that could have national political importance.But now the dog attack has become an unlikely flashpoint in an intra-Republican battle over a hotly contested House seat, pitting Trump adviser Roger Stone and his allies against Trump-backed congressional hopeful Anna Paulina Luna.The dog b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NYT CEO: TV News In Dead Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/former-new-york-times-ceo-mark-thompson-us-tv-news-is-in-dead-trouble-1234875928/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Times CEO Mark Thompson has said US TV news is in “dead trouble” as it loses audiences under the age of 60. Thompson, who used to be BBC Director General and ran the NYT between 201…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Voters have increasing doubts about Biden health, mental fitness...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/17/poll-biden-mental-fitness-job-approval-522785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new POLITICO/Morning Consult poll shows just 44 percent of voters approve of Biden's job performance, and 46 percent say he's "mentally fit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man was charged with hate crime after brutally beating gay man he targeted on GRINDR...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-oregon-man-was-charged-with-a-hate-crime-after-brutally-beating-a-gay-man-he-targeted-on-grindr-feds-say/ar-AAQNYs8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Supply Casualty: Garage Doors...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/15/garage-door-shortage-building-sacramento/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Sacramento will now allow garages to be boarded up in new homes, if the garage doors are not delivered in time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving essentials out of stock...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/17/business/thanksgiving-out-of-stock/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're noticing empty shelves when shopping for Thanksgiving, you're not alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Major storm could throw 'wrench' into Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/weather-for-early-thanksgiving-travel/1048187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters warn that anyone planning to get a head start on travel for the holiday may need to consider multiple weather scenarios that could cause big disruptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian cases hit record high amid quarantine for unvaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/581900-austrian-cases-hit-record-high-amid-quarantine-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus infections surged to a record high in Austria on Wednesday as the country entered the third day of a lockdown for unvaccinated people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The woods next door': Community forests take root...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211117095825-nqgsi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country is seeing a growing trend in green spaces governed by local residents, bringing conservation, educational benefits and income to urban and rural communities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools close as smog-laden India capital considers lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-environment-smog-new-delhi-d50847fe99122a711c080ce36802884a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Schools were closed indefinitely and some coal-based power plants shut down as the smog-shrouded Indian capital and neighboring states invoked harsh measures Wednesday amid considerations of a lockdown in New Delhi to combat worsening air pollution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN's Solomon Says Market Greed Now Outpacing Fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/greed-outpacing-fear-world-markets-100717268.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greed is outpacing fear in world financial markets as investors respond to the pandemic recovery, Goldman Sachs Chief Executive David Solomon says, adding that such periods of exuberance are usually not long-lived. The unprecedented levels of stimulus ordered by governments and central banks, he said, had led to exuberance in certain markets. Solomon said the expectation of rising interest rates could reduce the heat in some asset markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Taiwan Gaffes Risk Real-World Consequences...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-e2-80-99s-taiwan-gaffes-risk-real-world-consequences-with-china/ar-AAQOfVn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adele, Music's Comet, Returns With '30.' How Bright Will It Burn?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/17/adele-musics-comet-returns-with-30-how-bright-will-it-burn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time Adele released new music, six years ago, it became the type of hit many in the music</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300 Mins Week of Moderate Exercise May Help Ward Off Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/17/300-minutes-a-week-of-moderate-exercise-may-help-ward-off-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 46,000 cancer cases in the United States might be prevented each year if almost all of us walked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Astronaut to Be First Black Woman to Join Space Station Crew...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/16/nasa-astronaut-to-be-first-black-woman-to-join-space-station-crew/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two decades after the International Space Station became humanity’s long-lasting home in orbit, Jessica Watkins, a NASA astronaut, is poised</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate Stabbed in Eyeball in Latest Federal Prison Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2021-11-17/inmate-stabbed-in-eyeball-in-latest-federal-prison-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate at the largest federal prison in the U.S. was stabbed in the eyeball by a fellow prisoner earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would-be French presidential candidate Zemmour faces hate trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/would-be-french-presidential-candidate-zemmour-faces-hate-trial-2021-11-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Zemmour, the right-wing commentator whose surge in popularity and incendiary rhetoric on Islam and immigration are shaping France's presidential election campaign, is due in court on Wednesday on charges of inciting racial hatred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jarring GOP divisions come back into spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/581882-jarring-gop-divisions-come-back-into-spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republicans are pushing to retaliate against 13 of their GOP colleagues who voted for a bill to fix roads and bridges. At the same time, they’re defending Rep. Paul Gosar (R-Ariz.), a loyalist for former President Trump who tweeted an anime video depicting him killing a Democratic colleague.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeff earns groans at charity gala for only donating $500,000...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/11/16/fundraiser-audience-groans-when-jeff-bezos-only-donates-500000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Everyone was waiting for him to donate something,” an insider said. “Someone donated a million dollars … then a little later, he donated $500,000. There was an audible groan from…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give the dog a phone: Device could ease pain for lonely mutts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dog-phone-device-could-ease-103208611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does your chihuahua crave a chinwag or the Yorkie want to yak, the greyhound needs to gossip and the corgi loves a chat?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Rittenhouse jurors to return for Day 2 of deliberations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kyle-rittenhouse-wisconsin-homicide-kenosha-0e4b6ad5a286af9ddbb8c8546550f1dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (AP) — Jurors weighing charges against Kyle Rittenhouse were to return Wednesday for a second day of deliberations in his murder trial, after they failed to reach a swift verdict on whether he was the instigator in a night of bloodshed in Kenosha or a concerned citizen who came under attack while trying to protect property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's legal strategy tested in Jan. 6 fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-s-legal-strategy-tested-in-Jan-6-fight-16627703.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As president, Donald Trump stymied lawmakers seeking his financial records...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC correction officers refusing to get hots despite mandate, sparking fear of Rikers 'catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/new-york-elections-government/ny-nyc-correction-officers-refusing-covid-shots-despite-mandate-20211116-shqukn6ldrgofmn6wolvu4tz7u-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to data released Tuesday, only 63% of the DOC’s entire staff have gotten at least one dose of COVID-19 vaccine, the same vaccination rate the department had on Oct. 31 and the lowest out of all municipal agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In her quiet way, Jill Biden reinvents role of first lady...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/in-her-quiet-way-jill-biden-reinvents-role-of-us-first-lady-2613828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jill Biden promotes Covid vaccines and takes part in political rallies -- but only when her college professor schedule allows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID OUTBREAK KILLS 8 AT CT NURSING HOME; FULLY VAXXED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcconnecticut.com/news/coronavirus/8-dead-dozens-infected-with-covid-19-due-to-outbreak-at-connecticut-nursing-home/2652161/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcconnecticut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people are dead and just shy of 100 more have become infected with COVID-19 after an outbreak at a Connecticut nursing home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor of Brazil's first trans church preaches inclusion...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211117-pastor-of-brazil-s-first-trans-church-preaches-inclusion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When her mother asked an Evangelical pastor to "cure" her transgenderism at age 13, Jacque Chanel never imagined she would one day be an Evangelical pastor herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI LEADS NATION IN NEW CASES...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox2detroit.com/news/michigan-has-most-covid-cases-in-the-nation-in-latest-cdc-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox2detroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan is leading the nation in COVID-19 cases as it encounters its fourth surge since the pandemic started in March of 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT TO HEAR MANDATE CHALLENGE AFTER PING-PONG BALL LOTTERY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/16/politics/vaccine-mandate-osha-lottery/index.html	</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TO REQUIRE BOOSTER?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-vaccine-boosters-holidays-thanksgiving-america-4011f2c6-eecd-4e5d-8cfb-e5545ca59b8b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only slightly more than a third of adults 65 and older have gotten a booster shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's official: Science says grannies good for you...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-11-science-grannies-good.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say they have proven what many people fortunate enough to grow up with theirs have known all along: Grandmothers have strong nurturing instincts and are hard-wired to care deeply about their grandchildren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite attack: Mounting arms race in space...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-11-satellite-mounting-arms-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year a US general made an ominous revelation: two Russian satellites in orbit were stalking a US spy satellite high above the earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'New world order': Asia's virtual influencers offer metaverse glimpse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-order-asias-virtual-influencers-021414890.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sporting neon hair and flawless skin, Bangkok Naughty Boo is one of a new generation of influencers in Asia promising to stay forever young, on-trend, and scandal-free -- because they are computer generated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMA fighter Unvaccinated Assassin 'stabs doctor to death with animal bone in row over jab'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4079625/mma-fighter-unvaccinated-assassin-stabs-doctor-death-row-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN MMA fighter who called himself the Unvaccinated Assassin is facing a murder charge for allegedly stabbing a doctor to death in a row over the Covid vaccine. Akmal Khozhiev, 27, has been d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE WON'T FOLLOW DC GUIDANCE TO END MASKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/white-house-says-it-will-not-follow-dc-guidance-on-end-of-indoor-mask-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said on Tuesday that it will not follow District of Columbia guidance as it pertains to indoor mask wearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital testing nasal Alzheimer's vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/11/16/business/brigham-womens-hospital-is-testing-nasal-vaccine-alzheimers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hospital will enroll 16 participants aged 60 to 85 who have an early, symptomatic version of the disease to participate in the early-stage test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS watchdog declined to probe 'whipping' claims against border agents...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/16/dhs-watchdog-declined-to-probe-whipping-claims-against-border-agents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DHS Office of Inspector General declined to investigate allegations that border agents used whips against Haitian migrants earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest lunar eclipse in centuries... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/the-longest-lunar-eclipse-in-centuries-will-happen-this-week-nasa-says-what-to-know/article_b4d0edf6-f4d6-58cb-84f0-d5f36bcb6438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can see the longest partial lunar eclipse in hundreds of years this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOORDASH Driver Caught Defecating In Lobby Trash Can While Making Delivery!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/doordash-driver-brentwood-trashcan-toilet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DoorDash driver was caught on a security camera using the lobby of a Brentwood apartment building as a toilet while delivering food to a resident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buck takes shelter inside church on hunting season's 1st day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-lifestyle-michigan-animals-hunting-02bea9f79d1868f2af7b221610d752f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STURGIS, Mich. (AP) — A 10-point buck sought sanctuary inside a southern Michigan church on opening day of the state's firearm deer hunting season. Pastors at Grace Sturgis encountered the buck inside the church's auditorium on Monday before it leapt through a window and back into the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL IT EVER END!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211116201618-9nvu1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FAUCI (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Fauci says boosters for all key to U.S. reaching COVID-19 endemic level</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX TV STAR CANNED FOR NOT GETTING JAB...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/rockmond-dunbar-exits-911-covid-vaccine-mandate-medical-religious-exemptions-1234874927/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOILER ALERT: The story includes details about the Nov. 15 episode of Fox’s 9-1-1. EXCLUSIVE: Original 9-1-1 cast member Rockmond Dunbar is leaving the hit Fox drama series after more than f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIPCHAT hacked: Cam site security breach exposes 65 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4078374/stripchat-hacked-security-breach-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ADULT cam site security breach has caused the data of millions of users and models to be exposed. StripChat, which is one of the internet’s top five adult cam sites, suffered the breach ea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirates causing global shortage 'crisis', disrupting supply chains...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4075998/pirates-global-shortage-crisis-criminals-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIRATES and drug cartels could cause global shortages – as a “crisis” begins to unfold, experts have warned. The pandemic, coupled with driver shortages, are already causing probl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57% of Detroit public school students chronically absent
...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/education/2021/11/16/detroit-public-schools-students-absent/6390112001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of Detroit Public Schools students are considered chronically absent this school year from district schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. spies look to future:  China...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/16/1051170999/as-u-s-spies-look-to-the-future-one-target-stands-out-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When current and former U.S. intelligence officials gathered at a conference in Sea Island, Ga., there was a clear message — a pivot to China is already underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs, cannon fire, 184-mph winds: Life weird atop CA volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/ufos-cannon-fire-and-184-mph-winds-life-gets-weird-atop-this-california-volcano/ar-AAQLEAt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR labels first Asian-American Boston mayor a 'disappointment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/npr-slammed-disappointment-boston-asian-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NPR took heat Tuesday after its report that Asian American Michelle Wu’s election win in Boston was considered a "disappointment" to some for being chosen over Black candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gas prices soar to record highs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-gas-prices-soar-record-130054189.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soaring gas prices are one more challenge for residents heading into the second holiday season of the pandemic, with supply chain issues and inflation too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch plan to drop 'corona pass' for unvaccinated faces political push back...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211116193846-plu67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NETHERLANDS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Dutch plan to drop 'corona pass' for unvaccinated faces political push back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercers Throw Under Bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mercers-throw-steve-bannon-under-the-bus-in-election-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the FEC started looking into Cambridge Analytica’s campaign work in 2016, a lawyer for billionaire backer Rebekah Mercer blamed Steve Bannon for any potential misdeeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs, cannon fire, 184-mph winds: Life weird atop CA volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2021-11-16/he-lives-alone-atop-a-california-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vincent Valencia lives alone at the summit of Mammoth Mountain — a frozen world that is lashed regularly by California's ugliest weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: NO MATTER AGE, 2 SHOTS DON'T LAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/no-matter-how-old-you-are-two-shots-of-pfizer-vaccine-dont-last-study-685141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People’s ages had no effect on the vaccine’s waning, meaning that the vaccine waned for everyone and not just older people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea Giving Millions of Photos To Facial Recognition Researchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgdxqd/south-korea-is-selling-millions-of-photos-to-facial-recognition-researchers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers to the country are having their biometric data given to private companies under a program recently uncovered by civil rights advocates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag queens being swatted while streaming on TWITCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/drag-queens-are-swatted-streaming-twitch-want-stop-rcna5631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since September, six members of the streaming group Stream Queens, a collective of drag queens who stream mostly horror video games on Twitch, have been swatted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother Says Alec 'Target' Because Of His Political Views...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/news/alec-baldwins-brother-daniel-has-strong-words-about-rust-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin's brother Daniel Baldwin spoke out about the Rust shooting on Monday, complaining [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIMES SQ BACK OPEN FOR NEW YEAR'S -- WITH JAB PROOF...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-arts-and-entertainment-new-york-80d211eaa55312ebfe10dcfd479d5fbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Crowds will once again fill New York's Times Square this New Year's Eve, with proof of COVID-19 vaccination required for revelers who want to watch the ball drop in person, Mayor Bill de Blasio announced Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Russia admits destroying satellite with space missile strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/russia-admits-destroying-satellite-with-space-missile-strike/ar-AAQLmb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Tuesday admitted to destroying one of its satellites during a missile test but rejected US accusations that it had endangered the International Space Station. Last year, Britain and the US accused Russia of testing a "nesting doll" satellite that opened up and released a smaller craft to stalk an American satellite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gas prices soar to record highs...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-11-15/california-gas-prices-soar-to-record-highs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average price of a gallon of gasoline in California has climbed to a record $4.682. Several counties, including L.A., neared record highs as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos hits back at critics for saying Earth before space...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/jeff-bezos-hits-back-critics-25471455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Blue Origin founder has said billionaires need to "do both" when it comes to fixing problems on Earth and going to space, and recounted William Shatner's reaction to landing back on Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK accused of continuing to surveil teens...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2021/11/16/facebook-accused-of-still-targeting-teens-with-ads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The adtech giant formerly known as Facebook is still tracking teens for ad targeting on its social media platforms, according to new research by Fairplay, Global Action Plan and Reset Australia — apparently contradicting Facebook’s announcement this summer when the tech giant claimed it…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
