<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Muhammad makes list of 10 most popular baby names in USA for the first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10489360/muhammad-popular-baby-names-united-states-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE most popular baby names this year have been revealed with Muhammad making the top ten list for the first time in the US. According to BabyCenter’s list of 100 most popular baby names for …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napolitano Predicts Will Testify Under Oath in Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/foxs-napolitano-predicts-trump-will-testify-under-oath-in-impeachment-trial-with-200-million-people-watching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News analyst Andrew Napolitano told America's Newsroom that he believes President Donald Trump will testify in the now-likely impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Nye Science Guy Headed to Trial Against DISNEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/bill-nye-science-guy-headed-trial-disney-1259788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles judge trims Nye's profits lawsuit, but will allow the TV star to pursue punitive damages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar quietly gaining momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/politics/elections/ct-amy-klobuchar-iowa-2020-presidential-race-20191204-5cqtk5qhazgahk73hdtyojzqpe-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a time when many Democratic presidential candidates are stagnating in the polls and struggling to keep their campaigns financially afloat, Minnesota U.S. Sen. Amy Klobuchar’s operation is growing. She is one of just six candidates who has qualified for the December debate and is in the midst of doubling her Iowa campaign offices to more than 20, doubling her paid staff in New Hampshire and has hired up in the other early states of Nevada and South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal lawyer to be charged with graft in new woes for Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lawyer-charged-graft-woes-netanyahu-153616993.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's state prosecutor said Thursday he intends to charge the personal lawyer of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu with money-laundering in the state's purchase of submarines from German firm Thyssenkrupp. Netanyahu has in the past been questioned as a witness in the case but was not considered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' Ride Breaks Down Minutes After Opening...</title>
      <link>http://www.brevardtimes.com/2019/12/star-wars-rise-of-the-resistance-ride-breaks-down-minutes-afte-opening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.brevardtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE BUENA VISTA, Florida – The Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance ride broke down just minutes after opening today as part of Disney’s $1 billion Star Wars: Galaxy’s Edge expansion …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NIGHT OF HOPE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/12/05/kanye-west-joel-osteen-yankee-stadium-choir-americas-night-of-hope-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ye and Joel are hitting the road together, for one stop anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Mannequin Vaginas, Evil Babies: Inside Most Grotesque Movie of Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/in-fabric-is-the-most-gorgeously-grotesque-movie-of-the-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surrealist master Peter Strickland (“The Duke of Burgundy”) is back with “In Fabric,” a gory ode to Dario Argento about a cursed red dress that has to be seen to be believed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery at Center of Solar System; Spacecraft Reaches Sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/12/parker-solar-probe-nasa-sun/602962/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spacecraft has finally gotten close enough to the sun to gather clues about some lingering questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Average Person Can't Last 4 Hours With Family Over Holidays...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/breaking-point-average-person-cant-last-four-hours-with-their-family-over-the-holidays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holidays are supposed to be a time to come together with family and celebrate, but a new survey finds that most Americans can barely get through an evening with their family before needing a break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot to be based on singer after sensational AI agreement...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-based-russian-singer-21033186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anna Pletnyova has reportedly agreed to use her image as a prototype for a new South Korean doll after striking a deal with a company that produces erotic humanoid models</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Mother Upset With Son's Haircut Slams Car Into Barber Shop...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/12/04/mother-upset-with-kids-haircut-slams-car-into-antioch-barber-witnesses-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antioch police are searching for a woman who witnesses say intentionally drove her car into a barber after she was reportedly dissatisfied with the haircut he gave her son, police said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our democracy is at stake'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ea344e9bf24d8a8b64c20a305c14305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi announced Thursday that the House is moving forward to draft articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump. ‘’Our democracy is what is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Punches MCDONALD'S Workers Over Wrong Order...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/utah-mcdonalds-rage-801954</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 5--Two McDonald’s employees were assaulted by an irate customer who claimed that the workers botched his order, according to Utah police. Investigators say Victor Jimmy Castro placed an ord</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea: 'very dangerous challenge' if Trump calls Kim 'Rocket Man' again...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa/north-korea-very-dangerous-challenge-if-trump-calls-kim-rocket-man-again-idUSKBN1Y91L0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should U.S. President Donald Trump call North Korean leader Kim Jong Un "Ro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: DO IT FAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-challenges-do-nothing-democrats-if-you-are-going-to-impeach-me-do-it-now-fast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump returned from a shortened trip to the UK-based NATO summit amidst an ongoing Congressional impeachment inquiry threating his administration and issued an interesting challenge t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Releases Ad Showing World Leaders Laughing at Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/joe-biden-twists-the-knife-with-viral-video-showing-the-world-is-laughing-at-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President and Democratic presidential frontrunner Joe Biden capitalized on President Donald Trump's overseas trip by releasing a video mashup showing world leaders "laughing at P</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE WEST AND JOEL OSTEEN TO TAKE OVER YANKEE STADIUM...</title>
      <link>https://thesource.com/2019/12/05/kanye-west-and-joel-osteen-to-take-over-yankee-stadium-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesource.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a confirmed report from TMZ, Kanye West and Joel Osteen are going to o one bigger than Lakewood Church. The best part is that the date is already set; May 2, 2020 Joel and Ye are set to takeover the home of the Bronx Bombers. The event is an installment of Osteen’s “America’s …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMAC in the DARQ: Tech trends shaping 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/smac-darq-tech-trends-shaping-2020-042708248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Or will the world unify against Big Tech's privacy-busting, tax-avoiding practices? Apple has yet to launch a compatible phone, unlike rivals including Samsung. The rollout should quicken next year as more countries install base stations and networking equipment -- although US President Donald</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian faints during whipping for Sharia-banned sex...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/indonesian-faints-during-whipping-sharia-banned-sex-103819011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite international condemnation, public flogging is common for a range of offences banned under local Islamic law in the conservative Aceh region on Sumatra island, including gambling, drinking alcohol, and having gay or pre-marital sex. Aceh is the only region in Indonesia, the world's biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 hours in the shadow of Mexico's violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/24-hours-shadow-mexicos-violence-030820490.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mexico struggles to stop the bloodshed unleashed by its "drug wars," the violence casts a long shadow over ordinary life for many Mexicans. Everything in Ciudad Juarez is extreme: the arid climate of the Chihuahuan desert, the stark contrasts of the US-Mexican border, the violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France shuts down: Mass strike hits trains, Eiffel Tower...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a90ae89bba844a729e2d0ea894b11294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Eiffel Tower shut down, France’s vaunted high-speed trains stood still and teachers walked off the job as unions launched nationwide strikes and protests Thursday over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi to discuss 'status of inquiry'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/473135-pelosi-to-discuss-status-of-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) will deliver a statement on the “status of impeachment inquiry” into President Trump at 9 a.m., her office announced early Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Quiet Return of Bruce Weber and Mario Testino...</title>
      <link>https://businessglitz.com/us/the-quiet-return-of-bruce-weber-and-mario-testino/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;businessglitz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Showdown of NFL next generation QBs: Jackson vs Allen...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f333c12f27773587f0c76a3b31bfb045</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORCHARD PARK, N.Y. (AP) — It's easy to forgive Ravens coach John Harbaugh for forgetting this weekend's showdown of two of the AFC's more dynamic quarterbacks won't be the first meeting between...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DICK MORRIS:  SHE'LL WAIT FOR BIDEN TO DROP OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/former-bill-clinton-adviser-hillary-feels-god-put-her-on-earth-to-be-president-but-one-thing-is-keeping-her-from-running-2019-10-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dick Morris went on the John Catsimatidis’s radio show to talk about the likelihood of Hillary Clinton running for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10472853/results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10472853</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabbard moves to New Hampshire ahead of primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/gabbard-rents-home-in-nh-in-last-months-before-primary/30125406#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Democratic presidential candidate is making herself at home in New Hampshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans angry, concerned about Schiff release of phone records...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/republicans-angry-concerned-about-schiff-release-of-phone-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Intelligence Committee chairman Adam Schiff's decision to publish the phone records of the president's personal attorneys, a journalist, a fellow lawmaker, a National Security Council aide, and others has sent a chill among Republicans concerned about the reach of a powerful chairman…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ advocates slam Buttigieg for past history with Salvation Army...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/473128-buttigieg-criticized-over-past-volunteering-with-salvation-army</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg is facing criticism online from some members of the LGBTQ+ community and gay rights advocates after images of the South Bend, Ind., mayor volunteering with the Salvation Army resurfaced online Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN:  Hillary drops biggest hint yet she's mulling 2020 run...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/04/hillary-clinton-drops-biggest-hint-yet-that-shes-mulling-a-2020-presidential-run/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strongest indicator yet that Hillary’s mulling a 2020 run? She appeared Wednesday, for the first time ever, on Howard Stern. There was hardly a pretense she was there to promote the book she co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway rips First Lady...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/4/george-conway-rips-melania-trump-amplifying-nothin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-Trump lawyer George Conway accused first lady Melania Trump of violating Barron Trump’s privacy by protesting the 13-year-old boy’s name being mentioned at Wednesday’s impeachment hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman on oxygen killed while smoking cigarette...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article238016474.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: APPLE Pays $25M for Billie Eilish Doc...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/billie-eilish-lands-massive-payday-apple-tv-documentary-1259738</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple sources say Apple is paying $25 million for the project about the 17-year-old musician.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cemetery employees accused of stealing memorials, recycling them for cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/cemetery-employees-accused-stealing-memorials-recycling-them-for-cash/x7GLedV9p2B6ETWKr4onqM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two employees of a Carroll County cemetery are accused of stealing dozens of memorials and selling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD union will not defend officer accused of fondling dead woman's breasts...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/12/04/lapd-officer-bodycam-fondling-dead-womans-breasts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An LAPD officer was reportedly placed on leave after footage captured by a body-worn camera allegedly showed him fondling a deceased woman's breasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE THURS:  TRUMP HOUSEKEEPERS SPILL DIRT...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/how-two-undocumented-housekeepers-took-on-the-president--and-revealed-trumps-long-term-reliance-on-illegal-immigrants/2019/12/04/3dff5b5c-0a15-11ea-bd9d-c628fd48b3a0_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Undocumented workers got an unvarnished look at the lives of the now-first family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept watchdog concludes FBI had adequate basis to open Russia investigation... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/barr-s-handpicked-prosecutor-tells-inspector-general-he-can-t-back-right-wing-theory-that-russia-case-was-u-s-intelligence-setup/ar-BBXM9OT?q=7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press sec calls 'fabricated tabloid trash'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-two-housekeepers-took-on-the-president-and-14882448.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEDMINSTER TOWNSHIP, N.J. - It was important for Sandra Diaz to be invisible.  Before entering the Trump family villa, she would tie back her hair, pull on latex gloves and step into delicate paper shoe coverings. She knew not to wear makeup or perfume that might leave the faintest trace of her presence.  As Donald Trump's personal maid, Diaz was dealing with a fussy celebrity owner who presided like a monarch over the Trump National Golf Club Bedminster long before he was elevated to president. She was an immigrant from Costa Rica working illegally for Trump with a fake Social Security card she had bought for $50. Being invisible was her life's work.  Moving quickly through the two-story house in the mornings, Diaz carried out Trump's fastidious instructions. In his closet, she would hang six sets of identical golf outfits: six white polo shirts, six pairs of beige pants, six neatly ironed pairs of boxer shorts. She would smear a dollop of Trump's liquid face makeup on the back of her hand to make sure it hadn't dried out.  The years of service that Diaz and other undocumented immigrant housekeepers, cooks, landscapers, greenskeepers, waiters, bellhops, farm hands and caddies devoted to the Trump Organization have given them a remarkable vantage point into the unvarnished lives of the now-first family. They have seen poolside tantrums and holiday arguments. They've laughed with the in-laws and watched after the grandkids.  Their recollections also show how Trump's entrance into presidential politics - denouncing illegal immigrants as criminals and job-stealers - upended their lives and prompted some of them to publicly confront their former boss.  Over the past year, The Washington Post has spoken with 48 people who had worked illegally for the Trump Organization at 11 of its properties in Florida, New Jersey, New York...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Republican: We should hang them for treason!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/25e2f36b05b5eb2ad6c050493f195202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) — Local and national GOP leaders distanced themselves Wednesday from a Florida congressional candidate who sent a fundraising letter stating that “anti-American radical...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pearl Harbor on lockdown; Gunman leaves 'multiple injured'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2019/12/04/breaking-news/multiple-gunshot-victims-reported-at-pearl-harbor-naval-shipyard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rejects Nixon, Clinton precedent...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-rejects-Nixon-Clinton-precedent-on-14881575.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The showdown had been years in the making, Bill Clinton's personal lawyer confronting the lead investigator pushing for the second ever impeachment of a sitting president.  "Mr. Starr, good evening," David Kendall, the presidential attorney, said in November 1998.  "Good evening," replied Kenneth Starr, the independent counsel investigating Clinton. "How are you, David?"  "I'm very well, Ken," Kendall said.  For the next hour the two legal giants squared off in a prime-time clash exactly a month before the House voted to impeach President Clinton for his effort to cover up an affair with a White House intern. They debated the facts of the case and the merits of impeachment, as both Republicans and Democrats barely said a word.  It was the sort of legal battle royal that President Donald Trump would probably love to see from his legal team, feisty and carried live on national cable TV.  But Trump, unlike Clinton and President Richard Nixon in 1974, has opted against having legal advisers present for the House Judiciary Committee's first impeachment hearing Wednesday.  The White House decision, delivered to Democrats Sunday evening, accused them of a "complete lack of due process" but left open the possibility that his legal team "may consider participating" in future hearings if they are deemed a true process.  That move relinquishes Trump's side of the fight to Republicans on the committee, an unusual move for a president who loves to see his own top aides in public sparring with Democrats and the media. Many of those GOP lawmakers are his closest allies, and they plan to vigorously fight Democrats over committee procedures.  Some Republicans have quietly wondered whether this is a mistake, that it leaves out another combatant in the room who would be on Trump's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Secretly Moving Missiles Into Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/iran-is-secretly-moving-missiles-into-iraq-us-officials-say/ar-BBXM675</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy jets to Ukraine for documentary...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/giuliani-facing-scrutiny-travels-to-europe-to-interview-ukrainians/ar-BBXL2OK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC LAUNCHES 'AMERICA'S GOT TALENT' INVESTIGATION; COWELL SHOW CONTROVERSY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/americas-got-talent-gabrielle-union-nbc-simon-cowell-1203425205/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC is launching a deeper investigation into its reality competition series “America’s Got Talent,” eight days after Variety exclusively reported that judge Gabrielle Union would …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Epstein was Mossad Spy?</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@dylanhoward/world-elite-exposed-how-mossad-spy-for-hire-jeffrey-epstein-orchestrated-honeytrap-operation-5de6052fa3fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this exclusive extract from the sensational new book EPSTEIN: DEAD MEN TELL NO TALES, former CIA counter-terrorism specialist Philip…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania attacks witness who joked about Barron's name...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7757201/Melania-Trump-slams-Democrats-impeachment-witness-dropped-Barron.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First lady Melania Trump slammed a Democratic impeachment witness Wednesday after she name-dropped 13-year-old Barron Trump during the House Judiciary Committee hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK rumor about white vans spreading fear across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/04/tech/facebook-white-vans/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrifying rumors initially propelled by Facebook's algorithms have sparked fears that men driving white vans are kidnapping women all across the United States for sex trafficking and to sell their body parts. While there is no evidence to suggest this is happening, much less on a national, coordinated scale, a series of viral Facebook posts created a domino effect that led to the mayor of a major American city issuing a warning based on the unsubstantiated claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>668,000 will lose food stamp benefits under new work rules...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/46cda2574cbad2a31d52c33d07d7c77d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Hundreds of thousands of Americans who rely on the federal food stamp program will lose their benefits under a new Trump administration rule that will tighten work requirements...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer convicted of rape launches comeback with sold-out show...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/4/joe-lopez-tejano-singer-convicted-rape-launches-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jose “Joe” Lopez, a Grammy Award-winning Tejano singer who was convicted of raping an underage female relative and imprisoned for more than a decade, is preparing to relaunch his career with a sold-out show in Houston, despite the original terms of his release barring him from visiting the city and surrounding county because the victim lives there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Named best picture by NY FILM CRITICS...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/movies/story/2019-12-04/the-irishman-named-best-picture-by-new-york-film-critics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Film Critics Circle have named “The Irishman” the year's best film, handing Martin Scorsese's mob epic its second such honor in two days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel President will consider pardon if Netanyahu resigns, confesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Rivlin-will-consider-pardon-if-Netanyahu-resigns-confesses-report-609903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the report, Netanyahu has not yet responded to the idea which has been floated by a variety of third parties, though in the past he rejected any talk of a plea deal or pardon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine arrested for alleged human smuggling after Chinese woman found in trunk...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/marine-arrested-for-alleged-smuggling-after-chinese-woman-found-in-car-trunk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Marine stationed in Southern California was arrested Monday on suspicion of attempting to smuggle two Chinese women in the trunk of his car across the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside RING's Quest to Become Law Enforcement's Best Friend...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/bjw9e8/inside-rings-quest-to-become-law-enforcements-best-friend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's surveillance company has seeped into hundreds of American communities by throwing parties for police and giving them free devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani, Facing Scrutiny, Travels to Europe to Interview Ukrainians...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/giuliani-facing-scrutiny-travels-to-europe-to-interview-ukrainians/ar-BBXL2OK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM layoffs in Detroit...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/money/cars/general-motors/2019/12/03/uaw-gm-layoff-detroit-hamtramck/2600150001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GM will start laying off hundreds of workers at its Detroit Hamtramck plant in February. The automaker has said it will retool the plant to build EVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illustrated First-Person Guide to the C.I.A.'s Torture Program...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/12/04/an-illustrated-first-person-guide-to-the-c-i-a-s-torture-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - This article was produced in partnership with the Pulitzer Center on Crisis Reporting.GUANTÁNAMO BAY, Cuba — One shows the prisoner nude and strapped to a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR: 'Communities' without respect may lose 'police protection'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/12/04/william-barr-communities-without-respect-may-lose-police-protection/2606237001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;William Barr made the comments, which have drawn some criticism, while awarding law enforcement officers and deputies for service in policing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Birth Control Pills May Shrink Women's Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/birth-control-pills-may-be-shrinking-a-vital-brain-region-in-women-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A disconcerting new study finds that birth control pills may actually impact the size or even shrink a portion of women's brains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals Sue to Keep Prices Secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hospitals-sue-trump-to-keep-negotiated-prices-secret/ar-BBXL1Ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once-a-month? Works in animals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8b352ef7ac7f12855c10bf4a1d71b5d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Birth control pills work great if women remember to take them every day but missing doses can mean a surprise pregnancy. Now scientists have figured out how to pack a month’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Self-Sabotaging of Kamala Harris...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/12/the-self-sabotaging-of-kamala-harris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Playing to Twitter and the political press, testing new messages seemingly every week, the perfect candidate couldn’t help but get lost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In NYC, Paper Receipts Set to Go the Way of Foie Gras...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-12-04/in-new-york-city-paper-receipts-set-to-go-the-way-of-foie-gras</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/882282/rudy-giuliani-literally-ukraine-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This was most certainly not a good idea. Rudy Giuliani, the former New York City mayor turned lawyer to President Trump turned linchpin of this whole impeachment situation, is back in Ukraine while the House debates the impeachment of his boss. And not only that, but he's there to talk to multiple former Ukrainian prosecutors who sparked a lot of his problems in the first place, people familiar with his efforts tell The New York Times. As the House continues its investigation of Trump, Giuliani, and their dealings with Ukraine, Giuliani has been overseas in an effort to 'shift the focus to purported wrongdoing by President Trumpâ€™s political rivals,' the Times writes. On Tuesday, he reportedly met with former Ukrainian prosecutor Yuriy Lutsenko in Budapest. Lutsenko is one of the prosecutors accused of ignoring corruption in Ukraine's government and had once been skeptical of the Bidens' dealings in Ukraine before recanting his suspicions. Trump seemed to praise Lutsenko as a 'very good prosecutor' during his July 25 call with Ukraine's president, who had dismissed Lutsenko. Then on Wednesday, as the House Judiciary Committee began its impeachment hearings with legal experts, Giuliani reportedly headed to Kyiv in Ukraine to meet other ex-prosecutors who targeted the Bidens. They included Viktor Shokin, who was pushed out of his position amid criticism from then-Vice President Joe Biden, and Kostiantyn Kulyk, who led the investigation into Burisma. All of the information Giuliani gathers is apparently going into 'episodes of a documentary series for a conservative television outlet promoting his pro-Trump, anti-impeachment narrative,' the Times continues. Read more about Giuliani's inconveniently timed trip at The New York Times. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran leader calls for 'Islamic mercy' after bloody crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a66b89961c04a0082610607679e2f86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran’s supreme leader called Wednesday for those detained in recent gasoline price protests to be treated with “Islamic mercy” even after authorities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Who? Boris Plays It Safe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/president-boris-johnson-plays-safe-160900822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Has Boris Johnson forgotten the U.S. president’s name? Perhaps a mental blank explained why he completed a 21-minute press conference at the end of the NATO summit without once mentioning Donald Trump.The more likely reason is that with voting a week away, Johnson wanted to avoid as much</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 423 million guns in America; 8.1 billion rounds of ammo a year...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/atf-423-million-guns-in-america-1-2-per-person-8-1-billion-rounds-of-ammo-a-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s love affair with guns is only getting stronger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Trump caught on hot mic gossiping about Trudeau!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10483133/donald-trump-hot-mic-mocking-trudeau/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has himself been caught on hot mic revelling in the headlines generated by denouncing Justin Trudeau as “two-faced”. The US President had given Trudeau the cold shoulder fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  PLANES FILLED WITH GERMS; HEADRESTS CRAWLING...</title>
      <link>https://www.theladders.com/career-advice/these-are-the-exact-germs-you-come-in-contact-with-on-a-plane-and-what-they-can-do-to-your-body</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theladders.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study found that if you make contact with an object on a plane you risk infection with MRSA, or the E. coli O157:H7 gut bug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County makes it illegal to 'annoy' police...</title>
      <link>https://www.routefifty.com/public-safety/2019/12/police-annoy-law-new-york/161645/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.routefifty.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opponents say the law passed in Monroe County, New York, is too vague and likely unconstitutional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Designing 'Smart Suits' to Help Humans Withstand Biological Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/12/darpa-wants-smart-suits-protect-against-biological-attacks/161619/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new program aims to usher in a modern military ensemble that can provide 100% survival against lethal exposure from multiple chemical and biological agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Turns News Department Into PR machine...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2019/12/03/company-shills-news-show-or-disney-pr-reps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The journalists at Good Morning America on Tuesday again sold out the news department in order to shill for Disney and the whims of CEO Bob Iger. The morning show devoted almost five minutes to promoting a glossy new book singing the praises of the corporate behemoth. Dismissing her own program as nothing more than a product no different then co-division Marvel, co-host Robin Roberts cheered, “It is called One Day at Disney and it celebrates the people and the culture that makes all this happen from Walt Disney world to Marvel to GMA.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Zimmerman sues family of Trayvon Martin for $100M...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article238030539.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man killed by neighbor in dispute over who should mow grass...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-allegedly-killed-by-neighbor-in-dispute-over-mowing-grass</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tennessee woman says her fiance was killed by their next-door neighbor during a longstanding dispute that began over who was allowed to mow the grass between their homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HATE-O SUMMIT</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7755537/Donald-Trump-cancels-final-NATO-press-conference-London-world-leaders-mock-hot-mic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has given reporters an unprecedented level of access this week-more than two hours of Q&amp;Asessions. He called Canadian PM Justin Trudeau 'He's two-faced,'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Has Coughing Fit on 'Howard Stern Show'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/04/hillary-clinton-suffers-coughing-spell-in-howard-stern-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton suffered a lengthy coughing spell in an interview with Sirius/XM radio talk show host Howard Stern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Republican GA Gov Defies Trump with Senate Pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/04/brian-kemp-taps-establishment-backed-kelly-loeffler-setting-up-potential-clash-with-trump-conservatives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Kemp nominated Kelly Loeffler to the Senate despite GOP concerns regarding her ties to Planned Parenthood and Democrats</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
