<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pete and Chasten Buttigieg welcome twins...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/570854-pete-and-chasten-buttigieg-welcome-twins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg announced on Twitter that he and his husband, Chasten Buttigieg, have welcomed twins into their family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Still Grieving His Son, Finds That Not Everyone Wants to Hear About It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/04/biden-still-grieving-his-son-finds-that-not-everyone-wants-to-hear-about-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In the hours before Lance Cpl. Jared Schmitz, 20, was killed by a terrorist’s bomb in Afghanistan, he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ether Briefly Tops $4,000 as Upgrade, NFT Momentum Gathers Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/ether-briefly-tops-244000-as-upgrade-nft-momentum-gathers-pace/ar-AAO5hcP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ether briefly rose above $4,000 late Friday amid a monthlong surge around a major upgrade, and as demand for non-fungible tokens continues to widen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDA: As flood alerts lit up phones, did 'warning fatigue' set in?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-environment-and-nature-floods-12d4138915cabd7a08adcb682aced7ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Cellphones across New York and New Jersey pulsed with urgent warnings of catastrophic flooding as the fury of Hurricane Ida's remnants, carrying torrential rains, approached upper New Jersey and New York City on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dread at 30,000 ft: Inside increasingly violent world of flight attendants...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/flight-attendants-unruly-passengers-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unruly passengers are seemingly on the increase in the United States, leaving some flight attendants bracing themselves for violent encounters in the sky as they try to cope with Covid-19 risks and maintain safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bette Midler calls on women to refuse sex...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/570849-bette-midler-calls-on-women-to-refuse-sex-amid-texas-abortion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Bette Midler called for women to refuse having sex amid Texas’s recently enacted abortion law, and suggested that Congress should guarantee abortion rights for women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former DISNEY Star Spilling Juicy Secrets on YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/former-disney-star-spilling-juicy-040345693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christy Carlson Romano/YoutubeThis is a preview of our pop culture newsletter The Daily Beast’s Obsessed, written by senior entertainment reporter Kevin Fallon. To receive the full newsletter in your inbox each week, sign up for it here.This week:A full-on spiritual meltdown about Steve Martin’s TV show.An untreatable addiction to a Disney star’s YouTube channel.Diane Keaton singing “Thank U, Next” may have broke me.The new Dancing with the Stars casting definitely broke me.The only Real Housewi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map shows AMAZON rapidly growing air fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/04/map-of-amazon-air-locations-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's air cargo fleet is an increasingly critical component of its logistics machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 7,000 Steps A Day Cuts Risk Of Death By 70%...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/7000-steps-premature-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths among men fell by 58 percent however, that rate jumped to 72 percent among women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK mistakenly labels black men 'primates'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210904-facebook-mistakenly-labels-black-men-primates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook mistakenly labels black men 'primates'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildlife 'Red List' grim tally of extinction threat...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-09-wildlife-red-grim-tally-extinction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world will get an update Saturday of the Red List of Threatened Species, the authoritative catalogue of how many of the planet's animal and plant species are teetering on the brink of extinction due to human activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210904024628-nepjd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-abortion group, Texas Right to Life, was blocked from using the mechanism in the Texas law that enables private citizens to sue anyone who provides or "aids or abets" an abortion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremist was released from New Zealand jail despite fears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-zealand-islamic-state-group-3bd1cbbeec8eeda30caa0797f52ae227</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — New Zealand authorities imprisoned a man inspired by the Islamic State group for three years after catching him with a hunting knife and extremist videos — but at a certain point, despite grave fears he would attack others, they say they could do nothing more to keep him behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tahoe evacuees watching weekend with hope as fire slows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-fires-environment-and-nature-lakes-eb5907b71556a9853b38bf75fa0845b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH LAKE TAHOE, Calif. (AP) — Tens of thousands of South Lake Tahoe residents are watching hopefully this weekend for a chance to return home as firefighters make progress against a threatening California blaze that has turned their thriving resort into a ghost town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA DEATHS AT RECORD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-7ed6d05626848aca4e2827681b315770</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Funeral director Wayne Bright has seen grief piled upon grief during the latest COVID-19 surge. A woman died of the virus, and as her family was planning the funeral, her mother was also struck down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Flying Wing Aircraft Photographed Over Philippines...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42261/mystery-flying-wing-aircraft-photographed-over-the-philippines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The aircraft resembles the one seen in an image taken in California a year ago that is thought to be of the elusive RQ-180 stealth spy aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate boards, consulting, speaking fees: How generals thrive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/corporate-boards-consulting-speaking-fees-how-us-generals-thrived-after-afghanistan/ar-AAO5Iz8 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobs report adds fresh concerns over Monday's unemployment cliff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/570823-jobs-report-adds-fresh-concerns-over-mondays-unemployment-cliff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 9 million Americans are set to lose their unemployment benefits and millions more will see their weekly incomes plummet as a host of federal pandemic jobless aid programs expire next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand supermarkets take knives off shelves after 'extremist' stabbing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210904013457-5nck0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWZEALAND-ATTACK/ (PIX):New Zealand supermarkets take knives off shelves after 'extremist' stabbing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comPLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comPLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MU FOUND IN LA</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/mu-variant-los-angeles-first-cases-new-covid-1234827340/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci on Thursday said U.S. public health officials are “keeping a very close eye” on a new variant of Covid-19 that was first detected in Colombia. Known as B.1.621 or the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA DEATHS AT RECORD</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/florida-deaths-at-record-kids-hit-by-delta-wave-virus-update/ar-AAO4Pox?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida reported 2,345 additional Covid-19 deaths in its latest weekly report, the most ever in a similar period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPREADS AMONG VAXXED</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-spread-among-vaccinated-people-154240146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ubiquity of the Delta variant should be cause for some caution heading into Labor Day weekend, health officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians will pay highest gas prices ever for Labor Day weekend...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/californians-pay-highest-gas-prices-130058084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers in California are expected to pay an average of $4.39 per gallon -- the highest price ever for Labor Day weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas anti-abortion tipster site booted by web host...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-anti-abortion-tipster-booted-214357964.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A webpage seeking tips from the public to enforce Texas's severe new abortion restrictions has been told to find a new company to host its site or go offline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jolie feared for her family's safety during marriage to Pitt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/angelina-jolie-says-she-feared-220437513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Couple were married between 2014 and 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Australia Traded Away Too Much Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/09/pandemic-australia-still-liberal-democracy/619940/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How long can a democracy maintain emergency restrictions and still call itself a free country?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban declare China their closest ally...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3591782/taliban-declare-china-closest-ally-uk-refuses-recognise-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALIBAN officials have declared China as their closest ally in the international community. Militants say Beijing is “ready to invest in and reconstruct” Afghanistan and describe the nation as thei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT FOR HIS LIFE:  Oscar De La Hoya hospitalized with covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/oscar-de-la-hoya-hospitalized-after-contracting-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 48-year-old boxer said he was fully vaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Corona Tracking App!</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2021/09/03/australia-testing-orwellian-facial-recognition-coronavirus-tracking-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia is developing an app that uses facial recognition and geolocation data to track its citizens, in part of the country's draconian efforts to control coronavirus, with even the establishment leftist magazine the Atlantic branding the app "Orwellian."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Eye National Plastic Tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/democrats-eye-national-plastic-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats may impose a national plastic tax to finance their $3.5 trillion ($3,500,000,000,000) tax and spending spree, according to a leaked Senate Finance Committee document.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;The document lists a "Plastics Excise Tax" which will "impose a $.20 per pound fee on the sale of virgin plastic." Virgin plastic is a vital material in medical devices and products, clothing, toys, and thousands of household products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Masker Tries to Zip-Tie School Principal...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5gegj/an-anti-masker-just-tried-to-zip-tie-a-school-principal-over-covid-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His kids don't even go to her school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British mob clashes with cops, trying to storm medicine watchdog building...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/03/anti-covid-19-vaccine-mob-in-london-clashes-with-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four police officers officers were hurt as protesters — include actor Sean Ward — tried to storm the headquarters where COVID-19 jabs were approved in London, England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-louisiana-c457a7807315fda6f5772cadbbbf16a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — The owner of seven Louisiana nursing homes that were evacuated to a warehouse where four residents died after Hurricane Ida amid conditions deemed squalid faced criticism after a prior evacuation-related death two decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NH Gov. hospitalized for flu-like symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/sununu-hospital-flu-like-symptoms-evaluation/37474780#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Chris Sununu was hospitalized Friday with a bleeding ulcer and needed a blood transfusion, his chief of staff said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida funeral homes work overtime...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2021/09/03/florida-funeral-homes-work-overtime-to-help-families-impacted-by-covid-19-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 deaths are keeping funeral homes across Florida busy as workers do their best to provide quality service to families who have lost loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ida power outages fueling shortages in groceries, essentials...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hurricane-ida-power-outages-fueling-shortages-in-groceries-and-other-essentials/ar-AAO4Nzn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 800,000 customers still without electricity, many Louisiana residents are scrambling to load up on milk, bread and water and find gas for their cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her Leaks Exposed Global Corruption. Now She's In Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/davidmack/treasury-official-whistleblower-global-banking-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Treasury Department official Natalie “May” Edwards said she is a whistleblower who sent suspicious activity reports to BuzzFeed News after trying in vain to work through lawful channels. Her actions became the basis for the global FinCEN Files investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden caves; Will declassify 9/11 docs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-orders-declassification-sept-11-investigation-documents-n1278487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The order lays out specific timelines over the next six months for the release of the documents with some set to be released as early as next week’s 20th anniversary of the terror attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Man Fatally Shoots Half-Brother In Head During Argument Over Vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/illinois-man-shoots-half-brother-and-father-of-4-in-head-over-dispute-over-covid-19-vaccines-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson County Sheriff Pete Sopczak called the crime "senseless" and said that Geyman was “one of the greatest guys around,” according to the The Southern Illinoisan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VATICAN SILENT ON CHINA ABUSES. WHY?</title>
      <link>https://www.ucanews.com/amp/vatican-should-talk-to-china-but-not-at-any-price/93985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ucanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any dialogue with Beijing must include a robust focus on human rights and a fierce defense of religious freedom and human dignity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former operative plans rally for those charged in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/former-trump-campaign-operative-plans-rally-for-those-charged-in-capitol-riot/ar-AAO2qWf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt Braynard, a former Trump campaign operative, is planning the rally with an estimated 700 people attending, according to a permit application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shaman' pleads guilty...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/q-shaman-jacob-chansley-pleads-guilty-in-jan-6-attack-could-face-months-behind-bars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The so-called “QAnon Shaman,” Jacob Chansley, who with his spear, horns and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket built by startup FIREFLY explodes off California coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/03/tech/firefly-rocket-explosion-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 100-foot-tall rocket burst into flames mid-air after launching from California Thursday evening, dashing the hopes of a Texas-based startup to put a rocket into Earth's orbit on its first-ever launch attempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newlywed busted for post-wedding meltdown...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/erratic-newlywed-375892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 3--After fleeing from the scene of an auto crash he caused, a 25-year-old motorist--who was married earlier in the day and appeared under the influence--declared “All hail Donald Trump” be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>800 Louisiana nursing home residents rescued squalid...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/healthcare_hospitals/article_4f729062-0c65-11ec-a306-bfb48902f0bf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two nurses who worked inside the Tangipahoa Parish warehouse where more than 800 nursing home residents have now been rescued from squalid conditions say they are haunted by the scenes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Jill returns to classroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/jill-biden-returns-to-the-classroom-live-and-in-person/ar-AAO3NbI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden will be spending two days a week teaching English at a Virginia community college.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Alligator Snatches Blogger's Drone Out Of Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/alligator-chomps-down-on-drone-in-floridas-everglades-69619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident stirred up controversy on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Liberals Are Knocking Out Local Judges Across Country...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/09/03/robert-saleem-holbrook-conservative-judges-criminal-justice-506966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive activists are challenging “tough on crime” judges in a place they have long avoided: the voting booth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium creates garbage highway for flood victims' waste...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210903-belgium-creates-garbage-highway-for-flood-victims-waste</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Belgium creates garbage highway for flood victims' waste</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenner at 1%...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wwjnewsradio/news/national/jenner-pitches-backup-plan-to-voters-scared-of-elder?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A lot of things are coming out about him, which, if correct, he’s got a lot of issues,” Caitlyn Jenner said of rival Larry Elder, who leads the polls among candidates to replace Gov. Gavin Newsom in the event a recall is approved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Baradar the Butcher' to reportedly lead new govt...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/03/taliban-co-founder-baradar-to-reportedly-lead-new-afghan-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite initially claiming to want to form a consensus government, the Taliban are now only considering one made up solely of Taliban members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  NEW 'DUNE' STUNNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/03/review-too-soon-for-new-dune-new-take-on-sci-fi-classic-is-stunning-granular-moody-artful</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ah, “Dune.” It seems like yesterday that David Lynch gave us the hoary epic adaptation of Frank Herbert’s landmark sci-fi novel.  Kyle MacLachlan headed up a very eclectic and wei…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
