<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'I Got Virus Three Times'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/emaoconnor/covid-three-times</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t worry, you (probably) won’t become me. But yes, you can get COVID twice, and even more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convicted killer to join NY State Assembly...</title>
      <link>https://patch.com/new-york/harlem/eddie-gibbs-makes-history-harlems-new-assembly-nominee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;patch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gibbs, a Black man, is set to take over the historically Latino East Harlem seat after a racially fraught nominating process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA Cartoonist Turns...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/maga-cartoonist-ben-garrison-turns-on-trump-after-pro-vaccine-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial, MAGA cartoonist Ben Garrison’s latest offering takes aim at former President Donald Trump who he once supported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant marine reptile skull discovery reveals new evolutionary theories...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/23/world/giant-marine-reptile-skull-intl-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery of a giant marine reptile skull in the United States has revealed new theories about the speed of evolution and how quickly the process can produce diversity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas refinery blast could push gas above $4...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/23/energy/gas-prices-texas-refinery-blast/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blast at a Texas oil refinery early Thursday will probably push already high gasoline prices even higher — although not immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space weapons: 'Rods from God' meteorites, molten metal cannons, weaponized asteroids...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4329646/space-war-weapons-satellites-shoot-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEAPONISED asteroids, “rods from god” raining down on Earth and cannon firing molten metal and — it sounds like something from a sci-fi movie.  But these bizarre weapons may soon become…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Very young people' ending up in ICU...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/health/very-young-people-in-icu-in-nsw-top-health-official-warns/news-story/6bfb139aabe2a2103c3bc16577652a83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 70 per cent of new Covid cases in New South Wales are among people under the age of 40, the state’s chief health officer has stressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China fires up 'artificial sun' -- unlimited energy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4330598/china-fires-up-artificial-sun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has fired a machine designed to make unlimited energy known as the “artificial sun” – and wants to make it even hotter. Tests being run on the Experiential Advanced Supercon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of celeb candidates comes to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/23/trump-spurs-rise-in-celebrity-candidates-525865</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House experience isn't necessarily the best way to get traction across the Capitol anymore — as Herschel Walker and Mehmet Oz are proving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOURTH woman accuses Noth of sex assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10340789/FOURTH-woman-comes-forward-accuse-Sex-City-star-Chris-Noth-sexual-assault.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lisa Gentile, 54, claims she was 'sexually abused' by actor Chris Noth in 2002 after drinking with him at Da Marino's restaurant, which they both frequented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA to halt games on screens in moving cars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-games-video-games-ce6e7bd75a9b1339475ce4243f61a71e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Under pressure from U.S. auto safety regulators, Tesla has agreed to stop allowing video games to be played on center touch screens while its vehicles are moving. The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration says the company will send out a software update over the Internet so the function called “Passenger Play” will be locked and won't work while vehicles are in motion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Rejected Oct. Proposal for 'Free Rapid Tests for Holidays'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/12/the-biden-administration-rejected-an-october-proposal-for-free-rapid-tests-for-the-holidays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With omicron cases spreading like wildfire, the White House is finally taking steps to make free antigen tests available to all. But this fall, Vanity Fair has learned, it dismissed a bold plan to ramp up rapid testing ahead of the holidays. Frustrated experts explain how confusion, distrust, and a single-minded fixation on vaccinating Americans left testing on the back burner for so long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise ship prevented from entering 2 island nations due to outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/royal-caribbean-covid-outbreak-port-entry-denied/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Royal Caribbean cruise ship was denied entry into two island nations after 55 fully vaccinated crew members and passengers contracted Covid-19 only days after the ship had set sail from Fort Lauderdale, the Miami Herald reported Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bambi Variant? Infections in Deer Capable Of Jumping To Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-infections-in-deer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers add that the animals may also be a potential "reservoir" for coronavirus, meaning COVID could survive within their bodies and evolve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research blocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-689647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masks, social distancing required at Times Square NYE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/23/new-york-will-require-masks-and-social-distancing-at-times-square-new-years-celebration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attendees at the Times Square New Year's Eve celebration will have to wear masks, New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verdict in murder trial of cop who claimed she pulled gun instead of Taser... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/23/verdict-reached-in-trial-of-kim-potter-over-daunte-wrights-killing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An outcome was reached Thursday in the trial of Kim Potter, the former Minnesota police officer who claimed she meant to pull her Taser when she shot and killed Daunte Wright, a 20-year-o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Won't Let Them Have Kids, So They Turn to Sperm Black Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxdjbw/japan-sperm-black-market-lgbtq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese law allows only married couples to have children, leaving LGBTQ couples navigating a clandestine market for sperm donation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public takes contact tracing into own hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/online/social/south-australia-residents-take-contact-tracing-into-their-own-hands/news-story/83f3d8e02d7d368d7576ca8f1129954c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents in South Australia have rallied together to create their own Covid-19 exposure site alert system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo won't be charged for touching trooper at racetrack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-andrew-cuomo-d0aa8439df0a35193922bd8352255c33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Former New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo won't face criminal charges after a female state trooper said she felt “completely violated” by his unwanted touching at an event at Belmont Park in September 2019, a Long Island prosecutor said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DONALD V. CANDACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-pushes-back-on-candace-owens-undermining-vaccine-people-arent-dying-when-they-take-the-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump reaffirmed his recent touting of the Covid vaccine when he reminded Candace Jones that people aren't dying after getting the vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOAN DIDION DEAD</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/23/joan-didion-legendary-american-writer-dead-at-87/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iconic essayist and novelist famously chronicled the 1960s counterculture in her best-selling book “Slouching Towards Bethlehem”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Leap of Faith on 4th Shot Puts Focus on U.S. Next Steps...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/israel-s-leap-of-faith-on-4th-shot-puts-focus-on-us-next-steps/ar-AAS5Ju4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid infections rocket 509% in FL, 541% in DC and 670% in HI... MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10340061/US-hits-second-daily-highest-average-diagnoses-rate-pandemic-began.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States logged a seven-day average coronavirus case count of 168,981 on Wednesday, surpassing a summer peak of over 165,000 infections with Omicron detected in every state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Faces Grim 60th as Jury Goes on Break Without Verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10337295/Ghislaine-Maxwell-facing-prospect-spending-Christmas-Day-locked-bars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell will spend Christmas Day in a 10x12ft prison cell in New York as she awaits a verdict in her high-profile sex trafficking case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers Question Why Jury Only Heard From Four Accusers!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/lawyers-question-why-maxwell-jury-only-heard-from-four-accusers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers Question Why Maxwell Jury Only Heard From Four Accusers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes it spread so easily?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/makes-omicron-variant-spread-easily-130010038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early research points to mutations in the spike protein. But much remains unknown or unconfirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON WORKERS WALK; DEMAND BETTER TREATMENT DURING HOLIDAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4328393/amazon-warehouse-workers-walkout-new-york-illinois/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOZENS of Amazon warehouse workers staged a walkout in protest to demand better treatment and higher wages during the holiday rush. The pre-Christmas strike took place at two Amazon warehouse locat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Is Loneliest Day Of Year For Singles...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/christmas-loneliest-day-singles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4 in 10 people feel the holiday season shines a spotlight on their relationship status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Call '21 Worst Year Of Lives!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/2021-worst-year-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Think 2020 was bad? Half of Americans are calling 2021 the “worst year of their lives so far.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faking vaccine card in NY now comes with jail time...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/faking-a-covid-19-vaccine-card-in-new-york-can-now-get-you-a-year-in-jail/3465563/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Falsifying a COVID-19 vaccination card is now a class A misdemeanor in the state of New York, and tampering with computer records related to vaccinations is now a class E felony, after Gov. Kathy Hochul signed new legislation late Wednesday. The bill clarifies that “a COVID Vaccination Card shall be considered a written instrument for purposes of the forgery statute,” which…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP V. CANDACE OWENS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-candace-owens-dying-vaccine-covid-92fd3eb3-f5ec-4167-8649-113903119de1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"[I]f you take the vaccine, you're protected."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPE:  Omicron may bring record cases but fewer deaths, forecast says...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/omicron-may-bring-record-breaking-165110822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A highly influential COVID-19 forecast is projecting the Omicron surge may result in as many as 400,000 new coronavirus cases a day across the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans for urgent mass graves?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17121278/russia-approves-plans-urgent-mass-graves-ukraine-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has reportedly approved plans for “urgent mass graves” amid fears that World War Three could break out after an invasion of Ukraine. The move comes amid deepening concerns that Vladimir Puti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unjabbed trust in government plunges...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-ipsos-poll-unvaccinated-covid-0b2f2a54-472e-418b-9281-b32763f4c7b4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Japan draw up joint military plan for possible Taiwan emergency...</title>
      <link>https://english.kyodonews.net/news/2021/12/f5ed60ab6502-japan-us-draft-operation-plan-for-taiwan-contingency-sources.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.kyodonews.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's Self-Defense Forces and the U.S. military have drawn up a draft joint operation plan that would enable the setup of an attack base along the Nansei island chain in the country's southwest in the event of a Taiwan contingency, according to Japanese government sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Weighs How To Ration PFIZER Pills...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-weighs-how-to-ration-pfizer-pills-early-on-among-high-risk-1.1699825</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has cleared Pfizer Inc.’s Covid pill, and now comes another hurdle -- deciding who should get it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gum disease could be linked to mental health, other chronic illnesses...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/nationworld/gum-disease-increases-risk-of-developing-mental-health-problems-by-nearly-40-study-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poor dental health may also lead to poor mental health, a new study reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Obscure Charge Jan. 6 Investigators Looking at for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-obscure-charge-jan-6-investigators-are-looking-at-for-donald-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have hit 240 insurrectionists with the rare charge of obstructing an official congressional proceeding. The Jan. 6 Committee might be looking at that charge for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGHWAY HELL:  100+ vehicles involved in Wisconsin crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4328011/highway-pile-up-sees-dozens-cars-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICY roads on Interstate 94 saw a massive pile-up after a crash that reportedly involved over 100 vehicles and an overturned semi-truck which erupted into flames. Traffic on the icy Interstate 94 wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Smartphone Addiction Leading To Poor Self-Control, Negative Thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smartphone-pandemic-feel-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too much smartphone use during COVID-19 leads to poor self-control, increased fear of missing out (FOMO), and repeatedly dwelling on negative news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who defied orders to keep diner open dies of virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox2detroit.com/news/michigan-man-who-defied-state-pandemic-orders-to-keep-diner-open-dies-of-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox2detroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Parney said he kept the Quincy Diner open partly to pay for medical bills. The south Michigan man wasn't vaccinated when he got infected, but pledged during his illness he would, arguing "the battle, at this point, was worse than any training he endured in the military."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens Vanish Without Trace in America's New 'Bermuda Triangle'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dozens-vanish-without-trace-america-100231297.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEA / G. SIOENCIUDAD JUÁREZ, Mexico—In the dead of night this fall, 12 migrants left the small northern Mexican town of Coyame to enter the vast Chihuahuan desert, with the hopes of crossing into the U.S. by way of the Texas border. Among them was a 14-year-old boy from Southern Mexico who was dreaming of reuniting with his family on the other side of the border.Before taking off on the journey on Sept. 25, a 32-year-old man with the group reportedly called his wife to tell her that he had paid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Bottomed Out in '21. Will Viewers Come Back?</title>
      <link>https://autos.yahoo.com/cnn-bottomed-2021-viewers-come-100210316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;autos.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/GettyAt the beginning of 2021, CNN was on top of the cable news world.The network, which revolutionized round-the-clock news coverage when it launched more than four decades ago, had finally retaken the ratings crown from Fox News and pushed its conservative rival to third place for the first time since 2000.Less than a year later, CNN’s viewership has shrunk—the channel is buried in third place, behind Fox and MSNBC after a series of controv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation-Adjusted Spending Stagnates as Prices Surge...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/u-s-inflation-adjusted-spending-stagnates-as-prices-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tasty TV: The lickable screen...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211223134857-g33zq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-TASTE SCREEN/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Tasty TV: Japanese professor creates flavourful screen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gambling addiction rises amid COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/an-invisible-addiction-amid-pandemic-a-rise-in-gambling-addiction-emerges/ar-AAS5tIX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  20% couldn't pay energy bill in last year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/23/20percent-of-americans-couldnt-pay-their-energy-bill-in-the-last-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. households have struggled in the last year to meet basic needs, such as paying energy bills. This year, costs may be even higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimp beaten to death by first apes she'd met after raised by humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4328050/chimp-beaten-death-apes-abandoned-mother-raised-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHIMP who was sent to a Kenyan sanctuary to learn how to live with apes after spending her whole life with humans has been beaten to death by fellow chimpanzees.  Baran died aged four only m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In highly vaxxed New England, hospitals under unprecedented strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-highly-vaccinated-new-england-hospitals-are-under-unprecedented-strain-as-coronavirus-surges/ar-AAS5yoT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forces Build Near Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-builds-up-forces-near-ukraine-ahead-of-u-s-talks/ar-AAS4D4o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Worth $15 Quintillion Is Just Another Day in Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-12-23/bitcoin-btc-worth-15-quintillion-is-just-another-day-in-crypto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope demands humility in new zinger-filled Christmas speech...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pope-francis-lifestyle-religion-christmas-a04d3c12674a14127f8efbdaafd3ae97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis urged Vatican cardinals, bishops and bureaucrats Thursday to embrace humility this Christmas season, saying their pride, self-interest and the “glitter of our armor” was perverting their spiritual lives and corrupting the church’s mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another danger to illicit drug users: Animal tranquilizer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-opioids-centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention-7cb475c8559bf922265124e927e55bfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHESTER, Vt. (AP) — Brooke Goodwin came home one night last March after being out with friends. She had just turned 23 the day before, had a good job and was planning to go away with friends the following weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How solitude can help regulate mood...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/07/15/891564595/how-solitude-can-help-you-regulate-your-mood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone needs a little alone time, but with the current pandemic, you might have either too much "me" time or not enough. Let's get that balance back. This episode breaks down some of the research behind what makes even small bouts of solitude restorative and what to do when you're alone too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says supply chain crisis didn't materialize: 'Gifts being delivered, shelves not empty'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-says-supply-chain-crisis-didn-e2-80-99t-materialize-e2-80-98gifts-are-being-delivered-shelves-are-not-empty-e2-80-99/ar-AAS3Nu6?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems confront rising retirements...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/587028-democrats-confront-rising-retirements-as-difficult-year-ends</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are facing a growing wave of retirements as they close out 2021 and enter what’s expected to be a challenging midterm election year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Fraud Inquiry Won't Be Resolved When Vance Term Ends Next Week...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/23/trump-fraud-inquiry-wont-be-resolved-when-vances-term-ends-next-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney, Cyrus R. Vance Jr., has run out of time. Even as prosecutors in his office have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Mouth Molds and Michelin Stars: Chef Finds Fame After Epic Takedown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/23/of-mouth-molds-and-michelin-stars-chef-finds-fame-after-epic-takedown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LECCE, Italy — The restaurant’s guests had finished their appetizers of fermented ricotta puffs and a paper-thin slice of fish</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heir Apparent or Afterthought? The Frustrations of Kamala...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/23/heir-apparent-or-afterthought-the-frustrations-of-kamala-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The president needed the senator from West Virginia on his side, but he wasn’t sure he needed his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadlock...</title>
      <link>https://www.unilad.co.uk/news/ghislaine-maxwell-jury-have-made-plans-as-they-opt-for-long-christmas-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unilad.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors in Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;#8217;s trial have broken up for Christmas and won&amp;#8217;t return to court until next week. Maxwell is accused of being a madam for her former partner Jeffrey Epstein, the late convicted sex offender and paedophile who was found dead in his cell in 2019 after also being arrested on federal charges for &amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory Mask Order in Colorado Ski Country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/omicron-triggers-mandatory-mask-order-in-colorado-ski-country/ar-AAS3Y5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin to hold marathon session with journalists amid showdown with West over Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-to-hold-marathon-session-with-journalists-amid-showdown-with-the-west-over-ukraine/ar-AAS4OfV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Luxury-Home Sales Wrapping Up Biggest Year on Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/realestate/manhattan-luxury-home-sales-wrapping-up-biggest-year-on-record/ar-AAS3AUC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Faces Grim 60th as Jury Goes on Break Without Verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/maxwell-jury-asks-for-testimony-of-house-manager-u-k-accuser</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxwell Jury Asks for Testimony of House Manager, U.K. Accuser</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says will run for reelection if 'in good health'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/587040-biden-says-he-plans-to-run-for-reelection-in-2024-if-im-in-good</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden said he plans to run for reelection in 2024, assuming he's still in good health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen jumps out of MCDONALDS drive thru to save choking customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/minnesota-teen-jumps-out-of-mcdonalds-drive-thru-window-to-save-choking-customer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sydney Raley didn’t think twice about jumping through a McDonald’s drive-through window to render first-aid to a choking customer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60% of Americans infected by March?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10337845/Enormous-spread-Omicron-cause-140-MILLION-new-infections-January-1-March-1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation at the University of Washington expect the virus to hit the US hard come January, peaking at 2.8 million new cases a day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congresswoman carjacked in Philly...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/mary-gay-scanlon-carjacked-congresswoman-carjacking-philadelphia-fdr-park/11372337/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scanlon's government cell phone and ID were among the items stolen in the mid-afternoon carjacking.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
