<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA grounds drones over espionage fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51100759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US officials are reviewing a civilian drone programme because of concerns about Chinese infiltration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARIANA GRANDE SUED OVER '7 RINGS'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/ariana-grande-7-rings-copyright-suit-1203469915/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande was sued on Thursday by a hip-hop artist who claims she ripped off the chorus of his song for her hit “7 Rings.” Josh Stone, who performs as DOT, wrote and recorded &amp;#8220…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly Homicide Rate On Track to Triple...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/01/15/philadelphia-leaders-call-for-end-of-violence-as-homicide-rate-already-triple-what-it-was-at-this-time-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philly is already at triple the number of homicides in 2020 than where it was at this point last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporters getting 1st taste of restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd945e7c4c820637272a087d6b99043b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The impeachment trial of President Donald Trump has barely started and already journalists are getting a glimpse of how hard it will be cover the event under harsh new media...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee calls out perks for CEO, fired days later
...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/01/16/great-lakes-water-authority-manager-fired-questioning-retirement-ceo-whistleblower/4421510002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She told a GLWA board member that a new benefit program and changed-on-the-fly policies meant a retirement windfall for the CEO. Then she was fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Wars: NBC's 'PEACOCK' nears launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/nbc-peacock-price-launch-date-and-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peacock Free will consist of 7,500 hours of programming, including next-day access to current seasons of first-year NBC shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS moving into poor areas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c6133a81c3be90025e9142bb756f5117</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Starbucks has a point to prove: There's more to the company than selling $4 lattes to rich people. The Seattle-based coffee giant that has cultivated a reputation for being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay inmates tie the knot inside prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/gay-inmates-tie-knot-inside-cyprus-prison-n1117226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two men, one a Cypriot and the other a Brazilian national, are only the second same-sex couple to marry in a prison within the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  ALPHABET worth $1,000,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/alphabet-stock-hits-1-trillion-market-cap-for-first-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet's milestone follows Apple, Microsoft and Amazon. Analysts are bullish on the company's new CEO, Sundar Pichai, who previously ran Google, the business that accounts for substantially all of Alphabet's revenue and profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs testing male birth control -- gel rubbed on shoulders...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2020/01/16/i-think-its-great-doctors-looking-for-couples-to-test-male-birth-control-gel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Kansas conducting a clinical trial for a form of male birth control are looking for couples to test it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein lawyers want 'circus' trial moved...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e9d8114b704466ba6e5454fb09683466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Harvey Weinstein’s lawyers went to court Thursday with a last-minute demand to halt jury selection and move his rape trial out of New York City, where they say intense publicity,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB sign stealing scandal explodes: Stars wore 'devices that buzzed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/yankees/2020/01/mlb-rumors-carlos-beltrans-niece-says-astros-jose-altuve-alex-bregman-wore-devices-that-buzzed-as-part-of-sign-stealing-scandal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlos Beltran, the only player named in commissioner Rob Manfred's report on illegal sign stealing by the Houston Astros in 2017, stepped down Thursday as New York Mets manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas nuclear missile silo converted into castle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/a-couple-converted-a-kansas-nuclear-missile-silo-into-a-bizarre-18000-square-foot-castle-and-now-its-on-the-market-for-dollar32-million-%e2%80%94-see-inside/ss-BBZ1Cve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloodthirsty Squirrel Leaves 2 Hospitalized, Residents In Hiding...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/01/16/bloodthirsty-squirrel-leaves-2-hospitalized-neighbors-hiding-out-during-daytime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unruly squirrel is defying Disney stereotypes by terrorizing one Houston neighborhood, according to KPRC-TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI arrests alleged members of white supremacist group 'the Base'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fbi-arrests-alleged-members-of-white-supremacist-group-the-base/ar-BBZ1t9m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-year-old boy to become father...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7895845/13-year-old-schoolgirl-pregnant-boy-aged-TEN-Russia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The children study at different schools in the Krasnoyarsk Territory but are understood to have been friends since they were younger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: Chief Justice Roberts sworn in...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/video/senate/478569-watch-live-impeachment-articles-formally-introduced-in-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts was sworn in at just after 2 p.m. to preside over the Senate impeachment trial of President Trump.After being sworn in, Roberts is swearing in members of the Senate by administering the same oath.House impeachment managers went to the Senate on Thursday to formally introduce the two impeachment articles against President Trump by reading them aloud.Watch the Senate proceedings live in the video above.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolf puppies play fetch too, scientists find...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wolf-puppies-play-fetch-too-scientists-162741111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a game familiar to most people: you throw an object a short distance, and wait as your joyful canine companion leaps to intercept and return the missile, encouraged by words of praise or a pat on the head. The finding was made by chance as researchers in Sweden subjected 13 wolf puppies born</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US military training for Saudi students could resume soon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c5fda84e69e46ff8c88c5b85d4f9c250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. training for more than 800 Saudi Arabian military students could be restarted "in the coming days," the Pentagon said Thursday, nearly six weeks after a shooting by one...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVOCADO TERROR:  Inside female drug lord La Catrina's New Generation Cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10734265/maria-esquivel-la-catrina-sicaria-jalisco-new-generation-cartel-cjng-bridges-avocados/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA Catrina raised her bloodied hand to the soldier filming her final moments — the hitwoman with the golden gun had been shot in the neck in a firefight with cops and the Mexican Army. The 21-year-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dozens of drones 'as big as cars' repeatedly seen in skies over Colorado... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/263700/drone-colorado-conspiracy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRONES described as big as cars have been spotted over the Midwestern sky, sparking conspiracy theories and leaving many scratching their heads. Sightings have been reported in Colorado since Novem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLL CALL:  Is Trump really the MVP of the GOP?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/campaigns/is-trump-really-the-mvp-of-the-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He flipped 3 states in 2016, but Trump may not be as amazing a candidate as he gets credit for, and his status as savior may be overrated, Gonzales writes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCHDOG: WHITE HOUSE BROKE LAW</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/16/white-house-violated-the-law-by-freezing-ukraine-aid-gao-says-099682</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats have said the Ukraine aid pause is part of a broader “pattern of abuse” by the White House budget office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3rd MLB manager fired as sign stealing scandal explodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28496773/sources-carlos-beltran-mets-manager</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlos Beltran, the only player named in MLB's investigation of the Houston Astros sign-stealing scandal, is out as manager of the Mets before beginning his first season with the team, soures told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLD ON UKRAINE AID ILLEGAL</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/478557-gao-finds-trump-administration-broke-law-by-withholding-aid-from</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration’s decision to freeze the release of security assistance to Ukraine violated the law, the Government Accountability Office (GAO) said in a new</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators sworn in for Trump trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-articles-heading-senate-134141787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid a solemn silence, articles of impeachment against Donald Trump were read aloud on the Senate floor on Thursday as the bitterly divided chamber began a historic trial of the US president for abuse of power and obstruction of Congress. Senate Sergeant of Arms Michael Stenger opened just the third</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tax cut hands $32-billion windfall to top banks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tax-cut-hands-32-171229567.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Savings for the top six U.S. banks from President Donald Trump’s signature tax overhaul accelerated last year, now topping $32 billion as the lenders curbed new borrowing, pared jobs and ramped up payouts to shareholders.JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co., Bank of America Corp., Citigroup Inc., Wells</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to announce 'big action' on prayer in schools... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article239348103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmer eaten by own pigs as horrified neighbours discover bones in yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/farmer-eaten-pigs-horrified-neighbours-21295063</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The elderly man was in his 70s and lived alone on a farm in Osiek in Lower Silesia, Poland, where his pigs were found roaming freely around the yard near fragments of bone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN:  Joaquin Phoenix never talked about brother's death -- until he thought it would win him an Oscar...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/15/joaquin-phoenix-and-all-stars-will-talk-about-anything-for-an-oscar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to know how much any given actor wants an Oscar? Just listen to them talk — and talk and talk and talk — about people and subjects that were once famously off-limits. Take Joaquin Phoenix. Lon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Purple Haze' Filling Arizona Skies Coming From UV Lights At Pot Farm...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2020/01/15/lights-from-marijuana-farm-create-purple-sky/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lights from a medical marijuana farm filled the sky over Snowflake, Arizona, with a bright purple glow on a recent foggy morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient in Japan confirmed as having new virus from China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3845a158612c6cc556c8cb7b91f5d078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan's government said Thursday a man treated for pneumonia after returning from China has tested positive for the new coronavirus identified as a possible cause of an outbreak in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More police officers died by suicides than on duty in 2019, advocacy group says...</title>
      <link>https://www.readingeagle.com/news/world/more-police-officers-died-by-suicides-than-on-duty-in/article_65d5e020-e1e3-5cfe-9e4c-a2d3d8cb127f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.readingeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — More police officers died by suicide than in the line of duty in 2019, and the number of reported police suicides rose for the fourth consecutive year,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READ REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/478565-read-gao-report-finding-trump-administration-broke-the-law-on-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration violated the law by withholding promised security assistance aid to Ukraine, the Government Accountability Office said Thursday in a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Faithful execution of law does not permit President to substitute own policy priorities for those Congress enacted'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200116144118-rwhda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-GAO (URGENT):U.S. watchdog says Trump administration violated law by withholding Ukraine aid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Post Different Photo With President Every Time Claims Not to Know Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/hes-lying-lev-parnas-says-hell-post-a-photo-with-trump-every-time-president-claims-not-to-know-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indicted Rudy Giuliani associate Lev Parnas said President Donald Trump is "lying" when he claims not to know Parnas, and promised to release a different photo of the pair together each time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battles, Backlash, CIA Meetings and Secret Call With Snowden...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/homeland-declassified-battles-backlash-cia-meetings-a-secret-call-edward-snowden-1269957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claire Danes, Mandy Patinkin, Damian Lewis and the creators of the era-defining Showtime drama — now entering its eighth and final season — reveal in The Hollywood Reporter’s oral history never-told tales of a show that smashed records, captivated presidents and predicted everything from terrorist attacks to Russian election hacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein had burst capillaries in eyeballs which 'suggests he was strangled'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7894685/The-burst-capillaries-Epsteins-eyeballs-pathologists-say-suggests-murder.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING GRAPHIC CONTENT: In an exclusive clip from a Dr. Oz special set to air on Thursday, pathologist Dr. Michael Baden examines photographs of Epstein's eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW HITS NEW RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/us-futures-after-us-china-trade-deal-ahead-of-bank-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose to hit fresh record highs after Morgan Stanley reported quarterly figures that easily topped analyst expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUCUS CHAOS: NEW IOWA RULES COULD SPARK CLASHING CLAIMS OF VICTORY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/43354ef73124d58d94ca434b9016b4a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — The Iowa caucuses are never simple. Voters spend hours in high school gymnasiums or public libraries, starting their night by declaring support for their preferred...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With rivals stuck in impeachment trial, Biden and Buttigieg to barnstorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-impeachment/with-rivals-stuck-in-impeachment-trial-biden-and-buttigieg-to-barnstorm-iowa-idUSKBN1ZF18S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidates Joe Biden and Pete Buttigieg will blitz Iowa ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Seychelles, nature is prized above mass tourism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/seychelles-nature-prized-above-mass-tourism-015617936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a shady patch along a pristine white beach on Mahe Island, a radio spits out reggae and snapper sizzles on the barbecue, as Seychelloise Nareen tops up her rum and coke on time off from her job aboard a luxury yacht.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-pope's shadow Vatican role in the spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ex-popes-shadow-vatican-role-spotlight-040302571.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2013, Benedict became the first pontiff to resign in almost 600 years. This week, Benedict's contribution to a book on celibacy was seen as a strategic attempt to undermine his successor Pope Francis and boost the cause of a combative ultra-conservative wing of the Church. Experts say the problem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Woman Walks Topless Through Baggage Claim At Miami Airport...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/01/15/woman-caught-on-camera-walking-naked-at-miami-international-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman walking through the baggage claim area of Miami International Airport while casually removing all of her clothes is now in custody for a mental evaluation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin cements power as Russian lawmakers approve his new PM...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a93f5457f64b46fc3a4d142c6478198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian lawmakers on Thursday quickly approved the appointment of a new prime minister, a day after President Vladimir Putin kicked off an unexpected reshuffle of his inner circle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine volcano's quakes, cracks send more people fleeing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/884fefdfc719392d6df1f070ff9734c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEMERY, Philippines (AP) — A Philippine volcano that erupted last weekend belched smaller plumes of ash and shuddered continuously with earthquakes Thursday, prompting authorities to block access...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete decision on police chief shadows presidential run...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/03c58d5429448bfbf78cfb76fe682d24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Karen DePaepe had been waiting all day for a call back from Pete Buttigieg. It was March 2012, and the 30-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, had just decided to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the odyssey: Taking closer look at Kubrick's '2001'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/jan/16/2001-a-space-odyssey-stanley-kubrick-exhibition-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At an expansive new exhibition in New York, the director’s defining science fiction opus is explored in detail with help from those who made it with him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULTIPLE VICTORIES?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/16/iowa-caucus-vote-totals-change-099519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The release of raw vote totals for the first time could give multiple candidates grist to claim victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery virus spreads from China to Japan as epidemic fears grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-sars-like-coronavirus-spreads-21290545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SARS-like virus has spread from China to Japan sparking fears the mysterious contagion could become an epidemic and infect more people worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost 40% of world will witness civil unrest in 2020, research claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/40percent-of-countries-will-witness-civil-unrest-in-2020-report-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Risk of backlash by security forces is deemed high in countries such as Russia, Saudi Arabia and China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine opens criminal investigation into possible surveillance of U.S. ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/ukraine-opens-criminal-investigation-surveillance-marie-yovanovitch/story?id=68324113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine is opening a criminal investigation into possible illegal surveillance of former U.S. Ambassador Marie Yovanovitch after the release of Lev Parnas' text messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonstruck: Japanese billionaire's girlfriend entrants top 20,000...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200116050425-quq38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-BILLIONAIRE/MAEZAWA (PIX):Moonstruck: Japanese billionaire's girlfriend entrants top 20,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWNEY DISASTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/0/dolittle-savaged-critics-robert-downey-jr-seems-determined-sabotage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universal has barely had a moment to shake the shame off its whiskers after Cats, but now it's got another big-budget disaster on its hands:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major test for McConnell, Schumer...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478513-trumps-trial-a-major-test-for-mcconnell-schumer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The looming Senate impeachment trial is a major test for both Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) and Minority Leader Charles Schumer (D-N.Y.) as they square off in what could be the most defining battle on Capitol Hill this year before the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa Dems view flawed front-runners with anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/478509-iowa-democrats-view-flawed-front-runners-with-anxiety</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMES, Iowa — Democratic voters fear their party is on the brink of repeating the mistakes that sent President Trump to the White House as they consider their choices weeks before the state’s first-in-the-nation caucuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TRIAL: FOUR REPUBLICANS COULD PREVENT RAPID ACQUITTAL...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-senate-trial-kicks-off-090000031.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s impeachment moves to the GOP-controlled Senate where the president and Democrats will battle over a small group of Republicans whose votes will determine the course of a trial on whether he should be removed from office.The Senate proceedings will begin formally on Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump turns signing into rambling hour-plus monologue...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-turns-trade-deal-signing-into-rambling-hour-plus-monologue/ar-BBYZOrc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$95 Billion Centerpiece Already In Doubt?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/95-billion-centerpiece-trade-deal-190120191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. China has pledged to buy almost $95 billion worth of additional U.S. commodities as part of a phase one trade deal. The market is not so sure.Prices fell Wednesday for most raw materials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren-Sanders rift has progressives nervous about fallout...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2bdb63b80b33b5dcd676cd6889e49f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — For nearly a year, Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders pushed strongly progressive ideas into the Democratic primary spotlight, feeding off each other to build support for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Rudy associate on MADDOW...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/708b81d4c77038eb0b751c30f72ff315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A close associate of President Donald Trump's personal lawyer says he delivered an ultimatum in May to the incoming president of Ukraine that no senior U.S. officials would...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. and China tiptoe around holes in new trade agreement...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200115222233-ea7xk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-U.S. and China tiptoe around holes in new trade agreement</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
