<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CA Gov. Newsom to Sign Bill Targeting Trump Tax Returns...</title>
      <link>https://yashar.substack.com/p/exclusive-newsom-trump-tax-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;yashar.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to share this post on social media, please use this link: https://yashar.substack.com/ Exclusive: California Gov. Newsom to Sign Bill Targeting Trump Tax Returns California Gov. Gavin Newsom, my former boss, tells me that he has decided to sign a bill that would require all presidential and gubernatorial candidates to submit five years of tax returns in order to qualify for the primary ballot in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  LEADS PRAYER SESSION FOR WHITE PEOPLE TO APOLOGIZE FOR WRONGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n1Mxs06hBe8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribe to our channel! https://goo.gl/pyGqbu Footage has emerged of the 2020 Democratic Candidate leading a prayer which called for the audience to apolog...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not much desert diversity: Burning Man attendees white, well-off...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Burning-Man-Census-2018-diversity-inclusion-Burner-14151360.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Black Rock City Census Project shows us demographics of Burning Man 2018 participants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica wants to end beatings and paddling of kids, saying it leads to later violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/latinamerica/top-stories/jamaica-wants-to-end-beatings-paddling-of-kids-saying-it-leads-to-later-violence/ar-AAENQ8b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing portrait emerges of  Garlic Festival shooter...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/disturbing-portrait-emerges-of-gilroy-garlic-festival-shooter/ar-AAF49v3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brad Pitt Compares Weinstein Scandal To Manson Murders...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/brad-pitt-compares-harvey-weinstein-scandal-to-manson-murders-129510 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's more that I think we're getting recalibrated, but in a good way."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO SHOT DEAD AT WALMART IN TN...</title>
      <link>https://www.commercialappeal.com/story/news/2019/07/30/southaven-mississippi-walmart-shooting-police-respond-report-active-shooter/1864992001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.commercialappeal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two were killed and at least two injured at a Southaven, Mississippi, Walmart outside of Memphis Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARIANNE WILLIAMSON: I'M NOT A NEW-AGE NUT!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/455311-marianne-williamson-i-am-not-a-wacky-new-age-nutcase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Marianne Williamson pushed back against what she described as a false narrative surrounding her, insisting that she is not a “wacky new-age nutcase.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tech firm eyes IPO for gay dating app GRINDR...</title>
      <link>https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/china-tech-firm-eyes-ipo-104659233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese parent company of the popular gay dating app Grindr on Tuesday said it will "restart" plans for a public listing after a US national security panel dropped its opposition to the move. US authorities had earlier raised concerns about the potential misuse of the app's data by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLASH OF THE LIBS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/clash-liberals-warren-sanders-set-showdown-141610910.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading liberals in the 2020 presidential race will command the spotlight in Tuesday's Democratic debate, and sparks could fly as Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders battle over who will be torchbearer for the party's progressive wing. Frontrunner Joe Biden takes the stage Wednesday night between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Center tracking two tropical waves in Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/weather/hurricane/fl-ne-two-tropical-waves-atlantic-20190730-lh5k6dxdkbh7bkdna5g5fjqtoi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tropical wave that’s path points toward Florida could strengthen by the weekend. Meanwhile, another disturbance has formed off the west coast of Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 COMCASTNBC Execs Funded Harris Campaign Before Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/business/joseph-vazquez/2019/07/29/12-nbccomcast-execs-funded-harris-campaign-debate </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN head Zucker calls the shots but checks his aim...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/CNN-head-Zucker-calls-the-shots-but-checks-his-aim-14250723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Side shot! Side shot! Side shot!"  It's Mueller Day in Washington, and the man calling out instructions in the darkened control room of CNN's Washington bureau gets his wish as the screens on the wall in front him, along with TV screens across the country, change at his command. These decisions are usually made by one of the network's many producers, but this particular camera angle was emphatically suggested by none other than network president Jeff Zucker, who came down from New York to prepare for this week's Democratic primary debate and decided to make a quick stop in the control room. Mueller's halting testimony was not making for the most riveting TV, and Zucker was doing his best to liven things up.  Zucker has long prided himself on his ability to do just that. He oversaw NBC's "Today" show in its prime Katie Couric years. He bought the reality show "The Apprentice," which turned into a monster hit and turned Donald Trump into a TV star. But since he has come to CNN, the network has been in third place in the cable-news ratings race, and someone, somewhere - often but certainly not exclusively the resident of the White House - always seems to be pointing out how CNN is messing up.  The first debates last month on NBC networks set viewership records for Democratic primary season, and now CNN plays host for two nights with 20 candidates in Detroit on Tuesday and Wednesday. It's the network's biggest moment yet in the 2020 election cycle - an election cycle that could serve as a sort of do-over for Zucker, for CNN and for the media in general.  Zucker came under intense criticism for CNN's mode of coverage in the 2016 election. He has acknowledged some mistakes while defending the network overall, and vows that this time will be different.  The network won't air any candidate rallies live and unedited, as it did...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia blamed for radioactive cloud over Europe...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/07/30/russia-blamed-nuclear-accident-sent-radioactive-cloud-floating-across-europe-10481891/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious incident in 2017 was the worst release of radioactive material since Fukushima.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fly buzzes Duterte as he attacks priests...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/asia/philippines/fly-buzzes-rodrigo-duterte-as-he-attacks-philippine-priests-1.65532509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President uses the incident to criticise the country’s influential Catholic church</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body of 1930s gangster John Dillinger to be exhumed...</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2019/07/29/body-of-1930s-gangster-john-dillinger-to-be-exhumed-from-grave-at-crown-hill-cemetery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS, Ind. – The body of gangster John Dillinger is set to be exhumed from his grave at Indianapolis’ Crown Hill Cemetery. A permit to disinter, remove and reinter Dillinger’s remains was issued on June 18, according to documents from the Indiana State Department of Health. Michael C. Thompson, who is listed as Dillinger’s nephew, is the person who applied for the permit. FOX59 is working to determine why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Oscar Buzz For Joaquin Phoenix 'JOKER'?</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/dc/2019/07/30/joker-joaquin-phoenix-oscar-nominations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not the first time we've heard this, but it looks like Todd Phillips' Joker is shaping up to [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS:  Drone makes 50 mile commercial delivery...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/drone-makes-first-commercial-delivery-in-the-bahamas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone successfully made a commercial delivery in The Bahamas last month traveling&amp;nbsp;more than 50 miles over land and water in 28 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren, Bernie awkward truce faces biggest test yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/30/elizabeth-warren-bernie-sanders-2019-debates-1440419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longtime ideological comrades have resisted going after each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-animal hybrid experiments set to begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/human-animal-hybrid-japan-stem-cell-research-tokyo-genes-a9027131.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temps Dip Into 30s In MN; Break 121-Year-Old Record!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/07/30/minnesota-weather-temperatures-dip-to-37-degrees-in-international-falls-breaking-121-year-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the calendar says Minnesota is in the middle of summer, it felt like fall in northern Minnesota on Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pattinson, DaFoe Slowly Lose Minds in 'LIGHTHOUSE' Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/trailers/2019/07/30/the-lighthouse-trailer-robert-pattinson-willem-dafoe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hyag7lR8CPA "How long have we been on this rock? Five weeks? Two days? Help me to recollect," Willem Dafoe asks…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyachts and bad art: Mykonos party island of super-rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/money/2019/jul/30/superyachts-and-bad-art-how-mykonos-became-the-party-island-of-the-super-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Greek island has long attracted a glamorous clique, but the influx of billionaires has transformed it into a haven of absurd luxury</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tax threat on French wine 'completely moronic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-france/trumps-tax-threat-on-french-wine-is-completely-moronic-says-farming-minister-idUSKCN1UP0M2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French farming minister Didier Guillaume said on Tuesday U.S. President Donald T...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA issuing hacking alert for small planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6219f26c3ea145b6b29b5e69115504a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman Urinates On Potatoes At WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/07/30/woman-wanted-for-urinating-on-potatoes-at-pennsylvania-walmart-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement, Walmart said it "it immediately disposed of the affected products and sanitized the area."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plastic junk spawns desert island disaster in Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/plastic-junk-spawns-desert-island-disaster-pacific-063617712.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Floating plastic garbage has swamped a remote Pacific island once regarded as an environmental jewel and scientists say little can be done to save it while a throwaway culture persists. Henderson Island is an uninhabited coral atoll that lies almost exactly halfway between New Zealand and Peru, with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto invites black men who kneeled during anthem...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7a6f72f6e8404562867722ce14db8edb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weightlifter becomes lightning rod for criticism of trans policy...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190730054454-gybhb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hubbard, who competed for New Zealand in men's weightlifting before her transition in her thirties, won two golds and a silver in Samoa earlier this month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOOGLE bought my friend's face for $5'...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/google-bought-my-friends-face-for-5/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Google works on a version of Face ID for its next Pixel phone, its employees are stopping people in public places and enticing them with a $5 gift card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosquito-borne virus that causes brain swelling, death detected in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/mosquitoborne-virus-that-causes-brain-swelling-death-in-humans-detected-in-florida-230118395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mosquitos carrying a virus that can infect humans, causing brain swelling and death, has been found in Florida. Here’s what you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-Right Proud Boys Go on Trial -- but Anti-Fascists Boycotting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/30/nyregion/proud-boys-nyc-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four victims have not cooperated with the authorities and are not even known to prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Wrong With Big Tech's Eyes?</title>
      <link>https://www.newswars.com/whats-wrong-with-big-techs-eyes-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newswars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something is not right with the tech industry's most powerful leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Affordability Crisis Spreads to Heartland...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-housing-affordability-crisis-spreads-090002233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Low mortgage rates and thriving employment should be the recipe for a strong housing market. Instead, they’re deepening America’s affordability crisis.What began on the coasts, in areas like New York and San Francisco, is now radiating into the nation’s heartland, as well as to cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, Spies, Audio Tape: AMAZON ALEXA Snooping on Private Lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9611689/outrage-as-amazons-alexa-listens-to-brits-having-sex-rowing-swearing-and-sharing-medical-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SUN investigation today reveals Amazon staff can listen to Alexa recordings of British couples rowing, discussing private family matters — and having sex. The sounds of lovemaking are among noise…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allowance forever? Millennials still taking money from parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/personal-finance/allowance-forever-some-millennials-still-taking-money-from-parents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 13 percent of millennials admitted they have no savings at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPY AGENCIES PUSH FOR ENCRYPTION 'BACK DOOR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7300373/British-spies-want-backdoor-access-encrypted-Facebook-WhatsApp-messages.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK intelligence chiefs will meet with their Five Eyes allies from the US, Canada, Australia and New Zealand today to discuss access to encrypted messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot can serve up piping hot bowl of noodles in just 45 secs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sophie-robot-whips-oodles-singapore-noodles-090350309.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Singaporean engineering company has built a robot that can serve up a piping hot bowl of laksa, one of the city-state's most well-known dishes, in just 45 seconds. "It's excellent, I would say there's no difference between the one created by the robot and human," said Paul Yong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tickle' therapy could help slow aging...</title>
      <link>https://eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-07/uol-tc072919.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Adviser Said to Have Pursued Saudi Nuclear Deal as He Sought Administration Role... </title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/07/30/trump-adviser-said-to-have-pursued-saudi-nuclear-deal-as-he-sought-administration-role/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — Twelve days after President Trump was sworn in and five days after he roiled the Arab world with his first effort to restrict the entry of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senators Cool to Trump Choice for Top Intelligence Post... </title>
      <link>https://time.com/5637792/trump-ratcliffe-warning-burr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pick also elicited fatalism from the intelligence community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNIVES OUT FOR BIDEN</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/vodkapundit/on-the-eve-of-the-debates-the-long-knives-come-out-for-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Democratic contenders warm up for the second round of debates, the other candidates' knives are out for Joe Biden -- with the mainstream media helping keep those edges sharp. This morning the New York Times published a hit piece by Katie Glueck and Jonathan Martin, headlined "Why Joe Biden...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly unrest in Latin America's jails...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deadly-unrest-latin-americas-prisons-194030475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadly riot in a prison at Altamira in northern Brazil, which left more than 50 dead on Monday, is the latest unrest in Latin America's notoriously overcrowded jails. Of the deadliest prison riots around the world in recent years, the vast majority have been in Latin America. In 1994, 121 inmates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president will not commit to safe third-country agreement...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190730023917-pbpab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-PRESIDENT/MIGRATION (URGENT):Mexican president says Mexico could not commit to safe third-country agreement - Bloomberg</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Internet Pioneer Who Exposed Misdeeds Gets Heavy Prison Term... </title>
      <link>http://bkknews.org/chinese-internet-pioneer-who-exposed-misdeeds-gets-heavy-prison-term/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bkknews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.I. to identify -- A.I...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/f/614021/a-new-tool-uses-ai-to-spot-text-written-by-ai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI algorithms can generate text convincing enough to fool the average human—potentially providing a way to mass-produce fake news, bogus reviews, and phony social accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  PELOSI STRONGER THAN EVER!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/nancy-pelosi-trump-wrestler-and-tightrope-walker-wins-the-hearts-of-democratic-centrists/ar-AAF1fqJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two rapes put 19-year-old in therapy. Then, her therapist told her she was 'so sexy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article233235271.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic Cash Kings: CHAINSMOKERS New Highest Paid DJs...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/monicamercuri/2019/07/29/the-worlds-highest-paid-djs-of-2019/#44fea55f7a97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top 15 acts clocked $358 million in pretax earnings over the past 12 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAHM EMANUEL: Door Closed on Swing Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/07/29/rahm-emanuel-2020-democrats-closed-door-swing-voters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rahm Emanuel penned a memo to 2020 Democrat presidential hopefuls, urging them to go beyond Twitter to connect with American swing voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and little-known candidates have most at stake...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/biden-and-little-known-candidates-have-the-most-at-stake/article_01063733-f250-5b22-8ba3-9da62c164183.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a two nights of debate that recast the Democratic race, a new round beginning Tuesday could shake up the contest even more by culling the presidential field to just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex workers give red light to leaving famed Amsterdam district...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/sex-workers-red-light-leaving-famed-amsterdam-district-020150310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bathed in red neon light, hundreds of prostitutes ply their trade from behind windows in the narrow canalside streets of Amsterdam – and that's how they want it to stay. The Dutch capital's first female mayor has vowed to clean up the notorious red light district and possibly even close some</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY ARE SO MANY YOUNG MEN SO ANGRY...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/29/angry-young-men-continue-to-be-americas-greatest-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than 24 hours after yet another mass shooting in America, the youngest fatalities a 6-year-old boy and a 13-year-old girl, authorities said they were still seeking a motive. It seems the 19-ye…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  At least 57 dead in Brazil prison riot... </title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/least-52-dead-brazil-prison-riot-official-172817830--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 57 inmates were killed during a prison riot in northern Brazil on Monday as rival gang factions fought each other, an official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A$AP Rocky, the eccentric Harlem rapper on trial in Sweden... </title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/ap-rocky-eccentric-harlem-rapper-trial-sweden-022122161--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A contrarian businessman with a penchant for fashion and a boyish smile, rapper A$AP Rocky has risen out of poverty in Harlem to become one of contemporary hip hop's VIPs in the past decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury says Katy Perry copied Christian song...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7eef738596e9458eacb9f9015d7fd7fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPITAL ONE DATA BREACH, 100 MILLION IMPACTED; FBI ARRESTS SEATTLE WOMAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberscoop.com/capital-one-data-breach-credit-cards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cyberscoop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Capital One announced a large data breach Monday, with the company saying that one person accessed personal information on up to 100 million people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Dems keep shifting left. Moderates fret they'll shift even further...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article233177051.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR:  ELEVATORS KEEP GETTING STUCK IN CHICAGO SKYSCRAPER...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-elevator-rescue-weekend-20190729-n7z3e2khdrbopogyx2iwexqgdy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s one of those things where it’s the boy who cried wolf or something. . . I don’t know what they have to do with their elevator system.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Trump blasts black congressman as racist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4175ea0e61e746cd95d7c684cd6a59f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman kills 2 kids, 1 other at California festival...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/35e45f6d09e347c4a1c51c52cf77725c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Giving Up Custody of Kids -- to Get Need-Based College Aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/university-of-illinois-financial-aid-fafsa-parents-guardianship-children-students</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First, parents turn over guardianship of their teenagers to a friend or relative. Then the student declares financial independence to qualify for tuition aid and scholarships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 KIDS AMONG DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-id-gilroy-garlic-festival-shooter-as-santino-william-legan-victims-include-2-children/ar-AAF1idz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police clarifies: Won't pull people over in 'positive ticketing' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/tempe/2019/07/29/tempe-police-positive-ticketing-campaign-could-unconstitutional/1858566001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tempe Police Department started a "Positive Ticketing Campaign" initiative to hand out Circle K drink coupons for following traffic laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's youngest terrorist gets lifelong anonymity...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/uknews/britains-youngest-terrorist-gets-lifelong-anonymity-after-lawyers-argue-he-may-become-isis-poster-boy/ar-AAF0XFg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 up for grabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-07-28/usc-latimes-poll-democratic-primary-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since April, half of Democratic primary voters have changed their minds about which candidate they favor, the latest USC-Dornsife/Los Angeles Times poll finds. Joe Biden continues to lead, but the poll highlights the volatile nature of the contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUNMAN ID'D</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7298307/Hateful-final-Instagram-posts-Gilroy-Garlic-shooter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santino Legan, 19, has been identified as the gunman who opened fire on crowds at Sunday's festival, killing three people including a six-year-old boy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline CEO warns: BOEING better get its 's*** together'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/29/ryanair-rails-against-boeing-for-aircraft-delays-from-737-max-grounding.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryanair's CEO also warns investors about potential job cuts due the Boeing 737 Max grounding, now in its fifth month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Information Of LAPD Officers, Applicants Exposed By Data Breach...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/29/lapd-officers-applicants-data-breach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Eric Garcetti’s office issued a statement Monday confirming that the breach was discovered Thursday and “involved limited information about city of Los Angeles job applicants in a database that is no longer used by the Personnel Department.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER lays off 400...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9163254ba16a4c36a5f0f67f0c990b6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIL NAS X breaks record for most weeks No. 1 on BILLBOARD...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/music/lil-nas-x-s-old-town-road-breaks-record-most-n1035686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer-rapper joked that he would celebrate the accomplishment by sending Mariah Carey flowers after beating her 16-week record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control new GOOGLE phone -- without touching...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/29/google-pixel-4-teaser-video-shows-face-unlock-and-gestures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google confirmed the upcoming Pixel 4 will offer face unlock and gesture controls in a new video on Monday that teased the phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA finds missile launcher in passenger's bag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/29/tsa-finds-missile-launcher-in-passengers-checked-bag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A traveler flying out of a Maryland airport packed a missile launcher from Kuwait in his checked bag in the hopes of keeping it as a souvenir, officials said. Transportation Security Administration…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another NYC Bicyclist Killed: 18th To Die This Year...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/07/29/another-bicyclist-killed-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It happened around 9 a.m. at 35th Street and Third Avenue in the Greenwood Heights section of Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin critic Navalny returned to jail despite poisoning fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-politics-navalny/kremlin-critic-navalny-returned-to-jail-despite-poisoning-fears-idUSKCN1UO0TF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny was discharged from a Moscow hospital o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linked to INSTAGRAM posts?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/29/us/gilroy-california-food-festival-shooting-monday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect in the California food festival shooting used an assault-type rifle in his attack and was fatally shot by three officers who responded within a minute, Police Chief Scot Smithee said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Stars Form Lobbying Group to Counter Tech Giants' Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-07-29/rock-stars-form-lobbying-group-to-counter-tech-giants-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug-resistant superbug spreading in hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-49132425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are "extremely concerned" by a bacterium resistant to antibiotics of last resort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana to subsidize Communist-owned chemical plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/28/louisiana-plans-to-subsidize-dangerous-communist-o/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, “the great sucking sound” of outsourcing flowed in one direction. Jobs of all kinds migrated from high-wage countries to their impoverished counterparts. Think textiles moving from the Carolinas to India, and autos from Michigan to Mexico. China was the biggest beneficiary, as U.S. manufacturers were attracted to its massive, low-wage labor force and minimal environmental standards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: WHEN ZUCKER STUMPED FOR KAMALA...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article233256089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATHLETIC Sports News Site Hits 500,000 Subscribers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-07-29/the-athletic-sports-news-site-hits-500-000-subscribers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
