<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Most Psychopathic States USA...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1307670/us-states-with-the-most-psychopaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Connecticut wins the dubious award of most psychopathic state in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Egos get bigger after meditation, yoga...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1307380/yoga-and-meditation-boost-your-ego-say-psychology-researchers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So much for quieting your inner narcissist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative wins presidency in Colombia, stops leftist rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/D-C-Colombian-squares-off-against-former-13001753.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTA, Colombia - Conservative Ivan Duque captured Colombia's presidency on Sunday, bringing to power a U.S.-educated 41-year old whose victory promises an aggressive new era in the drug war and could upend a historic peace deal that ended Latin America's longest running insurgency. With nearly all the votes counted, Duque held a commanding 54-42 lead. Turnout was 53 percent of voters, higher than in other recent Colombian elections. By winning Sunday's vote, Duque - who spent years studying and working in Washington -- stopped the rise of his leftist opponent, Gustavo Petro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasure-hunters warned to keep pickaxes away after claim lost masterpiece hidden beneath Belgian street...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/ghent-altarpiece-code-solved-gino-marchal-belgium-treasure-dig-holes-kalandeberg-mystic-lamb-a8402156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Do not go to the shopping street with a shovel or spade,’ says Ghent’s mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman shoots husband in testicles after he tries to take air conditioner...</title>
      <link>https://www.actionnewsjax.com/news/local/report-woman-shoots-husband-in-testicles-after-he-tries-to-take-her-air-conditioner/770435073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.actionnewsjax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In October of last year, Kimberly Dunn, 35, shot her ex-husband in the testicles after he tried to take an AC unit, according to an arrest report. Story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Domain jacker' jailed over armed website heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/17/internet-domain-jacker-jailed-20-years-armed-website-heist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has been jailed for 20 years over the first known instance of armed &amp;quot;domain hijacking&amp;quot; in which he sought to gain control of a website at gunpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret rainforest at heart of African volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/17/mozambique-mount-lico-rainforest-new-species</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ‘dream team’ of scientists scaled Mount Lico and found a wealth of new species</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanctions on Russia spotlight threat posed to undersea cables...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/392577-spotlight-falls-on-russian-threat-to-undersea-cables</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New sanctions are highlighting fears Russia could target the telecom cables for espionage or sabotage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Puts Cyberwarriors on Offensive, Increasing Conflict Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/pentagon-puts-cyberwarriors-on-the-offensive-increasing-the-risk-of-conflict/17634489/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Pentagon has quietly empowered the United States Cyber Command to take a far more aggressive approach to defending the nation against cyberattacks, a shift in strategy that could increase the risk of conflict with the foreign states that sponsor malicious hacking groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landon Donovan Blasted By USA Team Members, Fans Over Mexico Support...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2781516-landon-donovan-criticized-by-past-present-usmnt-members-for-supporting-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former U.S. men's national soccer team players have been critical of Landon Donovan , who suggested in a video for Wells Fargo that American soccer fans should support ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUV fleeing Border Patrol crashes; 5 dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.kens5.com/article/news/5-people-die-in-south-texas-pursuit-crash-involving-undocumented-immigrants/273-565118086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kens5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Suburban was being chased by a Dimmit County deputy prior to the crash, the sheriff said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FATHER'S DAY: Bill Clinton 'son' calls for 'dad' to take paternity test...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/fathers-day-bill-clinton-son-calls-for-dad-to-take-paternity-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danney Williams still wants to have a relationship with the man he calls his “dad.” This Father’s Day, Williams, who says Bill Clinton is his father, is backing calls for Clinton to undergo a paternity test to prove — or disprove — his assertion. Retweet! https://t.co/tTArv8DjPM — Danney Williams (@danney_williams) June 17, 2018 “Retweet!” Williams …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ BEATS KIMMEL AT GAME...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Cruz-edges-out-Kimmel-in-charity-basketball-game-13000976.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the Thunderdome from "Mad Max" or the coliseum from "Spartacus," if either Max or Sparty were two, middle-aged American men playing a slow-motion car-crash of half-court basketball for charity and political one upsmanship. Conservative Texas Sen. Ted Cruz triumphed over liberal ABC late-night host/comedian Jimmy Kimmel with a hard-won 11-9 victory in the first Blobfish Basketball Classic at Texas Southern University's Health and Physical Education Arena Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman shouting 'Allahu akbar' attacks 2 with box cutter at France supermarket...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/woman-yelling-allahu-akbar-slashes-two-blade-france-181330845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were hurt in a town in southern France on Sunday when a woman shouting "Allahu akbar" (God is greatest) attacked them in a supermarket with a boxcutter knife, prosecutors said. A customer was struck in the chest during the late-morning assault in La Seyne-sur-Mer, outside the Mediterranean</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked Russian man falls to death from window injuring soccer fans below...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/naked-russian-man-falls-sixth-12729920</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the South Americans were hurt with one suffering with serious neck injuries and the other with a leg wound</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots will turn down sex if not in mood...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/sex-robot-turns-down-steamy-12726878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sexbot Samantha's ability to say "no" was demonstrated to an audience of stunned academics at one of the UK's leading science villages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico World Cup fans cause an EARTHQUAKE celebrating...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/mexicos-goal-celebration-against-germany-12730188</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican authorities reported the reading was recorded at the exact time Mexico took the lead in their Group F game</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY:  INVESTIGATE MUELLER!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-lawyer-calls-inquiry-muellers-russia-probe-160552705.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's personal lawyer on Sunday called for an investigation into special counsel Robert Mueller's Russia probe, claiming it was tainted from the outset under former FBI director James Comey. Giuliani's comments were the latest in a barrage of attacks on the probe by the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ministers back ban on filming soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israeli-ministers-back-ban-filming-soldiers-134728070.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli ministers on Sunday backed a draft law carrying a jail term of up to 10 years for those who film or photograph soldiers with harmful intent, the justice ministry said. The ministerial committee on legislation endorsed the bill against "people who film, photograph or record soldiers performing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOTTI' Whacked At Boxoffice With Just $1.7 Million Weekend...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/17/box-office-gotti-whacked-with-just-1-7-mil-weekend-incredibles-2-at-180-mil-biggest-ever-animated-weekend-open</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Gotti” is dead with just  $1,670,000  for its opening weekend. It’s Travolta’s lowest among regular openings based on theater count. But Travolta is used to low numbers&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem lawmakers make surprise visit to ICE detention center...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/392680-dem-lawmakers-make-surprise-visit-to-ice-detention-center</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Democratic lawmakers on Sunday paid a "surprise Father's Day visit" to an Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) detention center in New Jersey, capping off a week of heightened tensions surrounding the issue of migrant f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.Y. Assembly passes single-payer health care...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/17/new-york-assembly-passes-single-payer-universal-he/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York state Assembly has again endorsed a single-payer universal health care system. The proposal would allow all New Yorkers to enroll for health coverage that comes with no network restrictions, deductibles or co-pays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE:  FBI Informant Tried to Spy on Me...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-associate-Roger-Stone-reveals-new-contact-13001555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI - One day in late May 2016, Roger Stone - the political dark sorcerer and longtime confidant of Donald Trump - slipped into his Jaguar and headed out to meet a man with a Make America Great Again hat and a viscous Russian accent. The man, who called himself Henry Greenberg, offered damaging information about Hillary Clinton, Trump's presumptive Democratic opponent in the upcoming presidential election, according to Stone - who spoke about the previously unreported incident in interviews with The Washington Post. Greenberg, who did not reveal the information he claimed to possess, wanted Trump to pay $2 million for the political dirt, Stone said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman shouting 'Allahu akbar' attacks 2 with box cutter at France supermarket...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/06/17/woman-shouting-allahu-akbar-attacks-2-with-box-cutter-at-supermarket-in-france.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who allegedly shouted Allahu akbar attacked two people with a box cutter at a supermarket in southern France on Sunday before she was arrested, local media reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE:  FBI Informant Tried to Spy on Me...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/392662-roger-stone-russian-wanted-trump-to-pay-2m-for-dirt-on-clinton-during</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump campaign adviser Roger Stone said that he met with a Russian man during the 2016 campaign who wanted President Trump to pay $2 million for damaging information on Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress claims TESLA 'spontaneously' burst into flames...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5852195/Actress-Mary-McCormack-claims-husbands-Tesla-Model-S-spontaneously-combusted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is what happened to my husband and his car today,' McCormack wrote on Twitter Friday, posting a shocking video of a Model S spewing flames from the front driver's side front wheel well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Everest, The High-Altitude Dump...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mount-everest-high-altitude-rubbish-dump-033148000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades of commercial mountaineering have turned Mount Everest into the world's highest rubbish dump as an increasing number of big-spending climbers pay little attention to the ugly footprint they leave behind. "It is disgusting, an eyesore," Pemba Dorje Sherpa, who has summited Everest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist launches hunt for Loch Ness 'monster DNA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/scientist-launches-hunt-loch-ness-monster-dna-035644306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tales of a giant creature lurking beneath the murky waves of Loch Ness have been around for more than 1,500 years -- and one academic hopes the marvels of modern science can finally unravel the mystery. Neil Gemmell has travelled from the University of Otago in New Zealand to collect water samples in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON 'WILD WEST'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5853179/Less-one-20-street-robberies-burglaries-solved-police-new-figures-reveal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than one in 20 street robberies and burglaries are being solved in the UK, shocking new figures have revealed. The statistic will fuel concerns there is a crisis in the nation's policing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rapid Retreat in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationaljournal.com/s/669236?unlock=L6H53FDW9A8QQYG9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans have abandoned Senate races in states Trump carried, and could lose several key governorships as well. Trump’s boasting of crashing the blue wall is rapidly becoming ancient history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE:  FBI Informant Tried to Spy on Me...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-associate-roger-stone-reveals-new-contact-with-russian-national-during-2016-campaign/2018/06/17/4a8123c8-6fd0-11e8-bd50-b80389a4e569_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime political operative suspects the meeting in a South Florida restaurant was an FBI setup designed to hurt the Republican nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian on Running for Office: 'Never Say Never'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kim-kardashian-running-office-never-say-never-1120748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new interview with CNN's Van Jones, she also discussed her marriage to Kanye West and how being a mom has changed her for the better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Chicago, Stormy muses: 'Should I run for president?'</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-stormy-daniels-20180616-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though Stormy Daniels is at the center of one of the largest scandals to hit any White House in recent history, the adult film star says her bare-it-all show at the Admiral Theatre this weekend is, like the rest of her shows nationwide, not about politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Shooting At NJ Art Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/1-Dead-Several-Injured-in-Trenton-Art-Festival-Shooting-485766011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcphiladelphia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say at least one person has been killed and several others injured when shooting broke out at an all-night cultural event in Trenton, New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 injured...</title>
      <link>http://6abc.com/20-injured-suspect-killed-in-trenton-arts-festival-shooting/3612187/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty people including a child were injured and a suspect was killed after shots were fired during a 24 hour arts festival in Trenton, New Jersey where hundreds were in attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE Columnist Suspended For Fabrications...</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/news/local_coverage/2018/06/boston_globe_suspends_columnist_accused_of_embellishing_boston_marathon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Globe columnist Kevin Cullen has been suspended without pay for three months after “serious violations” in remarks he made about the Boston Marathon bombings — a penalty his union says he’s going to fight.Scott Steeves, president of the Boston Newspaper Guild, told the Herald last night Cullen will take his case to arbitration.“Kevin looks forward to defending himself,” Steeves said. “The guild stands behind Kevin 100 percent.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Use of Driver's License Databases to Nab Crooks Spurs Privacy Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/police-use-of-drivers-license-databases-to-nab-crooks-spurs-privacy-concerns-1529233200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law-enforcement officials who advocate for using facial recognition searches of driver’s license photos argue that it is a valuable tool; civil liberties advocates say it infringes on privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moped thieves steal UK Home Secretary's phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6550824/ive-been-robbed-by-a-moped-crook-says-sajid-javid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOME Secretary Sajid Javid has revealed he was a moped mugging victim — as he launches a blitz on street crime. He admits it left him fearing for his kids’ safety when they go out. The Tory, 48, wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama gas station clerk shoots customer as he walks out of store...</title>
      <link>http://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article213196489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a man was shot at the Obama gas station on Farrow Road, police have arrested the store's clerk, according to a Columbia police statement. Antar Daralhaj was arguing with a customer Saturday afternoon about overcharging for gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue ships dock in Spain as migrant debate roils Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3eeb4671542a40b39ded7b736cd685ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VALENCIA, Spain (AP) — Ships in the Aquarius aid convoy docked Sunday at the Spanish port of Valencia, ending a weeklong ordeal for hundreds of people who were rescued from the pe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NBA player charged for home invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/former-nba-player-charged-with-armed-robbery-coweta-county/RKsjSFosvDioSvzq2AkqzO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former NBA player who went to high school in Cobb County was arrested Friday night in connection w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How string of violent sex crimes traced to ex-NFL star...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/17/how-a-string-of-violent-sex-crimes-were-traced-to-former-nfl-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An eagle-eyed neighbor helped crack the bizarre case of a former NFL star now accused in a slew of attacks on women. It was just after 2:30 p.m. on June 7 when the Encinitas, Calif., resident spott…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Likens Abortion to Nazi Eugenics...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pope-francis-likens-abortion-to-nazi-eugenics-1529178587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In unusually blunt language, Pope Francis said that “to have an easy life, one does away with an innocent.” The pope also said the only real families are those based on marriage between a man and a woman.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
