<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TWISTED CANNES:  Movie where woman has sex with car takes Palme d'Or ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3303541/titane-sex-cars-cannes-film-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shock-fest Titane – a film about a woman having sex with cars – took home the top prize  Palme d’Or at Cannes last night. The news was revealed early at the closing ceremony in an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  20% of Americans believe microchips inside covid vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/omg/20-percent-of-americans-believe-microchips-are-inside-covid-19-vaccine-study-674272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;False content has been published on social media regarding the microchip theory, with many conspiracy theorists saying that COVID-19 is just a coverup to track people using the vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaotic scene after shots outside baseball stadium...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-baseball-mlb-washington-nationals-san-diego-padres-4ef44d26efc5499bcd96986c68e1a4ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the gunshots started to echo all around Nationals Park, San Diego Padres star shortstop Fernando Tatis Jr. quickly thought about the team's family members and friends in the seats. Tatis bolted from the bench down the left field line Saturday night, helped open a gate to the stands and began ushering a group back to the dugout to shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Jews visit contested holy site in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-jerusalem-b87218462ca854370b216798f62803a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Hundreds of Jewish pilgrims visited a contested Jerusalem holy site under heavy police guard on Sunday, shortly after Muslim worshippers briefly clashed with Israeli security forces at the flashpoint shrine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leak uncovers global abuse of cyber-surveillance weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/18/revealed-leak-uncovers-global-abuse-of-cyber-surveillance-weapon-nso-group-pegasus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spyware sold to authoritarian regimes used to target activists, politicians and journalists, data suggests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>180 reporters identified...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/18/ft-editor-roula-khalaf-among-180-journalists-targeted-nso-spyware</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data leak and forensics suggest NSO’s surveillance tool used against journalists at some of world’s top media companies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatters lie that innocent need not fear surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2021/jul/18/huge-data-leak-shatters-lie-innocent-need-not-fear-surveillance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our investigation shows how repressive regimes can buy and use the kind of spying tools Edward Snowden warned us about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quiet and secretive BLUE ORIGIN hopes to start new chapter with  Bezos space flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/quiet-and-secretive-blue-origin-hopes-to-start-new-chapter-with-jeff-bezos-s-space-flight/ar-AAMiims?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos has said Blue Origin is "the most important work I am doing." Tuesday, he'll launch to space on the company's New Shepard rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW NORMAL:  Real estate values have surged by 25% since pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/the-new-real-estate-normal/ar-AAMir6k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the fracturing American economy, any property can inspire a bidding war — and shut some people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takeaways from 'Pegasus Project'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Takeaways-from-the-Pegasus-Project-16322652.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military-grade spyware leased by the Israeli firm NSO Group to governments for tracking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Responses from nations...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Responses-from-countries-to-the-Pegasus-Project-16322662.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forbidden Stories, a Paris-based journalism nonprofit, and Amnesty International had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spyware sold to authoritarian regimes used to target activists, politicians and journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Private-Israeli-spyware-used-to-hack-cellphones-16322695.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military-grade spyware licensed by an Israeli firm to governments for tracking terrorists...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak closes Boy Scouts camp, another hits retirement home...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article252863438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boy Scouts camp canceled its scheduled activities in response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys and Antifa clash...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9799077/LAPD-orders-crowd-disperse-protests-transgender-rights-Koreatown-spa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles police arrested dozens of people during a transgender rights protest and fired non-lethal projectiles to disperse the unruly mob that turned violent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers seize ONLYFANS account to stream ISIS beheadings...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3303817/hackers-seized-onlyfans-model-account-isis-beheadings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ONLYFANS model’s account has been seized by hackers who are using it to stream “terrifying” ISIS beheadings. Tina Bean, 22, has lost almost all of her followers and has lost thousands of pounds …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Conservative pornstar' derails TURNING POINT USA's youth gathering...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/07/18/conservative-pornstar-derails-turning-point-usas-right-wing-youth-gathering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The adult entertainer Brandi Love was banned from a right-wing gathering after mounting pressure online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rebuffs DeSantis over CDC cruise rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/18/appeals-court-cdc-cruises-desantis-499987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11th Circuit's stay order puts on hold a courtroom victory that Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis won last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears: Won't perform while father rules career...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/jul/18/britney-spears-refuses-to-perform-again-while-father-retains-control-over-career</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the latest twist of her legal battle, the singer says she would rather share videos from her living room than go on stage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Rudy to face criminal investigation in AZ?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/donald-trump-and-rudy-giuliani-could-face-criminal-investigation-in-arizona-over-their-attempts-to-overturn-election/ar-AAMhV9y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona Sec of State Katie Hobbs asked AG Mark Brnovich to launch a criminal investigation into Donald Trump and allies for trying to overturn election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC socialites scared of BBC's Ghislaine Maxwell docu-series...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/17/nyc-socialites-running-scared-from-bbcs-ghislaine-maxwell-docu-series/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High society types who once rubbed elbows with Ghislaine and Jeffery Epstein are running scared and keeping mum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'America First' rally canceled in Anaheim amid 'public safety concerns'...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/america-first-rally-anaheim-gaetz/10893930/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Reps. Marjorie Taylor Greene of Georgia and Matt Gaetz of Florida had been expected to speak at the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far more adults don't want children than previously thought...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/07/17/far-more-adults-dont-want-children-than-previouslythough_partner-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study found that child-free people were just as satisfied with their lives as those with kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems look to crush highway habit...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/18/democrats-states-highways-transportation-499906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposed changes are riling up opposition from state transportation departments and the road-building lobby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside OXFORD's Most Exclusive Sex Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3dqxm/inside-oxford-universitys-most-exclusive-sex-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I saw my girlfriend going down on another girl on stage, in front of a cheering crowd."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Risks Increase With Alcohol Use...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2021/07/16/1016586837/new-study-says-nearly-3-4-million-cancers-a-year-linked-to-alcohol-use</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people don't realize alcohol consumption can cause cancer. A report in Lancet Oncology shows how big a risk factor it is for esophageal, mouth, larynx, colon, rectum, liver and breast cancers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-haul symptoms last 3 years?!</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/everything-smells-like-garbage-9-months-after-i-contracted-covid-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am living with a long-COVID symptom called parosmia, which distorts by sense of smell to make everything smell unpleasant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot police break up dueling trans protests outside LA spa...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/18/police-break-up-transgender-rights-protests-outside-los-angeles-spa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles police declared unlawful assembly as pro and anti-transgender rights protests gathered outside of Wi Spa, where a customer complained about a transgender woman using the spa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>31 hospitalized after SIX FLAGS chemical leak...</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/chemical-leak-six-flags-water-park-texas-hurricane-harbor-hospital-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 60 people were decontaminated by washing off and massaging their eyes under a fire truck hose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran insists prisoner swap deal struck...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-07-18/iran-insists-prisoner-swap-deal-was-agreed-with-us-says-ready-to-proceed-today</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken to diplomats: OK to admit America's flaws...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/16/blinken-us-human-rights-499833</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secretary of State shared details of his human rights and democracy priorities in a cable sent to U.S. embassies around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli police step up enforcement measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/coronavirus-in-israel-430-new-cases-147-percent-of-tests-positive-674215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The police will be able to verify the location of those quarantining through an SMS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Science Cure Death?  Sure Looks Like It...</title>
      <link>https://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:w4O9029kuNwJ:https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a36712084/can-science-cure-death-longevity/+&amp;cd=1&amp;hl=en&amp;ct=clnk&amp;gl=us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;webcache.googleusercontent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first unified theory of aging might be the key to humans living forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE:  Learn to switch off...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210718085456-5znvq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-SURGERY/VATICAN (PIX, TV):Learn to switch off, says pope in first appearance at Vatican after hospital stay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan hits RED SOX player with baseball in wild YANKEE scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/07/17/sports/fan-hits-alex-verdugo-with-baseball-crazy-scene-yankee-stadium-game-rain-delay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Red Sox and Yankees played through a downpour, cameras caught the left fielder screaming toward the left-field seats, with the Red Sox departing the field, claiming he was struck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Radio host Larry Elder not on list of CA recall candidates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-health-government-and-politics-elections-california-c5eedc7f144b2e7baa5745b800e67709</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California on Saturday released a list of 41 candidates running in the recall election targeting Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom that was striking for who wasn't on it: conservative radio talk show host Larry Elder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST COVID AT OLYMPIC VILLAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-2020-tokyo-olympics-health-coronavirus-pandemic-8cef15127de660b161807f1a9fd60ecd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Two athletes living in the Olympic Village have tested positive for COVID-19, the first to do so with the Tokyo Games opening on Friday. Organizers confirmed the positive tests on Sunday and both were listed as non-Japanese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMES:  BOOM OR BUST?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jul/17/boom-or-bust-can-troubled-tokyo-olympics-sparkle-once-the-flame-is-lit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most controversial Olympic Games in 40 years are going ahead despite fierce opposition and somehow could still draw us in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police scramble to deal with deadly road rage during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.police1.com/vehicle-incidents/articles/police-scramble-to-deal-with-deadly-road-rage-during-pandemic-IxON1B6pRtbC8yX3/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.police1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2020, 42 people a month on average were shot and killed or wounded in road rage incidents, according to a recent report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media scramble over, books, books, books...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-media-scramble-at-the-heart-of-trump-book-summer/ar-AAMg5ci?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As multiple books about the last president race to the shelves, juicy revelations have journalists chasing advance copies and looking for the best parts. It’s not bad for sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans  turn to 'critical race theory' in push to win back suburbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/article252807478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are betting the issue will not only energize their base, but help bring back some of the swing suburban voters they lost in the last election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop saves stabbing victim's life using potato chip bag and tape...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-officer-saves-stabbing-victims-life-using-potato-chip-bag-and-tape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The officer used the potato chip bag and the tape to fashion a covering for the wound ahead of paramedics’ arrival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  McAfee died broke after blowing $100 million on 'bizarre' houses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9796559/Once-worth-100M-John-McAfee-broke-died-bars-Spain-friend-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon before his death on June 23, McAfee claimed in a tweet that he had no hidden cash and was worth 'nothing' -- though tax evasion charges gave him ample reason to conceal any assets.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
