<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sandstorm Wreaks Havoc in Canary Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2020/02/24/canary-islands-airports-reopen-after-nightmare-sandstorm-haze/4854890002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All airports on Spain's Canary Islands had reopened Monday after authorities said the worst is over from a sandstorm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar-bait no more: Why serious-issue dramas floundering...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/feb/24/oscar-bait-no-more-why-serious-issue-dramas-are-floundering-dark-waters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worthy movies such as Dark Waters used to be the toast of Hollywood. But is the audience for them drying up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORE SHELVES EMPTY AS PANIC BUYING HITS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/coronavirus-store-shelves-empty-as-panic-buying-hits-italy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infected victims jump from 3 to 165 in just a few days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild 'MATRIX' filming keeps San Fran up all night with helicopters and fireballs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8037089/Wild-Matrix-4-filming-keeps-Downtown-San-Francisco-night-helicopters-300ft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flames lit up the city's streets as cameras rolled from 6pm to midnight on Saturday and Sunday, and helicopters flew low from 5am to 9am Sunday. Matrix 4 will be released next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside fight over FBI surveillance powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fbi-fisa-court-carter-page-trump-barr-2f54116e-47e3-4ba3-9f13-8c7ccf996228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has told officials, including Attorney General Barr, that he wants a major overhaul of the FISA process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nations seek biodiversity accord to stave off mass extinction...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nations-seek-biodiversity-accord-stave-off-mass-extinction-135358881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nature experts and government delegates gather this week in Rome to thrash out an international deal for endangered species, trying to avoid a mass extinction event caused by human activity. Having been hastily relocated from Kunming in China following the coronavirus outbreak, negotiators from more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: 1 of every 3 Venezuelans facing hunger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/88519b3806497d02619e710e91bc4ed8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — One of every three people in Venezuela is struggling to put enough food on the table to meet minimum nutrition requirements as the nation's severe economic contraction...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: Impact on companies 'more severe than thought'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/24/cramer-on-market-plunge-coronavirus-impact-more-severe-than-thought.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global stock market sell-off on the widening outbreak of coronavirus beyond China indicates further negative effects on U.S. multinational companies' earnings, CNBC's Jim Cramer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi calls to arrest 'sugar candy' female rapper draw ire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-calls-arrest-sugar-candy-female-rapper-draw-041725884.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official calls to arrest a Saudi female rapper who appeared in a music video has sparked an online backlash with many calling the move hypocritical as the kingdom invites Western women to perform. In the video, the young rapper from Mecca, who identifies herself as Asayel Slay, praises what she describes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A police raid, viral videos and broken lives of Nigerian gay law suspects...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200224092435-t19tg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among 47 Nigerian men on trial for same-sex affection are people who have been made homeless and lost their jobs by the publicity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Denies Cover-Up After Lawmaker Contradicts Official Figures...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/iran-denies-cover-up-after-lawmaker-contradicts-officia-1841883351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of Iran’s parliament announced on Monday that 50 people had died from the new coronavirus in the city of Qom and accused Iran’s Health Ministry of covering up the true extent of the outbreak in the country. The Health Ministry claims just 12 people have died in Iran from COVID-19, with 66 people sick from the disease. The official numbers in Iran were up from a total of 8 deaths and 43 illnesses reported on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Decaying skin': Fans grossed out by sex scene on 'WALKING DEAD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/fans-grossed-out-sex-scene-the-walking-dead-074423622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans weren't ready for Negan and Alpha to hook up with her still wearing her decaying human skin mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSANGE FIGHTS EXTRADITION TO USA IN COURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2020/feb/24/julian-assange-hearing-journalism-is-no-excuse-for-breaking-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for US government deliver opening arguments as extradition case begins</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman 'possessed by demons' restrained by nine men in terrifying exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/woman-possessed-demons-restrained-nine-21548275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Katchia, 29, turned "extremely violent" as she watched pastor Bob Larson's talk on casting out demons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots will develop 'freedom of thought' to escape human control...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/robots-freedom-thought-escape-rebel-21518301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Artificial intelligence (AI) expert Dr Ian Pearson told Daily Star Online that robots in future will be capable of developing their own line of thought – but it won't be good news for us</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'America loves India': Trump raucous welcome from 110,000 at cricket stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8036815/Crowds-line-greet-Donald-Melania-Trump-couple-touches-India.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald and Melania Trump stopped by the Taj Mahal Monday evening, capping off their first day in India with a visit to the world's most famous monument to love.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'll fight them to death': Judge Judy warns Bernie Bros...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8035481/Judge-Judy-says-shell-fight-Bernie-Bros-death-bid-Bloomberg-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Judy who officially threw her support behind Michael Bloomberg (pictured together in Texas) last month has a few words for the Bernie bros: 'I'll fight them to the death.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers 'treading water' despite booming economy, analysts say...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/22/workers-are-treading-water-despite-booming-economy-analysts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US economy is booming — but not half fast enough for the masses of workers still waiting on a pay raise, or who are in financial straits, according to analysts. Call them the other half. Despit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Pence 2024 Presidential Campaign Has Already Begun...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mike-pence-2024-presidential-campaign-090000463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump’s bid for a second term in office is giving Vice President Mike Pence an early edge in the race that’s already shaping up for the Republican nomination in 2024.Pence has lately been a mainstay at Trump’s signature campaign rallies, seldom missing the opportunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVOLUTION ON LEFT</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Sanders-ascent-forces-reckoning-for-Democrats-15078704.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders has seized a commanding position in the Democratic presidential race, building a diverse coalition that is driving his liberal movement toward the cusp of a takeover of a major political party.  The senator's ascendancy, though years in the making, is forcing a sudden reckoning in the Democratic Party's hierarchy as centrist politicians and their wealthy benefactors grapple with the upheaval brought by an electorate not only hungry to defeat President Donald Trump but also clamoring for radical change.  After Sanders' resounding victory in Saturday's Nevada caucuses, and with polls showing him on the rise, Democrats are entering a season of open warfare over whether Sanders, I-Vt., is equipped to beat Trump in what could be a brutal general election. The senator and his allies insist he could, but his detractors say he is too polarizing to win in November - and could severely cost Democrats in congressional or state races if Republicans use Sanders' self-description as a Democratic socialist to paint all Democrats as extreme.  The Sanders insurgency is the culmination of angry grievances that have simmered for the past decade among liberals who say Washington has all but ignored the problems of income inequality, health-care access and climate change.  "The party has shifted to the left, and I don't think many of the more traditional, legacy leaders of the party got it," said Andrew Stern, a longtime former president of the Service Employees International Union. "The good news for Bernie Sanders is he's like a broken clock. He's been in the same place for 35 or 40 years in terms of his positions, and the times have found him."  A headstrong, 78-year-old senator, Sanders has galvanized his supporters with an unwavering commitment to their shared cause and rageful critiques of the "billionaire class." They...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies Roger Stone's effort to disqualify her...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/23/roger-stone-judge-berman-jackson-117066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amy Berman Jackson accuses the defense of abusing the court’s docket with claims of bias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua's last newspaper dared to criticize the government. Then it lost its ink and paper...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/nicaraguas-last-newspaper-dared-to-criticize-the-government-then-it-lost-its-ink-and-paper/ar-BB10iga7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents warn kids against YOUTUBE 'killer Jump Trip Challenge' after deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/parents-warn-kids-against-youtube-21563313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mums and dads have taken to social media to warn kids about the Jump Trip Challenge or Skull-Breaker which has appeared on YouTube and TikTok</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab monkeys infected with coronavirus in desperate bid to find vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/lab-monkeys-infected-coronavirus-desperate-21559290</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US monkeys were treated with a new experimental drug to combat the respiratory disease, which has spread across the globe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SET FOR SPIRAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/24/us-futures-coronavirus-outbreak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of 9:45 p.m. ET Sunday, Dow Jones Industrial Average futures were 392 points lower, pointing to an implied opening plunge of 385.41 points for the index on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie reveals free childcare plan for preschoolers...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bernie-sanders-60-minutes-free-childcare-plan-d500ce83-7b95-4e03-89aa-c08ecde9bc5c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have a tax on wealth to pay for that," he told Anderson Cooper on "60 Minutes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEVELOPING:  Three Weinstein accusers could send producer to prison for life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-weinstein-accusers-could-send-195906337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the jurors in Harvey Weinstein’s sexual assault trial wrestle with a pair of charges that could send the fallen movie mogul to prison for life, the testimony of three women who don’t even appear in his indictment could help seal his fate.They’re known as Molineux witnesses in New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz Memorial Rips Bezos &amp; Pacino TV Series For Fake History... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/auschwitz-memorial-hunters-amazon-prime-nazi-hunters-1202866536/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: Hunters creator and executive producer David Weil has responded to the backlash in regards to the new Amazon series about a band of Nazi hunters in 1977. As Weil pointed out, the new series…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man drives Jeep off 6-story roof of Los Angeles-area garage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95409b68a3659f250aadbcb13c4659d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA MONICA, Calif. (AP) — A man drove his Jeep off the the sixth floor of a Los Angeles-area parking garage early Sunday and was taken to a hospital in critical condition, authorities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd person in days killed by Mardi Gras float in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/556c18effc1de332d6cb3b970946d4a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — A man was struck and killed by a Mardi Gras float during a raucous weekend street parade in New Orleans, becoming the second person in days killed along a parade route during...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40,000 bees attack police, firefighters in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article240565296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body found hanging lifeless from tree in Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-central-park-body-hanged-tree-20200223-mtwcoo4yjvg4ngdmkctk3key6e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops responded to the scene inside the park near Fifth Ave. and E. 74th St. as shocked onlookers passed by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens shortages of 150 drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-threatens-drug-shortage-318c9e7b-5d92-4a5e-b992-2478023c6d01.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is a huge supplier of the ingredients used in many drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims results 'plagued with errors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/buttigieg-campaign-nevada-errors-inconsistencies-dd412de1-066e-4f59-858d-9de61684a9aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campaign said it received more than 200 incident reports from precincts around the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Matthews faces calls for resignation after comparing victory to Nazi invasion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/484237-chris-matthews-faces-calls-for-resignation-after-comparing-sanders-victory-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC's Chris Matthews is under fire after comparing Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders' path has echoes of Trump's 2016 campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bfcd0845c5bc45c2103832d55d0fed3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A burn-it-down candidate is topping a splintered field of more moderate contenders and setting the party’s establishment wing on edge. It’s how Donald Trump began his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Speakers 'Accidentally' Recording Conversations 19 Times Per Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/dont-worry-alexa-and-friends-only-record-you-up-to-19-times-a-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you ever wondered how often your smart speaker accidentally activates itself? A study from Northeastern University tried to find oiut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia braces for pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/politics/federal/no-need-for-face-masks-business-as-usual-says-australia-s-chief-medical-officer-20200223-p543gf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Brendan Murphy said there had been no community transmission of coronavirus in Australia, but warnings have been issued about a possible Victorian pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Olympics Could Be Moved or Canceled Due...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5786657/tokyo-olympics-coronavirus-asia-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hypothetical situation is slowly becoming more tangible</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
