<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael 'squatter' ex-boyfriend arrested for smashing up star's mansion!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/9572544/fadi-fawaz-arrest-george-michael-london-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Michael’s ex Fadi Fawaz was dramatically arrested after going berserk and allegedly smashing up the late singer’s £5million house. Cops swooped on the London property last night after …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing takes aim at USA, Taiwan in new military blueprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/China-takes-aim-at-U-S-Taiwan-in-new-military-14118706.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - China sharpened its hostility toward the United States and Taiwan in a new high-level report on its future military strategy that accused Washington and its allies of undermining global stability.  Releasing the document on Wednesday, officials of the People's Liberation Army repeatedly warned that Beijing would be willing to deploy military force to assert its claims over Taiwan. The self-ruled island has pulled closer to the Trump administration and agreed this month to buy $2.2 billion in weapons, including M1A2T Abrams tanks and Stinger missiles.  Taiwan's incumbent Democratic Progressive Party favors declaring formal independence from China, a move that could spark confrontation in the Taiwan Strait, one of the world's most heavily militarized flash points. China's navy this month sailed its sole aircraft carrier into the strait in a show of force reminiscent of similar U.S. operations two decades ago that showcased American military dominance in Asia.  "If anyone dares to separate Taiwan from China, the Chinese military would not hesitate to go to war," Chinese military spokesman Wu Qian said as he laid out what officials called a revised national defense policy for "the New Era" - a catchphrase that denotes the imprimatur of China's assertive leader, Xi Jinping.  The military blueprint comes as tensions simmer in the western Pacific and China moves to enforce its strategic aims across the region, including in the disputed South China Sea. Beijing views democratically ruled Taiwan, which separated from the Communist-ruled mainland in 1949, as a renegade province.  Global military competition was rising, with the United States "strengthening its Asia-Pacific military alliances" and engaging in "technological and institutional innovation in pursuit of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: NFL star Adrian Peterson deep in debt despite earning $99 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/jul/24/adrian-peterson-nfl-debt-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial problems continue to mount for Washington running back Adrian Peterson, who is being sued for failure to repay a $5.2m loan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confused, Stuttering...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/07/robert-mueller-stuttering-confused-doddering-lost-nervous-he-did-not-run-this-thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions Between Sanders, MSNBC Boil Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-war-between-bernie-sanders-and-msnbc-reaches-a-new-peak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator’s campaign sees the cable news network as part of a brewing problem that allows vague and unverified claims to go unchecked on air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats getting fatter...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fat-cats-literally-new-study-finds-felines-are-getting-chubbier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The term "fat cat" is thrown around quite frequently, but usually not to describe actual cats. Well, a new study out of the University of Guelph finds that cats are indeed getting fatter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron gambles on IVF for lesbians...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-reform-ivf/macron-gambles-on-cultural-shift-with-bill-allowing-ivf-for-lesbians-idUSKCN1UJ20A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government on Wednesday sent to parliament draft legislation that wou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Euphoria' in White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/24/robert-mueller-testimony-gop-white-house-1430049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Wing aides were spiking the proverbial football even before the former special counsel had finished testifying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live-tracking deflections...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/robert-mueller-house-testimony-tracker-july-2019-n1033166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow along as the former special counsel delivers his testimony in front of House committees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlogger dies live-streaming himself eating poisonous centipedes and lizards...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/man-35-dies-live-streaming-18763663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese vlogger, named only by his surname Sun, was reportedly found lifeless in his flat after the bizarre stunt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's Chinese billionaire and member of Mar-a-Lago. Also communist spy?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article232973237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>