<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>U.S. carrier group enters South China Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southchinasea-usa/us-carrier-group-enters-south-china-sea-amid-taiwan-tensions-idUSKBN29T05J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. aircraft carrier group led by the USS Theodore Roosevelt has entered the South China Sea to promote "freedom of the seas", the U.S. military said on Sunday, at a time when tensions between China and Taiwan have raised concern in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration plan may be risky for Dems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-politics-race-and-ethnicity-health-care-reform-7c0584e2e7a795e24aa3c829b98dde08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is confronting the political risk that comes with grand ambition. As one of his first acts, Biden offered a sweeping immigration overhaul last week that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan reports 2nd day of incursions by Chinese air force...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210124091524-55023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/SECURITY (URGENT):Taiwan reports second day of incursions by Chinese air force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten People Fighting the Forever War...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2021/01/america-forever-war-afghanistan/617776/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A devastating incident in Afghanistan shows the perils of relying on Special Operations alone to fight the nation’s battles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia's 'El Chapo' arrested in Amsterdam...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-55784104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia believes Tse Chi Lop's syndicate controls up to 70% of narcotics entering the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge of Student Suicides Pushes Vegas Schools to Reopen...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/24/surge-of-student-suicides-pushes-las-vegas-schools-to-reopen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reminders of pandemic-driven suffering among students in Clark County, Nev., have come in droves. Since schools shut their doors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb thrown into CA church criticized for extremist views on gay people...</title>
      <link>https://www.sgvtribune.com/2021/01/23/bomb-damages-el-monte-church-that-opposes-gay-marriage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sgvtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pastor of the First Works Baptist Church had filed a police report after an online threat was made. The FBI is investigating the attack and trying to close in on the motive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17-year-old in ICU after receiving second dose...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/17-year-old-in-icu-after-receiving-second-coronavirus-dose-656527</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man used $2M bailout for BENTLEY, TESLA, Vegas condos...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/24/man-used-2m-in-covid-relief-for-a-bentley-tesla-las-vegas-condos-feds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Las Vegas man allegedly stole about $2 million in federal COVID-19 relief funds meant for small businesses — all so he could buy luxury cars and homes, prosecutors said. Jorge Abramovs has …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MALIBU SNOW: Winter storm brings rare sight to SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/weather/winter-storm-brings-rare-snowfall-to-malibu/9958516/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malibu Canyon saw a rare snowfall on Saturday, just a week after seeing temperatures in the 80s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioting youths in Netherlands torch testing center...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/netherlands-health-coronavirus-pandemic-riots-amsterdam-550ce0c260d45131181727fbf41e8340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;URK, Netherlands (AP) — Rioting youths protesting on the first night of a Dutch curfew torched a coronavirus testing facility and threw fireworks at police in a Dutch fishing village. Police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wastes no time in first 100 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/24/joe-biden-president-100-hours-trump-legacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democrat has kicked off his presidency with a blitz of executive orders and measures – here are the key themes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests of leadership comes quickly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/tests-of-biden-e2-80-99s-leadership-and-gop-e2-80-99s-willingness-to-cooperate-come-quickly/ar-BB1d1NFv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president hopes to show government can work effectively to combat the pandemic and revive the economy while trying to change the political climate in the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will USA deploy Iron Dome to protect bases in Gulf?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/will-us-deploy-iron-dome-to-protect-bases-in-the-gulf-656516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"the system will assist the US Army in protecting American troops from ballistic and airborne threats as well as from developing threats in the areas where US troops are deployed on various missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tacoma cop plows through crowd of pedestrians...</title>
      <link>https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2021/jan/23/tacoma-police-car-plows-through-crowd-of-pedestria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video footage is clear and hard to watch: a Tacoma Police patrol car running into and through a group of pedestrians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californian dies hours after getting shot, prompting probe...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/23/californian-dies-hours-after-getting-covid-19-vaccine-prompting-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California resident who was vaccinated against COVID-19 died just hours later — and authorities are trying to find out why. The Placer County Sheriff’s Office announced the death and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK earnings still flourishing amid pandemic, economic slowdown and antitrust scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/facebook-earnings-still-flourishing-amid-pandemic-economic-slowdown-and-antitrust-scrutiny-11611356916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc. has been able to retain a Teflon sheen on Wall Street with a succession of blowout quarters of advertising revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol attack will spur broad crackdown on domestic extremists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/capitol-attack-will-spur-broad-crackdown-on-domestic-extremists/ar-BB1d1YFo?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement and national security officials will probably face significant legal, political and cultural obstacles, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Total war zone': Yosemite area hit hard by wind that toppled trees. What happens now?...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/article248696465.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mono wind events like the one that hit earlier this week might happen once every 10 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans remain sorely divided as Biden's quest for unity begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Americans-remain-sorely-divided-as-Biden-s-quest-15893019.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other day, Stu Ross, a retired elementary school teacher, threw his neighbor out of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington gets whiplash in shift from Donald to Joe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/washington-gets-whiplash-shift-trump-130028905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Changes at 1600: Days don't begin and end with tweets. The press secretary hasn't lied or insulted media. Policy papers are back. The president stays on message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ, FBI debate not charging some of  Capitol rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/justice-department-fbi-debate-not-charging-some-of-the-capitol-rioters/ar-BB1d1Upf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement officials are considering forgoing charges against those who went into Congress but are not linked to violence, threats or destruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aloha shirts on 'boogaloos' link symbol of peace to violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-race-and-ethnicity-elections-hawaii-civil-wars-c91fbd31b1eadae3179bdfabf174dbac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — People following a violent movement that promotes a second U.S. civil war or the breakdown of modern society have been showing up at recent protests across the nation armed and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope again cancels appearances due to nerve pain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-vatican-city-pope-francis-4e1aa0c402e6d6c5895a1f1c8656e972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis is once again canceling public appearances due to nerve pain. Francis will not participate in three events over the coming days “due to a recurrence of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 78 and oldest president, Biden sees world changed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-race-and-ethnicity-ronald-reagan-pennsylvania-48d1659d4469999be87fbd87d560a52c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When Joe Biden took the oath of office as the 46th president, he became not only the oldest newly inaugurated U.S. chief executive in history but also the oldest sitting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ, FBI debate not charging some of the Capitol rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/doj-capitol-rioters-charges-debate/2021/01/23/3b0cf112-5d97-11eb-8bcf-3877871c819d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement officials are considering forgoing charges against those who went into Congress but are not linked to violence, threats or destruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why McConnell Dumped Donald...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/02/01/why-mcconnell-dumped-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the Capitol assault—and after losing his perch as Majority Leader—the senator finally denounced the outgoing President. Was it a moral reckoning or yet another act of political self-interest?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17% of America has been infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/01/23/covid-cases-updates-larry-king-dies-after-being-hospitalized-covid-19/6674844002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A model estimates 168,000 more U.S. COVID-19 deaths before May. Meanwhile, about 5% of Americans have received a vaccine dose. Latest COVID-19 news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests of Biden leadership, and GOP willingness to cooperate, come quickly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/tests-of-biden-e2-80-99s-leadership-and-gop-e2-80-99s-willingness-to-cooperate-come-quickly/ar-BB1d1NFv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president hopes to show government can work effectively to combat the pandemic and revive the economy while trying to change the political climate in the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barred From USA Under Trump, Muslims Exult in Biden Open Door...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/23/barred-from-u-s-under-trump-muslims-exult-in-bidens-open-door/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya — As the results of the American presidential election rolled in on Nov. 4, a young Sudanese couple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Find Weather May Have Effect On Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/weather-effect-stock-market/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of all the reasons for the ups and downs of the stock market, weather is rarely given any credit. Certain meteorological events, like devastating hurricanes or tornadoes, obviously have at least a short-term effect on market events. But researchers have found correlations between the stock market an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 most memorable...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/01/23/here-are-larry-kings-10-most-memorable-interviews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry King conducted more than 50,000 interviews during his storied career. Here are some of his most memorable: Frank Sinatra Larry King interviewing Frank Sinatra in 1988. King called his 1988 si…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin defied...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98not-afraid-e2-80-99-protesters-across-russia-defy-putin-in-marches-for-jailed-opposition-leader-navalny/ar-BB1d19Pk?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police made widespread arrests as protests took place from the Far East to Moscow in a powerful message to the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile systems deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1387983/China-Taiwan-latest-news-World-War-3-fears-conflict-invasion-war-missile-fighter-bomber</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has breached Taiwan's Air Defence Zone with eight bombers and four fighter jets in a blatant provocation against the autonomous island, sending a clear signal to new US President Joe Biden in the process.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
