<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Women command VMI, Citadel cadets in historic first...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/575017-women-command-vmi-citadel-cadets-in-a-historic-first</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women are commanding the Corps of Cadets at the Virginia Military Institute (VMI) and The Citadel in South Carolina, marking a historic first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio is one of most prolific migrant smugglers. He's about to turn 18, and has decision to make...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2021/10/02/mexico-child-migrant-smuggler-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He guided his first group of undocumented migrants into the United States when he was 12. The work comes with an expiration date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent Crime Spikes Among Arabs in Israel as Officials Admit Neglect...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/02/world/middleeast/israel-arab-crime-killings-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Killings of Arabs by Arabs have soared in Israel. The prevailing assumption, an official said, was “as long as they are killing each other, that’s their problem.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'TITANE,' the Wildest and Sexiest Movie of Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/inside-titane-the-wildest-and-sexiest-movie-of-the-year/ar-AAP3uOo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drawn to the flaws of the flesh, the blemishes that spur insecurities but reassure our commonality, French director Julia Ducournau has introduced her own elaborate vocabulary to the blood-tinged language of body horror. Ruptured skin and the ensuing scar tissue communicate messages from the inner, unseen wounds of her characters. “I dig into imperfections because that is where humanity resides. This is where we are equal,” Ducournau tells The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply chain crisis could blow world economy off course; 'Perfect storm'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/oct/02/supply-chain-world-economy-energy-labour-transport-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Liverpool to LA, shortages of energy, labour and transport are threatening recovery from Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 1 In 8 Won't Buy Holiday Gifts For Loved Ones With Opposing Views...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/opposing-covid-views-holiday-gifts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two in three Americans say they're looking forward to the holiday season this year, despite many planning on buying fewer gifts in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St wild party in jeopardy as Fed threatens aid cutoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/02/wall-street-fed-threatens-aid-cutoff-514956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The central bank plans to begin yanking back assistance to the economy as early as next month, and many Fed officials are open to increasing interest rates next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural Americans dying at twice rate of urbanites...</title>
      <link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/covid-is-killing-rural-americans-at-twice-the-rate-of-urbanites</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pbs.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic is devastating rural America, where lower vaccination rates are compounding the already limited medical care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood faces new crisis in strike threat from off-screen workers who keep productions running...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hollywood-faces-new-crisis-in-strike-threat-from-off-screen-workers-who-keep-productions-running/ar-AAP4f0U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As virus cases mount and vax mandates spread, holdouts plague police and fire depts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-coronavirus-cases-mount-and-vaccine-mandates-spread-holdouts-plague-police-and-fire-departments/ar-AAP3YbH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health experts say the continued reluctance of scores of first responders to be vaccinated poses a particular risk to the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft reveals rare images of Mercury craters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/european-spacecraft-reveals-rare-images-of-mercury-e2-80-99s-craters-after-a-e2-80-98flawless-e2-80-99-flyby/ar-AAP4gm1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BepiColombo joint mission sent back its first images of the planet after a gravitational flyby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-GOOGLE worker recalls 'scary' moment he feared company was 'creating God'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/ex-google-worker-recalls-scary-25119798</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real-life Terminator looks like a very possible future according to a former Google Chief Business Officer Mo Gawdat, who reveals what he saw being developed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All in the mind? Mysterious Havana Syndrome is 'mass global experiment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10047491/Havana-Syndrome-global-experiment-mass-suggestion-not-targeted-attack-CIA-officers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it a sonic weapon or CIA officers just having an off day? Expert Dr Robert Bartholomew reveals why Havana Syndrome is a 'global experiment in mass suggestion' and not a sinister, targeted attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billion-Dollar Market for Phone's Location Data...</title>
      <link>https://themarkup.org/privacy/2021/09/30/theres-a-multibillion-dollar-market-for-your-phones-location-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;themarkup.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge but little-known industry has cropped up around monetizing people’s movements</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine leader Duterte announces retirement from politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elections-philippines-manila-rodrigo-duterte-8b611a7b54f1eb4b90910c88e265f84b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA, Philippines (AP) — Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte on Saturday announced he was retiring from politics and dropping plans to run for vice president in next year’s elections when his term ends, paving the way for his politician daughter to make a possible bid for the top post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Sinema Stars in Her Own Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/02/opinion/kyrsten-sinema-congress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Garbo of the Senate leaves Democrats confused and angry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Seeks Reinstatement of TWITTER Account in Court Filing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/trump-seeks-reinstatement-of-twitter-account-in-court-filing/ar-AAP3sjd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump asked a federal judge to force Twitter to temporarily reinstate his account while he sues to permanently return to the social media network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC takes aim at booming crypto industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/washington-takes-aim-at-the-booming-crypto-industry/ar-AAP3Zcz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report on stablecoins, now circulating among top officials, will kick off a Biden administration bid to bring federal oversight to digital assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OZY insiders describe doubts about metrics at scandal-ridden media company...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/ozy-insiders-describe-burnout-and-doubts-about-metrics-at-the-scandal-ridden-media-company/ar-AAP4iBy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;18 current and former staffers describe internal doubts about the company and a breakneck workplace culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In America's Next War, Machines Will Do Thinking...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/ai-machines-will-do-the-thinking-in-the-next-u-s-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In America’s Next War, Machines Will Do the Thinking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan angered by Chinese air force largest ever incursion...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211002114631-6gglt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Taiwan angered by Chinese air force's largest ever incursion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Agenda in Limbo...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-infrastructure-plan-stalls-leaving-his-agenda-in-limbo/ar-AAP4aiR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden’s sweeping economic agenda faces an uncertain future in Congress after he failed this week to unify his own party around a strategy to pass a bitterly contested infrastructure plan that’s one of his top priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J jab linked to another clotting condition?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/574992-jj-vaccine-could-be-linked-to-another-clotting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Medicines Agency (EMA), the European Union's drug regulator, on Friday found a possible link between Johnson &amp; Johnson's COVID-19 vaccine and rare cases of blood clotting in deep veins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letitia James Running for Gov? Decision Coming Soon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/02/is-letitia-james-running-for-governor-her-decision-is-coming-soon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Pole posts most severe cold season on record...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/south-pole-posts-most-severe-cold-season-on-record-an-anomaly-in-a-warming-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extreme cold over Antarctica helped push sea ice levels surrounding the continent to their fifth-highest level on record in August. Scientists credited a very strong polar vortex, strong winds in the stratosphere, for the intensity of the cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems dial down Manchin tension...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/574988-senate-democrats-dial-down-the-manchin-tension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats are trying to turn down the temperature after days of high-profile drama and a delay of the bipartisan infrastructure bill in the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Struggles to Quell Uproar Over INSTAGRAM Effect on Teens...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/facebook-struggles-to-quell-uproar-over-instagrams-effect-on-teens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — Over the past few weeks, top Facebook executives assembled virtually for a series of emergency meetings. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortion, guns, religion top big Supreme Court term...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-college-admissions-donald-trump-amy-coney-barrett-courts-e245e6b581143bc2f87c402f7c667535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The future of abortion rights is in the hands of a conservative Supreme Court that is beginning a new term Monday that also includes major cases on gun rights and religion. The court's credibility with the public also could be on the line, especially if a divided court were to overrule the landmark Roe v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party crowds spark effort to turn down volume in South Beach...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-miami-14f942c443de2bbfd3e996d2e346ec7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Miami Beach wants to turn down the volume in the city's South Beach party neighborhood, citing increasingly raucous crowds, public drinking and growing violence, but efforts to curb the carousing have raised complaints about racism, classism and business practices along one of the nation's most glamorous waterfronts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady-Belichick bout bringing fans from all over...</title>
      <link>https://www.wpri.com/sports/patriots-new-england-nation/brady-belichick-bout-bringing-fans-from-all-over-to-foxboro/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wpri.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not only will it be the first time Tom Brady squares off against his former team in Foxboro — it may also be the last, making tickets a hot commodity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk-food lovers 'more likely' to crash car...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3777863/junk-food-lovers-more-likely-to-crash-their-car-and-get-driving-convictions-study-finds/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen 'spending millions funding Prince Andrew sex abuse fight'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3777355/queen-prince-andrew-defence-sex-abuse/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen is reportedly spending millions of pounds to privately fund Prince Andrew’s fight against allegations of sex abuse. The Duke of York, 61, is battling a lawsuit filed by Virginia Rob…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special ops troops 'hunkered down' in CA airport hangar after ninja attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2021-09-30/ninja-attack-special-operations-california-airport-3076663.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After confirming that the incident described in the document leaked on social media did occur, U.S. Army Special Operations Aviation Command spokesman Maj. Jeff Slinker said officials did not have any further information to add.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sotomayor lets NY order remain...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-supreme-courts-sotomayor-lets-new-york-school-vaccine-mandate-remain/ar-AAP351d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/VACCINE (URGENT):U.S. Supreme Court's Sotomayor lets New York school vaccine mandate remain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh positive for Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/01/politics/brett-kavanaugh-covid-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Brett Kavanaugh has tested positive for Covid-19, the Supreme Court said Friday, the first publicly known case of coronavirus among the high court's justices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CUTS HOSPITALIZATION, DEATH IN HALF'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/merck-to-seek-emergency-authorization-for-oral-covid-19-treatment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merck and Ridgeback Biotherapeutics will seek emergency authorization for their drug, which they say could have “a profound impact in controlling the pandemic.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California first state to mandate vax for public and private schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/state/california-first-to-require-students-be-covid-19-vaccinated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom on Friday announced a COVID-19 vaccine mandate for all students – the first requirement of its kind in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants' Fragile Recovery Fizzling...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/restaurants-fragile-recovery-is-fizzling-in-the-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's most restrictive abortion law back in Texas court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-austin-texas-courts-lawsuits-a7961b629e913e1008f8e929c99fb310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — The Biden administration on Friday urged a federal judge to block the nation's most restrictive abortion law, which has banned most abortions in Texas since early September and sent women racing to get care beyond the borders of the second-most populous state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE COVID PILL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-health-pandemics-a9a2245fdcee324f6bbd776a0fffcc60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a potential leap forward in the global fight against the pandemic , drugmaker Merck said Friday that its experimental pill for people sick with COVID-19 reduced hospitalizations and deaths by half.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers arrested in Hawaii for fake test results...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-arrests-california-los-angeles-united-states-946e3983622e19d5617222f763964707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hawaii authorities arrested two people from California for submitting fake COVID-19 test results to avoid a mandatory traveler quarantine meant to curb the virus' spread in the islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  OZY shutting down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/ozy-media-is-shutting-down-after-reports-about-misconduct-and-lies-at-the-company.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ozy Media's board on Friday announced that the company is shutting down, according to The New York Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With gas pumps still dry, Britain brings in army...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001205906-6xhb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-TRUCKERS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-With gas pumps still dry, Britain brings in the army</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vaxxer Goes to Homeless Shelter to Pay Someone For Fake Status...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyvn3w/anti-vaxxer-went-to-homeless-shelter-to-try-to-pay-someone-for-fake-vaccine-status</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating the incident at a homeless shelter in northern Alberta. The incident occurred two days after the province announced vaccine passports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going to Make Rich Pay,' Manchin Tells Protesters From His Yacht...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kvgxe/were-going-to-make-the-rich-pay-joe-manchin-tells-protesters-from-his-yacht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists kayaked to Senator Joe Manchin's $700,000 yacht to ask why he wouldn't support the infrastructure bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces fractious Dems with agenda on line...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/01/house-democrats-biden-infrastructure-deal-514878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi repeated her mantra that Democrats are “on a path” to pass the infrastructure bill Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Skips Town for 'Medical Appointment', Fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/574941-sinema-in-arizona-as-democrats-try-to-get-spending-infrastructure-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Bezos Being Knocked Back Down to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/jeff-bezos-is-being-knocked-back-down-to-earth/ar-AAP328N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a summer of flying high, the space billionaire is facing a chaotic moment at his rocket company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER antibodies gone by 7 months for many...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001194329-xkwip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SCIENCE (GRAPHIC):COVID SCIENCE-Delta increases COVID-19 risks for pregnant women; Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine antibodies gone by 7 months for many</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV station has 'No News Monday' so staff can attend trauma, stress management seminar...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/entertainment/2021/09/portlands-katu-has-no-news-monday-so-staff-can-attend-trauma-and-stress-management-seminar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an unusual move, Portland's KATU-TV preempted morning and afternoon news shows so the staff could attend a seminar designed to help deal with job-related trauma and stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why this woman becoming world's most dangerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/leaders/kim-yojong-the-powerful-sister-of-north-korean-dictator-kim-jongun-on-track-to-become-worlds-most-dangerous-woman/news-story/70bf32c7f581b2ab577227ea84911e4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not too long ago, even the most devoted watchers of North Korean politics knew little to nothing about Kim Yo-jong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN WAR GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001155142-62r2v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-AZERBAIJAN/WARGAMES:Iran holds border war games amid tense relations with Azerbaijan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Union Boss Says 60K Members 'Deserve Respect' As Strike Ballot Voting Begins...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/iatse-srike-authorization-ballots-sent-out-network-studios-labor-1234848042/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The countdown has officially started this morning in what could be one of the largest labor actions in Hollywood history. Tens of thousands of IATSE members woke up early Friday or were …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers stole crypto from 6,000 COINBASE customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/coinbase-says-hackers-stole-cryptocurrency-least-6000-customers-2021-10-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers stole from the accounts of at least 6,000 customers of Coinbase Global Inc , according to a breach notification letter sent by the cryptocurrency exchange to affected customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Steps Up Taiwan Flybys as 38 Warplanes Enter Defense Zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-steps-up-taiwan-flybys-as-38-warplanes-enter-defense-zone/ar-AAP2QT7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese warplanes made multiple incursions close to Taiwan Friday in the second major display of military might in two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly Priest Shot With Paintball Gun In Church Parking Lot Over Funeral Parking Spat...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/09/30/priest-paintball-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baffert's Last Stand:  Horse racing's most successful, embattled trainer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/the-last-stand-of-bob-baffert-horse-racings-most-successful-and-embattled-trainer/ar-AAP28HQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Baffert has cultivated the story of a horse racing dynasty built from humble roots. He now faces scrutiny about short cuts he's alleged to have taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissension among Supremes as justices take anger public...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/01/politics/supreme-court-unhappy-justices/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court justices have revealed a new level of defensiveness and anger in recent weeks, showing irritation with public expectations, the news media and one another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Hosts First Royal Wedding Since Bolshevik Revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-romanov-royal-wedding/31488187.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rferl.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has held its first royal wedding since the 1917 Bolshevik Revolution toppled the Romanov monarchy, with royals from across Europe attending the lavish ceremony in the city of St. Petersburg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private jet rage grows; Record fliers strain system...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/private-jet-rage-grows-as-a-record-number-of-fliers-strain-the-system.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private jet fliers are facing increasing delays and cancellations as the industry struggles to serve a record number of new fliers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
