<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Surtax' on Millionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/10/26/billioniare-tax-dems-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many lawmakers want to resolve their differences by the end of the week, but they are still stuck on the thorny issue of taxation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror groups in Afghanistan could launch international strikes in months...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/afghanistan/2021/10/26/terrorist-groups-in-afghanistan-could-launch-international-strikes-within-six-months-officials-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense officials say the threat demands vigilance from American forces, including counter-terrorism strikes in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reno Criminalizes Possessing Whips Without Permit...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/10/25/reno-criminalizes-possessing-whips-without-a-permit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carrying this archaeologists' accessory in the city's downtown without government permission is now a misdemeanor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Sends Troops Into Tulum After Shootout Kills Tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/mexico-sends-armed-forces-into-tulum-after-drug-shootout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico Sends Troopss Into Tulum After Shootout Kills Two Tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Is Lowest-Revenue Company to Hit $1 Trillion Market Value...</title>
      <link>https://www.ttnews.com/articles/tesla-becomes-lowest-revenue-company-hit-1-trillion-market-value</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ttnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc. has joined the trillion-dollar-valuation club as the member with the lowest revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Gets Pulled Into Virginia Gov. Race After Earlier Cold Shoulder...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-gets-pulled-into-virginia-race-after-earlier-cold-shoulder/ar-AAPYoic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Terry McAuliffe distanced himself from President Joe Biden earlier this month in a bid for more votes in the closely fought Virginia governor’s race, prompting some sharp retorts from the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems' New Target Is $5 Trillion in Billionaire Wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/democrats-new-tax-target-is-5-trillion-in-billionaire-wealth/ar-AAPYq3W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- With their latest tax proposal, Democrats are going after an elusive target: U.S. billionaires, and their growing piles of untaxed investment gains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'YEARLY BOOSTER'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/578448-moderna-chairman-says-booster-could-be-yearly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna Chairman Noubar Afeyan indicated on Tuesday that his company's COVID-19 shot could require yearly boosters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Tightens Discharge Rules for Covid Patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.rthk.hk/rthk/en/component/k2/1617056-20211026.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.rthk.hk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government has announced that patients who have recovered from Covid-19 and are ready to be discharged from hospital will need to spend an additio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  40 FACEBOOK STORIES FROM PAPERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/facebook-papers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They paint a picture of Facebook that's very different from what Mark Zuckerberg likes to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Touch Screens Will Let You Feel Items Before You Buy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/10/better-touch-screens-could-let-you-feel-stuff-you-buy-it/186294/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal is for the screen to mimic textures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey reveals photos of 15 alleged Mossad spies arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/turkey-reveals-photos-of-15-alleged-mossad-spies-arrested-683017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged Mossad spies were of Arab descent and were reportedly present to spy on Palestinians living in Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK star accused of double murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/california-tiktok-star-pleads-not-guilty-to-double-murder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TikTok star with nearly a million online followers pleaded not guilty to shooting and killing his newly estranged wife and a man she was with last week at a San Diego high-rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to launch $10 billion luxury 'orbital reef' space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/jeff-bezos-build-luxury-orbital-25300989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon founder Jeff Bezos has announced that his space company, Blue Origin, will build the first private space station – it will host "exotic" space tourists and a "mixed-use business park"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms in Sights of Lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-algorithms-increasingly-sights-u-060000857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. lawmakers investigating how Facebook Inc. and other online platforms shape users’ world views are considering new rules for the artificial intelligence programs blamed for spreading malicious content. Most Read from BloombergCities' Answer to Sprawl? Go Wild.Hamburg Is at the Heart of Germany’s Growing Dilemma Over ChinaWhy Americans and Britons Are Rushing to Buy Idyllic Homes in ItalyOne of California’s Wealthiest Counties Could Run Out of Water Next SummerThe Top Money Mak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin says he's 'totally out of sync' with party...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sen-manchin-says-he-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98totally-out-of-sync-e2-80-99-with-fellow-democrats/ar-AAPYnCA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator from West Virginia, who has forced Democrats to pare back a social spending package, told reporters that he is ‘just trying to survive’ in a divided Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Las Patronas: Rise of Female Drug Bosses in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7ekkb/las-patronas-female-drug-bosses-in-latin-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VICE World News brings you exclusive reporting from Latin America’s criminal underworld on the boss women you’ve never heard of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China launches suspected anti-satellite weapon into space...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/oct/25/china-launches-suspected-anti-satellite-weapon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has launched a new satellite that analysts say can be used as a weapon capable of grabbing and crushing American satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST EXPENSIVE THANKSGIVING EVER?</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/life/food-drink/this-years-thanksgiving-feast-will-wallop-the-wallet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanksgiving 2021 is shaping up to be the most expensive meal in the history of the holiday. The nation’s food supply has been battered by a knotted supply chain, high transportation expenses, labor shortages, trade policies and bad weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College enrollment sees largest decline in 50 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/26/due-to-covid-college-enrollment-saw-largest-two-year-drop-in-50-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the pandemic's economic impact continues to weigh heavily, college enrollment is down for the second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcisms rise as evil takes over lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.christiantoday.com/article/pandemic.driving.up.demand.for.exorcisms.catholic.priest/137634.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.christiantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Catholic priest has claimed that the pandemic is behind a rise in people asking for exorcisms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: DEADLOCKED...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578430-mcauliffe-youngkin-deadlocked-one-week-out-from-election-day-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin are deadlocked exactly one week out from Virginia's gubernatorial election, according to a Suffolk University poll released on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor raised fears of Brandon Lee-style death...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/26/rust-actor-says-filming-movie-felt-life-threatening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ian A. Hudson told TMZ that he was terrified filming a scene where his outlaw character was gunned down by others using 20 pistols and two rifles — all real weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest 150 suspects in global dark web sting...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/technology/20211026-police-in-us-europe-arrest-150-suspects-in-global-dark-web-sting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police around the world arrested 150 suspects, including several high-profile targets, involved in buying or selling illegal goods online in one of the largest-ever stings targeting the dark web, Eur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too big to cover alone: Newsrooms team up...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/journalism-partnerships-facebook-papers-panama-127415c0-e11d-4e5e-8697-322ab75c02cc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsrooms are embracing quickly formed partnerships to years-long projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks rise on houses of worship...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/hate-crimes-houses-of-worship-religion-27580b09-006b-462b-b2cc-28b7b969f5b5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reported hate crimes in the U.S. have jumped in recent years and some of those attacks are linked to religious bigotry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi calls for new progress in military equipment, weapons...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211026110009-qktb6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-SECURITY/ (PIX):China's Xi calls for new progress in military equipment, weapons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 Protest Organizers Participated in 'Dozens' of Planning Meetings With Members of Congress, White House Staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/exclusive-jan-6-organizers-met-congress-white-house-1245289/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two sources are communicating with House investigators and detailed a stunning series of allegations to Rolling Stone, including a promise of a “blanket pardon” from the Oval Office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Algorithms Increasingly in Sights of Lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/facebook-s-algorithms-increasingly-in-sights-of-u-s-lawmakers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s Algorithms Increasingly in Sights of U.S. Lawmakers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration arrests plummet...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/department-of-homeland-security/578417-immigration-arrests-inside-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration arrests within the United States have plummeted to the lowest level in over 10 years, according t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKSTONE Schwarzman Says Energy Squeeze Will Trigger Unrest...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/energy-squeeze-will-trigger-unrest-says-blackstones-schwarzman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiker got lost in Colorado, then ignored rescuers' calls because they came from unknown number...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-hiker-got-lost-in-colorado-then-ignored-rescuers-calls-because-they-came-from-an-unknown-number/ar-AAPXOp8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rescue team's repeated calls were declined, so an hours-long search was launched. Rescuers were later notified the hiker had safely returned to their lodging location the next day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran gas stations hit by massive cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/iran-gas-stations-hit-by-cyber-attack-report-683141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cyberattack in Iran messaged some hacked systems addressing Iran Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, demanding “where is the gas?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed faces challenges to credibility...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/578398-fed-faces-challenges-to-credibility</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve is attempting to tamp down two significant challenges to its credibility as both its handling of inflation and internal ethics face growing scrutiny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to stump for McAuliffe in test of his electoral branding...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578403-biden-to-stump-for-mcauliffe-in-test-of-his-electoral-branding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will campaign for Virginia Democratic gubernatorial candidate Terry McAuliffe on Tuesday, one week out from an election that will test his electoral brand and amid one of the most consequential weeks of his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates tied to riot create new headaches for Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578392-candidates-tied-to-jan-6-create-new-headaches-for-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small but vocal group of Republican midterm candidates with ties to the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Taiwan war game, few good options for USA to deter China...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-taiwan-war-game-few-good-options-for-us-to-deter-china/ar-AAPXDrp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The war game and follow-on analysis comes at a moment of heightened tension between Washington and Beijing, with the United States opposing China’s military expansion in the region and China calling on the Pentagon to cut ties with Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chappelle sets conditions for meeting with trans NETFLIX employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/dave-chappelle-closer-transgender-community-1235036573/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You cannot come if you have not watched my special from beginning to end," the comedian says directly to the transgender community in a new video posted Monday to Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin must bear blame as star and producer, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/25/no-denying-alec-baldwins-role-in-shooting-mishap-tragedy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins has also been painted as Alec Baldwin’s tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affidavit Reveals More Details of Fatal Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/rust-shooting-affidavit-santa-fe-sheriff-read-it-1234862010/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin “had been very careful” about the handling of guns used on the New Mexico set of Rust in the days and hours before he accidentally shot and killed cinematographer Halyna Hutchins and w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caviezel Recites Battle Cry from 'BRAVEHEART' in Speech at QANON Convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/jim-caviezel-braveheart-qanon-convention-las-vegas-1642133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Caviezel has previously pushed QAnon talking points, including that children were being harvested for a natural chemical compound produced in their bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin was practicing pointing revolver at camera...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/alec-baldwin-fatal-shooting-filmed-search-warrant-cinematographer-halyna-hutchins-1234861151/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Santa Fe Sheriff’s Office is searching to find out whether footage exists of the fatal shooting Thursday on the New Mexico set of the Alec Baldwin film Rust. In an affidavit for a search warran…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unconstitutional mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/10/25/bidens-latest-tax-the-rich-scheme-would-be-an-unworkable-possibly-unconstitutional-mess/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it sounds too good to be true, it’s because it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandma convicted of assault for spraying coughing neighbor with disinfectant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16530773/gran-who-sprayed-neighbours-in-disinfectant-after-they-coughed-in-garden-is-convicted-of-assault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GRAN has been convicted of assault after she squirted her next door neighbours with disinfectant after they “coughed” in the garden during Covid.  Jane Downall, 61, used the antibacte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boomerang boomers: Over-50s moving back in with parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/oct/25/boomerang-boomers-the-over-50s-moving-back-in-with-their-parents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial and relationship woes caused by Covid in the UK are driving a rise in older people returning to live with family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago to create largest 'guaranteed basic income' program...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/chicago-poised-to-create-one-of-the-nation-e2-80-99s-largest-e2-80-98guaranteed-basic-income-e2-80-99-programs/ar-AAPWygB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic income programs are rapidly spreading across the country as critics raise concerns about record job openings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS WARN:  PUSH BACK HARDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article255235176.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With former President Donald Trump spreading conspiracies about the 2020 election, some Democrats are urging President Joe Biden to speak out more forcefully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Workers Block Roads in Mass Protest Against NY Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/25/we-will-not-comply-nyc-workers-protest-vax-mandate-with-march-across-brooklyn-bridge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days after the mayor announced a vaccine mandate for most of the city’s employees, about 5,000 incensed demonstrators marched over the Brooklyn Bridge to Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions Test Positive At Denver Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/25/covid-denver-zoo-lions-positive-tests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zookeepers in Denver are caring for 11 African lions that have tested positive for COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader of Kill Cult Dies in Car Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kevin-smith-leader-of-jamaican-cult-that-sacrificed-humans-dies-in-cop-car-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pastor Kevin Smith has died after the police car transporting him to face charges over “ritual killings” at his church crashed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parishioners arrested for 'human sacrifices'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jamaicaobserver.com/observer-west-front-page/-undeserved-death-co-workers-mourn-victim-of-church-ritual_234229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jamaicaobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER Anti-Joe Rap Tops iTunes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/media/anti-biden-rap-song-lets-go-brandon-reaches-top-spot-on-itunes-chart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anti-Biden rallying cry "Let’s Go Brandon" is taking over iTunes, with rapper Bryson Gray’s song poking fun at the president sitting in the No. 1 spot of the music service’s chart on Monday, ranking ahead of pop music superstar Adele’s latest single.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VAX MANDATE DELAYED UNTIL AFTER HOLIDAYS?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/25/businesses-ask-white-house-to-delay-biden-covid-vaccine-mandate-until-after-holidays.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House officials at the OMB are meeting with industry lobbyists this week as the administration conducts its final review of the mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few options to combat surging gas prices as inflation concerns grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/25/biden-has-few-options-to-combat-surging-gas-prices-amid-inflation-fears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are "no immediate plans" to tap into emergency reserves or limit energy exports outside the United States, the Energy Department told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas braces for 'mother of all caravans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10129323/Texas-troopers-Texas-Rangers-brace-thousands-migrants-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 3,000 migrants, including 250 children, were on the road for a third straight day Monday in an effort to reach Mexico City before continuing on to Texas' border with Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Saw Highest Number Of Reported Hate Crimes In Decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hate-crimes-report-2020-fbi-highest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The original data published in August had a technical error that inadvertently excluded some data from Ohio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme couponers sentenced in fraud plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/25/business/extreme-couponer-sentencing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is revealing new details about a $31.8 million counterfeit coupon scheme that landed a Virginia Beach married couple in prison for nearly 20 years combined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Workers Block Roads in Mass Protest Against NY Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/hundreds-emergency-workers-block-new-york-roads-protest-against-vaccine-mandate-1642309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City workers have until October 29 to get at least one dose of the vaccine or go on unpaid leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD/COSTA: Trump Was Calling Into War Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.msnbc.com/morning-joe/watch/what-happened-behind-the-scenes-ahead-of-the-january-6-attack-124530245759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Costa and Bob Woodward join Morning Joe to discuss new reports that prior to the January 6 insurrection, Trump lieutenants Rudy Giuliani, Steve Bannon and John Eastman were positioned in a Willard Hotel room with the goal of overturning the results of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Tallest Ferris Wheel Opens In Dubai; 38 Minute Ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/worlds-tallest-ferris-wheel-which-takes-38-minutes-to-ride-opens-in-dubai-70744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dubai Eye is almost double the size of the London Eye and can welcome 1,750 visitors at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman busted for striking mother in head with thrown tacos...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/domestic-battery/taco-battery-arrest-102358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a domestic taco battery, Florida police report. Braiden Lankford, 20, was arrested late Saturday evening for allegedly striking her mother in the head with two thrown tacos inside the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory loss and 'brain fog' may be side effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/10/25/memory-loss-long-term-covid-symptoms/6168210001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-term COVID-19 symptoms could be memory loss and other cognitive dysfunctions commonly labeled as "brain fog."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside AMAZON Worst Human Resources Problem...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/24/inside-amazons-worst-human-resources-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year ago, Tara Jones, an Amazon warehouse worker in Oklahoma, cradled her newborn, glanced over her pay stub on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA STAR RIPS NIKE: 'STOP SLAVERY'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/25/enes-kanter-china-nike-viral-video-modern-day-slavery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enes Kanter torched China and Nike in a new Twitter video. He criticized Nike for being &amp;amp;quot;silent&amp;amp;quot; on China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location Data Firm Got GPS Data From Apps Even When People Opted Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dgmqz/huq-location-data-opt-out-no-consent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news around location data firm Huq shows that data companies may not even really know if they've received consent to harvest information from ordinary phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepest quake ever detected struck 467 miles beneath Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/deepest-earthquake-ever-detected-struck-467-miles-beneath-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If confirmed, the temblor would be a shock to geologists who thought rocks that deep inside Earth were too putty-like to break and shake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After drought, west coast slammed by 'bomb cyclone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211025-after-drought-us-west-coast-slammed-by-bomb-cyclone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After drought, US west coast slammed by 'bomb cyclone'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Now Worth Over Quarter Trillion Dollars...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/elon-musk-quarter-trillion-dollars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So long, Jeffrey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor under fire for hiring registered child sex offender to inspect homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox32chicago.com/news/dolton-mayor-under-fire-for-hiring-registered-child-sex-offender-to-inspect-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox32chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: FOX 32 News has learned Lavelle Redmond spent 24 years in prison after pleading guilty to taking part in a brutal gang rape and beating in the Roseland neighborhood in 1991. He and three others kidnapped and sexually assaulted two girls, ages 13 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos wants to build tourism space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/25/tech/blue-origin-space-station-jeff-bezos-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin, the rocket and space tourism company founded by Jeff Bezos, is proposing a massive new commercial space station called "Orbital Reef" that could be used to host science experiments, vacation getaways, and potentially even in-space manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing removing domes from mosques to make them more 'Chinese'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/10/24/1047054983/china-muslims-sinicization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is removing domes and minarets from thousands of mosques. Authorities are taking down overtly Islamic architecture as part of a "sinicization" push to make them seem more traditionally Chinese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin open to it...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/578325-manchin-says-hes-open-to-tax-targeting-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) signaled on Monday that he's open to a tax targeting billionaires as Democrats scramble to figure out how to pay for their sweeping social spending bill.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
