<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS ON STREETS: Army brought into guard hospitals in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11175682/army-brought-into-guard-hospitals-supermarkets-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TROOPS could guard hospitals and supermarkets in drastic new measures set to be rolled out in a bid to tackle the coronavirus. It comes as the death toll in the UK soared to 21 and plans were annou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Airport to House Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/boeing-field-two-eastside-properties-to-be-used-for-housing-homeless-people-during-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle-area officials have scrambled to open up new space to create social distancing in crowded shelters, which house a vulnerable population at risk of contracting severe COVID-19 illnesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How USA Reached Turning Point...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/15/us/coronavirus-pandemic-us/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From behind the big oak desk in the Oval Office, the most solemn setting in times of national emergency, President Donald Trump somberly addressed the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP NEGATIVE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/14/trump-tests-negative-for-coronavirus-white-house-doctor-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump had said earlier Saturday that he had taken a test for the coronavirus and was awaiting results. He said he had decided he would do so after a press conference Friday, in which he was pressed on whether he would take a test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia delays primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/487611-georgia-to-postpone-primary-due-to-coronavirus-concern</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia election officials postponed the state's presidential primary election scheduled for March 24 due to concerns of over the coronavirus, the Georgia Secretary of State first announced Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Tycoon Who Criticized Xi Response to Coronavirus Has Vanished...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/14/chinese-tycoon-who-criticized-xis-response-to-coronavirus-has-vanished/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His nickname in China was “The Cannon,” and Ren Zhiqiang’s latest commentary was among his most explosive yet. Mr. Ren,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist With Fever Denied Access...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/journalist-fever-denied-access-white-house-press-briefing-cdc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporter's temperature "registered above" CDC's 100.4 guidelines, White House VP press secretary Katie Miller tweets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin signs sweeping constitutional changes into law...</title>
      <link>https://mia.mk/putin-signs-sweeping-constitutional-changes-into-law/?lang=en</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mia.mk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow, 14 March 2020 (dpa/MIA) - Russian President Vladimir Putin has signed into law a raft of ame</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats see road map for November in Michigan results...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/abc73b7595085888b7cdf887fbb0346b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's decisive victory in Michigan’s presidential primary offers what some Democrats hope will be the road map for success in November — a high turnout powered by a coalition that extends...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian aircraft intercepted approaching US airspace..</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/14/russian-aircraft-intercepted-approaching-us-air-sp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Russian reconnaissance aircraft came within 45 miles of the coast of Alaska on Saturday, the commanding general of the joint U.S.-Canada North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) said they are seeing repeated incursions into the Alaskan Air Defense Identification Zone, known as ADIZ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newborn baby becomes world's youngest victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11170653/newborn-baby-coronavirus-worlds-youngest-victim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEWBORN baby in England has tested positive for coronavirus — the world’s youngest victim. The child’s mother had been rushed to a London hospital days earlier with suspected pneumonia. ⚠️ Read o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Moviegoers Still Believe as Faith Based Weeper Number 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/03/14/friday-box-office-shows-christian-moviegoers-still-believe-as-faith-based-weeper-about-country-singer-jeremy-camp-is-number-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you still believe in movies? Well, Lionsgate’s Christian movie, “I Still Believe” will make $12 million this weekend after a $4 million Friday. Corona virus is not keeping away…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We Will See More Suffering And Death'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/dr-anthony-fauci-at-coronavirus-briefing-we-will-see-more-suffering-and-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci told reporters at a coronavirus briefing that "We will see more cases and we will see more suffering and death" from the disease, particularly "among the vulnerables in our society."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Could Take $20 Billion Hit!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hollywood-could-take-20-billion-hit-coronavirus-impact-1284582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking wide-release tentpoles off the schedule doesn’t come cheap, nor does shuttering production on hundreds of scripted and unscripted TV series — and what happens to the unemployed workers?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL BAN EXPANDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8112417/US-travel-ban-Europe-set-extended-UK-Ireland-Monday-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump announced a ban on all travellers coming from Europe but had excluded Britain because he believed the UK authorities were doing a 'good job'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP AWAITING TEST RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/14/vice-president-mike-pence-to-hold-press-conference-on-coronavirus-response-at-noon-et.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The press conference comes a day after Trump declared a national emergency in response to the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Forgets Year, Meanders Off Frame in Disastrous Livestream...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/03/14/nolte-joe-biden-forgets-year-meanders-off-frame-in-disastrous-livestream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grandpa Joe Biden wants to run the country and save us from coronavirus when he can't even run a livestream and has no idea what year it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robberies by suspects wearing medical masks in multiple states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/487572-robberies-reported-across-multiple-states-by-suspects-wearing-medical-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A string of robberies that have featured suspects wearing medical masks have taken place across the country in recent weeks, though all seem to be unrelated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First New York Death As State Surges To Lead As Most Infected...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/14/first-coronavirus-related-death-confirmed-in-new-york-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY — Coronavirus has claimed its first life in New York. A woman with underlying respiratory issues died in Wyckoff Heights Medical Center in Brooklyn, Gov. Cuomo announced this morning. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Bros warn of 'massive exodus' if Joe nominated...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/14/bernie-bros-warn-of-massive-exodus-if-democrats-nominate-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We will never – NEVER boost or support Joe Biden or defend his abysmal record and terrible policy positions,” Henry Williams, executive director of The Gravel Institute, told The…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When will there be vaccine -- and who will get it first?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/when-will-there-be-a-coronavirus-vaccine-and-who-will-get-it-first-165957441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the central questions for resolving the COVID-19 crisis is how long it will take to develop a vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Box Office Headed To 22-Year-Low...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/vin-diesel-bloodshot-i-still-believe-the-hunt-weekend-box-office-coronavirus-1202882333/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday AM Update: Refresh for updates and charts It’s a drastic time out there for movie theaters and studios as the domestic weekend box office is looking to land at a level that hasn&amp;#821…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straight-talking Fauci explains outbreak to worried nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e9d289a802222800a6eeb56e6be28333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — If Dr. Anthony Fauci says it, you'd be smart to listen. As the coronavirus has upended daily life across the globe, Fauci has become the trusted voice in separating fact and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO TEST FOR TRUMP?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/03/14/coronavirus-trumps-white-house-doctor-says-he-doesnt-need-test/5049602002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a Friday letter, Trump's physician said he didn't need a coronavirus test after his Mar-a-Lago meeting with Brazilian officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Being Stubborn, Rigid May Protect Against Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/just-say-no-being-stubborn-rigid-may-lower-your-alzheimers-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A truly fascinating new piece of research finds that being just a little stubborn and argumentative may just protect against dementia and Alzheimer's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEMP CHECKS BEGIN AT WHITE HOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/14/white-house-starts-temperature-checks-for-people-around-trump-129422</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House staff met reporters at the door of the press briefing room with a thermometer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For millions, no church on Sunday is cruelest closure so far...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/For-millions-of-Americans-no-church-on-Sunday-is-15131148.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Friday, Devra Torres saw some houses of worship around the country being shuttered for fear of spreading the coronavirus and considered it "extreme." People shouldn't be "left alone" without Communion or confession, said Torres, who has gone to Mass every day for decades.  Then came news Thursday that the Archdiocese of Washington was calling for parishes to be closed as well, including St. Mark's, to which the 55-year-old freelance editor walks each day at noon to worship.  And then came Friday, Torres' final Mass - at least for now.  "I feel sad. It may seem fanatical to some, but for me this is a very special time of connection with God every day," Torres, who went Friday morning with her 11-year-old son, said of the closures that right now are scheduled through March 27. Catholics, she noted, "believe Jesus is literally present in Communion. You can't get that on TV."  Fear of the contagion this week had religious leaders first altering, and then quickly canceling, access to rituals that for millions are sustenance that can feel as basic as food or water.  Houses of worship closing until further noticemeans empty confession booths. No Communion. No synagogue minyan, the 10-person quorum required by Judaism to pray certain key prayers, including the one mourners say for the dead. And for many who are less orthodox, the absence of a time they set aside in a place that to them feels holy.  "It really is a sense of deprivation," said Sarah Bartel, 42, who lives with her husband and five children outside Seattle, where the Catholic archbishop was the first in the country Wednesday to suspend all public Masses. Washington, D.C., came soon after, on Thursday. Bartel usually attends three times a week. "We believe that Jesus's life, death and resurrection are in the mystery of the Mass - it's at the heart of our...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR SYSTEM WILL BUCKLE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8112063/America-braces-coronvirus-collapse-100-00-ICU-beds-10-MILLION-hospitalized.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The estimate of how many more people are going to become infected ranges wildly but congress's doctor has said as many as 150million people may become infected and 10 million may need hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First human trials of vaccine could start within days...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8111771/First-human-trials-coronavirus-vaccine-start-days-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'genetic hack' was accelerated past the animal testing stage in the US and will be used on healthy volunteers, then patients if it deemed safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man busted with Andrew Gillum in hotel room with meth was gay escort...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/14/man-busted-with-andrew-gillum-in-hotel-room-with-meth-was-gay-escort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Gillum was caught in a room with more than just drugs. The man who overdosed on crystal meth in a Florida hotel room with Gillum, a Democrat who made an unsuccessful bid for Florida governor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC NIGHTMARE SCENARIO: 1.7 MILLION DEATHS...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/13/the-worst-case-estimate-for-u-s-coronavirus-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials at the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and epidemic experts from universities around the world conferred last</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S AN EMERGENCY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/83b0c8e168548fd453b0c177dd1f203a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Friday declared the coronavirus pandemic a national emergency, freeing up money and resources to fight the outbreak, and then threw his support behind...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll with implanted human hair leaves people 'certain it's real person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-doll-implanted-human-hair-21687823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A fresh range of sex dolls have been equipped with implanted human hair, giving them a look so realistic that some customers report believing they were alive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Percenters Keep Calm With $4,995 Go-Bag...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/one-percenters-keep-calm-during-coronavirus-with-a-4-995-go-bag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Is How the Richest 1% Keep Calm and Carry On</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna choreographer lets headless dancers loose...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/madonna-choreographer-damien-jalet-lets-headless-dancers-loose-083406334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dancers gyrate and contort their bodies into sculptures made by the human body but which look distinctly other-worldly. A choreographer favoured by superstars like Madonna, Radiohead singer Thom Yorke and Florence Welch of Florence and the Machine, Damien Jalet is on a mission to reinvent perceptions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could 2020 Election Be Postponed?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/14/could-the-2020-election-be-postponed-only-with-great-difficulty-heres-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus outbreak is inflicting new disruptions on the 2020 presidential campaign by the day, but few compare to Louisiana’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Am I on Camera?' Biden's Foray Into Virtual Campaigning...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/14/am-i-on-camera-joe-bidens-foray-into-virtual-campaigning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Joseph R. Biden Jr., campaigning these days means virtual fund-raisers. Field offices shuttered. And rallying support by live stream,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Could Easily Kill Them': Terrified Doctors Sound Alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/terrified-doctors-sound-alarm-on-coronavirus-chaos-nationwide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I desperately want to be tested, for the sake of my patients,” one doctor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish govt imposes lockdown of entire country...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/coronavirus-spain-news-nationwide-lockdown-emergency-covid-19-a9402166.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawls break out at stores across country as customers dash for supplies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8111333/Fights-break-stores-country-coronavirus-panic-buying-intensifies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fights broke out between customers in Georgia and New York on Thursday as tensions about the coronavirus emergency came to a head while shoppers battled to stock up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploys Large Fans to Blow Back Migrant Tear Gas Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2020/03/14/greece-deploys-large-fans-to-blow-back-migrant-tear-gas-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece deployed large fans at the border to blow back against tear gas fired by migrants allegedly armed by Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman In Italy Warns: 'Don't Do Anything'; 'Stay Home'; 'They Don't Know Where To Put Bodies'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/03/13/coronavirus-colorado-italy-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;rom her home in Garda, Italy, Shannon Unks, a CU graduate and former Colorado resident, has a harsh warning for Colorado residents: “Don’t do anything- don’t go to the cinemas, stay home, shut it down.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling Europeans tighten measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1dde718068517f188b3fa65a7edcbf86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA, Spain (AP) — Spain decided Saturday to follow Italy in declaring a nationwide lockdown to slow the accelerating spread of the coronavirus epidemic, Spanish media reported. Spain's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new epicenter... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11164783/europe-epicentre-coronavirus-pandemic/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE World Health Organisation has said Europe is now the “epicentre” of the global coronavirus pandemic. Dr Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus, the WHO Chief, said that the number of deaths sur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellish side of handwashing: How coronavirus affecting people with OCD...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2020/mar/13/why-regular-handwashing-can-be-bad-advice-for-patients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some OCD patients, not washing their hands is part of their treatment. So guidance to do so regularly is reviving their anxieties – and triggering them in others</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic groups across US 'mutilating cattle for sexual organs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/twisted-satanic-groups-across-are-21681674</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: More than 10,000 cattle have been slaughtered over the past 30 years in the US – with explanations still scarce (WARNING: GRAPHIC CONTENT)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italians singing songs from windows to boost morale...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/14/coronavirus-lockdown-italians-are-singing-songs-from-balconies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social media videos, from various cities and towns, show people singing from balconies and windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE closes all stores outside China...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/14/coronavirus-apple-to-close-all-stores-outside-of-china-until-march-27.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple said it had learnt lessons from the China outbreak and "the most effective way" to minimize transmission is to maximize social distance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do we wear exhaustion as badge of honor?</title>
      <link>https://thriveglobal.com/stories/why-do-we-wear-exhaustion-as-a-badge-of-honour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thriveglobal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The glamourisation of sleep deprivation in modern society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He's an inmate': Anguish mounts over virus-hit nursing home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5b2b93682be5937ee1cda05efa68b79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIRKLAND, Wash. (AP) — Desperate to talk to their dad, Scott Sedlacek and his brother, Steve, stood outside his open nursing home window and shouted. They could barely hear his weak replies, but...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
