<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Politics keeps Americans up at night...</title>
      <link>http://www.fltimes.com/tns/washington/politics-keeps-in-americans-up-at-night-survey-finds/article_3bdf8e9b-cb9a-537c-9a77-6178d37cdc76.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON —Suffering from insomnia? Here's a quick cure: Stop caring about politics so much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Purges Accounts Across Platform --  Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/08/16/twitter-purges-accounts-across-the-platform-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media platform Twitter has begun banning a large number of accounts from the website, specifically focusing on accounts that have previously been banned or have received suspensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fraud Latest Hurdle for Music Streaming...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/digital/news/music-streaming-sites-fraud-1202905665/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter’s recent housecleaning of some 70 million fake and automated accounts illuminates just how pervasive audience manipulation has become in the digital era. For Twitter, the fake accounts can …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enninful rising at VOGUE...</title>
      <link>https://fashionweekdaily.com/british-vogue-circulation-rise/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fashionweekdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the U.K.’s Audit Bureau of Circulations shows that the mag has seen a 54.5% increase in circulation since Enninful took the helm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatter primary turnout records...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/16/democrats-shatter-primary-turnout-records-bank-ant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats saw a surge in voter turnout in primaries in flyover country this month, leaving party leaders salivating over a potential enthusiasm gap they hope will deliver control of Congress and several major governorships in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's war games factory...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6065013/Workers-near-completion-Russias-latest-supersonic-strike-bombers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tu-22M3M is a 'deep moderisation' of the Tu-22M3 which Russia's air force has about 100 in service and used extensively in missions over Syria in support of the Assad regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Will Cut Five Zeros From Currency to Fight Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/swamped-in-inflation-venezuela-will-cut-five-zeros-from-currency/17774600/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDELLÍN, Colombia — Faced with nearly incomprehensible inflation — 32,714 percent as of Wednesday — Venezuelan officials thought they had a solution: They changed the color of the bank notes and increased their denomination. Then they said they would lop off three zeros. And when that didn’t seem enough, they announced they would cut off two more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: 1 in 4 adults have disability...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/news/cdc-1-in-4-adults-have-a-disability-that-impacts-daily-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aug. 16 (UPI) — One in four adults reported they have a disability that impacts major life activities with the most dominant one affecting mobility,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beads, booze -- and babies? New Orleans to become family friendly...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-new-orleans-french-quarter-20180816-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should New Orleans' French Quarter be more family friendly?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN: Youth Unemployment Hits 52-Year Low... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/youth-unemployment-hits-52-year-low-1534455755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unemployment rate among young Americans fell to its lowest level in more than 50 years this summer, though the share of young people looking for work remained well below its peak in 1989.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious X-37B Military Space Plane Nears 1 Year in Orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/41507-x-37b-space-plane-nears-one-year-orbit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force's X-37B miniature space plane has winged past 340 days of flight performing secretive duties during the program's fifth flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environmentalists sue federal government in Seattle to protect endangered orcas...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environmental-group-sues-federal-government-in-seattle-to-protect-endangered-orcas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit alleges that the government had agreed in February 2015 that expanding the protection zone for the orcas was "warranted," but has since failed to take action, putting the orcas at greater risk of extinction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarosa's publisher responds to Trump attorney: We won't bow to 'hollow legal threats'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Omarosa-s-publisher-responds-to-Trump-campaign-13162457.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publisher of former Donald Trump aide Omarosa Manigault Newman's explosive new book on Wednesday issued a defiant rebuttal to what it described as "hollow legal threats" from a Trump campaign attorney. The gist of the message: We will not be silenced. "Mr. Trump is the President of the United States, with a 'bully pulpit' at his disposal," Simon &amp; Schuster outside counsel Elizabeth McNamara said in the letter, a copy of which was obtained by The Washington Post. "To the extent he disputes any statements in the Book, he has the largest platform in the world to challenge them." Simon &amp; Schuster, McNamara added, "will not be intimidated by hollow legal threats and have proceeded with publication of the Book as scheduled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY STORM:  Texas plants spewed 8 million pounds of air pollutants as hurricane hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/harvey/2018/08/16/texas-petrochemical-plants-spewed-8-million-pounds-air-pollutants-hurricane-harvey-hit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Floodwater caused most of the damage when Hurricane Harvey slammed into the Texas coast a year ago. But that region's air quality was also harmed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAUDER:  As our media environment blurs, confusion often reigns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/127fe8b09ae74a57826ab5953922e711/As-our-media-environment-blurs,-confusion-often-reigns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A generation ago, the likes of Walter Cronkite, Peter Jennings and Diane Sawyer were the heroes of television news. Now the biggest stars are arguably Sean Hannity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Dems 'ready to sue' for Kavanaugh records...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/senate-democrats-ready-sue-kavanaugh-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We need these documents to do our job,” Blumenthal told reporters. “We will be ready to go to court.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon postpones military parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pentagon-says-trumps-proposed-military-parade-on-hold-until-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parade, which will occur on Veterans Day, is set to cost more than three times the original maximum estimate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Trump finally ready to turn his sights to remaking 9th Circuit Court?</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/politics/2018/08/15/is-trump-finally-ready-to-turn-his-sights-to-remaking-the-9th-circuit-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Trump took office, the Senate has confirmed only one 9th Circuit judge — in Hawaii — leaving seven openings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Woman Charged With Raping 5-Year-Old Boy, Posting Video Online...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/08/15/woman-charged-raping-boy-posting-video-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Westmoreland County woman is facing charges for allegedly raping a 5-year-old boy and sharing video of the act on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW NAFTA WITH MEX!</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/business/consumer/article_599976db-fea0-540a-a95b-6e3e924fc1a0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Trump administration is close to striking a deal with Mexico on a revamped North American Free Trade Agreement, analysts said, but thorny issues are yet to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE UNSTOPPABLE? EVERY PERSON WHO CHALLENGES MUELLER AUTHORITY LOSES...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/every-single-person-whos-challenged-muellers-authority-has-lost/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. officials moved to ban rental scooters  -- so why are they everywhere?</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-scooter-ban-20180815-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City Council passed a motion to ban electric scooters in March, but you wouldn't know it from the hundreds of scooters zipping through Venice Beach, Beverly Grove and other Los Angeles neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen hacks APPLE servers, steals files...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2018/08/16/apple-servers-hacked-teen-sensitive-data-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple’s servers are widely believed to be unhackable, and to date the company hasn’t suffered any massive breach that would have exposed user data to hackers. Well, it turns out that while mo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Phantom smells more common than thought, signal health troubles...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/phantom-smells-may-be-more-common-thought-study-finds-n901426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detecting odors that aren't there can be a sign of a serious health problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Loosens  Use of Cyberweapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-move-to-loosen-u-s-use-of-cyber-weapons-prompts-intrigue-1534456712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration’s move to loosen rules of engagement for U.S. cyberattacks has prompted questions about how the military will carry out offensive digital strikes, and whether hostilities with adversaries will escalate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Michael Avenatti Got Clinton Machine 'Dark Arts' Start...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/stevenperlberg/michael-avenatti-campaigns-oppo-research-rahm-emanuel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1990s, as an entry-level opposition researcher, Avenatti once climbed aboard a moving train to get research to FedEx on time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-carb diet linked to elevated mortality...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/low-carb-diet-linked-elevated-mortality-risk-study-233354036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Middle-aged people who get roughly half their daily calories from carbohydrates live several years longer on average than those with low-carb diets, researchers reported Friday. The findings, published in The Lancet, challenge a trend in Europe and North America toward so-called Paleo diets that shun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTRIGUE SURROUNDS 'ELUSIVE' SPECIAL COUNSEL TEAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/meet-the-special-counsel-team-so-careful-they-won-t-even-disclose-their-shake-shack-orders/17774617/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. — Greg D. Andres looked like any ordinary guest at the Westin hotel here, standing near the valet in flip-flops and a white Notre Dame boxing T-shirt, waiting for a Postmates delivery from Shake Shack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE ASKED TO REDEFINE 'REASONABLE DOUBT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Jurors-in-Manafort-trial-send-judge-four-13162070.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. - Jurors weighing the fate of President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort ended its first day of deliberations Thursday with a set of questions for the judge, asking for further explanation of legal points the defense made in closing arguments. Just before 4:50 p.m., there was a knock at one of the doors to U.S. District Judge T.S. Ellis' courtroom, behind which jurors are deliberating. The court security officer emerged minutes later with a note. Jurors had four questions, some of which centered around defense arguments made by Manafort's lawyers. Manafort faces 18 tax and bank fraud charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earliest galaxies in universe discovered 'on cosmic doorstep'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-45198764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the earliest galaxies to form in the Universe are sitting on our cosmic doorstep, a study says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bugged meeting claims escalate Brexit paranoia...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/brexit-bugging-claim-negotiations-paranoia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar bear steals 50,000-year-old woolly mammoth leg from scientist camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/polar-bear-steals-50000-year-13091507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explorers woke up to the bear dragging the ancient specimen out of their campsite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papadopoulos wife wants to scrap plea with 'Shady' Mueller...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/402260-papadopouloss-wife-wants-him-to-scrap-the-plea-deal-with-mueller</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Simona Mangiante, the wife of former Trump campaign aide George Papadopoulos, says her husband should end his plea agreement with special counsel Robert Mueller's office and refuse to cooperate further with its investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian strategic bombers deploy near Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://www.theintelligencer.com/news/world/article/Russian-strategic-bombers-deploy-near-Alaska-13161106.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theintelligencer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) - The Russian military says that two nuclear-capable strategic bombers have flown to the easternmost Chukotka Peninsula, near Alaska, as part of an air force exercise. The Russian Defense Ministry said that the Tu-160 bombers flew about 7,000 kilometers (4,350 Miles) from their home base near Saratov in southwestern Russia to Anadyr, on Chukotka, before returning to their home base. The ministry said the mission was the first time the bombers had flown to Chukotka, which faces Alaska across the Bering Strait. The ministry said the air force exercise also involved the Tu-95 strategic bombers and tanker planes. The Russian military has increased the intensity and scope of its drills amid strain in relations with the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE ADMITS TRACKING USERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ef95c6a91eeb4d8e9dda9cad887bf211</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Google clarified how it tracks users even if they've disabled a "location history" setting, revising a help page that erroneously said turning off that settin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURIOUSITY SURROUNDS DISCREET MUELLER TEAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/16/us/politics/special-counsel-investigation-mueller.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial of Paul Manafort, President Trump’s former campaign chairman, has provided the public with its first extended glimpse of Robert S. Mueller III’s investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pissed players want robot umpires...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/the-download/611901/baseball-players-want-robots-to-be-their-umps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sports world has been dealing with the human error of referees and umpires for decades—it’s pretty much tradition at this point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: FACEBOOK Misled Advertisers, Ballooned 'Reach'...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/08/16/fake-numbers-facebook-misled-advertisers-with-inflated-potential-reach-lawsuit-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit alleges that Facebook inflated its potential reach to sell more ads and compared Census data with Facebook’s numbers to show the disparity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govts Accidentally Expose Passwords, Security Plans To Entire Internet...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/16/trello-board-uk-canada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Trello, a project management site, the governments posted credentials for servers and domain names and even some emails and code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror Films Find Scares In Dead Cell Phone Batteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/8/16/17675474/modern-horror-films-dead-cell-phone-trope-isolation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Killing off the characters’ cellphones is now a standard trope, so horror filmmakers are learning to tackle it in creative ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says TESLA whistleblower 'super nuts'...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/elon-musk-on-whistleblower-accusing-tesla-of-illegally-1828399337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk on Thursday moved to discredit a former employee and self-proclaimed whistleblower whose attorneys have accused Musk of authorizing Tesla to allegedly engage in “unauthorized wiretapping and hacking” of another former employee of the electric car manufacturer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts Worry As Flight-Simulator Enthusiasts Confident of Real-World Skills...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/flight-simulator-enthusiasts-confident-of-real-world-skills-1534446556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virtual-flight hobbyists are in the spotlight after a man who stole an aircraft last week near Seattle said he learned to fly with “videogames.’’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort jury ends day of deliberations with questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7847c2d3498d403db0d8b28b942e5ec2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. (AP) — The jury in the fraud trial of former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort ended its first day of deliberations with a series of questions to the judge, in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask definition of 'reasonable doubt'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/402248-manafort-jury-ends-first-day-with-questions-including-definition-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury in the criminal trial against former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort sent a note to the judge asking him to redefine "reasonable doubt" and answer three other questions as their first day of deliberations drew to a close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Careful to Avoid John Edwards Case Failures...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-access-hollywood-tape-surfaced-michael-cohen-changed-tune-on-paying-stormy-daniels-1534455109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen initially balked at the idea of buying the silence of a former adult-film star who says she had sex with Donald Trump, but he did an about-face after a video of Mr. Trump talking about groping women became public in October 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT JURY SENDS 4 QUESTIONS TO JUDGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-jury-deliberations-start-manafort-trial-141550549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. (AP) — The Latest on the trial of Paul Manafort (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swerving UBER driver terrorizes riders: 'All gonna die!'</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/2018/08/14/terrifying-uber-ride-through-sacramento-leaves-3-women-shaken/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO -- Three friends are speaking out two months after a 25-minute nightmare Uber ride through Sacramento.  "I legitimately believed that we were going to die," said Theadora Fuerstenberg.  It's an app thousands use every day but a June 15 Uber trip on Interstate 80 from a book club in Arden to Oak Park traumatized three women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Phantom smells more common than thought, signal health troubles...</title>
      <link>hhttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/phantom-smells-may-be-more-common-thought-study-finds-n901426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bans on full-face Muslim veils spread across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2018/08/16/france-denmark-bans-full-face-muslim-veils-are-spreading-across-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A guide to where veils such as the burqa and niqab are banned on the continent — and why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't know if legally able to say this'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedenverchannel.com/sports/broncos/broncos-john-elway-wants-fast-starts-better-offense-but-no-kaepernick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedenverchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General manager John Elway wants more 'pride' in effort as team plays second preseason game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanted 'prostitute' leads cops on high-speed chase through residential area...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/communities/south/crime/2018/08/15/wanted-woman-leads-cudahy-police-high-speed-chase/995251002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A traffic stop in the 3100 block of East Layton Avenue was the catalyst for the chase after driver Laquitia Watson, 27, gave police a false name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police guard BOSTON GLOBE over 'serious threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/boston-globe-threat-editorial-trump-07a46bf9-9c6a-4266-a4b2-c90f8c15d03c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Police sent uniformed officers to patrol in and around the paper's headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM's Kaepernick comments may cause problems for NFL...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/elway-kaepernick-comments-could-problematic-202259239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the NFL tries to show that the collective shunning of Colin Kaepernick didn’t result from collusion, one of the teams at the heart of the before/after anthem protest attitude toward Kaepernick may have made things a bit more difficult. Broncos G.M. John Elway, who recently opened the door to bringing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON:  China Likely Prepping To Strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinese-bombers-likely-training-us-strikes-pentagon-194141619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual report to Congress, released Thursday, highlights China's growing military, economic and diplomatic clout and how Beijing is leveraging this to rapidly build its international footprint and establish regional dominance. In the case of China's air power, the report states that Chinese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATIMES REBUKES 'GROUPTHINK'...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/opinion/la-ol-enter-the-fray-the-los-angeles-times-is-not-1534376775-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 300 newspapers will be writing about free speech today to protest Trump's attack. The Los Angeles Times will not be among them. Here's why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon church drops 'Mormon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.deseretnews.com/article/900028401/the-church-of-jesus-christ-of-latter-day-saints-issues-new-name-guidelines-dropping-term-mormon-in-most-uses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deseretnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms 26th appellate judge as Trump reshapes court at record clip...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Senate-confirms-the-25th-and-26th-appellate-13161552.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate on Thursday confirmed the 25th and 26th appellate court judges during President Donald Trump's tenure, as Republicans continued reshaping the federal judiciary at a record clip. The Senate approved A. Marvin Quattlebaum Jr. by a vote of 62 to 28, and backed Julius Ness Richardson on a vote of 81 to 8. Both will join the U.S. Court of Appeals for the 4th Circuit. The GOP-controlled Senate has been approving appellate court judges at a rapid pace, already setting a record for the most confirmed during a president's first two years in office. GOP leaders are installing jurists favored by conservatives who are likely to influence decisions on immigration, voting rights, abortion and the environment for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Rep. on Asian opponent: 'Don't vote for the ching-chong!'</title>
      <link>https://www.metrotimes.com/news-hits/archives/2018/08/16/detroit-rep-bettie-cook-scott-on-asian-opponent-dont-vote-for-the-ching-chong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.metrotimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen community groups have called on Rep. Bettie Cook Scott (D-Detroit) to apologize for a series of racial slurs sources say she...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straw Company Thriving Despite Anti-Straw Movement...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/08/15/chicago-straw-company-thrives-despite-anti-straw-movement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago company hopes to thrive, despite making plastic straws, a product under fire this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAUNDROMAT In High School -- After Students Bullied Over Dirty Clothes!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/08/15/newark-school-installs-laundromat-in-attempt-to-wash-away-the-vicious-cycle-of-bullying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high school in New Jersey is getting off to a "clean" start this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Buy LANDMARK Movie Chain?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/2018/08/16/amazon-is-said-to-be-in-running-to-acquire-landmark-movie-chain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. is in the running to acquire Landmark Theaters, a move that would vault the e-commerce giant into the brick-and-mortar cinema industry, according to people familiar with the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the three-year-old with a 171 IQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/education-45195807</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natalie and Ben's daughter Ophelia joined Mensa at only three years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarosa Latest 'Bombshell' Tapes Disappoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/omarosa-goes-on-msnbc-to-drop-bombshell-tapes-of-her-getting-a-job-offer-from-the-trump-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacramento officials track license plates to monitor welfare recipients...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90220108/sacramento-has-been-tracking-license-plates-to-monitor-welfare-recipients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology snaps photos of license plates when the cars they are attached to make their way past telephone poles and police cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City urges break from sex to fight heat wave...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/city-urges-a-break-from-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials in one Colombian coastal city have a controversial recommendation for residents trying to stay cool during an intense heat wave: Take a break from sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Staff Protest Secret Work on Censored China Search Engine...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/16/google-china-crisis-staff-dragonfly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is facing mounting pressure inside and outside the company over its plans for a censored search engine in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORECAST:  75% CHANCE DEMS WIN HOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2018-midterm-election-forecast/house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight's predictions for the 2018 House elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington cardinal entangled in two sex-abuse scandals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a22e1a2a39c4fe385b265f7f7214d97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cardinal Donald Wuerl, the Roman Catholic archbishop of Washington, is facing a storm of criticism and calls for his resignation after becoming entangled in two major sexual abuse scand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC school board votes to stop spanking...</title>
      <link>https://wlos.com/news/local/north-carolina-county-school-board-votes-to-stop-spanking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wlos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporal punishment will end in one North Carolina county's schools.News outlets report Robeson County was one of two school systems in North Carolina that continued paddling students as part of disciplinary policy. The Robesonian was first to report the R</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City bans use of models at city events...</title>
      <link>http://www.oleantimesherald.com/news/world/mexico-city-bans-use-of-models-at-city-events/article_4d959714-0e7b-56a0-b3ca-14531a2cab0c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oleantimesherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — They've long been an unmissable part of public events in Mexico, from soccer matches to trade fairs: attractive women hired to be greeters or simply as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates use drain pipe to escape GA jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/two-inmates-use-drain-pipe-escape-from-georgia-jail-officials-say/rJyqtsR8rxWH9eTnPsIkEI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two inmates used a drain pipe to escape late Wednesday from the Troup County Jail, the sheriff&amp;rsqu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens if Mueller subpoenas Trump?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/mueller-decides-subpoena-president-trump/story?id=57219103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Trump refuses to submit to an interview, Mueller will be faced with a momentous decision of whether to seek to compel President Trump to testify.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt finalizing details of long-term Hamas-Israel truce...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-egypt-gaza/egypt-finalizing-details-of-long-term-hamas-israel-truce-source-idUSKBN1L1219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt is finalizing details of a long-term truce deal between Israel and Hamas in the Gaza Strip, an Egyptian security source said on Thursday, amid easing tensions on the border of the enclave where some two million Palestinians live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Ebola outbreak most dangerous test yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/08/16/ebola-outbreak-challenges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outbreak is occurring is in a conflict zone with scores of armed groups and “red zones” where health workers may not be able to travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy Parents Help Child Athletes Go Pro in Own Backyards...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wealthy-parents-help-child-athletes-go-pro-in-their-own-backyards-1534429841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich families are building gyms, soccer fields and baseball batting cages at home to develop their student-athlete skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>350 outlets  denounce president's attacks on media...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-newspapers-hit-back-trump-defend-free-press-153154562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading the charge was The Boston Globe, which had called for the drive highlighting the importance of a free press, accompanied by the hashtag #EnemyOfNone. "Today in the United States we have a president who has created a mantra that members of the media who do not blatantly support the policies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros foundation to quit Hungary...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/soros-foundation-quit-hungary-end-august-151523300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The foundation run by US billionaire George Soros said Thursday that the last of its operations in Hungary would cease by August 31, with its activities being transferred to Berlin. The Open Society Foundations (OSF) announced in May that it was leaving Hungary, citing what it called the "repressive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How she made 'Respect' a feminist anthem...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/aretha-franklin-made-respect-feminist-anthem-143229602.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be the most rousing feminist anthem ever, but "Respect" -- the song that made Aretha Franklin the "Queen of Soul" -- was actually written about a man demanding a break from his wife. Franklin's genius was to turn the song -- and the traditional values it espoused -- on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy Slams California Democrats, Faces Heckling...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/california/articles/2018-08-15/gops-mccarthy-slams-california-democrats-faces-heckling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Ellison Fights Back Tears In Interview on Alleged Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/keith-ellison-fights-back-tears-during-interview-about-abuse-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Look, we loved each other, we don’t have to destroy each other,’ he said he would say to Karen Monahan, the ex-girlfriend accusing him of physical abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As San Francisco grows, so does earthquake risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/15/san-francisco-earthquake--why-the-city-is-not-prepared.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's why San Francisco is not as ready as one may think when the next big earthquake hits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST to allow miniature horses onboard as service animals...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/southwest-airlines-to-allow-miniature-horses-as-service-animals-in-new-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Come September 17, people will be able to carry miniature horses onboard Southwest flights as trained service animals, according to airline officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aretha Franklin passes away on same day Elvis  died!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/7031351/aretha-franklin-dead-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUL legend Aretha Franklin has died from cancer aged 76, it was confirmed today. The Respect singer passed away at 9.50am this morning at her home in Detroit after an eight-year battle with pancre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN IS DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/entertainment/music/2018/08/16/aretha-franklin-dies/309137002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aretha Franklin was a transcendent figure in pop culture and the greatest name in Detroit's storied music history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>73 HIT SONGS</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/news/obituary/7318784/aretha-franklin-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aretha Franklin, whose legendary voice inaugurated her enduring reign as the Queen of Soul, died at 76 on Thursday (Aug. 16), Franklin's longtime publicist Gwendolyn Quinn confirms in a statement. The icon had been battling pancreatic cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Trust and Safety Council' Working Overtime to Ban Conservatives...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/it-seems-twitters-trust-and-safety-council-is-working-overtime-to-ban-conservatives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do we avoid breaking their rules in the future? Beats me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surrender to the Robots?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/will-baseball-surrender-to-the-robots-1534428425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In baseball, they’re beginning to sound sanguine about the robots, specifically the use of robot umpires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury begins weighing charges against Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/paul-manafort-trial-jury-begins-deliberation-in-former-trump-campaign-chairs-financial-fraud-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors now consider the 18 charges against the former Trump campaign chairman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of 401(k) millionaires hits record...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/08/16/number-401-k-millionaires-hits-new-record/1000228002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 401(k) millionaire's club hit a record high of 168,000 in June, according to Fidelity Investments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicidal Vet Calls MDMA Treatment 'Miracle'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/suicidal-vet-calls-mdma-treatment-a-miracle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He suffered from post-traumatic stress disorder after the Iraq War. Thanks to MDMA, Jonathan Lubecky finally feels like he’s recovering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACKSTREET BOY Rape Accuser Tells All...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/melissa-schuman-accused-backstreet-boy-nick-carter-of-rape-and-then-the-vultures-came-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pop star, formerly of the girl group Dream, accused Carter of rape. She opens up to Amy Zimmerman about the harassment, doxxing, and industry silence she’s endured since.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow unveils world's first AI nuke bomber...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/723671/Russia-Kazan-new-bomber-plane-AI-supersonic-nuclear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese satellites to keep real-time watch on South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2159891/string-chinese-satellites-keep-real-time-watch-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each reef and island in the contested waters will be monitored from space after launches start next year, developer says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust computer? Film explores perils of tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/aug/16/do-you-trust-your-computer-documentary-technology-perils</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Paine’s documentary looks at the potential dangers of our intimate relationship with smartphones and laptops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans don't want self-driving car...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/nearly-half-of-americans-dont-want-a-self-driving-car-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cox Automotive says more consumers are aware of the technology, but acceptance is on the decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress Keeping Americans Up at Night...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-care-news/articles/2018-08-16/poll-stress-about-money-relationships-keeps-americans-up-at-night</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial gills for humans could become reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/amphibio-underwater-breathing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designer Jun Kamei has created Amphibio, a 3D-printed 'gill' that may allow humans to breathe underwater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turks taking sledgehammers, handguns, fire to iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/turkey-anger-donald-trump-us-tariffs-turks-smash-iphones-burn-fake-dollars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turks show support for their gov't as it clashes with U.S. over a jailed American Pastor Andrew Brunson by destroying U.S. products</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers steal $13M from cash machines in global heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hackers-steal-10m-cash-machines-113407064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyber criminals have hacked cash machines in 28 countries to loot over £10 million from an Indian bank. Hackers infected the bank's credit card payment system with malware, which allowed them to approve transactions and access client accounts. Fake credit cards were then used to force ATMs around</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Fastest Sales Growth in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/walmart-rides-strong-consumer-spending-to-fastest-sales-growth-in-over-a-decade-1534419073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart said sales rose at the fastest rate in over a decade as the world’s largest retailer continues to draw more people to stores and benefit from strong consumer spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower shocking IRS, insider trading allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/15/whistleblower-makes-shocking-irs-insider-trading-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A whistleblower made this shocking allegation to me last week: the IRS was tipping off members of Congress to corporate takeovers so the elected officials could profit from insider trading. My snit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBS AND SOCIAL MEDIA STARS INVESTIGATED FOR NOT LABELLING POSTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.eveningexpress.co.uk/news/business/celebrities-and-social-media-stars-investigated-for-not-labelling-posts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eveningexpress.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The competition watchdog has launched an investigation of social media stars over concerns they are not declaring when they have been paid to post about products and experiences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Close on trans role row: 'Anyone should be able to play anyone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/glenn-close-weighs-scarlett-johansson-093138248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given that her 2012 Oscar nomination was for a role in which she played a woman masquerading as a man (Albert Nobbs) – it should come as no surprise that Glenn Close has waded in on the debate surrounding Scarlett Johansson's contentious casting as a transgender man in the now–dormant film Rub &amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosses now earn 312 times average worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/aug/16/ceo-versus-worker-wage-american-companies-pay-gap-study-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomical gap between the pay of workers and bosses exposed in report on earnings of America’s top 350 CEOs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam sentences activist to 20 years prison amid dissent crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-vietnam-dissident/vietnam-sentences-activist-to-20-years-prison-amid-dissent-crackdown-idUKKBN1L10RD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A court in northern Vietnam on Thursday sentenced an activist to 20 years in prison after he was convicted in a one-day trial of attempting to overthrow the state, his lawyer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastating dolphin loss in red tide disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180815-devastating-dolphin-loss-florida-red-tide-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Home for $90K? Manufactured Housing Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/16/cheap-and-sleek-manufactured-housing-is-primed-for-a-comeback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Home for $90,000? Manufactured Housing Is Making a Comeback</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malaysian parliament throws out law against 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180816102404-kp8ii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MALAYSIA-POLITICS/FAKENEWS:Malaysian parliament throws out law against</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury to begin weighing charges against Manafort...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180816100001-wopdy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA-MANAFORT (PIX):Jury to begin weighing U.S. charges against ex-Trump aide Manafort</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying droids to trap feral swine...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/08/15/drones-help-trap-feral-pigs-part-faa-experiment/994498002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drones will help trap wild pigs under an FAA program examining broader use of commercial unmanned aircraft. Drones are doing everything from delivering defibrillators to spraying insecticide to inspecting oil pipelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Strikeouts Than Hits? Baseball's Latest Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/16/sports/baseball-mlb-strikeouts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This could be the first season in major league history to feature more strikeouts than hits, a slowdown that worries many league officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dr Bumbum' charged with murder over patient death...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/dr-bumbum-brazil-murder-plastic-surgeon-cosmetic-lilian-calixto-a8493931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operation to enlarge woman's buttocks went fatally wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Member Arrested in Sacramento...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/08/15/sacramento-man-arrested-isis-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government of Iraq has charged Omar Abdulsattar Ameen with premeditated murder that happened during an ISIS takeover of the Rawah District of the Al-Anbar Province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese sexbots flood America...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/723504/sex-robot-doll-china-company-wmdoll-moving-limbs-sales-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone stalks woman outside bedroom window...</title>
      <link>http://www.kmov.com/story/38893394/its-disgusting-surveillance-shows-drone-flying-outside-womans-window-at-night</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kmov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a disgusting invasion of privacy." An airborne intruder hovering outside her home late at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Mead Could Drop Below Critical Threshold...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/agency-says-lake-mead-could-drop-below-critical-threshold-1534374220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nevada’s Lake Mead, the biggest reservoir in the West, is on track to fall below a critical threshold in 2020 and could trigger a federal shortage declaration on the Colorado River, according to a new forecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: World Droid Conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/picture-gallery/tech/2018/08/15/robots-come-alive-beijing-world-robot-conference/999190002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visitors look at a robot making drinks during the World Robot Conference in Beijing on Aug. 15, 2018. The conference includes a conference on robotics, an exhibition and a robot competition with the participation of robotics enterprises to showcase their products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS: Marital spats cause disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/08/15/marital-rows-could-make-say-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Occasional squabbling is a normal part of marriage, but when it descends into vicious rows it can makes couples ill, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaceship may lay off Florida coast, says DISCOVERY CHANNEL treasure hunter...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/science/Alien-spaceship-may-lay-off-Florida-coast-says-Discovery-Channel-treasure-hunter_170882935</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a close encounter of the submerged kind, a Discovery Channel treasure hunter said he found what could be a massive extraterrestrial structure at the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean off the Florida co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican 'disturbing' silence on abuse cover-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvz.com/news/national-world/pressure-mounts-on-pope-francis-to-address-abuse-coverups/781898736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican has declined to respond to an explosive grand jury report detailing decades of sexual abuse and cover-ups by priests and bishops in Pennsylvania, refusing even to say whether church officials in Rome have read the damaging documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Tells Catholic Leaders: 'I Want to Kick Your Ass'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/08/15/duterte-catholic-bishops-kick-your-ass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte threatened violence against any Catholic bishop or priest present at remarks he delivered Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: Maxine Waters 'Strikes Fear in the Heart' of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/15/nancy-pelosi-maxine-waters-strikes-fear-in-the-heart-of-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) claimed on Wednesday that Rep. Maxine Waters (D-CA) “strikes fear in the heart” of President Donald Trump. | Big Government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presence of threatening humanoid improves performance...</title>
      <link>http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/08/being-watched-cranky-robot-might-help-you-focus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New study is the first to explore how robot moods affect human concentration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's largest fire ever  -- keeps growing...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-mendocino-complex-update-20180815-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the River fire is 100% contained as of Monday, the Ranch fire has consumer more than 314,000 acres and is 64% contained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Drug overdoses hit new record...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/401961-cdc-drug-overdoses-hit-new-high-in-2017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 72,000 Americans died from drug overdoses in 2017, according to preliminary data from the Centers for Disease Control and Preven</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University Installing AMAZON Alexa in Dorms...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/08/15/amazon-alexa-echo-back-to-school-dorm-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexa, do ever go to class?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space arms race...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-raises-questions-over-apos-191925908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has challenged Russia about a satellite orbiting the earth exhibiting "abnormal behaviour", raising questions about Moscow's intentions to develop space weapons. A US official said the satellite was acting suspiciously, describing its recent launch as “a very troubling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Russia testing 'killer satellite' in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/military/russia-accused-of-testing-a-killer-satellite-in-orbit/news-story/618fa3f5cf0bf28f83e0bf370f7cdd0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT’S small. It's nimble. It’s doing strange things over our heads. And Russia's new Kosmos 2521 satellite has the potential to bring the world’s economy to its knees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES: BLATANT LIES BEING TOLD ABOUT ME...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/alex-jones-its-a-blatant-lie-im-calling-for-violence-its-a-hoax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSM talking heads falsely claim Infowars 'inciting violence' against media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica farm seizures: List of whites facing expropriation...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1003985/South-Africa-farmers-white-seize-list-rural-Cyril-Ramaphosa </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH Africa's government has been accused of drawing up a list of almost 200 farms it allegedly wants to seize from white farmers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastating dolphin loss in red tide disaster...</title>
      <link>Devastating dolphin loss in red tide disaster...</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRENNAN SECURITY CLEARANCE REVOKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/15/trump-pulls-security-clearance-of-ex-cia-director-brennan-778791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Mr. Brennan’s lying and recent conduct characterized by increasingly frenzied commentary is wholly inconsistent with access to the nation’s most closely held secrets.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TRUMP SUBPOENA...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/politics/politicalheadlines/13977755-74/trumps-lawyers-prepare-to-fight-subpoena-all-the-way-to-the-supreme</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- Rudy Giuliani, President Trump's lead lawyer for the ongoing Russia probe, said Wednesday that he is still awaiting a response from Special Counsel ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
