<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  As FACEBOOK Raised a Privacy Wall, It Carved an Opening for Tech Giants... </title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/facebook-offered-users-privacy-wall-then-let-tech-giants-around-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internal records show that the social network had arrangements with Microsoft, Amazon and others, effectively exempting some partners from its usual privacy rules. The documents underscore how personal data has become the digital age’s prized commodity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercise as good as drugs at cutting high blood pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/18/exercise-could-good-drugs-cutting-high-blood-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise may be as good at drugs at reducing high blood pressure, research suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egyptian Curse? Six archaeologists DIE mysteriously after opening sarcophagus...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1060487/egyptian-curse-six-archaeologists-die-mysteriously-opening-sarcophagus-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIX archaeologists died mysteriously just months after they opened up an ancient Egyptian coffin, a bombshell documentary has revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitelists...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-gave-some-companies-access-to-additional-data-about-users-friends-1528490406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook struck customized data-sharing deals that gave select companies special access to user records well after the point in 2015 that the social network has said it walled off that information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's most stressful airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6507947/Americas-stressful-airports-revealed-New-Yorks-LaGuardia-coming-top.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research shows that LaGuardia airport has reported the highest percentage of cancelled flights so far this year, with a 4.9 per cent rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet 'world's most popular sperm donor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6508859/Kyle-Gordy-fathered-18-children-sperm-donation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles resident Kyle Gordy, 27, said he donates his sperm so he can have children without being in a relationship. He has sex with about a quarter of his clients. He also has repeat business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENSPAN TO INVESTORS: RUN FOR COVER!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/18/business/alan-greenspan-stock-market-party-over/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fed chairman Alan Greenspan says he thinks the bull market is at an end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS braces for big shake-up...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/cbs-news-challenges-60-minutes-cbs-this-morning-1203092718/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At CBS News, President David Rhodes has a series of important decisions to make that could affect the trajectories of some of TV’s best-known news programs. As its parent company seeks to mov…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loneliness peaks at 3 key ages -- but wisdom may help...</title>
      <link>https://consumer.healthday.com/mental-health-information-25/psychology-and-mental-health-news-566/3-in-4-americans-struggle-with-loneliness-740748.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;consumer.healthday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Folks feeling lonely as the holidays approach have a lot of company, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  As FACEBOOK Raised a Privacy Wall, It Carved an Opening for Tech Giants... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/18/technology/facebook-privacy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internal documents show that the social network gave Microsoft, Amazon, Spotify and others far greater access to people’s data than it has disclosed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JARED'S BIGGEST WIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/senate-passes-bipartisan-trump-criminal-justice-reform-bill-9ac9618e-d0c3-4644-8169-a5cb771b0177.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The First Step Act has passed the Senate, and will now likely become law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate overwhelmingly passes criminal justice reform bill, delivering bipartisan bill to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af276b3dfa8548f0b1f9992e60bb59f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the Senate's consideration of criminal justice legislation (all times local): 8:52 p.m. The Senate has passed a sweeping criminal justice overhaul supported by groups on the left and right, handing President Donald Trump a victory as Congress prepares to adjourn for the holidays. The bill gives judges more discretion when sentencing some drug offenders and boosts prisoner rehabilitation efforts. It also reduces the life sentence for some drug offenders with three convictions, or "three strikes," to 25 years. The changes would only apply to federal prisoners. The Senate vote is the culmination of years of negotiations aimed at addressing concerns that the nation's war on drugs has exploded the prison population without helping people prepare for their return to society. The vote in the Senate Tuesday was 87-12. The House is also expected to pass the measure this week, sending it to Trump for his signature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL FUNDING OFF TABLE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/136873bdf74f4a01892815357658679e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump appeared Tuesday to back off his demand for $5 billion to build a border wall, signaling for the first time that he might be open to a deal that would avoid a partial government shutdown. The White House set the tone when press secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders indicated that Trump doesn't want to shut down the government, though just last week he said he'd be "proud" to do so. The president would consider other options and the administration was looking at ways to find the money elsewhere, Sanders said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare tornado rips roofs off Seattle area homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/weather/tornado-touches-down-on-kitsap-peninsula-rips-roof-off-home-weather-service-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tornado touched down and damaged homes near Port Orchard. No injuries were discovered in a primary search, according to the Washington State Patrol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot roams house seeking hugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/2178621/meet-lovot-japanese-robot-intelligence-hamster-who-will-roam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lovot is also equipped with three cameras – 180-degree, depth and temperature – to map and navigate the surrounding environment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Men shoplift purses, crash getaway car, carjack students and leave ride on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/skokie/news/ct-skr-skokie-theft-carjacking-tl-1227-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of men on Tuesday, Dec. 18 allegedly shoplifted purses at Old Orchard Mall in Skokie before crashing their getaway car and and stealing a Jeep from Niles North High School, which police found abandoned and on fire in Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man claims hunter 'mistook for Bigfoot', shot at him...</title>
      <link>https://helenair.com/news/local/helena-man-reports-being-shot-at-multiple-times-in-the/article_b8d711ca-a200-5503-bb4e-088fa34eb827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;helenair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Helena man target shooting on public land near Helena reported being shot at multiple times by another man who "mistook him for Bigfoot."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loneliness peaks at 3 key ages -- but wisdom may help...</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/health/study-loneliness-peaks-at-three-key-ages-but-wisdom-may-help</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising rates of loneliness may not be news, but the three periods when it peaks may come as a surprise: More people reported feeling moderate to severe loneliness during their late 20s, their mid-50s and their late 80s than in other life periods, according to research published Tuesday in the journal International Psychogeriatrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Lucas Tops Wealthiest Celebs List...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/natalierobehmed/2018/12/18/americas-wealthiest-celebrities-2018-george-lucas-leads-with-5-4-billion-net-worth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's 10 wealthiest celebrities boast a combined net worth of $18.7 billion, more than the GDP of Iceland. Here are those with both fame and fortune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia AI cameras detect thousands of distracted drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-16/new-cameras-detect-drivers-using-their-mobile-phone/10624648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A preliminary trial catches more than 11,000 drivers using their phones while behind the wheel and now the new high-definition cameras — which can detect drivers in all light and weather conditions — are set to be rolled out across parts of Sydney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallen metropolis: Collapsed Caracas once jewel of Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2018/dec/18/the-fallen-metropolis-the-collapse-of-caracas-the-jewel-of-latin-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once a thriving, glamorous city, Venezuela’s capital is buckling under hyperinflation, crime and poverty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Far From Over'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/report-cbs-footing-bill-for-ex-ceo-les-moonves-legal-fees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company will reportedly continue to do so if Moonves decides to sue over his $120 million severance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court Upholds Grand Jury Subpoena In Secret Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/18/mueller-probe-legal-foreign-owned-company-1068725</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling offers the intriguing detail that the entity fighting the Mueller subpoena is a foreign-owned company, not a specific individual, as many had speculated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada makes US history with first female-majority legislature...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/news/politics/2018/12/18/nevada-seat-first-female-majority-statehouse/2351542002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Appointment of two new Assemblywomen rounds out record-breaking feat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Footing Moonves Legal Bills -- Giving Him Incentive to Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/18/business/cbs-les-moonves-legal-fight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When CBS ousted its former chief executive, it agreed to pay his legal bills into the future — an arrangement likely to cost CBS tens of millions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials baffled by large migrant groups at remote crossing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f3bf396116574f9b9bd0c0f017e39983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Large numbers of Guatemalan families and unaccompanied children are surrendering to U.S. immigration agents in an extremely remote and dangerous stretch of New Mexico desert, a new smuggling route that has baffled authorities. It is where 7-year-old Jakelin Caal and her father were found Dec. 6 with 161 others near a border crossing in Antelope Wells. Caal started vomiting on the bus ride to the nearest Border Patrol station 94 miles (150 kilometers) away and had stopped breathing by the time she arrived. She died at a hospital in El Paso, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court Upholds Grand Jury Subpoena In Secret Case...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/muckraker/appeals-court-upholds-grand-jury-subpoena-in-secret-mueller-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The appellate court that heard a sealed grand jury case believed to be linked to special counsel Robert Mueller&amp;#8217;s probe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL hits player with 7th 'random' drug test after wearing Kaepernick cleats...</title>
      <link>https://ftw.usatoday.com/2018/12/eric-reid-random-drug-test-nfl-odds-chances-reaction-11-weeks-panthers-kaepernick-cleats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ftw.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are the chances? We figured it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock as 'Santa' collapses, dies at school Christmas party...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/santa-claus-collapses-dies-front-13751689</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING CONTENT: The Russian Santa was energetically performing and running around with the youngsters before footage captured him coming to a stop and falling backwards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL FUNDING OFF TABLE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/18/white-house-suggests-it-will-back-down-on-5-billion-border-wall-demand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's push for the money has threatened a partial government shutdown when funding for seven agencies lapses after midnight Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drama as Flynn sentencing DELAYED...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/421901-flynn-asks-judge-to-delay-sentencing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's former national security adviser Michael Flynn on Tuesday requested to postpone his sentencing for lying to FBI agents about his contacts with a Russian ambassador until his cooperation with federal prosecutors is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABRAMS: Justice either 'unprepared' or 'vindictive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/dan-abrams-says-michael-flynn-got-railroaded-at-hearing-judge-either-unprepared-or-vindictive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor hires mercenaries to rescue student from ISIS war zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2018/12/18/this-badass-professor-hired-mercenaries-to-rescue-a-college-student-from-an-isis-war-zone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some educators genuinely care about their pupils, but this Swedish professor went above and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used to bucking establishment, Tulsi Gabbard eyes run...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/592af52341dc4e0daf10a3de39fdfc33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — One of Rep. Tulsi Gabbard's duties when she deployed to Iraq with the Hawaii Army National Guard in 2005 was to scan a list of U.S. combat casualties for names of her unit's soldiers. Her job as a brigade surgeon operations specialist was to make sure these soldiers got the care they needed. This daily confrontation with the cost of war helped propel the 37-year-old Hawaii Democrat on a path to Congress and now, potentially, a run for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHATNER:  #MeToo hysterical, like French Revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6504445/William-Shatner-says-MeToo-hysterical-like-French-Revolution.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Trek legend William Shatner sat down with DailyMailTV as he promotes his own Christmas album Shatner Claus, saying the MeToo movement is like the French Revolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Votes to Legalize Sports Betting...</title>
      <link>https://www.actionnetwork.com/news/washington-dc-legal-sports-betting-district-of-columbia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.actionnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read more about the Washington D.C. city council's vote to legalize sports betting on Tuesday, Dec. 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-MARLINS President Brags About Fleecing Fans, Taxpayers in $1.2B Team Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.miaminewtimes.com/news/miami-marlins-david-samson-brags-about-12-billion-team-sale-10956381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miaminewtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At this point, every single person who worked for the Miami Marlins when Jeffrey Loria owned the team should be under strict FBI surveillance. Robert Mueller should be stalking these people. They keep revealing themselves to be vampires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calif. poised to offer 2 years of free college...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/Democrats-poised-to-offer-two-years-of-free-13475389.php?t=648874c522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California community college students could reap the benefits of Democratic dominance in the state Legislature, with lawmakers pushing for the state to cover the cost of two years of tuition for students who commit to enrolling full time right out of high school. Democratic lawmakers across the country have made affordability at public colleges and universities a rallying cry, with free tuition programs popping up at the state and local levels. During the 2018 midterms, the free-college mantra of Vermont independent Sen. Bernie Sanders became a key campaign promise for liberal candidates in congressional and state races. Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women spots stolen 'tiny home' on highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultralight plane flying with no lights drops 129 pounds of meth...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-ula-calexico-drugs-20181218-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border patrol agents arrested two people and seized 129 pounds of narcotics with an estimated value of $1.4 million after watching a suspicious ultralight aircraft land north of Calexico over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Dem Tells Republican To Kill Herself...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/18/kevin-parker-candice-giove-kill-yourself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And then it got worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Going to Davos -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/421919-trump-to-attend-world-economic-forum-in-switzerland-for-second</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump will travel to the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, next month, the White House said Tuesday, making it the second consecutive year Trump will attend the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON EXODUS:  Another Exec Leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/18/amazon-exec-diego-piacentini-has-left-after-two-year-leave.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diego Piacentini, one of the most senior executives at Amazon who had previously led its international business, has left the company, adding to a string of executive departures over the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENNY MARSHALL DEAD AT 75...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/advance-obit-penny-marshall-dead-686405</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She starred for eight seasons on the ABC ratings hit, created by her late brother Garry Marshall, and directed such films as 'Big,' 'A League of Their Own' and 'Awakenings.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA GIVING $4.8 BILLION TO MEXICO</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0fcda32812024680ad98676379c47233</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — The United States pledged $5.8 billion in aid Tuesday for strengthening government and economic development in Central America, and another $4.8 billion in development aid for southern Mexico. The U.S aid aims to promote better security conditions and job opportunities as part of a regional plan to allow Central Americans to remain in their countries and not have to emigrate. The plan was announced in a joint U.S.-Mexican statement released by the State Department and read aloud by Mexican Foreign Relations Secretary Marcelo Ebrard in the Mexican capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream of augmented humans endures...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181218-dream-augmented-humans-endures-despite-sceptics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dream of augmented humans endures, despite sceptics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA:  Saturn losing rings quicker than expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/18/world/saturn-rings-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturn's rings make it one of the most striking planets in the solar system, but scientists believe they could disappear in less than a 100 million years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Dies After Cosmetic Butt Injection In NYC...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/18/police-woman-from-philadelphia-dies-after-cosmetic-butt-injection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident has been deemed a homicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal K-9 handlers earn more than VP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/k-9-handlers-for-department-of-homeland-security-earned-more-than-vice-president-mike-pence-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outsized overtime pay allowed some Homeland Security employees to outearn top government officials, report finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 dying industries...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/12/18/americas-dying-industries-businesses-losing-most-workers/38693221/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall St. reviewed annual employment data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics from 2008 to 2017 to identify the fastest dying industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery delivery, with no humans drivers, underway...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/256e18799e7a4959bed312ead8a60683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. (AP) — Deliveries from an Arizona grocery store will soon be arriving with no one behind the wheel. A fully autonomous vehicle is about to pilot public roads Tuesday with no back up driver, though it will be monitored by humans in another automobile. After almost a thousand test runs with humans aboard modified Prius vehicles, deliveries will be made Tuesday in Scottsdale, Arizona, using the R1, an automobile with no steering wheel and no seats for humans. The R1, when summoned, will travel within a one-mile radius of the Fry's Food grocery store just east of the Phoenix Zoo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XI DEFENDS COMMUNISM...</title>
      <link>https://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/world/chinas-economy-open-but-party-will-remain-in-control/news-story/ab92349ebe831245f17b3316410cc5b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theaustralian.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have cookies turned off To use this website, cookies must be enabled in your browser. To enable cookies, follow the instructions for your browser below. Facebook App: Open links in External Bro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's secret detention camps...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/central-asians-cry-over-chinas-secret-detention-camps-101732645.html;_ylt=Awr9CW3WJBlcV.IA8ntXNyoA;_ylu=X3oDMTByM3V1YTVuBGNvbG8DZ3ExBHBvcwMzBHZ0aWQDBHNlYwNzcg--</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asyla Alymkulova fights back tears in her home in Kyrgyzstan as she recalls the first time she heard her husband was whisked away to one of the notorious internment camps in neighbouring China's troubled Xinjiang region. Shairbek Doolotkhan, a Chinese-born Muslim and mining executive, had told his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab refugees in sights of Berlin's crime 'clans'...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/arab-refugees-sights-berlins-crime-clans-034423567--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berlin crime gangs of Arab origin have long earned infamy with violence and brazen robberies but now, police warn, they have targeted a new generation of refugees for recruitment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians 'Standing in the Way' of Totalitarian Rule...</title>
      <link>http://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/world/2018/december/christians-standing-in-the-way-of-chinas-xi-jinpings-totalitarian-rule</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since coming to power in 2012, China's leader Xi Jinping has severely cracked down on human rights, religious freedom and freedom of expression. Christians are experiencing some of the worst persecution in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie top choice of progressives in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/bernie-sanders-top-choice-of-progressives-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The progressive wing of the Democratic Party, vying to control the 2020 presidential primaries, wants Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders — by a country mile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited farm animals coming. Will public eat?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Gene-edited-farm-animals-are-coming-Will-the-13472924.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVIS, Calif. - Three cows clomped, single-file, through a chute to line up for sonograms - ultrasound "preg checks" - to reveal if they were expecting calves next summer. "Right now. This is exciting, right this minute," animal geneticist Alison Van Eenennaam said as she waited for a tiny blob of a fetus to materialize on a laptop screen on a recent afternoon at the Beef Barn, part of the University of California at Davis's sprawling agricultural facilities for teaching and research. The cows had been implanted a month and a half earlier with embryos genetically edited to grow and look like males, regardless of their biological gender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves to ban bump stocks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6c1af80fb290472c89fb930e223505af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration moved Tuesday to officially ban bump stocks, which allow semi-automatic weapons to fire rapidly like automatic firearms, and has made them illegal to possess beginning in late March. The devices will be banned under a federal law that prohibits machine guns, according to a senior Justice Department official. Bump stocks became a focal point of the national gun control debate after they were used in October 2017 when a man opened fired from his Las Vegas hotel suite into a crowd at a country music concert below, killing 58 people and injuring hundreds more in the deadliest mass shooting in modern U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Women abused every 30 seconds on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/18/women-are-abused-every-30-seconds-on-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black women are 84 percent more likely to experience abuse than white women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal With New York Attorney General...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/18/politics/trump-foundation-dissolve/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Donald J. Trump Foundation has agreed to dissolve under judicial supervision amid an ongoing lawsuit concerning its finances, according to a document filed Tuesday in Manhattan Supreme Court by the New York state Attorney General's office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY IN DECLINE?</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/17/decline-of-tom-brady-patriots-film-breakdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady and the Patriots have lost two straight games. How much is the quarterback to blame, and is this a sign that the end is near?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Government, Immigration America's 'top problems'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/michael-w-chapman/survey-americas-no-1-problem-government-no-2-problem-immigration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled Trump Foundation agrees to dissolve...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/beta-story-container/Politics/embattled-trump-foundation-agrees-dissolve-agreement-york-ag/story?id=59884847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL FUNDING OFF TABLE</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/white-house-signals-its-backing-down-in-shutdown-dispute-will-find-other-ways-to-fund-border-wall/2018/12/18/159994dc-02d9-11e9-9122-82e98f91ee6f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Sanders: “At the end of the day we don’t want to shut down the government.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Has Third-Highest Suicide Rate...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/media-has-third-highest-suicide-rate-in-the-u-s-cdc-report-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicide rates should concern us all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President orders space command...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/military/trump-plans-to-create-us-space-command-sources-say-20181218/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is expected to sign an executive order, possibly today, creating a U.S. Space Command that will better organize and advance the military's vast operations in space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On TWITTER, Trump comes out swinging in many directions...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/On-Twitter-Trump-comes-out-swinging-in-many-13474522.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump lashed out Tuesday morning at threats from many directions, taking aim at the special counsel's Russia inquiry, the Federal Reserve, social media companies and undocumented immigrants in tweets that spanned more than two hours. Trump's Twitter tirade - which included some false and questionable claims - comes as he faces increasing peril from the investigation of special counsel Robert Mueller and remains in a standoff with Democrats in Congress over funding for his long-promised southern border wall that could prompt a partial government shutdown at midnight Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Final Act as Speaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/ryan-on-track-for-his-final-act-as-speaker-government-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such an exit by Ryan would stand in stark contrast to his predecessor, John Boehner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Space-Launch Day Fizzles as 3 of 4 Missions Scrubbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-18/big-space-launch-day-fizzles-as-three-of-four-missions-scrubbed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk to unveil underground tunnel, transport cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6d24c149b46d4a1da97e3412e60ca93e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Tech entrepreneur Elon Musk is set to unveil an underground transportation tunnel on Tuesday that could move people faster than subways. Musk also plans to show off the autonomous cars that will carry people through the test tunnel, which runs about 2 miles (3.2 kilometers) under the streets of Hawthorne, California, Musk's SpaceX headquarters. He's also planning to unveil elevators he says will bring users' own cars from street level to the tunnel. Tuesday's reveal comes almost two years to the day since Musk announced on Twitter that "traffic is driving me nuts" and he was "going to build a tunnel boring machine and just start digging."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Man-free' feminist music festival found guilty of discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6508263/Swedens-man-free-feminist-music-festival-guilty-discrimination-authorities.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The event, called Statement, was held in Gothenburg, Sweden, in August this year having been billed as 'the world's first major music festival for women, non-binary and transgender only'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Leopard decapitates 3-year-old...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/leopard-kills-decapitates-3-old-india-111014305.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The headless body of a three-year-old boy snatched from his home by a leopard in India was handed over to his parents on Tuesday, wildlife officials said. Wasim Akram was in the kitchen with his mother when the animal snuck inside, pounced on the child and took him deep into the woods, officials said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos on French highways as 'yellow vests' torch toll booths...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181218145115-px79z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PROTESTS/ROADS (PIX):Chaos on French highways as 'yellow vests' torch toll booths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos on French highways as 'yellow vests' torch toll booths...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181218144844-kadx4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE-SPACEX/LAUNCH (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-SpaceX halts U.S. satellite launch for national security mission</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebound?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/18/us-futures-on-tuesday-after-wall-street-rout-a-day-earlier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rebounded Tuesday, recovering some of the steep losses of the prior trading session that sent both the Dow and the S&amp;P 500 tumbling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Tarantino 'scares off' burglars from Hollywood home...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/quentin-tarantino-burglars-home-la-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-film-a8688351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Criminal Case May Be Crumbling, Experts Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/harvey-weinstein-criminal-case-may-be-crumbling-experts-say-1170260 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a key hearing approaches, the disgraced mogul's defense hinges on discrediting accusers with emails and preventing "prior bad act" witnesses — which helped convict Cosby — from speaking: "This is the prosecutor's worst-case scenario."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit Revote? Calls for Second Referendum Grow Louder...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/brexit-revote-calls-for-a-second-referendum-grow-louder-11545139544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two years after Britons voted to leave the European Union, the U.K.’s politicians still can’t agree on what kind of Brexit they want. Now more lawmakers are calling for a do-over, a second referendum that could potentially reverse the results of the first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN NAMED 'JESUS' SMASHES UP CHURCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/748761/jesus-church-window-luke-ripley-monk-st-patricks-roman-catholic-hayling-islands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four back-to-back satellite launches in historic space day...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/18/four-back-to-back-satellite-launches-expected-today-huge-step/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's SpaceX will send a new US spy satellite into orbit today in one of four launches expected to take place within 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police scan faces of London shoppers in controversial trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/uk/446774-facial-recognition-camera-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London’s Metropolitan Police have begun testing facial recognition technology on the capital’s Christmas shoppers, in a move that was attacked by a civil liberties campaigner as an “authoritarian surveillance tool.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mysterious explosions put Phoenix on edge...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/arizona-news/new-mysterious-explosions-puts-north-phoenix-neighborhood-on-edge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More mysterious explosions are putting a north Phoenix neighborhood on edge.&amp;nbsp;FOX 10&amp;#39;s Nicole Garcia reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-Controlled Bionic Limbs...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/17/mind-controlled-bionic-limbs-developed-at-mit-brigham-womens-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "smart limbs" being developed at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology are possible because of the Ewing Amputation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big-screen TV rolls up like poster...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-roll-up-tv-20181218-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 65-inch TVs will retract automatically at the touch of a button like a garage door, a source told Bloomberg. They will sport organic light-emitting diode, or OLED screens that produce crisper images and fold more easily than traditional LCD, or liquid-crystal displays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear that recovered from wildfire burns killed by hunter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cinder-the-bear-wildfire-killed-by-hunter-washington-california-idaho-rich-beausoleil/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cinder the bear, whose recovery received national attention, was found shot to death with her tracking collar cut, a wildlife official said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing: Fiscal sanity...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/421737-missing-fiscal-sanity-in-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modern history shows few examples of deficits this high outside of recession, war or the immediate aftermath of either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin claims Russia's new weapons have no foreign equivalent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0647e2d000964f9f8956d05a570953cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — President Vladimir Putin says Russia's new weapons have no foreign equivalents and will help ensure the country's security for decades to come. Putin, speaking during Tuesday's meeting with the top military brass in Moscow, specifically mentioned the new Kinzhal hypersonic missile and the Avangard hypersonic glide vehicle, saying they have significantly bolstered Russia's military capability. Kinzhal has already been commissioned by the military. Russian Defense Minister Sergei Shoigu said the aircraft carrying missiles have flown 89 patrol missions this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRACLE: Girl's inoperable brain tumor disappears; Doctors can't explain it...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/12/18/miracle-texas-girls-inoperable-brain-cancer-disappears/2346822002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roxli Doss was diagnosed with a deadly brain cancer in June. Now, doctors can't find any trace of it on her MRI scans. Her family calls it a miracle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chance of recession rises to highest level of Trump presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/18/cnbc-fed-survey-chance-of-recession-rises-to-23percent.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Respondents boosted the chance of recession, reduced their support for the president's handling of the economy and lowered their outlook for economic growth and Fed rate hikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As life expectancy falls, West Virginia offers lessons...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f1915b8dafdb462986883142ed2ccac6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, W.Va. (AP) — If you want to understand why U.S. life expectancy is declining, West Virginia is a good place to start. The state is a bellwether of bad health, portending major problems years before they became severe nationally. "It seems that the worst outcomes happen here first," said Dr. Michael Brumage, a West Virginia University public health expert who formerly ran the health department in Charleston. "We're the canary in the coal mine." The drug overdose death rate for all Americans today is where West Virginia's rate was 10 years ago. The nation's suicide rate is where West Virginia's was nearly 20 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good boy! Service dog gets honorary diploma...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7d77b8be4e484c8cb456ef42173c00e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — Whenever Brittany Hawley went to class, her loyal service dog Griffin was there. If she needed her cell phone, Griffin would fetch it. Even when she assisted patients as part of an internship, Griffin was there helping out as well. So it's only fitting that when Hawley was honored for receiving her master's degree in occupational therapy from Clarkson University over the weekend, Griffin was once again at her side — with an honorary diploma of his own. "I pushed for him to graduate from Day One," Hawley said Monday. "He did everything I did."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 2,000 jailed for life since 2016 coup: Turkey state media...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181218-nearly-2000-jailed-life-2016-coup-turkey-state-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 2,000 jailed for life since 2016 coup: Turkey state media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90.5% of plastic not recycled...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/scary-stat-90-5-percent-of-plastic-is-not-recycled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The burgeoning crisis in plastic waste has won the attention of Britain's Royal Statistical Society, which chose 90.5 percent — the proportion of plastic waste that has never been recycled — as its international statistic of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man set for world's first head transplant cancels after falling in love...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/man-set-worlds-first-head-13748350</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disabled Valery Spiridonov, 33, was ready to have his neck severed by Professor Sergio Canavero - dubbed 'Dr Frankenstein' - and his head reattached to a new, healthy body</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic Space Launch Day: Bezos, Musk, GPS Satellite...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/historic-space-launch-day-includes-troubled-lockheed-satellite#gs.9mu3Pz4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Historic Space Launch Day Includes Troubled Lockheed GPS Satellite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Get Used to It America: We're No Longer No. 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/china-as-no-1-economy-to-reap-benefits-that-once-flowed-to-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get Used to It America: Weâ€™re No Longer No. 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn sentencing keystone moment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/421774-flynn-sentencing-marks-keystone-moment-in-mueller-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Flynn, President Trump’s first national security adviser who began cooperating with special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation about a year ago, will be sentenced Tuesday for lying to the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba's Ma, NBA star Yao among 110 honored by Communist Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181218-alibabas-ma-nba-star-yao-among-110-honoured-communist-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alibaba's Ma, NBA star Yao among 110 honoured by Communist Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey still lashing out...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/former-fbi-chief-lashes-trump-republicans-225706154.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI director James Comey lashed out at Donald Trump on Monday for telling "lies" and undermining the rule of law, and urged Republicans to stand up to the president. "The FBI's reputation has as taken a big hit because the president of the United States, with his acolytes,</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
