<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>12 wounded in shooting at South Carolina nightclub... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/faf507c074e0df2ae1f24f54fb12c49f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENVILLE, S.C. (AP) — A shooting at a South Carolina nightclub left at least 12 people in “various conditions” early Sunday, a sheriff's official said. A Greenville County sheriff's deputy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISUNITED STATES</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8490715/Thousands-Americans-gather-Fourth-July-protests-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters in New York City burned an American flag near Trump tower and thousands gathered outside the White House as protests fighting racial inequality and police brutality spark on July 4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep fear and anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/independence-day-marked-division-streets-washington-022034790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators chanting "Black Lives Matter" exchange words with activists waving pro-Trump signs outside a fortified White House: America's Independence Day was marked in Washington on Saturday by confrontation and disunity. As it struggles to contain the coronavirus and reckons with waves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivers speeches in grim monotone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/at-mt-rushmore-and-the-white-house-trump-updates-american-carnage-message-for-2020/ar-BB16kXtQ?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militias flock to Gettysburg...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Militias-flock-to-Gettysburg-to-foil-supposed-15386643.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GETTYSBURG NATIONAL MILITARY PARK, PA. - For weeks, a mysterious figure on social media talked up plans for antifa protesters to converge on this historical site on Independence Day to burn American flags, an event that seemed at times to border on the farcical. "Let's get together and burn flags in protest of thugs and animals in blue," the anonymous person behind a Facebook page called Left Behind USA wrote in mid-June. There would be antifa face paint, the person wrote, and organizers would "be giving away free small flags to children to safely throw into the fire." As word spread, self-proclaimed militias, bikers, skinheads and far-right groups from outside the state issued a call to action, pledging in online videos and posts to come to Gettysburg to protect the Civil War monuments and the nation's flag from desecration. Some said they would bring firearms and use force if necessary. On Saturday afternoon, in the hours before the flag burning was to start, they flooded in by the hundreds - heavily armed and unaware, it seemed, that the mysterious Internet poster was not who the person claimed to be. Biographical details - some from the person's Facebook page and others provided to The Washington Post in a series of messages - did not match official records. An image the person once posted on a profile page was a picture of a man taken by a German photographer for a stock photo service. The episode at Gettysburg is a stark illustration of how shadowy figures on social media have stoked fears about the protests against racial injustice and excessive police force that have swept across the nation since the death of George Floyd in police custody on May 25. Armed vigilantes lined the streets of small Idaho towns last month after false claims circulated online about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals in at least two Texas counties reach full capacity...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/505889-texas-hits-new-record-of-coronavirus-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas reported 8,258 new coronavirus cases on Saturday, setting a record for the second time this week and bringing its total number</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE 2020</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/kanye-west-presidential-bid-july-4th-donald-trump-elon-musk-joe-biden-kim-kardashian-1202977608/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian West has spent a fair amount of time at the White House the past few years, but now it looks likes she is seriously thinking about moving into the ultimate reality show as First Lady…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: Protesters Pull Down City's Columbus Statue, Toss It Into Harbor...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/07/04/video-shows-baltimore-protesters-tear-down-columbus-statue-throw-it-into-harbor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video posted on social media Saturday shows protesters pulling down Baltimore's statue of Christopher Columbus and throwing it into the Inner Harbor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enemy within...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95698f178a15e56a0f4e286708d06668</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On a day meant for unity and celebration, President Donald Trump vowed to “safeguard our values” from enemies within — leftists, looters, agitators, he said — in a Fourth of July...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHE'S GOING TO TALK'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1077230/ghislaine-maxwell-knows-things-that-implicate-prince-andrew/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell knows things that implicate Prince Andrew and will be willing to name names as she is “fighting for her freedom”, two Jeffrey Epstein experts have claimed. John Connol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK VOWS SUPPORT</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1087067/kanye-west-running-president-elon-musk-full-support/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West announced to his fans on the Fourth of July that he plans on “running for president of the United States.” Tesla CEO and Kanye’s friend, Elon Musk, quickly offered up his “full support” …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.spin.com/2015/09/donald-trump-kanye-west-presidency-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger mauls keeper to death at Zurich zoo in front of horrified visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/tiger-mauls-keeper-death-zurich-22303070</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 55-year-old woman died as a result of her injuries after the attack, zoo bosses confirmed. It is not yet known why she and the Siberian tiger were in the enclosure at the same time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW:  WOKE DAUGHTER SLAMS TRUMP, PARENTS ON SOCIALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8489983/Kellyanne-Conways-daughter-15-slams-parents-blocking-freedom-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claudia Conway, 15, became a viral star this week for her anti-Trump videos on TikTok and now claims her parents Kellyanne and George are trying to stop her from speaking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full speed ahead on race and culture wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Analysis-Trump-s-push-to-amplify-racism-unnerves-15386161.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- President Donald Trump's unyielding push to preserve Confederate symbols and the legacy of white domination, crystallized by his harsh denunciation of the racial justice movement Friday night at Mount Rushmore, has unnerved Republicans who have long enabled him but now fear losing power and forever associating their party with his racial animus.  Although amplifying racism and stoking culture wars have been mainstays of Trump's public identity for decades, they have been particularly pronounced this summer as the presidenthas reacted to the national reckoning over systemic discrimination by seeking to weaponize the anger and resentment of some white Americans for his own political gain.  Trump has left little doubt through his utterances the past few weeks that he sees himself not only as the Republican standard-bearer, but as leader of a modern grievance movement animated by civic strife and marked by calls for "white power," the phrase chanted by one of his supporters in a video the president shared last weekend on Twitter. He later deleted the video but did not disavow its message.  Trump put his strategy to resuscitate his troubled reelection campaign by galvanizing white supporters on display Friday night under the chiseled granite gaze of four past presidents memorialized in the Black Hills of South Dakota. He celebrated Independence Day with a dystopian speech in which he excoriated racial justice protesters as "evil" representatives of a "new far-left fascism" whose ultimate goal is "the end of America."  "Our nation is witnessing a merciless campaign to wipe out our history, defame our heroes, erase our values, and indoctrinate our children," Trump said to boos from a packed crowd of supporters. "Angry mobs are trying to tear down statues of our Founders, deface our most sacred memorials, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick calls 4th Of July a 'celebration of white supremacy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8490247/Colin-Kaepernick-calls-Independence-Day-celebration-white-supremacy-REJECTS-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaepernick took to Twitter to share the powerful rejection, along with a video of actor James Earl Jones reciting Frederick Douglass's renowned speech 'What to the Slave Is the 4th of July?'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET VIDEOS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8490099/She-definitely-danger-Friends-Ghislaine-Maxwell-fear-safety-talks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell's friends have spoken out ahead of her transfer to a Manhattan jail, saying that they are concerned the she might take her own life, or even be killed to silence her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus floats in air as aerosol...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-ignores-risk-coronavirus-floats-120014485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 researchers worldwide sign an open letter saying current guidance ignores evidence that the coronavirus readily spreads on microscopic particles known as aerosols that can hang in the air for long periods and float dozens of feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FARRAKHAN:  Fauci wants vaccine to depopulate Earth...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/07/04/louis-farrakhan-fauci-bill-gates-vaccine-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis Farrakhan accused Dr. Anthony Fauci and Bill Gates of trying to &amp;quot;depopulate the Earth&amp;quot; through the development of vaccines for coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emails Tell the Inside Story of How the NATIONAL ENQUIRER Got  Bezos Nudes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/emails-tell-the-inside-story-of-how-the-enquirer-got-jeff-bezos-nudes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* At least, they tell the Enquirer’s side of the story. But there are all kinds of inconsistencies in the tabloid’s account, drawn from emails, text messages, and sworn statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In West Texas, Lingering Distrust in Public Health Measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/04/us/coronavirus-texas-lubbock.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early in the pandemic, much of rural Texas had low case counts and few worries. Now, conservative areas are seeing a surge in cases, but distrust in government mandates endure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:   I pledge to rebuild America's foundation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/trump-erodes-america-s-foundation-fourth-july-i-pledge-rebuild-ncna1232887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has always been a push and a pull between our founding ideals and the forces of inequality. But today is a celebration of our persistent march toward greater justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Reopening Is Warning Sign for Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/the-nba-e2-80-99s-reopening-is-a-warning-sign-for-the-us-economy/ar-BB16ktX1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Population Growth Has Been Driven Exclusively by Minorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-population-growth-has-been-driven-exclusively-by-minorities/ar-BB16kTl6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$10 Trillion Rally Hinges on Earnings Nobody Has Clue About...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/a-2410-trillion-rally-hinges-on-earnings-nobody-has-a-clue-about/ar-BB16kqB8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE KNOWS TOO MUCH!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8488471/New-Hampshire-county-jail-Ghislaine-Maxwell-is.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spencer Kuvin told DailyMail.com in an exclusive interview that Maxwell 'knows too much' and that powerful people may want to silence her even as she is locked up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearful and Frugal: Covid Wreaks Havoc on Psyche...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Fearful-and-frugal-Coronavirus-wreaks-havoc-on-15386037.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the U.S. reopens, Americans aren't much interested in going out and spending.  A survey of 2,200 U.S. adults shows how Covid-19 has dramatically changed behavior in the world's biggest economy, potentially for the long haul. The data flashes warning signs for the recovery, showing waning interest in public events and material things, like appliances and clothes, and a new austerity, expressed through pantry stockpiling and delayed big-ticket purchases.  This foreshadows an era of fear and frugality that could push a full economic rebound-one that Washington and Wall Street are banking on-out of reach. The data also raises doubts about how much rising consumer confidence will translate into spending, on which the economy heavily relies. And this survey, polled last weekend, doesn't account for the past week when a spike in cases stalled reopenings in several states, potentially deepening the pandemic's behavioral impact.  "People are generally expressing that they'll do certain things less, or at home, on their own," said Victoria Sakal, managing director of brand intelligence at Morning Consult, Bloomberg News's partner on the survey taken the last weekend of June. "There's also a health component to how safe, comfortable and protected people feel."  Americans-often stereotyped around the world as confident to the point of arrogance-have developed a fear of enclosed retail spaces. While about three-quarters of U.S. adults feel OK shopping inside grocery stores or small businesses, more than half don't feel safe inside a shopping center, the data show. This is only adding to the woes of malls.  And that new preference for smaller retailers appears to have staying power: Even once the pandemic ends, nearly 30% of Americans say they plan to buy more from small businesses than they did before the virus.  "Small businesses...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen caught at NYC restaurant -- and it could land him back in prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/03/michael-cohen-eating-at-nyc-restaurant-could-land-him-back-in-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen could soon be back to chowing down in a prison cafeteria. The recently sprung jailbird was caught by The Post dining out on Manhattan’s Upper East Side — and the meal may …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Turning Point In Nation's History?</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/03/july-4th-independence-day-celebration-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A discussion of July 4th with Louise Stevenson, professor of History and American Studies at Franklin &amp; Marshall College.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PEAK:  Florida cases rise by record 11,458 on Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704142842-m73rh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (PIX):Florida sees coronavirus cases spike to new daily record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57,683  cases single day in USA...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-07-covid-cases-hours-tracker.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US notched 57,683 COVID-19 cases in 24 hours Friday, a tally by Johns Hopkins University showed, the third consecutive day with record numbers of new infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUICIDE' WATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1084647/epstein-lawyer-maxwell-die-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAWYER for the victims of Jeffrey Epstein believes Ghislaine Maxwell will also die in prison because she “knows too much.” Epstein’s alleged pimp was arrested by the FBI on Thursday on six …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom vows crackdown on scofflaws. Will law enforcement cooperate?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-vows-crackdown-coronavirus-scofflaws-120059900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom again Wednesday threatened more enforcement for businesses that fail to follow coronavirus guidance, but how it would work remains unclear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wears maks made of gold to ward off virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/indian-man-wears-gold-face-mask-ward-off-134617710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indian man said he paid about $4,000 for a bespoke gold face mask to protect him from the coronavirus raging in the country. The precious metal covering weighs 60 grams (two ounces) and took craftsmen eight days to make, said businessman Shankar Kurhade, from the western city of Pune. "I am</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACK IN:  Spain quarantines 200,000...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britain-eases-virus-quarantine-us-under-siege-132441661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain put 200,000 people back in confinement and England reopened its beloved pubs on Saturday as Europe stuttered its way out of lockdown while the United States braced for large crowds hitting the streets to celebrate Independence Day. The death toll in Russia surpassed 10,000 and Brazil's right-wing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro fans applaud his maverick response despite more than 63,000 deaths in Brazil... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-fans-applaud-maverick-virus-response-013322991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the number of dead from coronavirus shot up in Brazil, the popularity of far right President Jair Bolsonaro has remained unchanged. For his supporters, the president has done nothing wrong despite more than 63,000 deaths and 1.5 million infections. Bolsonaro originally dismissed the coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia locks down high-rise apartments...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australia-locks-down-high-rise-apartments-virus-cases-100139655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of residents in several high-rise apartments in Melbourne went into lockdown for at least five days Saturday, as officials struggle to control a virus outbreak in Australia's second biggest city. Hundreds of police were deployed to enforce the lockdown of nine public housing towers, as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PEAK:  Florida cases rise by record 11,458 on Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704134911-59b8w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FLORIDA (URGENT):Florida coronavirus cases rise by record 11,458 on Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire flares at Iranian power plant, latest in series of incidents...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704130210-qbsd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-FIRE/:Fire flares at Iranian power plant, latest in series of incidents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris prepares for virtual fashion week...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704101435-e7ikl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FASHION-PARIS/HAUTE COUTURE-PREVIEW (PIX, TV):With no paparazzis or parties, Paris prepares for virtual fashion week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pubs open, gyms shut: England's health dilemma... </title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-07-pubs-gyms-england-health-dilemma.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is raining hard but Bradley, a fitness instructor, and four of his gym rats are sweating profusely while alternating between squats and abdominal exercises in a London park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57,683  cases single day in USA...</title>
      <link>https://cms.trtworld.com/life/us-marks-record-57-683-new-cases-in-24-hours-latest-updates-37850</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cms.trtworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global coronavirus pandemic has infected more than 11.1 million people and claimed over 528,000 lives. Here are updates for July 4:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independence Day in a land of confusion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d70ce42ae5da13ef66be501df5a8be01</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the worst of times. It was the weirdest of times. It was a season of sickness and shouting, of defiance and tension, of industrial-strength falsehood and spin. It was a moment of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French government ministers investigated over virus crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b0cffb6249302a0adcde84eafb540c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A special French court ordered an investigation Friday of three current or former government ministers over their handling of the coronavirus crisis. COVID-19 patients, doctors,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
