<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'AQUAMAN' Will Cross $250 Million Without US Release...</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/weekend-box-office-aquaman-crosses-260m-overseas-1169835</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The superhero pic opens Dec. 21 in North America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Vending Machines Dispense Emergency Contraception...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/to-expand-access-to-emergency-contraception-some-colleges-try-vending-machines-11544961601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universities are installing vending machines where students can purchase emergency contraception, an effort to remove barriers to and anxiety surrounding products like Plan B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Hospitality Comes to Hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/hotel-style-hospitality-comes-to-hospitals-11544968800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As hospitals face greater competition amid broader shifts to value-based care, some New York facilities are putting a little hotel experience into the health-care setting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Ruling poses new problems for Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/16/judge-reed-oconnors-obamacare-ruling-poses-new-pro/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans, still stinging from their loss of the House in the midterm elections, are facing a fresh political quandary after U.S. District Judge Reed O’Connor said the entire 2010 health law was invalid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porch pirates run rampant this holiday season...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2018/12/14/porch-pirates-package-theft-climb-more-americans-shop-online/2218910002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Package theft is a growing problem as more Americans buy goods online and have them delivered to their homes. And the solutions aren't that great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago BLACKHAWKS mascot fights with fan...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nhl/blackhawks/2018/12/15/blackhawks-mascot-tommy-hawk-fights-fan-viral-video/2327520002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video of Blackhawks mascot Tommy Hawk fighting a fan was caused by an attack on the mascot, police tell the Chicago Sun-Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May slams Tony Blair in blistering attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7989416/theresa-may-slams-meddler-tony-blair-brexit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May launched a blistering attack on Brexit saboteur Tony Blair. She accused the former Labour PM of insulting the British people with his shifty attempts to thwart the referendum result. An…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients Blame Breast Implants For Making Them Ill...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/where-women-turn-when-doctors-dont-believe-breast-implants-are-making-them-ill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They think their implants are destroying their health and are frustrated that many doctors don’t agree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY actor arrested in child predator sting...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/nation-world/2018/12/15/disney-actor-stoney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York • Disney Channel actor Stoney Westmoreland has been fired after he was arrested in Salt Lake City for allegedly attempting to have a sexual relationship with an online acquaintance he believed was 13 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$150,000 Treehouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/realestate/article/Co2-treehouse-pinecone-for-sale-airbnb-13464389.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An extraordinary treehouse with 64 diamond-shaped windows forming an 11,000-pound pinecone that dangles high in the trees is on the market for $150,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey says Trump working on extraditing wanted cleric...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-us-gulen/turkey-says-trump-working-on-extraditing-wanted-cleric-gulen-idUSKBN1OF0BM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump has told his Turkish counterpart Tayyip Erdogan that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran blogger held on 'security charges' dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-rights-blogger/iran-confirms-death-of-blogger-held-on-security-charges-idUSKBN1OF0JO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian authorities have confirmed the death of a social media activist jailed o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN:  Rap should be controlled in Russia, not banned...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/putin-says-rap-should-be-controlled-russia-not-banned-n948471</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian president's comments come amid a crackdown on contemporary music that has evoked Soviet-era censorship of the arts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch build artificial islands to bring wildlife back...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181216-dutch-build-artificial-islands-bring-wildlife-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch build artificial islands to bring wildlife back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Rourke marvels at Beto-mania...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2018/12/16/orourke-marvels-beto-mania-conceding-great-question-whether-ready-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON--TMZ trails him around the capital. Fans still check his Facebook page to see if he's going live again anytime soon. Democratic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Popularity Slides Despite Concessions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-16/macron-s-popularity-slides-despite-yellow-vest-concessions-jdd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS bankruptcy court OKs $25 million in bonuses for top execs...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/421565-sears-gets-approval-to-pay-253-million-in-bonuses-to-top-execs-after-filing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. bankruptcy court on Friday reportedly approved Sears’s request to pay as much as $25.3 million in bonuses to the company’s top executives and high-ranking employees, just months after the company filed for bankruptcy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Damascus prepares for Christmas without mortar fire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/damascus-prepares-christmas-without-mortar-fire-091724245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas decorations are going up for the first time in years in a Damascus neighborhood that was a frontline in Syria's war until government forces wiped out the last rebel enclaves in the capital earlier this year. "Christmas preparations this year are more than excellent. Abbasiyeen Square</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frogs, fish, birds die in English zoo fire...</title>
      <link>http://www.wtoc.com/2018/12/16/frogs-fish-small-birds-die-english-zoo-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtoc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chester Zoo says insects, frogs, fish and small birds perished in a fire that broke out in an enclosure devoted to exotic tropical habitats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER STILL WANTS TRUMP INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-special-counsel-is-fighting-a-witness-in-court-who-is-it/ar-BBR0uoL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN Galactic May or MAY NOT Have Gone to Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2018-12-15/virgin-galactic-s-spaceshiptwo-may-or-may-not-have-gone-to-space</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Leads Iowa Caucus Poll...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-16/biden-leads-sanders-o-rourke-in-iowa-democratic-caucus-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Concessions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-15/police-make-arrests-in-paris-ahead-of-new-yellow-vest-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too old?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/adc92878ae0044868176760aff44e3cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he considers running for president, Joe Biden is talking with friends and longtime supporters about whether, at 76, he's too old to seek the White House, according to several sources who have spoken with the former Democratic vice president. The discussions suggest Biden is aware that his age may be the biggest hurdle to launching another bid for the Democratic presidential nomination, especially in an era when many in the party yearn for a new generation of leadership. He would be the oldest person to ever be elected president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outraged Dems vow to challenge court ruling that kills Obamacare...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-judge-rules-obamacare-unconstitutional-democrats-vow-appeal-102729204.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US District Judge Reed O'Connor ruled late Friday that the health insurance reform, officially known as the Affordable Care Act (ACA), is unconstitutional. The White House said it expects the ruling to be appealed to the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visits Arlington...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-criticized-skipping-earlier-visits-travels-cemetery-204802809.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eleven die after eating 'toxic' rice at temple...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/eleven-die-eating-toxic-rice-indian-temple-045559194--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven people have died after eating rice that had likely been contaminated with a toxic substance at a Hindu temple ceremony, a health official said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens to dominate third year in office...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/12/15/trumps-legal-quandaries-multiply/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every organization he has led in the past 10 years is under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trucker saves dogs thrown from vehicle on highway...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dedbdfa83ab14d89b68b24f94a214a1b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A pair of beagle mixes are on the mend after authorities say someone threw them out of a moving vehicle on a snowy New York highway. The dogs were rescued by a passing trucker, but one was so badly mangled that a front leg had to be amputated. New York State Police on Saturday asked for the public's help in finding the suspect or suspects in the incident Wednesday morning on Interstate 81 near Whitney Point, about 16 miles (26 kilometers) north of Binghamton. So far, they said, they have no leads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost every part of Trump's life under investigation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d6361fdf19846cb9eb020d9c6fbfa5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Investigations now entangle Donald Trump's White House, campaign, transition, inauguration, charity and business. For Trump, the political, the personal and the deeply personal are all under examination. Less than two years into Trump's presidency, his business associates, political advisers and family members are being probed, along with the practices of his late father. On Saturday, Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke became the fourth Cabinet member to leave under an ethical cloud, having sparked 17 investigations into his actions on the job, by one watchdog's count.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
