<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Should cars be banned in downtown LA?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-02-16/los-angeles-ban-cars-broadway-downtown-streetcar-pedestrian-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Councilman Jose Huizar's idea is approved, Broadway would be the first major street in Los Angeles to go car free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athletes killing themselves and schools fear their players could be next...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/in-depth/sports/columnists/jeff-seidel/2020/02/16/student-athlete-suicide-michigan-football-zachary-winston/4654919002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everybody knows it's a problem. Can it be fixed?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bansky's Valentine's Day mural vandalized...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9395357a334dc928bf39bd50df2cb74e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The family who owns a house in southwest England where an artwork from Banksy appeared in time for Valentine's Day has covered the mural after it was defaced. Temporary fencing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wall claim beyond 'redemption'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/850cf00b403e230809f9d07e2a0a9c7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On the eve of the New Hampshire primary, President Donald Trump told a rally that people who are in the United States illegally are paying for his Mexico border wall. It was the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl beats trans track star in state championship...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/16/chelsea-mitchell-beats-terry-miller-transgender-tr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chelsea Mitchell, of Canton High School, won the Class S 55-meter dash title on Friday night with a time of 7.18 seconds, edging Terry Miller of Bloomfield High School.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters rally against planned quarantine centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health-hongkong-protests-idUKKBN20A08N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of demonstrators rallied for a second day in Hong Kong on Sunday to pro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Candidate Built an Empire of Influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/bloombergs-billions-how-the-candidate-built-an-empire-of-influence/ar-BB101RuJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt builds border wall with Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://www.al-monitor.com/pulse/originals/2020/02/egypt-builds-new-barrier-to-boost-border-security-gaza-strip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al-monitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the measures Egyptian authorities have taken to boost border security, including the construction of a border wall, an Egyptian security delegation conducted a field inspection along the Egypt-Gaza border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway's 'JAGGED LITTLE PILL' evacuated after pepper-spray incident...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/15/broadway-showing-of-jagged-little-pill-evacuated-after-pepper-spray-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was nothing ironic about this Broadway mishap. The Broadhurst Theatre on West 44th Street was evacuated during the second act of the Alanis Morissette-inspired “Jagged Little Pill” Saturday, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Tame Virus, Mao-Style Social Control Blankets China...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/15/to-tame-coronavirus-mao-style-social-control-blankets-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHANGHAI — China has flooded cities and villages with battalions of neighborhood busybodies, uniformed volunteers and Communist Party representatives to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>69,000+ infected globally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/142253f88e3f0d2fca7607ae44121bea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A viral outbreak that began in China has infected more than 69,000 people globally. The World Health Organization has named the illness COVID-19, referring to its origin late last year and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Forgers Get True Believers to Buy Fakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/eliseo-gil-trial-highlights-how-forgers-prey-on-true-believers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;History is full of examples of knockoffs that exploited religious or political agendas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF stops Hamas 'honeypots' from trapping soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/IDF-foils-Hamas-operation-targeting-soldiers-Operation-Rebound-617744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of "Operation Rebound," the IDF has foiled the third such Hamas network foiled in three years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US finally evacuating Americans from cruise ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/16/asia/coronavirus-outbreak-diamond-cruise-us-evacuation-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US plan to evacuate Americans and their families from the Diamond Princess cruise ship appears, on its face, to be the case of a powerful government coming to the aide of its most vulnerable citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman accused posed as photographer to drug moms, steal babies...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/15/woman-accused-of-posing-as-photographer-to-drug-moms-steal-babies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman posing as an amateur photographer allegedly fed a Washington state mom a “drugged” cupcake in a sick attempt to sedate her and steal her baby, officials said this week. The unsu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake orgy prompts closure of Florida park...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/snake-orgy-prompts-partial-closure-florida-city-park-071644758.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A city in Florida closed off part of a park after residents spotted dozens of snakes which had apparently gathered for their annual coupling. "It appears they have congregated for mating," the City of Lakeland Parks and Recreation Department said on Facebook with a photo of one of the serpents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested over sex tape that sank ally of France's Macron...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/woman-arrested-over-sex-tape-sank-ally-frances-105045441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police have arrested the girlfriend of a Russian activist who released a sex video of a prominent ally of French President Emmanuel Macron, prosecutors said on Sunday. Pyotr Pavlensky's girlfriend was arrested on Saturday evening on charges of invasion of privacy and publishing images of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi's early involvement in virus outbreak raises questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/194c2fc481010f210de218dd9e9901d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A recent speech by Chinese President Xi Jinping that has been published by state media indicates for the first time that he was leading the response to a new virus outbreak from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHE WANTS BACK IN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/bloomberg-campaign-downplays-report-he-is-considering-hillary-clinton-for-vp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Mike Bloomberg’s presidential campaign on Saturday downplayed a report that he is considering 2016 Democratic nominee Hillary Clinton as his pick for vice president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr's internal reviews and re-investigations feed resentment, suspicion inside Justice Department...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Barr-s-internal-reviews-and-re-investigations-15059763.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Justice Department in the Trump era has repeatedly tasked U.S. attorneys from far-flung offices to parachute into politically explosive cases in Washington, raising concerns among current and former officials that agency leaders are trying to please the president by reviewing and reinvestigating cases in which he is personally or politically invested.  After a tumultuous week for federal law enforcement in which Attorney General William Barr declared he could not do his job if the president kept tweeting about criminal cases, and officials revealed they had dropped one politically charged case while adding new prosecutors to others, several current and former officials expressed alarm at what they characterized as a troubling pattern.  "The power to investigate is the power to destroy," said Gregory Brower, a former U.S. attorney and former senior FBI official. The current approach to sensitive cases, he said, "gives the appearance of politics coming into play whenever the president has a perceived political enemy. . . . The ability to simply point to a pending investigation against a person can have devastating effects on that person and can have a potential political benefit to the person orchestrating the investigation."  On Friday, prosecutors said they would no longer pursue a criminal case against Andrew McCabe, the former acting FBI director who has long been a target of President Donald Trump's vitriol.  The decision infuriated the president, according to a senior White House official, who like others spoke on the condition of anonymity to detail internal discussions. Trump ranted privately to associates about the announcement, telling one he's always known McCabe was a "bad guy."  While the president is angry over the decision not to charge McCabe with lying to investigators during a leak...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The implausible ticket?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/15/michael-bloomberg-hillary-clinton-vp-115407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg’s campaign downplayed the report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Harvey Weinstein's fate heads to jurors, who will they believe?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/as-harvey-weinsteins-fate-heads-to-jurors-who-will-they-believe/ar-BB102d3T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXCLUSIVE:  BLOOMBERG CONSIDERS HILLARY RUNNING MATE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/15/bloomberg-is-considering-hillary-clinton-as-his-running-mate-says-matt-drudge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate Mike Bloomberg is considering Hilary Clinton as a vice presidential running mate after positive internal polling about the potential pairing, the Drudge Report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton could get her revenge against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/15/as-bloombergs-vp-hillary-clinton-could-get-revenge-against-trump-goodwin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Watch for smoke signals from Chappaqua,” a Democratic friend said recently. “She wants back in.” She — there is only one political she — might be getting what she wants. The report that Hillary Cl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE BANS NICK FUENTES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/youtube-bans-popular-conservative-commentator-nick-fuentes-for-hate-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comes after Conservative Inc. called for his de-platforming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juror 1261 in Roger Stone's case: Was justice undone?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/483210-juror-1261-in-roger-stones-case-was-justice-undone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is serious question as to whether the conviction itself should be reevaluated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like Something Out Of Book Of Exodus': Locust Armies Devouring Farms In  30 Seconds...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/like-something-out-of-the-book-of-exodus-locust-armies-are-devouring-entire-farms-in-kenya-in-as-little-as-30-seconds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Locust armies numbering in the billions are absolutely ravaging large portions of eastern Africa and vast stretches of the Middle East.  We are being told that these locust armies "are unprecedented in size and scope", which means that we have never seen anything like this before.  And as you will s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nimitz Navy crew 'ordered to stay quiet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/third-navy-crew-saw-2004-21491602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nimitz UFO encounter in November 2004 is one of the most famous sightings in history. Now, a previously-unknown witness has come forward to say he saw it "form" in front of his Navy craft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem rivals sharpen attacks as Bloomberg rises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/483185-democratic-rivals-sharpen-attacks-as-bloomberg-rises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House hopefuls are unloading on Mike Bloomberg in an effort to draw him into the fray</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers to sweep entire sky for signs of extraterrestrial life...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/feb/15/astronomers-to-sweep-entire-sky-for-signs-of-extraterrestrial-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project is collaboration between privately-funded firm and New Mexico observatory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>change his official residence from New York to homes he owns in Colorado or Florida</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/407672/bloomberg-hillary-clinton-running-mate-trump-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIKE Bloomberg is thinking about making Hillary Clinton his running mate as he runs for president, according to a new report. “Polling found the Bloomberg-Clinton combination would be a formi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump supporter's defense of Mike...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/482796-a-trump-supporters-defense-of-michael-bloomberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Trump and Bloomberg rip each other for campaign advantage, tens of millions of desperately poor Americans need help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources close to Bloomberg campaign tell DRUDGE REPORT that candidate is considering Hillary Clinton as running mate</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/15/bloomberg-reportedly-considering-hillary-clinton-as-his-running-mate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg’s internal polling has found the combo “would be a formidable force,” campaign sources told the Drudge Report Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka in Abu Dhabi ahead of women's conference...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff0b1ea536afd8056d72dee415f5dedd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABU DHABI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Ivanka Trump, daughter of U.S. President Donald Trump, arrived in the United Arab Emirates on Saturday, where she met with women entrepreneurs and was to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>change his official residence from New York to homes he owns in Colorado or Florida</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/drudge-report-bloomberg-considering-hillary-clinton-for-running-mate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg is considering Hillary Clinton as a running mate, according to the Drudge Report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEEP CRACKS EMERGE IN BIDEN FIREWALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/15/joe-biden-south-carolina-firewall-114862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One South Carolina lawmaker says she switched allegiances after warning several Biden staffers that their grassroots approach was outdated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showdowns at political conventions are rare. Dems may get one...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Showdowns-at-political-conventions-are-rare-15058979.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speculation about a brokered, deadlocked or contested political conventionsurfaceseveryfouryears with the regularity of Brigadoon rising from the mist. Back in 1980, self-styled Democratic brokers called themselves the "wait in the weeds gang," ready to identify a compromise candidate between President Jimmy Carter and Sen. Ted Kennedy. Such predictions show up in virtually every cycle when there's even a hint of the possibility - usually early on, when a platoon of still-viable candidates suggests that a divided primary contest will fail to produce a winner. Just as frequent are the skeptical dismissals (I wrote one myself a dozen years ago) that note, with metronomic regularity, that there aren't any more brokers: no more Jake Arveys, Ed Flynns, Mark Hannas or Harry Daughertys to trade delegates like so many poker chips.  But this could be the year it really does happen. The Democrats may arrive in Milwaukee in July with no candidate having locked down enough delegates to win the nomination on the first vote. Three factors are present, even dominant, in the Democratic fight that are often absent: a genuine ideological split; four candidates (and possibly more) with enough money to wage long campaigns; and the long-standing Democratic method of allocating delegates proportionally, which can drag out primaries even if the outcome is clear months before the convention - which it certainly isn't today.  Conventions were not always the slick infomercials they've become in recent years, and the shift to primaries instead of smoke-filled rooms after the chaotic 1968 Democratic convention didn't immediately end the prospect of floor fights. In 1972, George McGovern beat back an attempt to deny him a first-ballot victory by contesting his right to all the delegates from California's winner-take-all primary. (He'd won 43.5...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources close to Bloomberg campaign tell DRUDGE REPORT that candidate is considering Hillary Clinton as running mate</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8007521/Mike-Bloomberg-wants-Hillary-Clinton-running-mate-say-sources.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bloomberg is considering making Hillary Clinton his running mate, a source close to his campaign has told Drudge Report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A woman was killed and skinned. Now Mexico is up in arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-woman-was-killed-and-skinned-Now-Mexico-is-up-15057813.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - One morning this week, Mexico City police received a radio call about an "aggression against a woman." Arriving at the scene - an apartment in a lower-middle-class neighborhood - they discovered a horror: the body of a 25-year-old who had been stabbed to death, cut up and partially skinned.  The killing of Ingrid Escamilla last weekend has gripped the nation and ignited a fresh round of protests over Mexico's high levels of violence against women.  On Friday, demonstrators hurled paint at the entrance to the National Palace to protest Escamilla's death and other "femicides" - murders of women because of their gender. Additional protests were planned for Friday evening and Saturday.  Escamilla's case shocked Mexicans not only because her death was so gruesome but because it was so publicized. Photos of her mutilated body were leaked to two tabloids. One of them, Pasala, headlined a photo spread, "It was Cupid's fault."  Mexicans struck back on social media, insisting that Escamilla should be memorialized not by such ghastly photos but instead by beautiful images. Thousands of people posted or shared pictures of flowers, rainbows and animals, using hashtags such as #IngridEscamilla and #IngridFotos.  "You deserve to be remembered for who you were, not what they did to you," said Twitter user @itsamonbebe, who posted nature pictures.  Prominent figures including the writer Valeria Luiselli and Mexico's ambassador to Washington, Martha Bárcena, joined the campaign.  Escamilla's husband confessed to the crime, according to media reports. The city's public security department confirmed his arrest.  Mexicans have voiced increasing frustration with violence against women. The country recorded more than 1,000 deaths classified as femicides last year, part of a historic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Daytona 500 appearance could include lap in presidential limo...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/sports/trump-daytona-500-nascar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is the latest of several sitting presidents to attend races at Daytona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: Julia Louis-Dreyfus and Will Ferrell's 'DOWNHILL' Worse Than Stale Popcorn...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/02/downhill-review-will-ferrell-julia-louis-dreyfus-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It doesn’t have a clue about what kind of movie it wants to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi urges more policing as virus toll rises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chinas-xi-urges-more-policing-virus-toll-rises-115750208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping has called for tightened control over online discussion and increased policing to ensure "positive energy" and social stability, state media said Saturday, as the country struggles to contain the deadly new coronavirus. Censors had allowed some online criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia emerges as South progressive leader under Dems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/55cdfed8d8f1bf661bc94f860a522fd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — In a state once synonymous with the Old South, Democrats are using their newfound legislative control to refashion Virginia as the region's progressive leader on racial,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions complicate efforts to contain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/137ebbee2968d17097e685f3141ad632</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Reports one day suggest the respiratory outbreak in China might be slowing, the next brings word of thousands more cases. Even the experts have whiplash in trying to determine if...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
