<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside Andrew Yang's Next Move...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article237624999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Mandelblit-reportedly-will-announce-Netanyahu-indictment-today-608541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avichai Mandelblit and his team had been working on drafting the indictments to charge Netanyahu before a third election would begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Buttigieg holds 7-point lead in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/471505-poll-buttigieg-holds-7-point-lead-in-iowa-followed-by-warren-and-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg has a 7-point lead over his Democratic presidential rivals in Iowa, marking the third consecutive poll to show him leading in the Hawkeye State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli Prime minister charged with bribery, fraud, breach of trust...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26414b844f5c4d4eb0e7a9a99f9f70de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel’s attorney general on Thursday formally charged Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in a series of corruption cases, throwing the country’s paralyzed political system into...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OY VEY!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191121170000-t5eia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-NETANYAHU/ (WRAPUP 1, TV, PIX):WRAPUP 1-Netanyahu charged in corruption cases, deepening Israeli political disarray</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Witch-hunt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/israeli-pm-netanyahu-indicted-charges-bribery-fraud-breach-trust-n1084831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli prime minister has denied any wrongdoing and said he is the victim of a politically orchestrated "witch hunt."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standing ovation...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/archives/news/clint-eastwood-richard-jewell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clint Eastwood was greeted with a standing ovation Thursday night as he introduced his new film "Richard Jewell," a searing cautionary tale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposes 'Media Lynching'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/richard-jewell-review-1256384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clint Eastwood's latest tells the true story of a security guard initially celebrated as a hero for saving lives in the bombing of the 1996 Summer Olympics, then vilified when the press reported he was a suspect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestors gather in Berkeley for Ann Coulter appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=14020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things got a little chaotic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's attorney general to announce decision on Netanyahu indictment... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-netanyahu-indictment/israels-attorney-general-to-announce-decision-on-netanyahu-indictment-idUSKBN1XV1T3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's attorney general said he would announce later on Thursday his deci...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even animal adolescence filled with teen drama, peer pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Even-animal-adolescence-is-filled-with-teen-drama-14851975.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are no reported sightings of surly teenage elephants reluctantly sitting down at the family dinner table, trusty ear buds in place, occasionally trumpeting monosyllabic answers.  But adolescent elephants do exhibit other behaviors many parents of human teens would recognize, said Cynthia Moss, a researcher who has studied and written books about elephants in Kenya's Amboseli National Park for nearly five decades.  "They're naive, they have a lot to learn and they make mistakes," Moss said.  This is particularly true for males, she explained: They raid crops. They get speared. They die. "It's just like young human males who drive too fast," she said, "and the insurance companies know very well to make them pay higher insurance rates."  These sorts of low-judgment, high-risk actions, and many other youthful traits that traverse species, are explored in a recent book, "Wildhood: The Epic Journey From Adolescence to Adulthood in Humans and Other Animals" by Barbara Natterson-Horowitz, a Harvard evolutionary biologist, and Kathryn Bowers, a science journalist.  The authors make clear that, in a fundamental sense, adolescent animals and teen humans encounter the same sorts of challenges - and that what may strike elders of any species as nutty, exasperating behavior is not only inevitable for most creatures in that stage of development but truly valuable.  Other scientists who have studied adolescents - human and nonhuman - echo their findings. Those elephants that charge right into harm's way? Their behavior is wholly in keeping with the adolescent modus operandi.  Human "adolescents frequently put themselves in danger deliberately," Natterson-Horowitz and Bowers write, adding: "Adolescent risk-taking is seen throughout the animal world."  The result, unsurprisingly, is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-Year-Old Venezuelan: 'The Police Electrocuted Me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/11/21/11-year-old-venezuelan-the-police-electrocuted-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unnamed 11-year-old Venezuelan boy in the state of Anzoátegui accused police of torture, including a severe beating and electrocution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges respect for prostitutes at crowded Bangkok mass...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-meets-thai-buddhist-patriarch-visit-promoting-religious-063119345.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis led an impassioned mass for tens of thousands of emotional worshippers at a packed Bangkok stadium Thursday, urging respect for prostitutes and trafficking victims in a part of the world where sex work is rampant. The remarks came at the end of a whirlwind day of meetings for Pope Francis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Island referendum could give world tiny new country...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pacific-island-referendum-could-world-210000097.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Born out of bloodshed, colonial politics, civil war and the pursuit of mining riches, the independence referendum on the island of Bougainville starting on Saturday has been a long time coming for Barbara Tanne.Tanne, one of the 300,000 or so people who live on the small group of islands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence, Pompeo in spotlight...</title>
      <link>http://www.msnbc.com/rachel-maddow-show/pence-pompeo-the-spotlight-after-impeachment-hearing-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Everyone was in the loop," Ambassador Gordon Sondland testified. "Everyone" appears to include many of the administration's most powerful players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Reverses Navy Decision to Oust Edward Gallagher From SEALs...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/21/donald-trump-overrules-navy-edward-gallagher-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday morning publicly overruled the U.S. Navy and declared the military “will NOT” strip Navy SEAL Edward Gallagher of his Trident pin, which symbolizes his membership in the elite unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSUS: Number of 'majority Hispanic' US counties doubles...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/census-number-of-majority-hispanic-us-counties-doubles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the latest evidence of the effect Latin American immigrants are having on the United States, the number of U.S. counties that have turned majority Hispanic has doubled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming Discovery in Astronaut's Bloodstream...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/11/astronaut-blood-clot/602380/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study has turned up a side effect of human spaceflight that no one had observed before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kissinger Warns U.S. and China in 'Foothills of Cold War'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/kissinger-warns-u-s-and-china-in-foothills-of-a-cold-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kissinger flew to Beijing in 1971 to begin trade talks with China when he served as Richard Nixon’s secretary of state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can 'dopamine fasting' really reboot brain?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20191115-what-is-dopamine-fasting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Dopamine fasts’ reboot your brain and make you appreciate everyday pleasures more, proponents say. But is there any science to back it up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standing ovation...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/movies/story/2019-11-21/richard-jewell-clint-eastwood-premiere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Richard Jewell," Clint Eastwood's drama about the 1996 Atlanta Olympics bombing case, will likely be the subject of much contention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2019/11/richard-jewell-review-clint-eastwood-1202190791/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director gets out of his own way to deliver a no-frills, solid-as-oak, competently mounted slice of biopic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/trump-impeachment-hearing-coverage-fiona-hill-david-holmes-testimony-live-stream-2019-11-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiona Hill, a former NSC official, and David Holmes, a diplomat in Kiev, are appearing at the final hearing of the week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466380-1/impeachment-inquiry-hearing-fiona-hill-david-holmes&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiona Hill, a former National Security Council senior director for Europe and Russia, and David Holmes, counselor for political affairs at the U.S. Embassy in Ukraine testify at a House Intelligence…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast porn on rise...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/20/podcast-porn-is-on-the-rise-and-revealing-strange-new-kinks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready to get hot and heavy? Slip on your headphones. Audio porn, a buzzy new genre of X-rated erotic recordings, is the latest tool for intimate exploration — and the greatest, if you ask its flush…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key witnesses cap intense week in impeachment inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b1c24927ea954c729381859ad90e25d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A former White House Russia analyst on Thursday denounced as “fictional” the contention from some Republicans that Ukraine interfered in the 2016 election and warned lawmakers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah woman fights charge after kids see her topless at home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2b962a7218d949ee84963d91f370edec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A Utah woman charged with a crime after her stepchildren saw her topless in her own home is fighting the case that could force her to register as a sex offender, citing a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can stay at hotel for $1 -- if live-stream everything...</title>
      <link>https://www.unionleader.com/news/back_page/you-can-stay-at-a-japanese-hotel-for--/article_58201270-d8c7-5273-b8f8-eff3e2f22cd5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The voyeurs around the world logged onto a YouTube stream Wednesday, hoping to see a random hotel guest scurry about their room. Instead, the viewers were greeted with an empty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolation Epidemic? One In Five Lonely On Friday Nights...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/isolation-epidemic-survey-finds-one-in-five-lonely-on-a-friday-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In all, one in five respondents say they're typically lonely on a Friday night, and nearly two thirds say they sometimes feel lonely over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVERSAL delays guest at gate over 'retired police officer' shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/business/os-bz-universal-police-shirt-20191120-obowmlc3frcztmbfpixn7edvma-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universal Studios stopped an Ormond Beach man from going into the parks for nearly an hour earlier this month because he wore a shirt that said he is a retired police officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic 'orange cloud' smothers city in terrifying video...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/apocalyptic-orange-cloud-smothers-australian-20926912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of the city of Mildura said the suffocating conditions are "unliveable" and bushfire warnings have since been issued</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyper-Realistic Masks More Believable Than Human Faces...</title>
      <link>https://scitechdaily.com/hyper-realistic-masks-can-be-more-believable-than-real-human-faces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scitechdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some silicone masks are now so realistic they can easily be mistaken for real faces, new research suggests. Hyper-realistic masks are made from flexible materials such as silicone and are designed to imitate real human faces — down to every last freckle, wrinkle and strand of real human hair. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clint Eastwood seeks to restore Atlanta bomb hero's legacy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/clint-eastwood-seeks-restore-atlanta-bomb-heros-legacy-125134486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clint Eastwood's new film restores the "hero" status of the security guard whose life was ripped apart by claims he bombed the 1996 Atlanta Olympics, the director and stars said Wednesday. "Richard Jewell" dramatizes the story of the innocent man who found himself at the center</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greener, longer life: More trees reduce premature deaths in cities...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191120230050-tz45e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City dwellers tend to live longer if they are in leafy neighbourhoods, according to a study that links green areas to lower rates of premature death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLDPLAY pause touring until can offer 'environmentally beneficial' concerts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/nov/21/coldplay-pause-touring-everyday-life-carbon-neutral-concerts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British group delay tour to support new album Everyday Life as they work towards developing carbon-neutral concerts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX rocket explodes during disastrous test...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/elon-musks-spacex-starship-rocket-20928391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX's failed test saw the top of the rocket blown off, sending plumes of gas into the air. Thankfully the rocket was unmanned during the test, and no-one was hurt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clint Eastwood seeks to restore Atlanta bomb hero's legacy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/clint-eastwood-seeks-restore-atlanta-bomb-heros-legacy-063000290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clint Eastwood's new film restores the "hero" status of the security guard whose life was ripped apart by claims he bombed the 1996 Atlanta Olympics, the director and stars said Wednesday. "Richard Jewell" dramatizes the story of the innocent man who found himself at the center</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Moving at Lowest Rate on Record...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.wsj.com/economics/2019/11/21/newsletter-americans-are-moving-at-the-lowest-rate-on-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your daily economics newsletter from The Wall Street Journal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestors gather in Berkeley for Ann Coulter appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/ann-coulter-protestors-helicopter-berkeley-bcr-14851008.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowds of protestors are already encircling Wheeler Hall on the UC Berkeley campus, where conservative personality Ann Coulter is scheduled to speak on Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar's shaking leaves viewers rattled...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/20/democratic-debates-amy-klobuchars-shaking-leaves-viewers-rattled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Amy Klobuchar raised eyebrows during Wednesday’s Democratic primary debate when she appeared to shake as she answered questions. Some viewers were concerned for the 59-year-old Minnesota…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hosted Zuckerberg for undisclosed dinner at White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/trump-hosted-zuckerberg-undisclosed-dinner-white-house-october-n1087986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting took place during Zuckerberg’s most recent visit to Washington, where he testified before Congress about Facebook’s new cryptocurrency Libra.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden stumbles with gaffes on women and race...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-blog/nov-20-democratic-debate-live-updates-n1087226/ncrd1088101#liveBlogHeader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten candidates take the stage for the fifth Democratic debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg Boasts He's Least Wealthy Person on Stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/populist-pete-buttigieg-boasts-that-hes-the-least-wealthy-person-on-debate-stage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sound Bend mayor Pete Buttigieg had a moment at the Wednesday night 2020 Democratic Debate when he boasted that he was the least wealthy candidate standing on the stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala roasts Tulsi... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/kamala-harris-rips-tulsi-gabbard-over-assad-bannon-criticizing-fellow-dems-spent-years-on-fox-news-hitting-obama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's unfortunate that we have someone on this stage who ... spent four years full time on Fox News criticizing President Obama."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cancels Movie Premiere After Producer Accused of Sex Assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/apple-canceled-banker-premiere-sexual-abuse-claims-real-life-subjects-son-1256695</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cynthia and Sheila Garrett allege they were assaulted by their half-brother Bernard Garrett Jr., the son of the subject of the drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaks Into Southern Accent...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/2020-election/2019/11/20/watch-kamala-harris-deploys-southern-fried-accent-for-single-debate-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris, who was born in Oakland, California, and grew up in Berkeley, broke into a fake southern accent during the Democrat debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexicans sue WALMART over El Paso shooting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexicans-sue-walmart-over-el-paso-shooting-185938190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's government said Wednesday it has helped 10 Mexican citizens file lawsuits against Walmart over an August shooting at a store in El Paso, Texas, where a suspected white nationalist killed 22 people. "The objective of these suits, presented in El Paso county, is to hold the company responsible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European center-right's new leader vows to fight populism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/european-centre-leader-vows-fight-populism-185108452.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former EU Council president Donald Tusk pledged Wednesday to fight political populism as he was elected leader of Europe's main conservative parties during their group meeting in Croatia. The former Polish prime minister will be tasked with boosting the fortunes of the European People's Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate exposes divides despite united front on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-debate-buttigieg-rises-impeachment-engrosses-voters-063548891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an opening phase dominated by talk of impeachment of Donald Trump, participants in the fifth Democratic debate locked horns over health care, in particular the costly universal coverage program supported by liberal senators Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders. "The fact is that right now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montage: Moderators Urge Attacks on Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-supercut-msnbc-debate-moderators-challenge-dems-left-urge-go</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Would you support a potential criminal investigation into President Trump after he leaves office?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Under Mosquito Alert After Another Case Of Dengue... </title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/20/miami-dade-under-mosquito-borne-illness-alert-after-another-case-of-dengue-fever-detected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami-Dade is under a mosquito-borne illness alert after another case of Dengue fever has been confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren defends wealth tax: 'I'm tired of freeloading billionaires'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/democratic-debate-elizabeth-warren-defends-wealth-tax-tired-of-freeloading-billionaires-031040597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren defended her proposed wealth tax during the Democratic presidential debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow throws first question softball...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/20/maddow-democratic-debate-warren/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC host Rachel Maddow started off Wednesday night's Democratic debate by lobbing a softball question to Democratic Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC'S HORRID FUNDRAISING NUMBERS CONTINUE...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/20/dnc-fundraising-numbers-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Committee (DNC) released its disappointing October fundraising numbers in the middle of the party's fifth presidential primary debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS MAKE NICE</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191121034952-o6bxf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/DEBATE (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Democratic White House candidates unite on impeachment in most polite debate yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro: Scorsese Believes Trump Will Start War to Get Third Term...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/robert-de-niro-believes-trump-will-start-a-war-so-he-can-serve-three-terms-as-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The theory, apparently, began with his good pal—and “The Irishman” director—Martin Scorsese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/video/watch-live-msnbc-washington-post-november-democratic-debate-73562693607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Livestream of the fifth Democratic presidential debate on November 20th, 2019 as 10 candidates spar in Atlanta, Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBATE NIGHT DEMS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-blog/nov-20-democratic-debate-live-updates-n1087226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten candidates take the stage for the fifth Democratic debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone was in the loop. It was was no secret'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7704917/Unpredictable-Sondland-faces-questions-Trump-Ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambassador Gordon Sondland will face questions about his evolving accounts of dealings with Ukraine and a report he kept Secretary of State Mike Pompeo apprised of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE MADE IN THE USA!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/20/apple-ceo-tim-cook-and-preident-trump-tour-texas-computer-factory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When you build in the United States you don't have to worry about tariffs," Trump said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRISIS AT PALACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10389442/queen-prince-andrew-royal-duties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen put on a brave face tonight after ­summoning sex scandal-hit Prince Andrew to Buckingham Palace to strip him of all royal duties. Her Majesty’s extraordinary intervention this afternoon c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accusing Netanyahu of stealing election, Gantz launches campaign for another...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/accusing-netanyahu-of-stealing-election-gantz-launches-campaign-for-another/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Repeatedly contrasting his own outlook with Netanyahu's, the Blue and White chief succeeds in painting a picture of two different leaders and two different Israels</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466379-1/impeachment-hearing-laura-cooper-david-hale&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Cooper, a deputy assistant Defense secretary, and David Hale, a State Department under secretary for political affairs, testifies before the House Intelligence Committee as part of its…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy slams GOP impeachment lawyer, demands apology...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/20/giuliani-slams-gop-impeachment-lawyer-demands-apology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani on Wednesday slammed the Republicans’ staff counsel during the impeachment inquiry — charging him with parroting “Democrat lies.” “Republican lawyer doesn’t do his own research and pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSED:  Biden emails post-debate fundraising plea -- hours early...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/20/biden-team-debate-fundraising-plea-2020-072212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The email went out around 3 p.m., a good six hours before the event is set to begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Decode Human Thoughts, Emotions Using MRI, Computer Analysis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mind-reading-scientists-decode-human-thoughts-and-emotions-using-mri-and-computer-analysis-60-minutes-2019-11-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Pittsburgh's Carnegie Mellon University have found a way to map brain activation patterns using MRI scans to read peoples' thoughts and emotions. 60 Minutes reports, Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA test shows Hunter Biden is father of Arkansas woman's baby...</title>
      <link>https://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2019/nov/20/dna-test-shows-hunter-biden-father-arkansas-womans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arkansasonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DNA testing has established, “with scientific certainty,” that Hunter Biden is the father of an Arkansas baby, according to a motion filed Wednesday in Independence County on behalf of the child’s mother, Lunden Alexis Roberts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZOGBY: Is he finished?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/471262-is-joe-biden-finished</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has his challenges ahead, but he is very much in this race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Unmasks WIKIPEDIA's Anti-Israel Editors...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/wikipedias-anti-israel-editors-unmasked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pro-Israel organization has exposed the identities of top Wikipedia editors who use the online encyclopedia to promote anti-Israel bias and causes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Buttigieg's rise positions him as top target at debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3007c4c1b2e4772a9bb1a26ade5d9c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Pete Buttigieg’s rise in the Democratic presidential primary makes him a prime target at Wednesday’s debate as the four candidates now bunched at the top seek to distinguish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son of former German president stabbed to death while giving lecture...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/11/20/fritz-von-weizsaecker-stabbed-death-son-former-german-president/4249150002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 57-year-old German man is in custody after he jumped up from the lecture audience and attacked Fritz von Weizsaecker on Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabbed on way to synagogue in NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-man-stabbed-on-way-to-synagogue-20191120-2pjkiktsgzb3vj5tczqijbv76y-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim was heading to temple when at least two men pulled up in a car, jumped out and attacked him on Howard Drive in Monsey, about 35 miles from Manhattan, about 5:45 a.m., Yeshiva World News reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family drags uncle's corpse to insurance company to prove he's dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7706145/Relatives-bring-family-members-CORPSE-insurance-firms-office-South-Africa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ntombenhle Mhlongo and Thandaza Mtshali dragged the body of uncle Sifiso Justice Mhlongo into a branch of Old Mutual in South Africa after the firm refused to pay out on a claim for funeral expenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Trying To Stop Facial Recognition From Ever Coming To Denver...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/11/19/facial-recognition-denver-ballot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If one group has their way, the city of Denver won’t be able to use facial recognition technology now, or ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg opens the spigot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/16abd2f36e624f2e8065303d4b8d9c50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As he moves toward a presidential announcement, New York billionaire Michael Bloomberg is rolling out plans to spend an estimated $15 million to $20 million on a voter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside New Mexico ranch...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7703257/New-photos-Jeffrey-Epsteins-New-Mexico-ranch-pedophiles-eight-person-party-shower.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of new photos and video give the most revealing insight yet into Jeffrey Epstein's notorious 'baby making ranch' in the New Mexico desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake news amplifies fear, confusion in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fake-news-amplifies-fear-confusion-hong-kong-075057098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impending 'terrorist' attacks: false news online is amplifying fear and confusion in Hong Kong as months of pro-democracy unrest turns increasingly violent in the real world. "I just assume everything is fake until I have seen sources from both sides and more than two news agencies I trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES employee's secret meet with Dem donor group scrutinized...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/nyt-columnist-joins-secretive-dem-donor-conference/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Times columnist and CBS News political analyst Jamelle Bouie addressed a closed-door gathering of the Democratic Party's top donors last week in potential violation of the paper's ethical guidelines, which prohibit paid speeches to political groups and urge staff members to be "especially sensitive to the appearance of partiality when they address groups that might figure in coverage they provide."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems ponder huge tax hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-democrats-would-tax-high-income-professionals-not-just-the-mega-rich/ar-BBWZiV2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mogul arrested on yacht in journalist murder case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/malta-businessman-arrested-journalist-murder-case-104043689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malta on Wednesday arrested a tycoon in connection with the murder of journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia, the day after an alleged middleman was offered a pardon to identify the mastermind behind the killing. Maltese national Yorgen Fenech was detained on his yacht at dawn as he tried to leave Malta,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy distances himself from Sondland...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/20/rudy-giuliani-tweets-attacks-gordon-sondland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani, President Trump's personal attorney, tweeted then deleted a rebuttal of Gordon Sondland's testimony during Wednesday's impeachment hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge fund becomes TRIBUNE's largest shareholder...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/30b2b8288fc0413eac7def72fe1457a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hedge fund Alden Global Capital is now the largest shareholder of Tribune Publishing, the company that owns the Chicago Tribune, Baltimore Sun and New York Daily...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
