<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Top Mueller prosecutor advises Dems to evoke Watergate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/top-mueller-prosecutor-andrew-weissmann-offers-impeachment-advice-to-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of special counsel Robert Mueller's top prosecutors is offering advice to House Democrats for their impeachment proceedings against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother speaks about autistic son who died after being restrained at school...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/education/article237229909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATE ENTRY:  Deval Patrick running for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/former-mass-gov-deval-patrick-announce-presidential-bid-n1081881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A late-entry into the Democratic primary would face fundraising and organization challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC features George Conway...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/george-conway-on-msnbc-republicans-were-fundamentally-illogical-and-incoherent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway continued his surprising appearance on MSNBC panels covering the impeachment hearings and not disappoint loyal viewers eager for harsh criticism of Congressional Republicans in defense o</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  'Superbugs' on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/superbugs-rise-new-cdc-report-finds-threat-has-increased-previous-report-2013-2865723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report found that 35,000 people die every year from these drug-resistant "superbugs" compared to 23,000 in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA expects record number of fliers over Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/470366-tsa-expects-record-number-of-fliers-over-thanksgiving-holiday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) is anticipating a record number of fliers over the Thanksgiving holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal deficit hits $134 billion in one month!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/economy/470314-federal-deficit-hits-134-billion-in-one-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal deficit reached $134 billion in October, the first month of fiscal 2020, according to data the Treasury Department released Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Hong Kong chaos raises fears about what's next...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-descends-chaos-china-015123212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sharp escalation of violence in Hong Kong is once again raising the question of how China's central government will respond: Will it intervene, or allow the chaos to persist? The Liaison Office, which represents mainland authorities in Hong Kong, said Wednesday that actions in the semi-autonomous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS to be on hand for Kaepernick workout...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/cowboys/2019/11/13/colin-kaepernick-nfl-workout-dallas-cowboys/4179869002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite owner Jerry Jones' stance of mandating players stand for the anthem, the Cowboys will be in attendance for Colin Kaepernick's workout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a lot of mistakes? Try meditating, research says...</title>
      <link>https://preview.ajc.com/lifestyles/health/making-lot-mistakes-try-mediating-research-says/2Qfi3vRiTbSRNAW283cYMJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;preview.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers found that meditating even just once can help people make fewer mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop who investigated sex abuse accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bef8c2e19d1247268fd8c47141623719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A Roman Catholic bishop named by Pope Francis to investigate the church’s response to clergy sexual abuse in Buffalo, New York, has himself been accused of sexual abuse of a child,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurors to decide on Roger Stone's fate...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/11/13/roger-stone-trump-allys-trial-over-russia-wikileaks-concludes/2581039001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors hear closing arguments Wednesday in the trial of Roger Stone, a longtime GOP operative and Trump ally accused of lying to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Turkeys So Bold -- They Knock on Door for Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/where-wild-turkeys-are-so-bold-they-knock-on-the-door-for-food/ar-BBWHDw8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren buys CNBC commercial time to blast billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/13/elizabeth-warren-blasts-billionaires-in-campaign-ad-calling-for-wealth-tax.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is time for a wealth tax," Elizabeth Warren says in a fiery new campaign ad blasting billionaires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insect apocalypse coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/13/europe/insect-apocalypse-report-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's being called the unnoticed apocalypse. The number of insects is declining rapidly and 41% face extinction. However, scientists say we can be the first responders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow closes at record high as DISNEY pops more than 7%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/13/dow-futures-fed-chair-jerome-powell-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow hit an all-time high on Wednesday as Disney shares popped and investors digested testimony from the top-ranking Fed official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE To No Longer Sell Shoes On AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nike-shoes-no-longer-on-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nike's direct sales to consumers are growing, and some analysts say its split with Amazon could curb counterfeiting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL: WE WILL HAVE A TRIAL...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/13/mcconnell-trump-impeachment-articles-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell on Wednesday said the Senate cannot dismiss the articles of impeachment against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superbug infections rising...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a646fe6429ab46e0aab3f09a60d77b5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Drug-resistant “superbug” infections have been called a developing nightmare that could set medicine back a century, making conquered germs once again untreatable. So there’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop who investigated sex abuse in Buffalo accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wivb.com/news/national/bishop-who-investigated-sex-abuse-accused-of-sex-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wivb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney informed Catholic officials in New Jersey that he is preparing a lawsuit on behalf of a client who says he was molested by Brooklyn Bishop Nicholas DiMarzio in the mid-1970s, when DiMa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement Dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/11/13/jobs-why-retirement-disappearing-boomers-gen-xers/2579098001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Americans are opting to work well into retirement, a growing trend that threatens to upend the old workforce model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deval Patrick tells allies he's running for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/13/politics/deval-patrick-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick is telling friends and allies in phone calls on Wednesday that he has made a decision to run for president, two people familiar with the matter say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Wallace: Testimony 'Very Damaging'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/13/fox-news-chris-wallace-taylor-testimony-very-damaging-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Chris Wallace said that Ambassador William Taylor's House testimony Wednesday was &amp;quot;very damaging&amp;quot; to President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY Anthrax A Powerful Weapon -- In Fight Against Cancer?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-anthrax-a-powerful-weapon-in-fight-against-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of researchers say they have formulated a new method of bladder cancer treatment, and it involves an unconventional ingredient: anthrax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House projects disinterest: 'Boring'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/13/donald-trump-impeachment-hearings-070575</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA readies new nuke missile test?</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/space/2019/11/13/is-the-us-about-to-test-a-new-ballistic-missile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A test of an intermediate-range ballistic missile could be coming soon. Here's what to watch for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY+ surpasses 10 million sign-ups in 1 day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/13/disney-surpasses-10-million-sign-ups-since-launch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's new streaming service launched Tuesday with some technical difficulties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Prozac pollution' making fish less aggressive...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/prozac-pollution-making-fish-less-aggressive-says-study-11860507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the behaviour of solitary fish is not altered, it does appear to have an effect on fish in a group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UF student president faces impeachment threat over Trump Jr. visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/education/2019/11/12/uf-student-president-faces-impeachment-threat-over-trump-jr-visit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A push to oust Student Body President Michael Murphy comes after an email surfaces, suggesting he worked with the Trump campaign to bring a political speech to campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURLEY:  Are Dems building a collapsible impeachment?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/470217-are-democrats-building-a-collapsible-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The constitutional basis to remove a president from office must rest on a solid foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag queen sashays into hearings...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/drag-queen-sashays-trump-impeachment-hearings-n1081261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pissi Myles made an unexpected, and quite noticeable, appearance at Wednesday's impeachment hearings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIGHTS, CAMERA, ACTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/mag-features/adam-schiff-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mild-mannered, vegan congressman from Burbank has become the GOP’s worst nightmare—but is he tough enough to take on the Trump smear machine?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Unions Set to Go to War Over Streaming TV Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/streaming-tvs-ratings-black-box-could-lead-hollywood-guild-war-1254321</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the industry enters a direct-to-consumer era, the dearth of data beyond "self-serving marketing" metrics will play a large role in the 2020 union talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirates attack ship in Gulf of Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/pirates-attack-ship-in-gulf-of-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican navy says two Italian crew members were wounded in an attack by armed assailants who boarded their ship in the Gulf of Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT:  LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466134-1/impeachment-hearing-william-taylor-george-kent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Intelligence Committee holds its first open hearing of the impeachment inquiry against President Trump. Lawmakers will hear testimony from William Taylor, Acting U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Plan to sacrifice Rudy...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-impeachment-republicans-rudy-giuliani-f192d64d-2bee-4597-8de8-3e0477b988de.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Rudy will be cut loose because he was rogue."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Paying Residents To Catch Feral Cats; $15 Per Feline!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/12/miami-dade-animal-services-will-pay-you-to-help-control-outdoor-cat-population/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Got too many 'community' cats running around in your neighborhood? Now, Miami-Dade County Animal Services could use your help and you could make some money in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: Man Brutally Beaten By Pack of 15 Teens...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/11/12/baltimore-violence-mayor-jack-young-reaction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brutal attack, a shooting outside of a school, and a stabbing next to the Inner Harbor- three violent attacks, and police say what they all have in common is that teenagers are involved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHIFF SHOW</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8a31b8985b14303b71836d85ffd7d0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A “solemn day” or a “show trial”? Americans and the world can decide for themselves as House Democrats let the public in to the impeachment proceedings against President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREAT FLOOD OF VENICE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2e212a874a064ce4af63dc3ffda0258e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE, Italy (AP) — The worst flooding in Venice in more than 50 years prompted calls Wednesday to better protect the historic city from rising sea levels as officials calculated hundreds of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter attacked by gator tells how he was prepared to die in swampy wilderness...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-gator-bite-victim-interview-20191113-kmjirrjhmfbdnoy56otp5vsy34-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A makeshift tourniquet fashioned out of a belt and zip ties saved a hunter's life after he was bitten by an alligator in a swampy wilderness area over the weekend, a trauma surgeon at St. Mary's Medical Center in West Palm Beach said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery objects fall from sky over Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mystery-three-objects-fall-sky-20873143</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three UFOs have been captured in a mysterious video flying above the US city of Las Vegas at night, the conspiracy theorist who took the footage has claimed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regrets I've had a few, says 'MY WAY songwriter...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/regrets-ive-had-few-says-way-songwriter-152418252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He wrote the music for "My Way", one of the world's most popular songs, but Jacques Revaux would like to mention a few of his regrets. For one, "I don't even have a photo with Frank Sinatra," the French songwriter laughed. Fewer still -- not even in France, where the credit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Ginsburg Misses Supreme Court Argument With Illness...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/justice-ginsburg-misses-supreme-court-151618343.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg missed Wednesday’s argument session with what a court spokeswoman said was a stomach virus.Chief Justice John Roberts said from the bench that Ginsburg, 86, was ”indisposed due to illness” but would participate in the two cases based on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters launch flaming arrows at police...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10336052/hong-kong-protesters-flaming-arrows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROTESTERS in Hong Kong fired flaming bows and javelins at riot cops as “murderous” clashes continued overnight. Demonstrators armed with bows and arrows launched their blazing weapons …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Apocalyptic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10335517/venice-flooding-2019-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE has declared a state of emergency after a 1.8-metre flood devastated the tourist hotspot and killed at least two people. Shocking pictures show the historic St Mark’s Basilica under wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentarian Set Out to Expose Monogamy as Sham. Then Fell in Love With Her Subject...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bara-jichova-tyson-set-out-to-expose-monogamy-as-a-sham-then-she-fell-in-love-with-her-subject </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Czech filmmaker Bara Jichova Tyson’s provocative film “Talking About Adultery” condemns what it sees as the restrictive nature of marriage. Then comes an unexpected twist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway Scorches Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-george-conway-kick-off-live-impeachment-coverage-for-msnbc-with-devastating-takedown-of-republicans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney George Conway, husband of senior Trump adviser Kellyanne Conway, kicked off MSNBC's live coverage of the impeachment of President Donald Trump with a devastating takedown of Republicans,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman's eye bursts after using phone too much...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/womans-eye-bursts-after-using-20873392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A blood vessel in the woman's retina exploded after a long session on her phone in China, causing temporary blindness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot gas prices warm up US inflation in October...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hot-gasoline-prices-warm-us-inflation-october-142502242.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flare-up in US fuel prices in October sparked the biggest bump consumer inflation in seven months, but other price gains were more modest, according to new government data Wednesday. The rise in the monthly price index was hotter than expected, bolstering the Federal Reserve's decision to pause</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK app quietly turning on people's cameras...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/11/13/facebook-app-quietly-turning-peoples-cameras-freaking-11088107/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social network assures users the creepy 'bug' has not been filming their intimate moments and uploading them to Zuck's servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil Peep Doc Tells Familiar Story -- but Doesn't Make Less Sad...</title>
      <link>https://www.theringer.com/movies/2019/11/13/20962535/lil-peep-documentary-everybodys-everything-gustav-ahr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theringer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Everybody’s Everything" is about a promising young musician whose fame only deepened his substance abuse—a tale we’ve seen before, but like his music, Gustav Ahr’s life is well worth remembering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable news showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-13/msnbc-and-fox-news-girding-to-prosecute-and-defend-president-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impeachment inquiry into President Trump has widened a massive divide, nowhere more evident than on cable TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept faces biggest crisis since McCarthy hysteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/State-Department-faces-its-biggest-crisis-since-14831022.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As diplomats prepared to testify publicly at House impeachment hearings, the president of the American Foreign Service Association recalled another perilous era in U.S. history.  That was Sen. Joseph McCarthy's reign of hysteria in the early 1950s about supposed communists in Hollywood and the federal government - especially the State Department.  "I think it's fair to say in the past 70 years, since the McCarthy period, this is the most fraught time and the most difficult time for our members," said Eric Rubin, the president of AFSA, the union representing Foreign Service officers.  During McCarthyism, the Republican from Wisconsin wildly alleged that the State Department was infested with communists and chaired hearings to root them out.  Now, House Democrats are calling on diplomats to help uncover the truth concerning accusations that President Trump invited a foreign government into domestic affairs for his personal political benefit.  This time, unlike in the McCarthy era, Foreign Service officers are not the accused. Video showing William B. Taylor Jr., George Kent and Marie Yovanovitch on Capitol Hill for their closed-door testimony in the Ukraine matter provided images of proud, dedicated federal employees caught up in a political drama they cannot escape.  Taylor and Kent will testify publicly Wednesday, and Yovanovitch on Friday, on Trump's plan to have Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky embarrass Trump's political rival, former vice president Joe Biden, by investigating his son's activities in Ukraine.  This has plunged the diplomats into a legal predicament between the Democratic-controlled House of Representatives and the Republican-controlled White House, and leaves the association in unmapped terrain.  "Our colleagues are finding themselves...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing running 500 concentration camps?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uighur-researchers-china-running-hundreds-more-camps-181157759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uighur activists said Tuesday they have documented nearly 500 camps and prisons run by China to detain members of the ethnic group, alleging that Beijing could be holding far more than the commonly cited figure of one million people. The East Turkistan National Awakening Movement, a Washington-based</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces limits of his power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f43d4e272994e9ca321714c3974eac3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For three years, Donald Trump has unapologetically defied the conventions of the American presidency. On Wednesday, he comes face to face with the limits of his power, confronting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski leaves movie premiere in Paris by side door following protests...</title>
      <link>https://uk.movies.yahoo.com/roman-polanski-leaves-movie-premiere-in-paris-by-side-door-following-protests-130334639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roman Polanski made a swift exit from a back door at the premiere of his new movie in Paris last night, following angry protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy dogs headed to Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/470179-therapy-dogs-slated-to-visit-capitol-hill-today</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cuddly canines are coming to the rescue of stressed-out Capitol Hill staffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Nears Defining Hour as Impeachment Goes Public...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-nears-defining-hour-case-104512848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Balance of Power newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Politics on Twitter and Facebook for more.Congressional Democrats have a tall order ahead.Their challenge, at the start of public impeachment hearings today against President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff on Hook to Make Case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-hearings-open-schiff-090000658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s attempts to pressure Ukraine will be scrutinized in a historic public forum Wednesday as the House opens impeachment hearings that will pit him against Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff, who is tasked with making the case to remove the president from office.Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venetian anger after historic flood devastates city...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/devastation-venice-exceptional-tide-095855792.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venetians woke Wednesday to devastating scenes after the highest tide in 50 years washed through the historic Italian city, beaching gondolas, trashing hotels and sending tourists fleeing through rapidly rising waters. "The city is on its knees," Venice's mayor Luigi Brugnaro said in an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURTAIN-UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/468e0bcb51e74822a1f8cc11627a1c0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The closed doors of the Trump impeachment investigation are swinging wide open. When the gavel strikes at the start of the House hearing on Wednesday morning, America and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong readies for more chaos as violence spreads citywide...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191113012941-iptni</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-PROTESTS/ (PIX, TV):Hong Kong readies for more chaos as violence spreads citywide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pneumonic plague in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/13/two-people-diagnosed-with-pneumonic-plague-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities working to contain outbreak of disease that is worse than bubonic plague</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House laughs off Anonymous book as old news...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/12/white-house-anonymous-book-069684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminally-ill scientist completes transformation into 'world's first cyborg'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/terminally-ill-scientist-completes-transformation-20871943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Peter Scott-Morgan, who suffers from a muscle wasting disease, says he has fully completed his transition into 'Peter 2.0'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Israel-Gaza escalation rages for second day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deadly-israel-gaza-escalation-rages-second-day-113541641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exchanges of fire triggered by Israel's targeted killing of a top militant in Gaza raged for a second day Wednesday and showed little sign of easing, with 22 Palestinians killed. Fresh rocket barrages were fired at Israel, which responded with strikes on what it said were Islamic Jihad militant</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
