<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>There are no perfect defenses against shark bites. But wearable tech might help...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/there-are-no-perfect-defenses-against-shark-bites-but-wearable-tech-might-help-researchers-say/ar-BB1flH4G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say it's crucial to find better shark-deterring technology that saves humans from bites without harming an already-vulnerable species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friend with George Floyd on day of arrest to appear in murder trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/friend-george-floyd-day-arrest-122900221.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seventh day of testimony is on tap in the Derek Chauvin murder trial, but the jurors will not be present when a witness to George Floyd's arrest speaks in court Tuesday. Morries L. Hall was with Floyd on that night late last spring, when Floyd was apprehended by police outside a corner store in south Minneapolis and pinned on the pavement under an officer's knee until dying. Hall has said he ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Injured In Shooting Near MD Army Base; Sailors Involved...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/04/06/2-injured-in-active-shooter-incident-in-frederick-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frederick Police are on the scene of an "active shooter" in the 8400 block of Progress Drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Mykonos, Greece's Famed Party Island, 'Everyone About to Explode'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mykonos-greeces-famed-party-island-084758695.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisa Gouliamaki/AFP via Getty ImagesThe narrow, stone-paved alleys on the traditional village of Oia, in Santorini, are usually packed with tourists even this time of the year. The Greek island with the most famous sunset view in the world is always a top travel destination. But COVID-19 put the growing popularity of the Greek islands on hold in 2020 and even though the warm Mediterranean weather means the tourist season in Greece usually starts in early April and lasts until late October, the streets are relatively quiet.With vaccination continuing worldwide, though, and the convenience of rapid tests, Greece is opening up to international travelers May 14, after almost a year, and hopes to recapture its past success. And business owners on two of its most famous islands, Santorini and Mykonos, are expecting the reopening to go with a bang. Giorgos Dimitrokalis wakes up everyday looking at the magnificent view of the caldera, and although he was born and raised in Santorini, this view of the Aegean Sea never ceases to amaze him. But for the owner of KD Hotels and Resorts and vice president of the Santorini Hoteliers Association, it’s hard to be the only one to enjoy this view. “It feels like a completely different island. Unrecognizable. Last year we were joking that the locals had the chance to enjoy the island for themselves. I hope this summer, things will go back to as it was before the pandemic, because the island has really suffered."Unlike other places in Greece, islands such as Santorini and Mykonos base the majority of their economy on tourism. In 2019, tourism was a little more than 20 percent of the country’s overall economy , according to the Institute of the Greek Tourism Confederation. It was the best year in a decade.And then, coronavirus came. A view of Oia on the island of Santorini, Greece. Alkis Konstantinidis “It was summer outside, but the people out in the streets were as many as if it was winter. There was not even a soul out there. It was surreal,” says Poly Linoxylaki, owner of the Sand Lily boutique at Imerovigli in Santorini.Desperate not to lose another year, the Greek minister of tourism, Harry Theoharis, announced recently that the government will reopen tourism in Greece from May 14.There are two types of tourists who visit Santorini, explains Dimitrokalis, who owns 10 hotels all around the island: “At the hotels that are close to the beach, we’ve seen a more increased interest so far this year. Our customers there stay for around seven days, are usually families, and most of them Europeans. At the more central hotels, like the ones at Caldera and Fyra, are usually travelers who come from overseas, such as Americans, Brazilians, Chinese, and Australians, and they usually stay for no longer than three days. They come to see the island, admire the sunset, and leave.”For Embark Beyond, a luxury travel advisory company based in New York, “Greece and Turkey may be the only European countries open this summer” for Americans, and because of that they suggest to their clients to “reserve now, before the flood gates open and it’s too late."“What we’ve been told is that the international flights to Greece for tourism will be open from everywhere in the world on May 14. We are just waiting for the officials to tell us what the protocols for this year will be” says Dimitrokalis, who points out that Americans are among the biggest fans of the island.“Most tourists who visit Santorini are from the U.S. and Australia, and if they won’t be able to come for some reason, I will have a big trouble” says Linoxylaki, who sells clothes and accessories, mostly made by Greek designers. “These are my customers. They support small businesses like mine."During this time of the year the reservations for summer would normally be at around 70-80 percent, but according to Dimitrokalis, today the number is down to 25-30 percent. “We hope that next month more people will be interested and we expect that by the end of the season we might be able to reach around 50 percent of 2019. We are putting our hopes in last-minute reservations to reach our goal,” he says.Most of the reservations are starting from mid-summer, but everyone is optimistic. “If the weather is good we expect to expand this year’s season, because we are already losing the first three months” says Dimitrokalis, and that is something Linoxylaki agrees, even though she has her doubts about the reopening: “We are hoping that September and October will be the peak of this season. But I must be honest, I personally don’t believe that we will be able to open up on May 14, as the government said.”Similar to Santorini, most of the Greek islands suffered their share too last year. Among them, Mykonos, the popular Cycladic island with the bright white houses and wild nightlife.When Kim Kardashian and her family traveled to Mykonos in 2013 to film the eighth season of Keeping Up with the Kardashians, Kim was pregnant with North and the island was full with paparazzi… and lots of tourists. Overview of the Chora of Mykonos at sunset. Demetrios Ioannou Today Iraklis Zisimopoulos, CEO of the Semeli Hospitality Group who hosted the Kardashian family and their crew almost a decade ago, looks back at those days with some nostalgia, but with confidence for the future. “I am sure that they will come back again; coronavirus won’t last forever. It might not be this year, but we see that the dynamic of Mykonos is not lost and we are sure that even better days will come” he says.Zisimopoulos is also the general secretary of the Mykonos Catering and Entertainment Association, as well as the president of the Association of Businesses and Professionals of Mykonos Town. “I have hotels, restaurants, bars, clubs, and everything is shut down,” he says with a bitter smile.Speaking to the Athens News Agency last September, Konstantinos Koukas, the mayor of the island, said that last season they reached only 30 percent of 2019, and as Zisimopoulos explains: “Last year was catastrophic, but we hope this year will be different. It definitely won’t be anywhere close to a normal season, but for sure it won’t be like 2020."The most important role in shaping that will be the protocols under which tourists will be able to enter Greece. “So far we know that there are three options: 1) The people who have been already vaccinated, 2) Those who have tested negative the last 48 hours, and 3) Those who have already been sick and now have the antibodies” says Zisimopoulos, a doctor himself.When it comes to Mykonos though, people don’t travel to the island just for the nice view or to swim in the crystal clear blue sea. They go because they want to have fun and everyone has only one thing on mind… the nightlife!Mykonos is known worldwide as the “party island” of Greece and a land where you can openly be who you are. Anastasios Kapetanias contributed as much as anybody to this reputation. For the director and founder of XLSIOR Festival, the only gay music festival in Greece and among the top five in the world, last year was the first time that he had to cancel it, since it was first launched in 2009. But he has high hopes for this summer.“People are thirsty for fun” he says. “We receive lots of emails everyday from people begging us to do the festival this year. They tell us ‘we need to see our friends; we need to feel free again’. Everyone is about to explode; we can’t take it any more."For the Greek government, nightlife isn’t a top priority and will be one of the last things to open, and under which terms is yet unknown. But for the local economy, this is a huge blow. XLSIOR alone brings to the island more than 30,000 people every summer from all around the world. “We have people coming from the U.S., Brazil, Spain, Israel, and most of them are people who come every year”, explains Kapetanias, who also cooperates with several local businesses like hotels, rent-a-cars, restaurants etc. to assist his clients.“Last August when the government decided to close all bars and clubs at midnight, all reservations stopped and many canceled,” says Zisimopoulos. The whole situation was completely surreal, as Kapetanias describes it: “People were all around the streets, looking for some villa parties to go and everyone was hiding as if we were in a war. This is not Mykonos." One of the windmills overlooking the Chora of Mykonos. Demetrios Ioannou The Greek government decided to vaccinate all residents on small islands, with under 1,000 population, with some of the first COVID-free islands in Greece including Kastellorizo and Oinousses,Could a similar plan work for Mykonos, with around 10,000 people? Zisimopoulos is confident it would fix many of their problems: “If all the locals get vaccinated, whatever happens to the island, we will have a strong protective shield. In a normal season, we would have at least 10 reservations per day. Now the maximum is 2. The last 20 days we’ve seen some movement and we have some reservations from the U.K., Israel, and the U.S., where the vaccination goes faster. Most of those reservations are for July and August."Kapetanias, on the other hand, suggests that a good idea for the reopening of live festivals like his could be the rapid tests. “They could go to a clinic on the island earlier on the same day, do the test and if it is negative they could come with the results and enter. We just need to be super organized, so the people will be completely safe."And even though no one knows for sure how this summer nightlife will be like, the engines on the island are on and everyone is organizing, hoping they won’t have to cancel again. “Because of the situation we will be able to organize events in dreamy places, where other years it wasn’t possible. This year most of our events will be outdoors as well. Of course we will also be bringing the best DJs, musicians and dancers that we know our audience loves,” Kapetanias says about this year’s event, which has already been announced for August 18-25.“It will be a year in which we will get a big part of our life and vacations back, and because we have been deprived of so many things this past year, it will make us feel so much better. I really believe there is hope on the horizon,” says Zisimopoulos. Kapetanias concurs: “To be honest, what I want for this summer is to see happy people, who will be laughing, having fun, being safe and would want to come back again next year."Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANY SKIP SECOND DOSE</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/public-health-experts-urge-americans-to-not-skip-2nd-vaccine-dose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The overwhelming scientific evidence shows that both doses offer the best protection against COVID-19, according to experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian joins club...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/04/06/kim-kardashian-is-officially-a-billionaire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Not bad for a girl with no talent.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Confederate monument will become 'toilet' unless 'White Lies Matter' demands met, group vows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/activist-group-white-lies-matter-holds-jefferson-davis-monument-hostage/ar-BB1flbon?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group is not asking for money, but for the United Daughters of the Confederacy to display a banner with a quote by Assata Shakur, "The rulers of this country have always considered their property more important than our lives."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CIA director was skeptical about aliens until friend's aircraft 'paused at 40,000ft'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9439137/Former-CIA-chief-says-hopes-friendly-dealing-creatures-exist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Woolsey, CIA director under Bill Clinton, on Friday said that he had a new 'openness' to the possibility of alien life, and told how a source he respected said his plane was stopped at 40,000ft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny 'seriously ill'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/06/alexei-navalny-seriously-ill-on-prison-sick-ward-says-lawyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian opposition figure has fever, cough and has lost weight, according to legal team member who visited him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDs increasing in military...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/pay-benefits/military-benefits/health-care/2021/04/05/sexually-transmitted-infections-increasing-in-the-military/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chlamydia, gonorrhea and syphilis are on the rise across the military. HPV and genital herpes are decreasing in frequency, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Biden's surprising presidency...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/546511-joe-bidens-surprising-presidency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like his predecessors, time and chance have made “Sleepy Joe” both energetic and surprising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: COVID FEAR RECORD LOW</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/344183/americans-worry-catching-covid-drops-record-low.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record-low 35% of Americans worry about catching COVID-19. At the same time, 77% say the coronavirus situation is improving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After school shootings, NRA exec sought refuge on 108-foot yacht: 'Thank God I'm safe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/thank-god-im-safe-nra-leader-sought-refuge-from-public-outrage-aboard-yacht-after-mass-school-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NRA leader Wayne LaPierre says he faced an unprecedented “security threat” in the wake of bloody rampages at Sandy Hook Elementary in Connecticut and a Parkland, Florida, high school — and had to seek refuge aboard his Hollywood producer friend’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia army begins 'combat readiness' inspection...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210406105930-h4i42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-DEFENCE/ (URGENT):Russia's army begins planned 'combat readiness' inspection - RIA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEURALINK Co-Founder Says We Have Tech to Build Actual Jurassic Park...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/neuralink-cofounder-tech-build-actual-jurassic-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Why don’t we more intentionally try to generate novel diversity?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hikers scramble as new fissure opens up at Icelandic volcano...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/iceland-new-fissure-opens-volcano-7e1a37e887589d11de37d46f81fcc271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REYKJAVIK, Iceland (AP) — Steam and lava spurted Monday from a new fissure at an Icelandic volcano that began erupting last month, prompting the evacuation of hundreds of hikers who had come to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day of 4 Million Jabs Signals Sharp Turnaround...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/day-of-4-million-vaccines-signals-a-sharp-turnaround-for-us/ar-BB1flP7z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landscape architect Scheri Fultineer walked out of the white vaccination tent at Massachusetts General Hospital with a Band-Aid on her shoulder and a feeling of delight at how easy it was. “Earlier in the year,” she said, “I was not optimistic.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Sees Immunity by June...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/eu-sees-near-virus-immunity-by-end-june-despite-astra-doubts/ar-BB1flsxM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Commission has told governments the Covid vaccine rollout could hit a key target earlier than expected, under new projections that hinge on people accepting AstraZeneca Plc’s shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan hospitals have new type of patient: Younger and healthier...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/05/us/michigan-covid-surge-patients-variants/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan is in another coronavirus surge and hospitals are again on the front line, but this time they have a new type of patient: younger and healthier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos, Musk top record-setting billionaire list...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210406095525-aqecb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORBES-WORLDSBILLIONAIRES/ (TV, PIX):Bezos, Musk top Forbes' record-setting billionaire list</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crews race to drain Florida wastewater reservoir on brink of collapse...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210405232142-cbqyo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLORIDA-RESERVOIR/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Crews race to drain Florida wastewater reservoir on brink of collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With reluctance, Israel president tasks Netanyahu with forming new govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/with-reluctance-israel-s-president-tasks-netanyahu-with-forming-a-new-government/ar-BB1flk45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli President Rivlin said it was not an “easy decision, on an ethical or moral level.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for TRIBUNE: Inside campaign to find new owners for legendary newspapers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-battle-for-tribune-inside-the-campaign-to-find-new-owners-for-a-legendary-group-of-newspapers/ar-BB1fknZ8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It started with a group of reporters who decided to do everything they could to avoid a hedge-fund takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roubini Warns Yields Above 2% Will Bite Amid Excess Risk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roubini-warns-higher-u-yields-073514681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A fresh spike in Treasury yields will rattle markets and could send more family offices and hedge funds down a similar path to Bill Hwang’s Archegos Capital Management, according to Nouriel Roubini.Roubini, a professor at New York University’s Stern School of Business and a former adviser to the U.S. government, said the combination of low-to-negative rates across advanced economies and fiscal stimulus is leading investors to take excessive risk. He pointed to cyclically adjusted price-earnings ratios at highs seen in 1929 and the early 2000s as one sign of the recklessness.“We’re seeing widespread frothiness, bubbles, risk-taking and leverage,” Roubini said on Bloomberg TV. “Lots of players have taken too much leverage and too much risk and some of them are going to blow up.”Read More: Bubble Deniers Abound to Dismiss Valuation MetricsMeltdown WarningsThe professor, who earned the nickname “Dr. Doom” for his ominous prognostications about the economy and financial system, joins investors including Scott Minerd of Guggenheim Investments in warning that more Archegos-style meltdowns could be triggered. Roubini said one shock could come if 10-year U.S. Treasury yields climb higher than 2% this year.Bank of America Corp. strategists cited the same level as among the biggest risks to the bull run in equities, following record inflows of $372 billion in the first quarter. A burst of strong economic data may fuel such a move in yields as money managers price in an improving growth outlook. The thinking is that before raising rates, the Federal Reserve will begin to ponder trimming its bond purchases, a move that’s been a catalyst for higher real rates in the past.Read More: U.S. Yields’ Trek Higher Seen Getting Fuel From Real Rates Christian Mueller-Glissmann, a London-based strategist at Goldman Sachs Group Inc., said there’s a “very good chance” that the 10-year U.S. yield overshoots in the second quarter beyond the firm’s year-end forecast of 1.9%.“You’re dealing with peak growth momentum and we’re dealing with incredible pressure from a fund flow point of view as well, where you haven’t really seen major outflows out of bonds,” he said on Bloomberg TV.‘Hot War’Investors must also grapple with other risks, including the return of inflation and the prospect of a “hot war” between the U.S. and China, Roubini said.While a stronger dollar has led some hedge funds and other investors to capitulate on their bearish bets, the greenback will weaken over the medium term as twin deficits in the world’s largest economy widen, he said. Meantime, U.S. sanctions may lead countries like China, Russia, Iran and North Korea to diversify away from dollar assets.“Even if in the short-term growth outcomes in the U.S. strengthen the dollar, the direction of the dollar is south over time,” Roubini said.(Adds equity inflows data in fifth paragraph and Goldman comments beginning in sixth.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy Chief Says Mysterious 'Drones' That Swarmed Warships Still Unidentified...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/40071/navys-top-officer-says-mysterious-drones-that-swarmed-destroyers-remain-unidentified</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of bizarre events off Southern California in 2019 remain unexplained according to the Chief of Naval Operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Takeover? Video Shows Squadron of Droids Moving in Unison...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9438493/Chinese-robotics-firm-shares-terrifying-video-four-legged-robots-moving-unison.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video shared on Twitter has sparked fears of a real world robot take over. The clip shows a squadron of four-legged, canine-like robots made by a Chinese firm, all of which move in unison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40,000 American children have lost at least one parent...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/40-000-children-us-lost-012600264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “staggering” 40,000 children in the U.S. have lost at least one parent to coronavirus, three-quarters of them teenagers, a new model has calculated. Researchers at Stony Brook University on Long Island estimated the number of children of each adult to have died of COVID-19 and extrapolated to arrive at that conclusion. The model suggested that each such death left 0.078 children between ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France investigates secret restaurants for Paris elite...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/paris-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-france-931e731b1d0485ef938a4911944cc5b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Champagne, lobster and no masks: That's what a French TV documentary says is on the menu at one of multiple high-end “clandestine restaurants” catering to the Paris elite, in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN:  GLOBAL TAX!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/janet-yellen-minimum-global-corporate-income-tax-0a839a4705566a8b9f8bd5411bfe62d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Monday urged the adoption of a minimum global corporate income tax, an effort to at least partially offset any disadvantages that might...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Absolutely' Violated Policy, Minneapolis Police Chief Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/derek-chauvin-absolutely-violated-policy-minneapolis-police-chief-says/ar-BB1fksxA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief of the Minneapolis Police Department testified on Monday that Derek Chauvin had “absolutely” violated department policies when he knelt on George Floyd for more than nine minutes in May, saying Mr. Chauvin “should have stopped” when Mr. Floyd was calling out for help. Chief Medaria Arradondo said in court that Mr. Chauvin, who has been charged with murder, had failed to follow department policies on use-of-force, de-escalation, and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO: Full House As 40K Fans Fill Seats For RANGERS Opening Day!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/with-100-capacity-allowed-rangers-see-packed-stands-for-home-opener-at-globe-life-field/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 40,000 fans were inside Globe Life Field in Arlington Monday afternoon for the Texas Rangers' home opener.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOURTH Stimulus Check In The Works?</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/stimulus-check-update-fourth-relief-payment-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the latest round of stimulus checks already distributed to most eligible Americans, many wonder if additional aid is forthcoming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER halts vax shipments to Israel after country fails to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/banana-republic-pfizer-outraged-israel-failed-to-pay-for-covid-vaccines-664140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shipment of 700,000 doses was expected to arrive in Israel on Sunday but was halted until further notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU, Privacy Champion, Sharing Personal Info with FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/aclu-data-shares-facebook-4f1d21f4-d432-4998-8c67-364500015c28.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even organizations that don't like Facebook still find it an effective way to reach people online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS Not Following Guidance on PFIZER Spacing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/walgreens-not-following-u-s-guidance-on-pfizer-vaccine-spacing/ar-BB1fjIqp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walgreens has inoculated hundreds of thousands of Americans against Covid-19 this year using the vaccine developed by Pfizer and Germany’s BioNTech. But the pharmacy chain has not been following guidance from federal health officials about the timing of second doses. People are supposed to get two doses, three weeks apart. Walgreens, however, separated them by four weeks because that made it faster and simpler for the company to schedule...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid rule-breaker 'dies after exercise punishment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-56641398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was allegedly forced to do exercises after buying water during a curfew in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi to allow only 'immunised' pilgrims to Mecca...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210405-saudi-to-allow-only-immunised-pilgrims-to-mecca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi to allow only 'immunised' pilgrims to Mecca</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible second breach at toxic wastewater reservoir in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/possible-second-breach-toxic-wastewater-reservoir-florida-officials-say-n1263064</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone spotted the potential additional leak at about 2 a.m., forcing a brief evacuation of engineers at the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Gov Abbott Declines Invitation To Throw First Pitch At RANGERS Opening Game...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/texas-governor-mlb-false-narrative-voter-integrity-laws-1st-pitch-rangers-opener/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Greg Abbott declined to throw out the ceremonial first pitch at the opening game of the Texas Rangers because of his displeasure with Major League Baseball's decision to move this summer's All-Star game after sweeping changes to voting laws in Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Pilot Accused Of Exposing Genitals During Flight...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/southwest-pilot-michael-haak-accused-of-exposing-genitals-in-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities say pilot Michael Haak exposed his genitals in acts that began, continued and ended while flight 6607 on Aug. 10 was in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol arrests terror suspects in CA amid migrant surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/5/border-patrol-arrests-two-terrorist-suspects-calif/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Border Patrol announced Monday that agents arrested two Yemeni men who were on the FBI’s terrorist watch list over the past two months, confirming Republican lawmakers’ reports that terrorism suspects were attempting to sneak into the country as part of the migrant surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover Video Of Clandestine Luxury Dinner In Paris Prompts Police Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2021/04/05/984409984/undercover-video-of-clandestine-luxury-restaurants-in-paris-prompts-police-inqui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Once you pass through the door, there's no more COVID," a man told a visitor to one exclusive pop-up dining spot. The high-priced menu included Champagne and foie gras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White People Keep Posing As People of Color for Clout...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3vpn4/white-people-keep-posing-as-people-of-color-for-clout-identity-theft-racial-appropriation-v28n1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For generations, people of color have had to pass for survival. Now white people are wearing the experiences of racialized people like a costume—and getting called out for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END THE HYGIENE THEATER, CDC SAYS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/end-the-hygiene-theater-cdc-says-173440864.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s time to unplug the sanitizing robots and put away the bottles of Clorox that seem to line the entrance to every school, restaurant and supermarket wanting to advertise its safety protocols. While such protocols may be reassuring to an anxious populace, they are not necessary, revised guidance issued on Monday by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skepticism runs deep among white evangelicals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-baptist-coronavirus-pandemic-southern-baptist-convention-32898166bbb673ad87842af24c8daefb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president of the Southern Baptist Convention, America’s largest evangelical denomination, posted a photo on Facebook last week of him getting the COVID-19 vaccine. It drew more than 1,100...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Travel on Hold for UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/johnson-eases-lockdown-but-foreign-travel-on-hold-for-u-k/ar-BB1fkfNb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson confirmed restaurants, pubs and shops will open again as England’s lockdown is eased next week, but the ban on foreign travel may remain for longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Fed took control of economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/economy-federal-reserve-fed-control-2cc60f7f-4cde-43c7-9b83-5fa01d025b4a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with this control, the Fed has by its own admission failed to fully reach its goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Dead In TX Home In Suspected Murder-Suicide 'Pact'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/05/allen-murder-suicide-pact-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said there's a social media post by one of the victims saying he made a pact with his brother to kill his family and commit suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says trial is attempt at 'judicial coup'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/netanyahu-says-trial-is-a-witch-hunt-against-him-and-his-family-664185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  How evangelicals made Donald the new Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/161888/matt-labash-eric-metaxas-debate-trump-evangelicalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In which journalist Matt Labash (a Never Trumper) and radio host Eric Metaxas (a Trump supporter) agree to disagree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida bar owner didn't get in trouble for banning masks. But strip show landed him in jail!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-Florida-bar-owner-didn-t-get-in-trouble-for-16077074.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since September, Gary Kirby has banned masks and social distancing at his bar on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some patients get second shot at life thanks to lung transplants...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/some-covid-19-patients-get-second-shot-at-life-thanks-to-lung-transplants/article_476c942a-e96d-57e6-a658-7e25881161f9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio — Greg Borden knew that COVID-19 would wreak havoc on his body if he caught it, but he never expected it would take his lungs in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of stabbing family member to death after bible study...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-used-samurai-knife-to-kill-elderly-family-member-in-bellwood-prosecutors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is accused of stabbing an elderly family member dozens of times using a "samurai knife," killing her inside her Bellwood home before leaving with a phone and envelopes of cash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rules for GOOGLE in closely watched copyright case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/05/supreme-court-rules-in-googles-favor-in-copyright-dispute-with-oracle-over-android-software.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Monday sided with Google against Oracle in a long-running copyright dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLARENCE THOMAS: TREAT FACEBOOKGOOGLETWITTER LIKE UTILITIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/thomas-scotus-twitter-trump-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last fall, Justice Clarence Thomas argued that it was time to rein in Section 230 immunity. Now, Justice Thomas is laying out an argument for why companies like Facebook, Twitter and Google should be regulated as utilities. On Monday, the Supreme Court vacated a lower court ruling in finding that Pr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX, DRUGS AND MAGA?  Republicans Dumping Gaetz...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/mediaites-colby-hall-says-conservatives-are-dumping-matt-gaetz-crickets-coming-from-the-gop-caucus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mediaite Founding Editor Colby Hall weighed in on the Department of Justice's investigation into Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-FL) during a Monday morning appearance on Newsmax -- pointing to the complete lack of support the congressman has received from his own party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  USA WILL NOT MANDATE VACCINE PASSPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-vaccine-passports-fauci-federal-government-ece3e53c-82a1-4a14-8e0a-a92b547fe68b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea of requiring immunization credentials has become a point of contention.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
