<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>THE GREATEST</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/super-bowl-liii-rams-patriots-live-updates-score-halftime-show-commercials-today-2019-02-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots have won their sixth NFL championship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWFLAKE HITS OUT. DUMBO FEARS HE'S NEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/02/new-york-times-mary-poppins-racist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may never see the 1964 film “Mary Poppins” on television again – now that the New York Times has labeled it racist. In a piece for the paper by Professor Daniel Pollack-Pelzner, criticizes one of the film’s iconic moments, when Mary Poppins joins Dick Van Dyke’s Bert to dance on a rooftop for the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6!</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001016157/article/patriots-defeat-rams-133-in-super-bowl-liii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A low-scoring affair has returned the Patriots to the throne of pro football. New England defeated the Los Angeles Rams 13-3 in Super Bowl LIII on Sunday in Atlanta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lowest-scoring Super Bowl EVER...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/25918235/patriots-rams-combine-16-points-lowest-scoring-super-bowl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots took a 3-0 lead over the Los Angeles Rams into halftime, as the teams combined for the second-lowest-scoring half in Super Bowl history on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY, THE GREATEST</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/02/03/patriots-outlast-rams-in-win-sixth-super-bowl-franchise-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No, this is not a misprint. The New England Patriots are champions. Again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, JANET JACKSON:  Adam Levin shows his breasts during halftime show!</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/03/maroon-5-super-bowl-liii-halftime-show-shirtless-adam-levine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Levine sizzles during the Super Bowl halftime show ... shirtless, no less.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott Events in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/boycott-bowl-events-happening-in-new-orleans-sunday/26120355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a growing list of events happening around the New Orleans area where you can still show your support for the Black and Gold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male cheerleaders make history...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/8345660/super-bowl-male-cheerleaders-wow-crowd-la-rams-new-england-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Super Bowl’s first ever male cheerleaders took to the field tonight to wow the crowds as the epic clash kicked off in Atlanta. Quinton Peron and Napoleon Jinnies – who cheer for the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN anchor fired for leaking company information...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/03/rising-espn-star-adnan-virk-fired-escorted-out-in-leak-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN rising star Adnan Virk has been fired by the network, sources told The Post. Virk is accused of leaking confidential company information to the media on multiple occasions, according to source…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gladys Knight stuns crowds with exquisite national anthem...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/8345367/super-bowl-national-anthem-gladys-knight-star-spangled-banner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLADYS Knight stunned the crowds at the Super Bowl stadium tonight with her soulful rendition of the national anthem. The Empress of Soul had the audience in tears as she sang the Star-Spangled Ban…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM TOLD TO PURGE SUICIDE IMAGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2019/02/03/duty-care-matt-hancock-prepares-tell-instagram-boss-purge-site/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Health Secretary will tell the boss of Instagram he must use his experience of rooting out terrorist-related posts to purge the social media site of suicide and self-harm images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY POPPINS CALLED RACIST!  </title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/us-academic-sparks-mary-poppins-blackface-row-a4056126.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The classic family film Mary Poppins has been branded racist by a US academic who accuses Dame Julie Andrews of 'blacking up' with soot while dancing with chimney sweeps. In a piece for the New York Times, Professor Daniel Pollack-Pelzner criticises one of the film's iconic moments, when Mary Poppins joins Dick Van Dyke's Bert to dance on a rooftop for the classic song Step in Time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5G: Expert warns superfast broadband could cause cancer in humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/757194/5g-wireless-network-deadly-cancer-Arthur-Robert-Firstenberg-technology-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dementia patients to be tracked by smart meters in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6663779/Dementia-patients-tracked-smart-meters-doctors-monitor-sudden-changes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ministers have promised to install the devices in every home by 2020 to reduce energy consumption, but the rollout is massively over budget and behind schedule. Critics also warn of huge privacy concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-super-bowl/0ap3000001016001/Gladys-Knight-performs-National-Anthem-at-SBLIII</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gladys Knight sings the National Anthem at Super Bowl LIII.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of the Union Guests Will Reflect Immigration Split...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/state-of-the-union-guests-are-on-both-sides-of-border-wall-battle-11549197001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Trump delivers his State of the Union address, the debate over immigration that spurred the recent government shutdown will be well-represented in the guests invited to view from the House gallery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party leaving Hillary Clinton behind...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/02/democrats-are-leaving-hillary-clinton-behind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are heady days for Democrats. Speaker Nancy Pelosi is flexing her power in the House, state legislatures are sweeping away abortion boundaries and each day brings a new entry into the 2020 pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu, Trump grin down on Israelis in giant election poster...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netanyahu-trump-grin-down-israelis-giant-election-poster-161932676.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A giant billboard advert in Tel Aviv features Benjamin Netanyahu and US President Donald Trump grinning and shaking hands, as Israel's prime minister cranks up his campaign ahead of April elections. The 20 metre by 10 metre advert -- with the slogan "Netanyahu, in another league" in Hebrew</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Apologizes for Technical Difficulties Before Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cbs-news-sunday-morning-technical-difficulties-super-bowl-sunday-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech snafu hit the D.C. broadcast's full first segment and extended past commercials into the second, running nearly 10 minutes in total</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA' Win at Directors Guild Suggests Oscar Gold Around Corner...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/02/03/roma-win-at-directors-guild-suggests-oscar-gold-is-around-the-corner-for-alfonso-cuaron-and-maybe-marina-detavira</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alfonso Cuaron won Best Director last night at the DGA, as expected, for his brilliant movie “Roma.” It wasn’t unexpected. “Roma” is something that is going to happen …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider leaks Trump's private schedules...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-private-schedules-leak-executive-time-34e67fbb-3af6-48df-aefb-52e02c334255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unprecedented visibility into how the president spends his days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE takes rapper 21 SAVAGE into custody...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/21-savage-arrested-immigration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK TURNS CREEPIER; PAYS TO HARVEST ALL DATA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/02/proof-that-facebook-is-going-down-despite-its-big-earnings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook had a weird week. The social-media behemoth you love to hate posted some gaudy fourth-quarter earnings numbers on Wednesday. The report got a lot of likes on Wall Street. Some said it mean…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan opposition targeted by internet censors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d99b8fe46b434d3bb966b7531e04bf6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Opposition leader Juan Guaido's calls for Venezuelans to abandon Nicolas Maduro's government are booming across the world outside, but the self-declared interim president is having a harder time delivering his message at home. Watchdog groups in Venezuela and abroad say Guaido's efforts to reach citizens via the internet have been hindered by the dominant provider — state-run CANTV — in a country where critical newspapers and broadcast media already have been muzzled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDFACED:  Virginia governor clings to office, ignoring calls to resign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a41dfae7a1d49f48b15d1112b6db7a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Gov. Ralph Northam clung to office Sunday amid nearly unanimous calls from his own party to resign over a racist photo in his 1984 medical school yearbook, going silent after a bizarre 24 hours in which he first admitted he was in the picture, then denied it. The Democrat's stunning about-face — at a weekend news conference where he also acknowledged putting on blackface for a dance contest decades ago and appeared to briefly entertain the notion of doing the Michael Jackson moonwalk for reporters — only seemed to make things worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl Sunday, the last stand of live TV...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0b08f899347a46098ba8ffaad3f9ac51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Oh sure, there's plenty of evidence to support the soothsayers who are predicting the slow, inevitable death of live television. And there's plenty of proof to bolster theories about the NFL's slipping popularity. But when it comes to clicking away from Super Bowl Sunday — forget about it. Whether streaming it digitally, firing up the cable box or heading to a friend's house for chips, dip and commercials, it's a good bet that cord cutters, antenna owners and everyone in between can be found right where they always are on this day — gathered in front of the TV set in massive numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY FOR HISTORY!</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/02/03/super-bowl-why-the-rams-will-win/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McVay is half his age and in his first NFL title game, the youngest Super Bowl head man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASTOR USES BIBLE VERSE FOR SUPER BOWL PREDICTION:  RAM VS GOAT...</title>
      <link>http://949whom.com/new-hampshire-pastor-uses-bible-verse-for-super-bowl-prediction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;949whom.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out this cool sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINGER TO HONOR KNEELING PROTEST DURING HALFTIME SHOW?</title>
      <link>https://www.bizpacreview.com/2019/02/02/maroon-5-frontman-hints-superbowl-show-will-be-hip-hop-kneeling-fest-fox-news-offers-alternative-for-halftime-720139</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bizpacreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proud, flag-loving patriots who hate seeing the American flag be disrespected may have no other option but to tune out of the upcoming Super Bowl halftime show. The show has been mired in controversy because of a concerted effort by radical far-left activists to stop any artist from performing at the event. To them, any …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip from 'concerned citizen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-tip-from-a-concerned-citizen-helps-a-reporter-13585192.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reporter who exposed Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam's racist yearbook photo said a "concerned citizen" led him to the story that has prompted widespread outrage and calls for the Democrat's resignation. Patrick Howley, editor in chief of the website Big League Politics, first reported Friday the existence of a photo on Northam's page of his medical-school yearbook depicting a figure in blackface standing next to another person in a Ku Klux Klan hood. "It's very easy to explain," Howley, 29, said in an interview Saturday. "A concerned citizen, not a political opponent, came to us and pointed this out. I was very offended (by the photo) because I don't like racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Bow Wow arrested after fight with woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/crime/2019/02/rapper-bow-wow-arrested-after-fight-with-woman-in-atlanta-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper was booked with misdemeanor battery charges, according to CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party divide could be opening for independent...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/wide-party-divide-could-be-opening-independent-candidate-n966296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1987, only 25 percent said there was “a great deal” of difference in what the Democratic and Republican parties stood for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once red-hot smartphone market sees cooler trend...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190203-once-red-hot-smartphone-market-sees-cooler-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once red-hot smartphone market sees cooler trend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel begins construction of new Gaza border barrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190203-israel-begins-construction-new-gaza-border-barrier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel begins construction of new Gaza border barrier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Military intervention an 'option'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/428227-trump-military-intervention-in-venezuela-an-option</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump in an interview broadcast Sunday said U.S. military intervention in crisis-torn Venezuela is an “option.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: 'I would have a hard time' letting son play football...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/428233-trump-i-would-have-a-hard-time-letting-son-play-football</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said in an interview broadcast Sunday that he would let his son Barron play football if he wanted to, but that he would not steer him into that decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policewoman reprimanded for moonlighting in sex industry...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/crime/yamaguchi-policewoman-resigns-after-being-reprimanded-for-moonlighting-in-sex-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A policewoman in Shimonseki, Yamaguchi Prefecture, has resigned after she was reprimanded for working part-time at a fuzoku (sex industry) establishment. Yamaguchi prefectural police said this week that the officer, whose age and name were withheld, had worked at a commercial sex business in Fukuoka between September and November last year,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life under ISIS led these Muslims to Christ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/life-under-isis-led-these-muslims-christ-n963281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If heaven is made for ISIS and their belief, I would choose hell for myself instead of being again with them in the same place, even if it’s paradise."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAWAIIAN AIR flight returns to LAX three times...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/02/us/hawaiian-flight-33-turn-back/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 Hawaiian Airlines passengers aboard Flight 33 said "Aloha" to Los Angeles — and it meant both hello and goodbye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo drugged, raped teens, witness claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/el-chapo-drugged-and-raped-teenage-girls-witness-claims-11199544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK: A witness in the trial of Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman told the US government the Mexican drug kingpin drugged and raped girls as young as ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez doc wins Sundance audience award...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/428223-ocasio-cortez-campaign-documentary-wins-sundance-film-festival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Audience members at the annual Sundance Film Festival voted Saturday to recognize the documentary "Knock Down the House" with the festival's coveted annual audience award in the documentary category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa caucuses 1 year from today...</title>
      <link>http://www.newspressnow.com/news/local_news/iowans-look-ahead-a-year-to-presidential-caucuses/article_94d6163d-b7c5-5731-a291-98cb82ed3696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newspressnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank Jimmy Carter, or curse him if you prefer, for the steady stream of presidential candidates visiting Iowa every quadrennium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Some, Tax-Cuts Smaller Than They Once Appeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/for-some-companies-tax-cut-gains-are-smaller-than-they-once-appeared-11549195201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With earnings season in full swing, investors are starting to learn which companies were overly optimistic about their tax cuts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American anarchist 'John Galton' shot dead in Acapulco...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/3/john-galton-american-anarchist-shot-dead-acapulco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American anarchist who went by the name John Galton was shot dead at his home in the Mexican resort of Acapulco, sending shivers through a tightknit anti-establishment community of expatriates that organizes events in the violence-torn retreat with seminars on topics such as how to make money via cryptocurrencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theresa May vows to 'battle' in Brussels...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/theresa-may-vows-to-battle-in-brussels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust Paradox: Long Lives for Those Who Survived...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2019-01-28/holocaust-health-paradox-survivors-lived-longer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn jail lacks heat, hot water for week...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/2019/02/02/rally-held-at-brooklyn-jail-lacking-heat-hot-water-for-a-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — A congresswoman who visited a federal detention center in New York City where inmates have been stuck in cold, dark cells for days said Saturday it was "surreal" to hear the inmates banging on the walls. "I am frustrated. This is America. In America, everyone has rights," said Rep. Nydia Velazquez, a Democrat whose district includes the Metropolitan Detention Center in Brooklyn. "It's a violation of their human rights to be kept in the cold and not to be able to talk to anyone."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk Debt Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/junk-debt-is-back-11549142343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Junk-rated bonds and loans are flying off the shelves again, easing recent worries that a credit-market freeze could harm the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran -- where drug addicts outnumber high school students...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/philmatier/article/San-Francisco-where-street-addicts-outnumber-13571702.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco has more drug addicts than it has students enrolled in its public high schools, the city Health Department’s latest estimates conclude. There are about 24,500 injection drug users in San Francisco — that’s about 8,500 more people than the nearly 16,000 students enrolled in San Francisco Unified School District’s 15 high schools and illustrates the scope of the problem on the city’s streets. It’s also an increase of about 2,000 serious drug users since 2012, the last time a study was done. “There is an opioid epidemic in this country, and San Francisco is no exception,” Deputy Director of Health Dr. Naveena Bobba said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vivid' memory of blackening face to moonwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/virginia/government-politics/general-assembly/resisting-calls-to-resign-northam-denies-he-s-in-racist/article_f75d342d-e028-586e-8631-70d52424d604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ralph Northam refused to resign from his office Saturday and instead attempted to ride out a scandal that is threatening to end his political career by denying he was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret plan to evacuate Queen in case of Brexit unrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-royals/the-queen-to-be-evacuated-in-case-of-brexit-unrest-media-idUSKCN1PS005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British officials have revived Cold War emergency plans to relocate the royal fa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northam's bizarre press conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/02/ralph-northam-yearbook-1144281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Virginia governor joins the annals of bizarre political press conferences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coaching Duel: The Legend vs The Next One...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/02/02/guregian-super-coaching-duel-pits-the-legend-vs-the-next-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super Bowl pits the game’s most decorated head coach, Bill Belichick, against the NFL’s rising star, Sean McVay. Given their intellectual prowess, it figures to be an exciting chess…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refuses to Resign...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/virginia/article_311fc930-26ea-11e9-8adb-8777294eb3d2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic Virginia governor said Saturday afternoon that he had never seen the yearbook page until the day before when it was brought to his attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Queens' hidden sex district...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/02/inside-queens-hidden-sex-district/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s New York City’s Grand Central of illicit sex. A tiny Queens block has become a booming hotbed of hookers operating out of at least eight Chinese massage parlors, The Post found. The slim strip…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' star gets emotional: Attackers won't win...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a926a09b4af04ad19bb154468f53c9f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST HOLLYWOOD, Calif. (AP) — Jussie Smollett was blunt, emotional and defiantly determined Saturday night at a Southern California concert some urged him not to play, telling the crowd before singing a note that he had to go on with the show because he couldn't let his attackers win. "The most important thing I can say is 'thank you so much, and I'm OK," said the "Empire" actor and R&amp;amp;B singer from the stage at the Troubadour in West Hollywood in his first public appearance since he reported to police in Chicago on Tuesday that two masked men had assaulted him and put a rope around his neck while using homophobic and racial slurs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
