<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pilot Video, FAA Interview Reveal Bizarre Encounter With Unidentified Aircraft Over Atlantic City...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43986/pilot-video-and-faa-interview-reveal-bizarre-encounter-with-unidentified-aircraft-over-atlantic-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Air Force pilot flying a private plane seemed baffled after a strange-looking aircraft mirrored his maneuvers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Case Against Masks at School...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2022/01/kids-masks-schools-weak-science/621133/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Districts should rethink imposing on millions of children an intervention that provides little discernible benefit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists throughout Mexico say enough to killings and crimes against press...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/journalists-throughout-mexico-say-enough-to-killings-and-crimes-against-press/ar-AAT9q43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autopsy finds Palestinian American died of heart attack after bound and gagged by Israeli soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/autopsy-finds-palestinian-american-man-died-of-heart-attack-after-being-bound-and-gagged-by-israeli-soldiers/ar-AATamZn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks worst start to year ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/stock-market-2022-worst-start-year-ever-73c15533-b443-4290-8693-c215df7a44ab.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech shares tend to get disproportionately dinged up when interest rates rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Super Bowl nears, hundreds of LAPD employees sick...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/2500-lapd-and-sheriffs-department-employees-out-with-covid-related-issues-as-super-bowl-nears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Super Bowl events just a few weeks away, COVID-19 continues to wreak havoc with the Los Angeles Police Department and the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department, with about 2,500 personnel ei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside SUNDANCE Top-Secret Documentary on Putin Target Navalny...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-sundances-top-secret-documentary-on-putin-target-alexei-navalny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A last-minute add to the Sundance Film Festival, Daniel Roher’s ‘Navalny’ trails the Russian opposition leader as he takes on the evil Putin and investigates how he poisoned him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ZOOM'd out:' Kamala mulls escape from DC bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/26/harris-at-a-crossroads-shape-or-escape-the-d-c-bubble-00002173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallon hyped his NFTs on 'TONIGHT SHOW.' Conflict of interest?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/jimmy-fallon-hyped-his-bored-ape-nfts-on-the-tonight-show-conflict-of-interest/ar-AATabdj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime, Homelessness, Taxes: Hollywood Big Shots Fleeing LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hollywood-big-shot-fleeing-la-ryan-kavanaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles at a Crossroads: "A growing chorus of Hollywood executives are talking about leaving the city," one entertainment industry insider tells TheWrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anxiety tech' companies say glowing orbs, audio-playing rocks will improve mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Anxiety-tech-companies-say-their-glowing-orbs-16805366.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usually "mental health tech" means an app with some screen-based features such as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapaport films shoplifter boldly robbing NYC RITE AID...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/25/michael-rapaport-films-alleged-shoplifting-at-nyc-rite-aid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Rapaport posted a video of an alleged shoplifter walking out of a Manhattan Rite Aid, though the NYPD said there was no report of the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ reviewing role of fake Trump electors, top official says...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation-politics/justice-department-is-reviewing-role-of-fake-trump-electors-top-official-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Justice Department is investigating the fake slates of electors that falsely declared Donald Trump the victor of the 2020 election in seven swing states that Joe Biden had, in fact, won, a top agency official said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban peso in free fall against dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/cuba-economy-peso/cuban-peso-in-free-fall-against-the-dollar-idUSL1N2U50UV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cuban peso was trading at nearly 100 to the dollar on the informal market Tuesday, according to a trader and online trackers, a depreciation of more than 30% in less than a month and four times the fixed official rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NETFLIX first Arabic production ignites moral outrage in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20220126-netflix-s-first-arabic-production-ignites-moral-outrage-in-egypt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix's first Arabic film production was always set to be a big event, but within days of its release, public opinion in Egypt was so inflamed that critics called for a ban on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto, NFTs Rife With Fraud, IRS Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/irs-seeing-mountains-and-mountains-of-fraud-with-crypto-nfts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto, NFTs Are Rife With ‘Mountains’ of Fraud, IRS Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're Probably in Simulation. How Much Should That Worry Us?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/26/were-probably-in-a-simulation-how-much-should-that-worry-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine that when your great-grandparents were teenagers, they got their hands on a groundbreaking new gadget, the world’s first fully</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's biggest sperm donor' has fathered 129 children...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4542139/worlds-biggest-sperm-donor-health-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN who says he’s the “world’s most prolific sperm donor” has claimed he has fathered 129 children – but now medical experts have warned against his actions. Clive Jones, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy wants to get crashed stealth fighter back -- before China can...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/asia/us-f-35-crash-recovery-south-china-sea-intl-hnk-ml/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Navy is trying to retrieve its most advanced fighter jet from the depths of the South China Sea, an extremely complex operation that analysts say will be closely monitored by Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Cell Phone Usage Can Damage Sperm Quality...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cell-phone-usage-damage-sperm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers found that cell phone usage increases exposure to radiofrequency electromagnetic waves that could damage sperm quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Identify Factors That Appear Linked to Long Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/scientists-identify-factors-that-appear-linked-to-long-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists Identify Factors That Appear Linked to Long Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most PORNHUB-obsessed cities revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4539646/most-pornhub-obsessed-cities-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GLOBAL sex report has revealed the most Pornhub-obsessed cities in the world and you may be surprised at which location is on top. The research was conducted by LookFantastic with the aim of find…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Exhaustion After Walk May Signal Death Within 3 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/older-adults-fatigue-early-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older adults who feel particularly tired after activities such as light housework or a 30-minute walk may be at an increased risk of dying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi stock trades attract growing following online...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-house-speaker-pelosis-stock-trades-attract-growing-following-online-2022-01-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year since a Reddit-driven retail trading frenzy rocked the markets and created the 'meme stock' phenomenon, leading U.S. lawmaker Nancy Pelosi's investments have become a meme in their own right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support your children if they are gay, pope tells parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/support-your-children-if-they-are-gay-pope-tells-parents-2022-01-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis said on Wednesday that parents of gay children should not condemn them but offer them support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EYES ON FED</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/inflation-fighting-fed-likely-flag-march-interest-rate-hike-2022-01-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve is expected on Wednesday to signal plans to raise interest rates in March as it focuses on fighting inflation and sets aside, at least for now, economic risks posed by the ongoing coronavirus pandemic, a bout of market volatility, and Western fears of a Russian invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran 567% increase in anti-Asian hate crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/san-francisco-police-mark-567-increase-in-anti-asian-hate-crime-reports-in-2021/ar-AAT9JpH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Selloff Ultimate Test of What's Real and What's Not...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-26/is-the-stock-market-crashing-2022-stress-test-has-companies-crypto-scrambling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican defends Benedict after report faults abuse record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-religion-crime-germany-sexual-abuse-by-clergy-a7926c80e9af1a6c7688e3529231de82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican on Wednesday strongly defended Pope Benedict XVI’s record in fighting clergy sexual abuse and cautioned against looking for “easy scapegoats and summary judgments," after an independent report faulted his handling of four cases of abuse when he was archbishop of Munich, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATE HIKE MARCH?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-stock-markets-economy-1dd9283e46162b3c0d29a2c55a2934d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Wild volatility in the stock market this week has put heightened scrutiny on the Federal Reserve's meeting Wednesday and whether the Fed will clarify just how fast it plans to tighten credit and potentially slow the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest gorilla Ozzie dead at 61...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4541224/ozzie-zoo-atlanta-oldest-gorilla-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OZZIE, the world’s oldest male gorilla was found dead at Zoo Atlanta on Tuesday. He was 61-years-old. The primate had tested positive for Covid-19 last year along with a group of other gorill…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-variant of omicron on rise, WHO warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nny360.com/news/sub-variant-of-omicron-on-the-rise-who-warns/article_55f16a36-7f18-54af-b711-b9841536e904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nny360.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization warned this week that a sub-variant of omicron was on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia moves troops and USA sends weapons as fear of war mounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-moves-troops-and-us-sends-weapons-as-fear-of-war-mounts-in-ukraine/ar-AAT6Wri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He trades bitcoin naked. El Salvador paying price...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/he-trades-bitcoin-naked-el-salvador-is-paying-the-price/ar-AAT9azC </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guns stolen from rail cars spark LAPD concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/guns-stolen-from-rail-cars-spark-lapd-concern/article_d8a2c8f5-ae59-5caa-b21b-96d3dae43368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Guns are among the items that have been stolen from cargo containers on railroad tracks in Lincoln Heights, Los Angeles Police Chief Michel Moore said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths months after COVID point to pandemic's grim aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/deaths-months-after-covid-point-to-pandemic-s-grim-aftermath</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths Months After Covid Point to Pandemic’s Grim Aftermath</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picasso heirs launch digital art piece to ride 'crypto' wave...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-01-picasso-heirs-digital-art-piece.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pablo, meet Crypto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones says he took Fifth  '100 times' before Jan. 6 panel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/25/alex-jones-pleaded-the-fifth-nearly-100-times-when-questioned-by-jan-6-panel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infowars founder Alex Jones met with the House select committee investigating last year’s Capitol riot and exercised his right against self-incrimination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capsized boat found near Florida; 39 people missing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/florida-bahamas-us-coast-guard-fort-pierce-67fff9ed65f0432d2cfb09ce309eaff1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The U.S. Coast Guard searched on Tuesday for 39 people missing for several days after a boat believed to be used for human smuggling capsized off Florida’s coast en route from the Bahamas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook wins restraining order against stalker...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/25/1075619867/tim-cook-stalker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge granted a restraining order against a woman who allegedly showed up twice to Cook's home in Palo Alto. The filing states she also threatened Cook with photos of a handgun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto plunge wipes out profits for everyday investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/crypto-collapse-erases-more-than-1-trillion-in-wealth-forcing-a-reckoning-for-everyday-investors/ar-AAT8lXj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Jose approves gun owners liability insurance...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/san-jose-approves-controversial-gun-owners-liability-insurance-residents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California city has approved liability insurance for gun owners, the first such measure in the US, as it seeks to lower gun violence through stricter rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WITHDRAWS VAX MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/politics/vaccine-mandate-osha-withdrawn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is withdrawing its Covid-19 vaccination and testing regulation aimed at large businesses, following the Supreme Court's decision to block the rule earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Germany, activists rise up to counter vax skeptics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-berlin-religion-5dc72a0b8fa6956be7227b4100f23f4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Stefanie Hoener was at home one night in Berlin when she heard police sirens wailing through her Prenzlauer Berg neighborhood and anti-vaccine protesters shouting angry slurs as they marched down to the Gethsemane Church — a symbol of the peaceful 1989 revolution in East Germany that ended the communist dictatorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK holds breath as it awaits 'partygate' report...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-boris-johnson-health-business-london-75fb04edd2fb45483f5276bd1fe05079</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Prime Minister Boris Johnson is bracing for the conclusions of an investigation into allegations of lockdown-breaching parties, a document that could help him end weeks of scandal and discontent, or bring his time in office to an abrupt close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netherlands eases restrictions despite rising cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60129830</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch hospitality venues, including bars and restaurants, have been closed since 18 December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi running -- again!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/591339-pelosi-says-she-will-run-for-reelection-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) announced on Tuesday that she will run for reelection in 2022, quelling speculation for now that this year may be her last in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows adult male migrants released for transport across US...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/25/video-shows-adult-male-migrants-released-for-transport-across-us-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of single, mostly male adult migrants were reportedly shuttled from a makeshift processing center in Texas to a local airport for flights to various US cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sex robot swap shop' -- where lovers trade USED dolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17439812/used-sex-dolls-sold-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USED sex dolls are being sold online for a fraction of the original prize and people are snapping them up. Some of the used dolls come with names and even have human hair. A website called Galmato …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF urges El Salvador:  Drop bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/25/drop-bitcoin-as-legal-tender-imf-urges-el-salvador.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are large risks associated with the use of bitcoin on financial stability, financial integrity, and consumer protection," says the International Monetary Fund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  Extremists see power grid as target...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-united-states-law-enforcement-agencies-9e3d1d4d4cd429b69a787235caa7e4b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Extremist groups in the United States appear to increasingly view attacking the power grid as a means of disrupting the country, according to a government report aimed at law enforcement agencies and utility operators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside San Fran's open air drug market...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10439965/Photos-new-linkage-SF-facility-populated-drug-users-shooting-broad-daylight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images depict an illicit drug consumption site at a new linkage center in San Francisco that is now littered with needles and crowded with addicts shooting up in broad daylight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds looking at fake elector certifications...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/politics/fake-trump-electoral-certificates-justice-department/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors are reviewing fake Electoral College certifications that declared former President Donald Trump the winner of states that he lost, Deputy Attorney General Lisa Monaco told CNN on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booster drive faltering...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-492fb86ff65c0f9a2d87b129e5da90a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The COVID-19 booster drive in the U.S. is losing steam, worrying health experts who have pleaded with Americans to get an extra shot to shore up their protection against the highly contagious omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY forced to 'seize control' of Harry, Meghan's $675k-a-minute podcast flop

...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/17284466/queen-elizabeth-prince-harry-meghan-markle-spotify-latest-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOTIFY is taking Harry and Meghan’s £18million podcast project “into its own hands” by hiring a host of in-house producers to finally help deliver content. The streaming giant ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals use lottery to allocate scarce drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2022/01/25/1075432400/hospitals-use-a-lottery-to-allocate-scarce-covid-drugs-for-the-immunocompromised</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far the government has distributed about 300,000 doses of Evusheld, a new drug that protects against COVID-19. Some 7 million Americans could benefit from the drug right away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook targeted at home by possibly armed stalker...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2022/01/25/apple-ceo-tim-cook-targeted-by-possibly-armed-stalker-who-came-to-his-home-and-is-still-in-the-area-company-alleges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple cites ‘erratic, threatening, and bizarre behavior’ by woman who reportedly drove Porsche SUV to Palo Alto from Virginia in pursuit of company CEO Tim Cook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY consulting 'dwarfism community' on new 'SNOW WHITE'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/01/peter-dinklage-snow-white-disney-response-1234919571/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney has responded to remarks made yesterday by award-winning actor Peter Dinklage that called the studio’s plans for a live-action remake of Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs “f*cking …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Brown: BUCS tried to pay me $200K 'to go to crazy house'...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/patriots/2022/01/antonio-brown-buccaneers-tried-to-pay-me-200k-to-go-to-the-crazy-house.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brown sat down for an interview for the first time since throwing his uniform into the stands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even CNN Not Sure Who Will Replace Chris Cuomo...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/tv/news/cnn-chris-cuomo-brianna-keilar-jim-acosta-1235162755/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let’s get after it: Even as CNN puts much of its energy into launching a new streaming-video hub, it’s also trying to figure out how to replace Chris Cuomo in its pivotal 9 p.m. time slot. Some sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tallest mountain on Earth ascended -- for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/hawaii/article/Men-climb-Earths-tallest-mountain-16784886.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It wasn’t easy. This was like a very difficult triathlon."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Warns: Would Be 'Largest Invasion Since World War II'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/biden-warns-russia-invading-ukraine-could-change-the-world-would-be-the-largest-invasion-since-world-war-ii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden spoke in grave terms as he told reporters what the fallout could be like if Russia does end up invading Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Human smuggling' boat carrying 40 capsizes off Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4538952/human-smuggling-boat-capsizes-florida-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RESCUE mission is underway after a suspected human smuggling boat carrying 40 people capsized off the Florida coast, sparking a massive US Coast Guard effort. Officials said the boat capsized on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELTON JOHN TESTS POSITIVE FOR COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4538381/elton-john-cancel-tour-dates-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIR Elton John has been forced to cancel two dates on his delayed Farewell Yellow Brick Road tour after testing positive for coronavirus. The singer, 74, confirmed he had been vaccinated and said h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families fight to use deceased child's sperm to be grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-694548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Wahlberg, Mel Gibson faith-based 'FATHER STU' set for Good Friday release...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/mark-wahlberg-mel-gibson-movie-father-stu-sony-1235162943/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony Pictures has acquired “Father Stu,” a true-life drama starring Mark Wahlberg and Mel Gibson. Rosalind Ross wrote and directed the faith-based movie, which will be released in theat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside lab keeping frozen heads of 200 to be brought back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4535228/lab-keeping-frozen-bodies-heads-brought-back-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAB is holding the bodies and heads of 200 people in the hope that they can be brought to life in the future. The Alcor Life Extension Foundation offers the hope that science and technology will …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Oath Keepers plead not guilty to sedition charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/politics/oath-keepers-plead-not-guilty/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten Oath Keepers, including leader Stewart Rhodes, pleaded not guilty on Tuesday to new charges, including seditious conspiracy, related to the January 6, 2021, attack at the US Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. requires strippers to be masked...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2022/01/25/washington-d-c-strip-clubs-mask-mandate-warnings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington D.C. strip clubs have allegedly been warned about employees not wearing masks. Are strippers required to wear masks?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Jose closer to first-in-nation gun ownership requirements...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/us/san-jose-gun-law/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Jose, California, is getting closer to adopting a first-in-the-nation law to address gun violence by requiring all gun owners to pay a fee and carry liability insurance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV News Joins Streaming's Nostalgia Programming...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/cbs-cnn-nbc-streaming-programming-1235080401/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Networks like CBS and CNN are leaning on "iconic franchises" and "old-school" reporters in a bid to transition linear audiences to digital viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATE HIKE MARCH?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/25/the-federal-reserve-is-likely-to-signal-a-march-rate-hike.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with the market's violent correction, a hawkish Federal Reserve is expected to signal it plans to raise interest rates and consider other tightening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police investigating...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220125165641-ihwnx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-POLITICS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-British police probe lockdown parties in new blow to PM Johnson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Kennedy Jr apologizes for Holocaust remarks at anti-vaxxer rally...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220125163439-jrwmt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-KENNEDY/ (TV):Robert Kennedy Jr apologizes for Holocaust remarks at anti-vaxxer rally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Media Outlet GRID Backed by Progressive Stars, Gulf Money...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/uae-lobbyists-developed-progressive-media-outlet-grid-with-funding-from-uae-deputy-prime-minister/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new progressive media outlet Grid, which has attracted press buzz and big-name talent, was developed by registered lobbyists for the United Arab Emirates with funding from UAE's deputy prime minister, the Washington Free Beacon has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes Beats Brady As Chiefs Win Top Playoff Viewership With 43 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/01/tom-brady-nfl-patrick-mahomes-super-bowl-viewrship-networks-division-1234919304/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s just over two weeks to go to Super Bowl LVI, but the NFL’s Big Game is going to have to be something very special to top the drama of the game between the Los Angeles Rams and hosts Tom Bra…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
