<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Top MAGA gathering finds new reality complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/27/cpac-2021-462907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CPAC was at the top of its powers last year. Then Covid-19 hit, Trump lost, and the postelection chaos ensued. Now, the confab has some challenges ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK LOCKDOWN UNTIL MARCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/uks-johnson-warns-lockdown-will-last-until-at-least-march-8/ar-BB1d8UKN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson put England on notice that the national virus lockdown will continue for at least another six weeks, with schools staying closed and new border quarantine rules coming into force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Holds Off On New Lockdown, Worries About Unrest Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/france-holds-off-on-new-lockdown-worries-about-unrest-risk/ar-BB1d8Gyf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government is delaying an agonizing decision to lock down the country once more, mulling options to slow new variants of Covid-19 as the current curfew is considered insufficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 23ANDME Tool Assesses Risk of Covid Becoming Severe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/new-23andme-tool-assesses-risk-of-covid-19-becoming-severe/ar-BB1d8VpA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DNA-testing company 23andMe Inc. has launched a new tool that aims to predict an infected person’s risk of developing a severe case of Covid-19, expanding the company’s bid to deliver actionable insight on health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's 2021 COVID-19 Bill Costs More Than Entire 1981 Federal Government!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/bidens-2021-covid-19-bill-costs-more-entire-1981-federal-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $1.9 trillion relief bill that President Joe Biden wants Congress to pass now as his response to the COVID-19 pandemic would cost Americans more than the entire federal government cost in fiscal 1981.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All against all'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/27/russias-putin-warns-of-a-fight-of-all-against-all-at-wef.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin warned the World Economic Forum that the coronavirus pandemic has exacerbated preexisting imbalances and tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Donald rehab his reputation? Some lessons from Nixon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-trump-rehab-reputation-130022440.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Khachigian joined the president in exile after Watergate. One suggestion for Trump: Be quiet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trigger Volatility Halts Across Market...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/reddit-fueled-traders-trigger-volatility-160742020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The number of volatility halts across equity markets has soared in recent days amid the rapid ascension of amateur traders armed with Robinhood and their favorite social media platforms.About 30 circuit breaker halts were triggered in the first hour of trading Wednesday due to a rocky session that sent ripples across the stock market. From cult-favorite GameStop Corp. to stereo headphone and loudspeaker retailer Koss Corp., trading volume soared as gains and losses fluctuated by the minute.Day traders have taken to online forums like Reddit, posting bullish touts to encourage others to join an epic retail frenzy that has tested the mettle of short sellers. Reddit is also routinely used to drive up penny stocks that, unlike GameStop, have ceased publishing financial results and don’t trade on regulated exchanges. Volatility halts are relatively common for small stocks that are surging or tumbling and are used by exchanges to help smooth rapid movement in either direction and prevent flash crashes. They are often done to force traders to digest the news and recalibrate their trades over the typical five-minute pause.Online brokerages including Robinhood Markets and Charles Schwab Corp. were hit again Wednesday by service disruptions as traders were transfixed by wild swings in shares of GameStop Corp. and other heavily shorted stocks. TD Ameritrade Holding Corp., Morgan Stanley’s E*Trade and Fidelity were also affected, according to Downdetector.com, which tracks user complaints.GameStop shares, which soared as much as 140% in early trading, were halted at least twice, while movie theater company AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc. triggered four halts as it more than quadrupled on volume that was roughly ten times the three-month average.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI steps up efforts to build conspiracy case in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/536064-fbi-steps-up-efforts-to-build-conspiracy-case-on-capitol-riot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is stepping up its efforts to build a possible conspiracy case after authorities have arrested more than 150 people for their alleged role in the Capitol riot, law enforcement officials said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST REQUIRED FOR DOMESTIC TRAVEL?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210126222729-wmirw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAVEL (PIX):U.S. 'actively looking' at mandating COVID-19 testing for domestic air travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Average Human Fatter Than Elephant...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/humans-fatter-than-an-elephant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find the average human carries between 6 and 31 percent body fat. The average male elephant carries less than 9 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New war on opposition suggests he sees it as real threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/opinions-putins-new-war-on-the-opposition-suggests-he-sees-it-as-a-real-threat/ar-BB1d8VPA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both sides seem to think the future of Russia is at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China rolls out new anal swab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/china-rolls-out-new-anal-23393894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapid, invasive test inserts a swab 2-3 centimetres into the rectum and rotates it several times. It is currently being used in Beijing to curb the spread of a new Covid outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dangerous Lives of NFL Cheerleaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-dangerous-lives-of-nfl-cheerleaders </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five or six doses? Controversy over PFIZER vials...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210127-five-or-six-doses-controversy-over-pfizer-vaccine-vials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five or six doses? Controversy over Pfizer vaccine vials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks slide... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/26/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors pored through mixed earnings from major companies and awaited the latest policy decision from the Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People must explain travel reasons under new border measures...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210127135918-tptoe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-PATEL (URGENT):People must explain travel reasons under new British border measures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Arrested for Killing Weak to Save Strong...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/did-this-italian-covid-doc-kill-the-weak-to-save-the-strong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A primary care physician from one of the hardest hit regions in Italy has been arrested for lethally injecting weak COVID patients to free up beds during the peak of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots disinfecting hotels. It's tip of hospitality revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/robots-are-disinfecting-hotels-during-the-pandemic-it-e2-80-99s-the-tip-of-a-hospitality-revolution/ar-BB1d8SjZ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under Biden, Dems ready to revive net neutrality rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/under-biden-democrats-are-ready-to-revive-net-neutrality-rules/ar-BB1d8PCW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House, Federal Communications Commission and Congress face early pressure to bring back open-Internet safeguards scrapped under former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope marking Holocaust warns another genocide possible...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-pope-francis-europe-the-holocaust-5cad22f0e43abc3d3bc33d2b3526585f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis marked Holocaust Remembrance Day on Wednesday by warning that warped ideologies can pave the way to another genocide. Francis spoke off the cuff at the end of his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys leader was 'prolific' informer for law enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210127130008-0o116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PROUDBOYS/LEADER (EXCLUSIVE):EXCLUSIVE-Proud Boys leader was ‘prolific’ informer for law enforcement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International team disables world's most dangerous malware...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210127125007-efnid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International team disables world's most dangerous malware:International team disables world's most dangerous malware</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican TV host under fire after going to Florida to get shot...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/26/mexican-tv-host-gets-covid-shot-in-florida-amid-vaccine-tourism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Mexican TV host is under fire after traveling to Florida just to get the coveted COVID-19 vaccine, which most Americans have not received. Juan José Origel, who’s famous for hosting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump leaves GOP with identity crisis. First test: Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-leaves-gop-identity-crisis-110041043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Virginia races this year to the 2022 midterm, Republicans will face contests that pit Trump loyalists against those who want to distance the party from him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden signals tougher Russia stance in call with Vladimir...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-signals-tougher-russia-stance-213819197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden signalled a tougher US stance on Russia Tuesday in his first phone call with President Vladimir Putin, raising concerns over human rights and "aggression" against Ukraine, but welcoming cooperation on a new nuclear weapons accord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates Shocked by 'Evil' Microchip Theories...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-gates-conspiracies-idUSKBN29W0Q3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft co-founder turned philanthropist Bill Gates says he has been taken aback by the volume of "crazy" and "evil" conspiracy theories about him spreading on social media during the COVID-19 pandemic, but said on Wednesday he would like to explore what is behind them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly let 'college kids' distribute jabs. Result was 'disaster'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/philadelphia-let-e2-80-98college-kids-e2-80-99-distribute-vaccines-the-result-was-a-e2-80-98disaster-volunteers-say/ar-BB1d8ns7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One volunteer alleged that the 22-year-old CEO had pocketed vaccine doses. Another described a “free-for-all” where unsupervised 18- and 19-year-olds vaccinated one another and posed for photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART to build more robot-filled warehouses at stores...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/plano-texas-0237967389d2cc911f1ee729a9aacf19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Walmart is enlisting the help of robots to keep up with a surge in online orders. The company said Wednesday that it plans to build warehouses at its stores where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>131 arrested on 'calmer' night during Dutch curfew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mark-rutte-general-elections-netherlands-media-social-media-06f771a568eebdac2cdfbb99f6cc0740</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — Dutch police said Wednesday that the fourth night of the Netherlands' coronavirus curfew passed more peacefully than the previous three nights marred by rioting. Even...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swearing sign of intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9189539/Science-reveals-swearing-sign-intelligence-creativity-helps-endure-pain.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science shows using foul language may be beneficial. People who curse are seen as more honest, found to have a more fluent vocabulary and withstand more pain when using such words.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanted: New media bosses, everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/wanted-new-media-bosses-everywhere-658eb3b4-062a-4551-97d4-ef8ca4a40fb3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Post is the latest looking for a new boss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wear THREE masks?</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2021/01/27/experts-now-say-americans-should-wear-three-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why not just a full Hazmat suit?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With All Eyes on Covid, Drug-Resistant Infections Crept In...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/27/with-all-eyes-on-covid-19-drug-resistant-infections-crept-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Covid-19 took hold over the last year, hospitals and nursing homes used and reused scarce protective equipment — masks,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVY 'UFO Patent' Details 'Spacetime Modification Weapon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/38937/navy-ufo-patent-documents-talk-of-spacetime-modification-weapon-detail-experimental-testing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy spent three years and considerable sums of money testing the "Pais Effect" and may have transferred the program to another agency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT Traders Take on Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/gamestop-stock-market-0689e407-d1a3-4947-b4b5-5aef23c72acf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Short-selling is a crucial but dangerous element of efficient markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator presiding over trial taken to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senator-presiding-over-trump-impeachment-000826689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 80-year-old senator presiding over the impeachment trial of Donald Trump was briefly hospitalized Tuesday after sounding hoarse and unwell while being swore in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK's Covid death toll now worse than Great Plague, AIDS and the Blitz  -- combined?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/uks-covid-19-death-toll-23391399</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grim milestone surpasses the combined fatalities from the Great Plague, Aids pandemic, Blitz and all terror attacks and wars since 1945, which stood at 99,500</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father-of-seven who moved family from CA to TX then back again defends scathing op-ed complaining about Austin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9190455/Sales-exec-moved-family-California-Texas-jokes-Brett-new-Karen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brett Alder who moved his family from San Diego to Texas has defended his op-ed complaining about the rude locals and the oppressive heat in Austin and joked that 'Brett' is the new 'Karen'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: KGB began grooming 'young and vain' Donald Trump 40 years ago by saving him from financial ruin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9184687/How-Russia-began-grooming-Donald-Trump-40-years-ago-saving-financial-ruin-book-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Kompromat How the KGB Cultivated Donald Trump, and Related Tales of Sex, Greed, Power, and Treachery by Craig Unger is out January 26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The end of offices? New York's business districts face uncertain future...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/end-offices-yorks-business-districts-022038475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boarded-up stores, shuttered restaurants and empty office towers: Covid-19 has turned New York's famous business districts into ghost towns, with companies scrambling to come up with ways to entice workers to return post-pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS:  I'M DEEPLY SORRY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jan/26/ons-figures-show-uk-passed-100000-covid-deaths-by-7-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PM says it is ‘hard to compute the sorrow’ after number of deaths passes 100,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On this day in 1700, a magnitude 9.0 earthquake hit Western Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/northwest/on-this-day-in-1700-the-really-big-one-a-magnitude-9-0-earthquake-hit-western-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last huge earthquake, the last really "Big One" to hit the Pacific Northwest coast, struck around 9 p.m. on Jan. 26, 1700 — 321 years ago today. Japanese sources document the event, as do Indian legends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine Rollout Misses TSA Screeners...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/vaccine-rollout-misses-tsa-screeners-air-traffic-controllers/ar-BB1d7q5p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s incredibly frustrating.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans warned against travel as variants spread and testing rules go in effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/americans-warned-against-travel-as-covid-variants-spread-and-testing-rules-go-in-effect/ar-BB1d7vTj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jan. 27—The State Department warned Americans to strongly reconsider travel Tuesday as a new COVID-19 testing requirement went into effect and new variants of the virus were detected in Latin America and the Caribbean. "If you're overseas right now, it could be harder to come home for awhile," said Ian Brownlee, the State Department's acting assistant secretary for consular affairs. "Everyone ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk and Bezos risk space war over AMAZON satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-jeff-bezos-spark-23390890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk and Jeff Bezos are engaged in a war of words over satellite-based internet access, with the Amazon boss claiming that Musk's Starlink satellites could get in the way of his rival system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid sends big advertisers to sidelines for Super Bowl...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-sends-big-advertisers-sidelines-205609139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's Super Bowl will be missing some familiar big names from its advertising roster, with several major brands choosing to remain on the sidelines of America's football championship due to the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT FOR THE HEAVENS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/barbs-fly-over-satellite-projects-202425563.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spat erupted Tuesday between Jeff Bezos and Elon Musk as the tech titans' space firms exchanged barbs over their rival satellite internet projects being evaluated by regulators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pamela Anderson Quits Socials: 'I'm Free'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/pamela-anderson-instagram-twitter-facebook-b1793034.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Baywatch star also urged her followers to ‘find the strength and inspiration to follow your purpose’ and ‘not to be seduced by wasted time’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly CEO Accused of Taking 'Home Ziplock Bag-Full' of Doses...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/01/26/philadelphia-health-commissioner-dr-thomas-farley-claims-philly-fighting-covid-ceo-andrei-doroshin-taking-home-vaccines-disturbing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If that’s true, that’s very disturbing, they shouldn’t do that," Dr. Farley said during Tuesday's press conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertitta optimistic: 'Going to be Roaring Twenties'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/26/tilman-fertitta-sees-another-roaring-twenties-for-economy-post-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The consumer is coming back. I'm telling you, where we can do business, we are doing business," Tilman Fertitta told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linda Tripp memoir reveals dirty details...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/26/linda-tripp-memoir-reveals-how-she-learned-of-clinton-affair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her posthumous memoir, Linda Tripp, reveals the moment she learned of Monica Lewinsky’s affair with Bill Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let down your hair: New Army rules for ponytails, nail color...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-race-and-ethnicity-mark-esper-army-74e5d71ad043d0276d8cd46b7e76377f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Female soldiers can let their hair down, and flash a little nail color under new rules being approved by the Army. But male soldiers will still have to shave. Army leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA announces restoration of relations with Palestinians...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-world-news-israel-united-nations-a5f546bf188f808ba29f381d76d44729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — U.S. President Joe Biden’s administration announced Tuesday it was restoring relations with the Palestinians and renewing aid to Palestinian refugees, a reversal of the Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS hires Kudlow; McEnany may be next...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-larry-kudlow-kayleigh-mcenany-58f61b819e20ce588dc84723dabb3306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Trump administration alumni Larry Kudlow is joining Fox News amid reports that a colleague, former White House press secretary Kayleigh McEnany, will soon be joining him. Fox...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman upset by corona protocols throws bricks at CHICK-FIL-A...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/cops-woman-upset-by-covid-19-protocols-throws-bricks-at-buckhead-chick-fil-a/C6AEFYM6BJB73F4UYVRUOMZKZ4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was no pleasure for workers at a Buckhead Chick-fil-A to bar an irate woman from the restaurant Monday night after she allegedly railed against COVID-19 protocols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Warns Former Officers About Working for Foreign Govts...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/26/c-i-a-warns-former-officers-about-working-for-foreign-governments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The C.I.A.’s counterintelligence chief sent a note to retired officers this week warning against working for foreign governments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rep. indicated support for executing prominent Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/26/politics/marjorie-taylor-greene-democrats-violence/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene repeatedly indicated support for executing prominent Democratic politicians in 2018 and 2019 before being elected to Congress, a CNN KFile review of hundreds of posts and comments from Greene's Facebook page shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry farmers storm India Red Fort in challenge to Modi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-farmer-protest-654ef151a8af6de8c264c29363d0607b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Tens of thousands of farmers marched, rode horses and drove tractors into India’s capital on Tuesday, breaking through police barricades to storm the historic Red Fort — a deeply...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top malls' values crumble; Down 45%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/26/top-tier-mall-values-have-dropped-45percent-from-2016-levels-green-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commercial real estate services firm Green Street estimates so-called A-rated mall values have tumbled roughly 45% from 2016 levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 5 Republican senators vote Impeachment II is constitutional...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/535925-senate-rejects-paul-effort-to-declare-trump-impeachment-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate sent a strong signal Tuesday that there are not nearly enough votes to convict President Trump in an impeachment trial when only five GOP senators rejected an effort by Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kudlow Signs With FOXBUSINESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/larry-kudlow-fox-business-network-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Kudlow, former National Economic Council director under Donald Trump, will host a new show on Fox Business Network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia lawmaker booted from chamber for failing to get test...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/georgia-lawmaker-booted-from-chamber-for-failing-to-get-covid-19-test/UA2BRME7TVEQHOKKFVIQNRWJ4E/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Georgia state representative was removed from the House chamber Tuesday for refusing to be tested for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF chief orders plans to thwart Iran's nuke program...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/idf-chief-ive-instructed-military-to-prepare-plans-to-thwart-irans-nuke-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The only samurai colony ever attempted outside of Japan was in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/sfhistory/article/wakamatsu-farm-japanese-immigrants-california-15896619.php?IPID=SFGate-HP-CP-Spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first families from Japan arrived in California with fanfare, and most disappeared...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic Incidents Surge; 'Moving Into Dangerous Phase'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/anti-semitic-incidents-on-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Jewish leaders said the growth of crimes against Jews intensified under former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Fueling Deaths Of Despair...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/01/26/960492035/deaths-of-despair-how-the-pandemic-may-be-fueling-lethal-drug-overdoses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As drug overdose deaths rise during the pandemic, a former White House economist says social isolation could be partly to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: AC Unit Falls On FDNY Firefighter While Battling Blaze...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/01/26/air-conditioning-unit-falls-on-firefighter-in-bensonhurst-brooklyn-fdny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrifying moments were caught on camera at the scene of a fire in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Scant spread in schools --  with precautions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-finds-with-precautions-in-place-scant-spread-of-coronavirus-in-schools/ar-BB1d7hsi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers warn that indoor athletics, without masks and with close contact, pose danger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERIZONGOOGLEZOOM stall out...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/east-coast-internet-outages-494451f9-73bb-4025-9730-36ab5a6ad5d6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet users in the Washington-to-Boston corridor reported widespread outages Tuesday affecting service for both broadband and internet content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Weighs Race-Based Preferences...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/01/26/oregon-weighs-race-based-vaccine-preferences/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of allowing people with chronic medical conditions to get a higher place in line, a pivotal Oregon committee leans into racial justice considerations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes to tongue, hands or feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/changes-to-tongue-hands-or-feet-may-flag-coronavirus-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AFP) - Changes to the tongue, the hands or the soles of the feet could give an early indication of Covid-19 infection, Spanish researchers found in a study presented on Tuesday (Jan 26).. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing lung cancer cases -- turning up in unexpected population...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/01/26/growing-share-of-lung-cancer-turning-up-in-never-smokers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists disagree whether the number of lung cancer patients who never smoked is increasing, but the proportion who never did clearly is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian Premier Resigns as Instability Grows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-pm-quit-tuesday-seeking-193455597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte resigned Tuesday in the hope of forming a new government after weeks of turmoil in his ruling coalition, leaving Italy rudderless as it battles the deadly coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany mulls cutting all international air traffic...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-01-germany-mulls-international-air-traffic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany is considering almost completely halting flights into the country to slow the spread of more infectious strains of the coronavirus, Interior Minister Horst Seehofer said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread internet outages hit northeast... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/widespread-internet-outages-hit-northeast-175129937.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Verizon reported a fiber cut in Brooklyn via Twitter, although it’s not clear if that issue is responsible for the entire outage. The internet service provider didn't have any estimate when the problem spot would be fixed. Neither Verizon nor Comcast, another major internet service provider, immediately responded to requests for comment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's pandemic policy: No police. No curfews. No fines. No regrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Mexico-s-pandemic-policy-No-police-No-curfews-15898157.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - As the coronavirus swept the globe early last year, Mexican officials made...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orders Gov't Agencies to Buy American-Made Products...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/policy/2021/01/biden-orders-agencies-buy-more-american-made-products-and-publicly-post-exemptions/171613/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The order seeks to close existing loopholes and creates a new oversight regime, including a GSA-hosted website to post waivers publicly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  Neighborhood cat mauled to death after owners sic dogs on NYC strays...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/neighborhood-cat-mauled-to-death-after-owners-sic-dogs-on-group-of-brooklyn-strays/2848290/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One woman said that the owners let the dogs go after the cats, and when one escaped up a tree, they forced it to go back down to be mauled by the canine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye to Hollywood? ALBUQUERQUE Named Best for Moviemakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/best-places-to-live-and-work-as-a-moviemaker-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s list of the Best Places to Live and Work as a Moviemaker is different than any we’ve done before, because never have so many moviemakers seriously considered changing their lives dramatically — starting with where they live. Best Places Hall of Famers Los Angeles and New York City will always be our greatest […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 in USA has STD...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/1-in-5-americans-have-sexually-transmitted-diseases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New federal data show that an estimated 1 in 5 people in the United States have had a sexually transmitted infection on any given day and half of them are in people under the age of 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST executive editor Baron announces retirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/26/media/marty-baron/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marty Baron, the editor who transformed the Washington Post into an international powerhouse and led the news organization to win 10 Pulitzer Prizes, is retiring next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon restricted commander of DC Guard before riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pentagon-restricted-commander-of-D-C-Guard-15899083.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The commander of the District of Columbia National Guard said the Pentagon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortion Drama Leads SPIRIT AWARD Nominations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/2021-independent-spirit-awards-nominations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indie Spirit nominations are here, and the 36th Annual Independent Spirit Awards will air on Thursday, April 22 on IFC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS TO ADDRESS NATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/13853311/uk-covid-deaths-pass-100000-boris-johnson-address-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE than 100,000 people have now died with Covid in the UK – as Boris Johnson prepares to mark a bleak day in the battle against the deadly virus with a national address. A further 1,631 peo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACKED!  OR DID SHE SET UP HER MOM?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2211974/claudia-conway-nude-picture-leak-kellyanne-hacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLAUDIA Conway said she thinks her mom Kellyanne was hacked after an alleged nude photo leak and urged “don’t incite violence.” “I have faith and I know that my mother would…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fonda to Receive Cecil B. DeMille at GLOBES...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/01/26/triumph-jane-fonda-to-receive-golden-globes-cecil-b-demille-lifetime-achievement-award-for-acting-activism-philanthropy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Triumph! Jane Fonda will receive the Cecil B. DeMille Lifetime Achievement Award from the Golden Globes on February 28th. The two time Oscar winner will be honored for her acting, activism, and phi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  Entire family, including baby, found dead in Michigan woods...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlive.com/news/saginaw-bay-city/2021/01/missing-bay-city-family-found-dead-in-northern-michigan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The three were found outside their vehicle in Ogemaw County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani wasn't just Trump partisan but shrewd marketer of vitamins, gold, lawsuit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Giuliani-wasn-t-just-a-Trump-partisan-but-a-15898262.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he outlined how</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Sarah Huckabee Sanders' shameless campaign for gov...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/962986/sarah-huckabee-sanders-shameless-campaign-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can the former White House spokesperson lie her way to the Arkansas governor's mansion?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEATH TOLL TOPS 100,000 IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-tsunamis-united-kingdom-coronavirus-pandemic-leeds-76f125a9c79a766f4d8e84220a09804c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — For nine months, Gordon Bonner has been in the “hinterlands of despair and desolation” after losing his wife of 63 years to the coronavirus pandemic that has now taken the lives of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citing pandemic, Greece bans protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-greece-coronavirus-pandemic-2a2859442f65ded4f522eb5d7782cf10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Greece’s center-right government on Tuesday imposed a weeklong ban on public protests attended by more than 100 people, angering left-wing political opponents. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA LOOSENS UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-sacramento-coronavirus-pandemic-california-gavin-newsom-fc0c15eb5e7359b4bae50602f79a2cfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California’s health department on Monday released to the public previously secret projections for future hospital intensive care unit capacity throughout the state, the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
