<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DOJ DENIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/doj-denies-brian-stelter-book-account-about-barr-pushing-murdoch-to-muzzle-andrew-napolitano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department said a CNN journalist's claim that Attorney General William Barr attempted to "muzzle" Fox News legal analyst Judge Andrew Napolitano is false.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE:  WHATEVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/White-House-Trump-s-campaign-dismiss-recording-15508761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The White House and the Trump campaign on Sunday dismissed secretly recorded audio in which Trump's sister Maryanne Trump Barry said the president has "no principles" and "you can't trust him."  Mary Trump, the president's niece, surreptitiously taped the 15 hours of face-to-face conversations with Barry in 2018 and 2019. She provided The Washington Post with previously unreleased transcripts and audio excerpts.  In an interview Sunday on ABC News's "This Week," White House Chief of Staff Mark Meadows said Trump "has been public with his response - you know, just another day and another attack that we continue to see."  "I can tell you that I've never met the judge," Meadows said of Maryanne Trump, who retired last year from her job as a federal judge. "I was at the funeral the other day. I was hoping to meet her there. She didn't show up for her brother's funeral."  The president's brother Robert died Aug. 15 at age 71. A private memorial service was held at the White House on Friday.  In one of the secretly recorded conversations, Barry, 83, appeared aghast at how her 74-year-old brother operated as president. "His goddamned tweet and lying, oh my God," she said. "I'm talking too freely, but you know. The change of stories. The lack of preparation. The lying. Holy s---."  Meadows pushed back against that criticism Sunday while criticizing Mary Trump, who he said was "written out of a will" and "has an ax to grind because she wants Joe Biden to be president."  "The president that I have the privilege of serving is not the one that's being described on a 15-hour . . . secret tape," Meadows said. "I mean, what family member tapes another family member for 15 hours secretly?"  In 1999, when family patriarch Fred Trump Sr. died, Barry joined with Donald and Robert...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STELTER HITS #1 AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/Untitled-Brian-Stelter/dp/1982142448/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: 'DEEP STATE' DELAYING VAX</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/trump-pushes-covid-19-treatments-175709089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pushing for breakthroughs in treatments for the coronavirus, White House officials suggested Sunday there were politically motivated delays by the Food and Drug Administration in approving a vaccine and therapeutics for the disease. The accusations, the latest assault from President Donald Trump’s team on the so-called “deep state” bureaucracy, were presented without evidence and just hours before Trump was set to hold a news conference to announce an apparent advancement in therapeutics. “This president is about cutting red tape,” said White House chief of staff Mark Meadows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George to take TWITTER hiatus?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1356409/kellyanne-husband-george-conway-slams-trump-claudia-emancipation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Conway, husband to Trump’s adviser Kellyanne, has announced he might be taking a Twitter hiatus soon, shortly after his daughter announced she was seeking emancipation from her parents…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House eyes blood plasma help...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/08/23/fda-under-pressure-from-trump-expected-to-authorize-blood-plasma-as-covid-19-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision could generate intense controversy inside the administration and the broader scientific community because of a dearth of reliable data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW ORLEANS BRACES...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get the latest New Orleans, LA Local News, Sports News; US breaking News. View daily Louisiana weather updates, watch videos and photos, join the discussion in forums. Find more news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard and military helping to fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/national-guard-and-us-military-helping-to-fight-california-fires/ar-BB18huVK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOD PLASMA MIRACLE?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-to-announce-emergency-authorization-of-convalescent-plasma-as-covid-19-treatment/ar-BB18hG1R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAKER:  After Another Week of Setbacks, Trump Looks to Change the Story Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/after-another-week-of-setbacks-trump-looks-to-change-the-story-line/ar-BB18hF1I?li=BBnbfcL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong-un already dead?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/kim-jong-un-could-already-22565578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roy Calley, a journalist specialising in North Korean affairs, claims it could only be a matter of time before an official announcement is made and Kim’s sister Kim Yo-jong is confirmed as his successor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETS IT ALL ON THE BASE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/512675-the-memo-trump-bets-it-all-on-the-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump enters the Republican National Convention this week politically wounded — and even some members of his own party are not convinced he can stop the bleeding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Commander's Wallet Stolen While Responding To Blaze...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/08/23/czu-lightning-complex-fire-looter-commander-wallet-stolen-bank-account-drained/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire commander at the CZU Lightning Complex Fire in the Santa Cruz Mountains has became a looting victim, a Cal Fire official said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE BEFORE ELECTION</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200823170105-q991u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRUMP:Trump administration considering fast-tracking UK COVID-19 vaccine before election - FT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airplane mode and prepaid SIMs: Israelis dodge tracking...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200823164934-pzroc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-SURVEILLANCE (PIX):Airplane mode and prepaid SIMs: some Israelis dodge COVID-19 tracking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA player calls opponent "b**** a** white boy" while wearing social justice message on jersey...</title>
      <link>https://disrn.com/news/video-nba-player-appears-to-call-opponent-b-a-white-boy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Clippers player Montrezl Harrell appeared to have called Dallas Mavericks player Luka Doncic a "b**** a** white boy" during a playoff game on Friday night, as players, including Harrell, wore social justice messages on the backs of their jerseys:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 die in Peru disco stampede after police lockdown raid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb70b5ef15650c56e6d189a7cbe355fb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIMA, Peru (AP) — Thirteen people died in a stampede at a disco in Peru after a police raid to enforce the country's lockdown during the coronavirus pandemic, officials said Sunday. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emails show businesses held sway over state reopening plans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a9b056df95d41034064923612e4193d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As South Carolina Gov. Henry McMaster prepared to announce the end of a coronavirus stay-at-home order, his top staff received an email from the state health department. The message,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents flee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/76f2a9d689d179879fd6dd39ea997165</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — The Gulf Coast braced Sunday for a potentially devastating hit from twin hurricanes as two strong storms swirled toward the U.S from the Gulf of Mexico and the Caribbean....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domingo denies abusing power, seeks to clear name...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4003c84d46d4ab426d513a9473def0ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAPLES, Italy (AP) — Opera legend Plácido Domingo denied ever abusing his power during his management tenure at two U.S. opera houses in an interview with The Associated Press on Sunday, as he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Gulf Coast to feel Marco's wrath first as Laura looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/central-gulf-coast-to-feel-marcos-wrath-first-as-laura-looms/799325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOUBLE TROUBLE:  Dueling Tropical Systems!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-08-20-tropical-depression-thirteen-fourteen-laura-marco-tracker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical storms Laura and Marco are moving closer to the United States. Track them both here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Surprises' to Dazzle Party Into Unity...</title>
      <link>https://maa.theedgemarkets.com/article/trump-banks-convention-surprises-dazzle-party-unity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;maa.theedgemarkets.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Aug 23): As Donald Trump gears up for this week’s Republican convention, one thing is clear: recorded speeches, empty halls and parking-lot fireworks won’t cut it.“I think it’s pretty boring when you do tapes,” Trump said of his convention speech during an interview with Fox News host Sean Hannity. “I’m going to go live.”Trump is looking to outdo the Democrats’ mostly virtual convention with live speeches and at least a small group of supporters to energize speakers. He’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator to supporters: How about skipping a meal to donate?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/McSally-to-supporters-How-about-skipping-a-meal-15507664.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) - Sen. Martha McSally has suggested that supporters could "fast a meal" to donate to the Arizona Republican's campaign as she fights to fend off a tough challenge from Democrat Mark Kelly.  McSally made the request at a recent event in northern Arizona where she said her campaign needs financial help to counter advertising by Kelly and groups supporting the former astronaut's campaign, azfamily.com reported.  "We're doing our part to catch up, you know, to get our message out," McSally said. "But it takes resources. So, anybody can give, I'm not ashamed to ask, to invest. If you can give a dollar, five dollars, if you can fast a meal and give what that would be."  The remark drew critical attention on social media, while McSally's campaign said the candidate was just joking about skipping a meal.  "This is a dumb, non-story about a candidate," Caroline Anderegg, a McSally campaign spokeswoman, told the Arizona Republic. "It is frankly sad and disgusting that the Dems and the Kelly campaign are launching a misleading character assassination on Martha McSally, who would literally give the shirt off her back for anyone."  Republican businesswoman Christine Jones, who ran for Arizona governor in 2014 and Congress in 2016, called McSally's fundraising pitch "unconventional."  "I haven't talked to (McSally) about it, so I can't really opine on the specifics. But it does feel like its a little bit of an act of desperation," Jones said.  McSally trails Kelly in recent polls by anywhere from 5 to 11 percentage points, according to realclearpolitics.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party goes on for ravers, despite pandemic and police...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200823-the-party-goes-on-for-french-ravers-despite-pandemic-and-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party goes on for French ravers, despite pandemic and police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea reports highest daily total since March...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200823-south-korea-reports-highest-daily-virus-cases-since-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korea reports highest daily virus cases since March</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Surprises' to Dazzle Party Into Unity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-23/trump-banks-on-convention-surprises-to-dazzle-party-into-unity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers can break into home by listening to sound of key in lock...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/spikey-house-keys-listening-smartphone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh yeah, and your so-called smart doorbell could be a part of the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Islands Will Subpoena Billionaire Investor in Epstein Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/23/business/jeffrey-epstein-leon-black-virgin-islands.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The territory’s attorney general wants to know more about Leon Black’s dealings with Jeffrey Epstein, who died while facing sex-trafficking charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police stand down...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8655043/Portland-protests-turns-violent-hundreds-alt-right-anti-police-groups-clash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portland police decided not to intervene as violent clashes erupted between alt-right and anti-police protesters Saturday afternoon in the 86th day of demonstrations in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White-collar workers feel coronavirus squeeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/23/white-collar-unemployment-coronavirus-400130</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drop in overall employment that white-collar industries have seen in five months is already on par with or worse than the hits they took during the Great Recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops now filming incidents on phones to refute claims of racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8654727/Police-filming-incidents-mobile-phones-refute-claims-racism-online.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Marsh, chairman of the Met Police Federation says amid mounting anger at being erroneously shamed, officers are keeping personal records of exchanges 'for their own protection'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPS driver accused of series of highway shootings in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/23/us/oregon-ups-driver-arrested-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A driver for UPS was arrested in a series of shootings spanning three counties in southwest Oregon, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California 'dream house' in ashes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/58ee3764f92b31e50182f8ae8a165b5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VACAVILLE, Calif. (AP) — When he closes his eyes at night, Hank Hanson hears sirens in his dreams -- a byproduct of living nearly 30 years in the wildfire-prone wilderness of Northern California...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden enjoys post-convention bump in favorability...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/biden-enjoys-post-convention-bump-favorability-poll/story?id=72544897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Convention, with a smaller audience than 2016, still delivered a favorability boost for Joe Biden, a new ABC News/Ipsos poll finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Comic-Con More Funeral Than Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dc-comics-virtual-comic-con-was-like-a-funeral-more-than-a-festival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 12 days before the convention aired, WarnerMedia announced massive layoffs across its companies, primarily in its DC Comics arms. Was the party worth it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive 6-alarm fire rocks at Philly warehouse... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/5-alarm-blaze-breaks-out-in-north-philadelphia/2510492/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcphiladelphia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 200 firefighters were battling a five-alarm blaze raging in North Philadelphia Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Oklahoma State University, students' steps are tracked...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/oklahoma-state-university-students-steps-are-tracked-stop-coronavirus-n1237525</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The school president says students shouldn't be worried about privacy issues and the "Orwellian effect" because the data is collected for internal use only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires, broken windows in downtown Denver...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/local/protests/protesters-dpd-headquarters/73-80d28d47-a77c-4c60-94c8-3e50e42f004a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators gathered outside DPD headquarters and marched through downtown Denver Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How actress brought down Hollywood execs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/22/inside-charlotte-kirks-aggressive-tactics-with-hollywood-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How an affair with actress Charlotte Kirk brought down two media moguls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing weather prompts more fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Changing-weather-prompts-more-fire-fears-in-15508114.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) - An unwelcome change in the weather, with higher winds, temperatures and lightning that threatens to spark new wildfires was coming Sunday to parched Northern California, where firefighters have for nearly a week battled three huge "complexes" of fires that have destroyed hundreds of homes and forced tens of thousands to flee.  Firefighters made slow but hopeful progress in battling the blazes on Saturday, aided by good weather but hampered by smoky skies that grounded water-dropping aircraft for some of the day. Reinforcements arrived to bolster overwhelmed crews, and evacuation orders were lifted in some areas.  But the changing weather brought fears of new fires overnight and warnings from state and local officials for residents in threatened areas to prepare to flee at any moment.  "There's not a feeling of pure optimism, but a feeling of resolve, a feeling of we have resources backing us up," Sonoma County Supervisor James Gore said.  Since Aug. 15, state fire officials said more than 12,000 lightning strikes across the state have ignited more than 500 wildfires. Of those, about two dozen major fires were attracting most of the state's resources. Most of the damage was caused by three clusters of fire "complexes" that were ravaging forest and rural areas in and around the San Francisco Bay Area. They have burned 1,120 square miles (2,900 square kilometers).  Among the casualties were ancient redwood trees at California's oldest state park, Big Basin Redwoods, plus the park's headquarters and campgrounds. Smoke from the fires made the region's air quality dangerous, forcing people to stay inside.  Overall, the fires have killed five people, torched nearly 700 homes and other structures and forced tens of thousands from their houses.  "Tuesday night when I went to bed I had a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW:  Claudia  blasts 'selfish' mom; Says White House job 'about money and fame'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1354480/claudia-conway-selfish-mom-kellyanne-money-fame-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KELLYANNE Conway’s daughter Claudia launched a scathing attack on her “selfish” mom for “watching her kids suffer” because of her job. Claudia Conway – the daugh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge brawl erupts as Proud Boys and Antifa fight with bats in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1354432/portland-brawl-breaks-out-proud-boys-antifa-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND descended into violent chaos once again as a huge brawl erupted between hundreds of Proud Boys and Antifa protesters on Saturday. Shocking footage shows the rightwing militia wearing param…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THE BATMAN':  First trailer of dark, violent reboot... </title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/the-batman-trailer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;See the first footage of dark, gritty reboot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police hunt masked suspect accused of giving strangers 'covid hugs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1353388/police-hunt-masked-suspect-strangers-covid-hugs-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPS are hunting for a covidiot said to be giving strangers hugs and telling them “you now have COVID” in a Massachusetts Walmart.  “He told the victim, ‘Just giving you a COVID hug.  You now have …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans look to convention for campaign reboot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-looks-to-republican-convention-for-optimistic-campaign-reboot/ar-BB18gpsM?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail-in ballots were part of a plot to deny Lincoln reelection in 1864...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Mail-in-ballots-were-part-of-a-plot-to-deny-15507606.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traveling to Baltimore in the fall of 1864, Orville Wood had no way of knowing he would soon uncover the most elaborate election conspiracy in America's brief history.  Wood was a merchant from Clinton County in the most northeastern corner of New York. As a supporter of President Abraham Lincoln, he was tasked with visiting troops from his hometown to "look after the local ticket."  New York legislators had only established the state's mail-in voting system in April with the intent of ensuring the suffrage of White troops battling the Confederate Army.  The results of the 1864 elections would heavily affect the outcome of the war. Lincoln and his supporters in the National Union Party sought to continue the war and defeat the Confederacy outright. Meanwhile antiwar Democrats, also referred to as Copperheads, looked for an immediate compromise with the Confederate leaders and the end of the abolition movement.  Troops from New York were allowed to authorize individuals back home to cast a vote on their behalf. Along with their mail-in ballots, troops would assign their power of attorney on slips that required four signatures: the voter's, the person authorized as a recipient, a witness to the signed affidavit and a fellow officer. These documents would be sealed in an envelope and shipped back home to be counted in the final vote. This was the process that Orville Wood intended to uphold, he would testify in court later. He quickly found out what a challenge that would be.  Wood arrived at Fort McHenry in Baltimore to visit with the 91st New York Regiment. There, an Army captain suggested that there had been some "checker playing" when it came to the gathering of soldiers' mail-in ballots. These suspicions of fraud were echoed when Wood visited wounded men at the Newton University Hospital. The rumors of wrongdoing led...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
