<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'FORD V FERRARI' Speeds to No. 1; 'CHARLIE'S ANGELS' Crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ford-v-ferrari-speeds-to-no-1-while-charlies-angels-crashes-at-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox's Le Mans biopic on pace for $30 million opening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: LIL PEEP Documentary Beautifully Stirring...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/everybodys-everything-remembering-lil-peep-the-young-anxious-emo-rapper-who-might-have-changed-music</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beautifully stirring new documentary about Lil Peep’s short life borrows its title from his last social media post: “I don’t want help but I need help,” he wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers continue to struggle despite 'strong' jobs reports...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/470769-americas-workers-continue-to-struggle-despite-strong-jobs-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The priority should be to restore wealth-generating industries, like manufacturing, that can spur middle-class job growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Flooding Expected to Worsen Sunday With Rising Sea...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/st-marks-closed-fresh-flood-hits-venice-143012063.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice was on alert for more floods and fierce winds on Saturday after an exceptionally high tide swamped the city of canals, where authorities have declared a state of emergency. Mayor Luigi Brugnaro ordered the iconic St Mark's Square closed on Friday as the latest sea surge struck with strong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAP BACK?</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/sports/will-colin-kaepernick-make-his-nfl-comeback/5701473/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly three years after playing his last NFL game, Colin Kaepernick is looking to make a comeback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood, Texas: Kanye Takes Osteen to Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.texasmonthly.com/the-culture/hollywood-texas-kanye-west-takes-joel-osteen-to-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texasmonthly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget Staffer Could Shed Light On Inquiry Enigmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/16/779934386/omb-staffer-could-shed-light-on-impeachment-inquiry-enigmas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Closed-door testimony from the only White House staffer cooperating with the probe could provide first-hand knowledge about details that remain hazy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timing raises questions of NFL intentions...</title>
      <link>https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/news/story/timing-colin-kaepernicks-workout-raises-questions-nfls-intentions-67018301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goodmorningamerica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is holding a workout for Colin Kaepernick, but many believe it's nothing more than a public relations stunt. PR, sports and social justice experts weigh in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans at war with apes as villagers take revenge butchering baby-eating chimps...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/humans-war-apes-villagers-take-20876196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The powerful primates are losing their fear of humans as settlements expand – with devastating and deadly results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans receiving more than 2,000 robocalls -- every second...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/16/robocalls-hit-record-numbers-as-carriers-and-lawmakers-fight-back.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans received a record 5.66 billion robocalls last month, prompting carriers, lawmakers and start-ups to boost efforts to block calls and catch scammers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Flooding Expected to Worsen Sunday With Rising Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/venice-flooding-is-expected-to-worsen-on-sunday-with-rising-sea-1.1348999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice is headed for its second exceptionally high tide in a week, with water levels forecast to rise 160 centimeters (63 inches) above their benchmark, the Ansa news agency reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE: Germany's Greens re-elect leadership duo after electoral wins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-greens-elect-leadership-duo-electoral-wins-144813218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's Greens on Saturday re-elected the two people leading their party after strong performances in regional and European elections. The 800 delegates gathered for their annual congress at Bielefeld, western Germany, voted overwhelming to keep Annalena Baerbock and Robert Habeck in place --</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE: This is mission, not show...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/entertainment/kanye-west-visits-harris-county-jail-ahead-of-sundays-lakewood-appearance/285-a8df8545-a5bb-4bd6-8470-9f3e56e788a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rap superstar Kanye West made a surprise appearance at the Harris County Jail on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man survives croc attack by gouging its eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20191116-australian-man-survives-croc-attack-by-gouging-its-eye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian man survives croc attack by gouging its eye</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis Flameout Rivals Dot-Com Bust as Legal Fears Curb Growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-16/cannabis-flameout-rivals-dot-com-bust-as-legal-fears-curb-growth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Will.I.Am Accuses QANTAS Of Racial Profiling...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/will-i-am-racist-flight-attendant-qantas-twitter-090339669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airline have denied that the incident had "anything to do with race" after the musician was met by police when the plane landed in Sydney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters head to polls in critical Louisiana gubernatorial race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/470767-voters-head-to-the-polls-in-critical-louisiana-gubernatorial-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters are heading to the polls Saturday to vote in Louisiana’s crucial gubernatorial race as both Democrats and Republicans go all in to push their candidate over the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These trans bodybuilders can kick your ass...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/15/these-transgender-bodybuilders-can-kick-your-ass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They aim for the same goal as any other bodybuilder: to be strong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helmet swing is latest violent incident in sports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/52ee599532fd4a8398e3467d7c4ca07b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violence is part of the game in many sports but Myles Garrett crossed a line that attracts the attention of authorities sometimes from within their sport and in other cases from criminal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Crossed Antarctica Alone. Now He Plans to Row There...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/16/sports/antarctica-drake-passage-obrady.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin O’Brady ended up winning an unintended race across the frozen continent last year. He wants to go back in a boat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana gov race latest test of Trump clout...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/louisiana-governor-race-2019-democrat-john-bel-edwards-race-against-republican-eddie-rispone-test-trumps-clout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, the final governor's race of the year is the next test of how much Trump's clout can lift a candidate. In Kentucky, the GOP candidate lost, but in Mississippi, the Republican won</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Wilde stolen ring found by 'art detective'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oscar-wildes-stolen-ring-found-dutch-art-detective-091403182.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A golden ring once given as a present by the famed Irish writer Oscar Wilde has been recovered by a Dutch "art detective" nearly 20 years after it was stolen from Britain's Oxford University. The friendship ring, a joint gift from Wilde to a fellow student in 1876, was taken during a burglary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Erupt in Iran After Gasoline-Price Hike...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/one-dead-protests-erupt-iran-111419958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- At least one person was killed as protests erupted in Iran after the government unexpectedly raised gasoline prices, the semi-official Iranian Student’s News Agency reported.The fatality occurred during clashes in Sirjan in the southern province of Kerman on Friday, ISNA reported, citing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian rockets, Israeli airstrikes jolt tenuous Gaza truce...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191116062750-04ec5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/VIOLENCE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Palestinian rockets, Israeli airstrikes jolt tenuous Gaza truce</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama tells candidates to ease off talk of revolution... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Obama-tells-Democratic-candidates-to-ease-off-14839299.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Former president Barack Obama on Friday urged Democrats running for the White House not to lurch too far left in their pursuit of the nomination, while at the same time seeking to quell concerns in the party about its 2020 hopefuls and the messy primary season to come.  The comments - made in Washington at a meeting of the Democracy Alliance, a powerful network of liberal donors - marked some of Obama's most pointed words yet about a fluid primary in which he is not picking sides. They echoed previous comments in which he warned about the dangers of pursuing purity and rigidity in politics.  "This is still a country that is less revolutionary than it is interested in improvement," Obama said. "They like seeing things improved. But the average American doesn't think that we have to completely tear down the system and remake it. And I think it's important for us not to lose sight of that."  Obama did not name any candidates. But some Democrats associate the characteristics he described with Sens. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., and Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., staunch liberal candidates advocating sweeping change who are running near the top of the polls.  Beyond those two candidates, the contest has often been dominated by a discussion of ideas that were long seen as untenable, even in Democratic circles. Candidates have called for mandatory buybacks of certain firearms, decriminalizing border crossings and forgiving most or all student debt. In some cases, the proposals have come at a cost of tens of trillions of dollars, vast sums of money that would dwarf what Obama's administration spent and require historically steep tax increases on wealthy Americans. While some voters and activists have cheered this trend, President Donald Trump and his allies have been eager to highlight these themes.  However, Obama also warned...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Okies disappearing from Dust Bowl Festival, replaced by Latino migrants tending California's fields...</title>
      <link>https://www.theeagle.com/news/national/okies-disappearing-from-dust-bowl-festival-replaced-by-latino-migrants/article_71213d61-6934-54e0-92ce-a55e0e908d3d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEEDPATCH, Calif. — The girl was afraid to speak in class because of her accent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodell and Jay-Z Want Him to Get Second Chance...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebiglead.com/posts/dan-patrick-jay-z-pressured-roger-goodell-to-schedule-colin-kaepernick-workout-01dsqsq2sp6g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebiglead.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More vapers  making own juice, but not without risks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/vaping/more-vapers-are-making-their-own-juice-not-without-risks-n1081496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more states, cities and even the federal government consider banning flavored nicotine, thousands of vapers are flocking to social media groups and websites to learn how to make e-liquids at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine's young corruption fighters struggle against elites  -- and Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/ukraine-s-young-corruption-fighters-struggle-against-elites-and-donald/article_d7db3736-db16-5c37-af73-8b07c50bd86e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine — From her second-story walk-up office in Kyiv’s old Perchersk neighborhood, Daria Kaleniuk has been fighting the fire-breathing dragons of Ukrainian corruption — oligarchs and politicians and judges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Venice hit by another ferocious high tide, flooding city...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7688847/Venice-braces-flooding-water-levels-set-reach-five-feet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St Mark's Square in Venice was closed to tourists today after floodwaters overran the historic plaza this morning, while shops and hotels were invaded by water once again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New satellite measurements show how polluted Los Angeles air really is...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-11-satellite-polluted-los-angeles-air.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists who scanned the skies above dozens of U.S. cities have made a surprising discovery about the smog that's suspended over Los Angeles: one of its key ingredients isn't disappearing as fast as it once did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States in Midwest have outsized roles in 2020 elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/campaigns/states-in-the-midwest-with-outsized-roles-in-the-2020-elections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin, Minnesota, Michigan and Iowa all have competitive races that will help determine control of the White House and Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Says Average American Doesn't Want to 'Tear Down System'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/15/us/politics/barack-obama-2020-dems.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama, in an address to liberal donors, warned candidates not to go too far left and sought to calm those who were concerned about the state of the Democratic primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone guilty on all counts in federal trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/roger-stone-found-guilty-all-seven-counts-n1082326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP operative was charged with making false statements, obstruction and witness tampering tied to his pursuit of Russian-hacked emails in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump grants clemency to Army officers accused of war crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-clemency-army-officers-accused-of-war-crimes-navy-seal-eddie-gallagher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has granted clemency to two Army officers accused or convicted of war crimes and restored Navy SEAL Eddie Gallagher to the rank of chief petty officer after he was docked a pay grade after being convicted of posing for a photo with a dead Islamic State (ISIS) fighter, the White House announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 24 teams to attend Kaepernick workout...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28088983/sources-24-teams-attend-colin-kaepernick-workout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 24 teams are now expected to attend Colin Kaepernick's workout on Saturday at the Falcons' training complex, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Trump associates have been convicted in Mueller-related investigations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/15/politics/trump-associates-convicted-in-mueller-related-investigations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Trump associates have been convicted of crimes since he took office, all stemming from the Mueller investigation. Some of the defendants pleaded guilty, others were convicted after jury trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW 28,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/15/dow-futures-fed-reserve-financial-stability-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average rallied to record levels on Friday, reaching 28,000 for the first time ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Expresses Support For Kaepernick...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/11/15/tom-brady-colin-kaepernick-new-england-patriots-nfl-workout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many NFL players have voiced their support for Kaepernick over the last few days, and you can add Patriots quarterback Tom Brady to that growing list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio measure would ban abortion outright...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d2ac5095b9884dc3b629fe95797efc48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — A group of conservative lawmakers in Ohio has introduced a bill to outlaw abortion outright except to save the pregnant woman’s life. State Rep. Candice Keller, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaks Silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10331071/prince-andrew-speak-under-oath-virginia-roberts-lawyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAWYER for one of Jeffrey Epstein’s most high profile accusers has slammed Prince Andrew for talking to the BBC over the police. The Duke will break his silence on the Jeffrey Epstein scandal in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detectives search for motive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/why-did-santa-clarita-shooting-happen-detectives-search-for-motive/ar-BBWP5Ox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE ANDREW INTERVIEW: 'Let the Side Down' Staying at Epstein's Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-50431163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York speaks to the BBC for the first time about his links to convicted US sex offender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  COWBOYS to skip...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/cowboys-wont-attend-kaepernick-workout-says-team-owner-203713397--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas Cowboys owner and general manager Jerry Jones said Friday the team will not send a representative to former NFL quarterback Colin Kaepernick&amp;#39;s private workout in Atlanta. The league has confirmed at least 11 teams will attend Saturday&amp;#39;s practice session for Kaepernick, whose kneeling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Yang Proposes Making Social Media Algorithms Subject to Federal Approval...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/11/15/andrew-yang-proposes-making-social-media-algorithms-subject-to-federal-approval/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entrepreneur Andrew Yang has run a tech-centered campaign for the Democratic presidential nomination, positioning his Universal Basic Income proposal as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Born-again Christian' accused of trying to kidnap sex workers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/15/long-island-born-again-christian-accused-of-trying-to-kidnap-sex-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A married, churchgoing Long Island dad at least twice tried to kidnap prostitutes, driving them against their will to secluded locations only to have them leap for their lives from his moving car, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star witness against him feels 'horrible'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/after-roger-stone-conviction-star-witness-against-him-feels-horrible-192720079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Randy Credico told Yahoo News that he was in tears upon learning of the verdict and did not want to see Stone go to jail because of his testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' Plan to Shoot Down Drones Near Airports...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/dhs-plan-to-shoot-down-drones-near-u-s-airports-draws-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican leaders on the House Homeland Security Committee are opposing new proposals that would permit the federal government to shoot down rogue unmanned drones that fly near American airports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Releases Norwegian, Lithuanians in Unusual Spy Swap...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-releases-norwegian-lithuanians-in-unusual-spy-swap/ar-BBWOhmG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris bans wild animals in circuses...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-dithers-paris-moves-ban-wild-animals-circuses-152404642.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While France mulls whether to join a majority of EU nations in banning wild animals in circuses, the city of Paris pressed ahead Friday with its own plan to outlaw the practice amid fresh concerns over cruelty. A proposal was adopted by the municipal council late Friday that will see permits withheld</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago gang leader accused of trying to help ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b3be15d7e91349919a4c1cee974b234f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A purported street-gang leader from suburban Chicago who became radicalized in prison faces federal charges accusing him of seeking to provide money to Islamic State militants in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/15/kamala-harris-campaign-2020-071105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaign manager Juan Rodriguez is taking the most heat for the failings, but his defenders point their finger at the candidate's sister, Maya Harris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purrfect crime: Pet detective seeks lost animals...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/purrfect-crime-chinese-pet-detective-seeks-lost-animals-051212965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private sleuth Sun Jinrong brings heat detectors, tiny surveillance cameras, and a blow dart loaded with a tranquiliser to his search for one desperate client's missing loved one: A cat named Duoduo. Sun often gets calls from anguished pet owners in the middle of the night and rushes to cities and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 sailors injured in 5 hour fire aboard USS Iwo Jima...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2019/11/15/11-sailors-injured-in-5-hour-fire-aboard-amphib-uss-iwo-jima-3rd-warship-damaged-in-fire-during-maintenance-in-last-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven sailors suffered minor injuries during a fire that broke out late Thursday aboard the amphibious warship USS Iwo Jima (LHD-7), Navy officials told USNI News. “Sailors on board reported smoke in a cargo hold and a subsequent damage control investigation identified the fire and confirmed the fire had not spread to surrounding spaces,” read …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected School Shooter Didn't Fit Profile of Depressed, Angry Teen...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/15/saugus-high-school-shooter-nathan-berhow-had-girlfriend-honor-roll-track-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 16-year-old Saugus High School student was identified by CBS News as the gunman in the shooting that killed a 16-year-old girl and a 14-year-old boy. Nathan remains in grave condition from a self-inflicted gunshot wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror...</title>
      <link>https://www.wyff4.com/article/horse-found-stabbed-police-say-3-horse-attacks-in-2-weeks/29792322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wyff4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A horse had to be euthanized after it was found stabbed, according to Campobello police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRENNAN WARNS TRUMP:   'May Your Downfall be Swift'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/11/brennan-sends-president-trump-ominous-warning-in-the-middle-of-schiffs-impeachment-show-trial-may-your-downfall-be-swift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS HE WILL DIE IN JAIL... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/report-roger-stone-fears-hell-be-epsteind-in-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump confidant scared he will be murdered while in prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly 'axe attacks' on horses in North and South Carolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxcarolina.com/investigations/spartanburg-co-official-confirms-another-horse-stabbing-investigation-underway-in/article_a966583e-0702-11ea-9774-cfae5c04498b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxcarolina.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMPOBELLO, SC (FOX Carolina) – Spartanburg County’s Environmental Enforcement Department director confirmed Thursday his team was investigating another incident in Campobello involving a stab wound to a horse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces up to 50 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7690103/Roger-Stone-GUILTY-lying-Congress-WikiLeaks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone faces years in federal jail after he was found guilty today of lying to Congress about his efforts to procure stolen Democratic Party emails from WikiLeaks to help Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TV RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/myles-garrett-suspended-nfl-thursday-night-football-ratings-rise-fox-greys-anatomy-young-sheldon-1202787177/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blast radius from the chaos of last night’s Thursday Night Football grows as the NFL has fined the Pittsburgh Steelers and the victorious Cleveland Browns and suspended a trio of players for th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea calls Joe Biden 'rabid dog' who should be 'beaten to death with stick'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10354955/north-korea-joe-biden-rabid-dog-beaten-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korea has dubbed Donald Trump’s presidential rival Joe Biden a “rabid dog” which needs to be put down for slandering dictator Kim Jong-un.  The official KCNA news agency did not say how Biden…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRET BAIER: Trump Just Gave Schiff New Article of Impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/foxs-bret-baier-trump-gave-schiff-a-new-article-of-impeachment-in-real-time-with-twitter-attack-on-yovanovitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dramatic moment during Friday's House Impeachment hearing in which Rep. Adam Schiff (D-CA) read out President Donald Trump's tweet blasting former ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES LIVE:  TRUMP MUST PARDON!</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/watch-alex-jones-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank teller accused of attacking customer in 'reverse bank robbery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bank-teller-accused-of-attacking-customer-in-home-invasion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Maryland have arrested a bank teller accused of a home invasion of a customer who had recently withdrawn a large sum of money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Suspends BROWNS Player Indefinitely, Fines Both Teams $250,000...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/11/15/nfl-suspends-myles-garrett-indefinitely-fines-both-steelers-and-browns-250000-also-suspends-maurkice-pouncey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has handed down its punishments for last night’s violence during the end of the Pittsburgh Steelers-Cleveland Browns game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witness tampering, lying to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ad355d2c983e4a7c85bc17e86d8c563f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roger Stone, a longtime friend and ally of President Donald Trump, was found guilty Friday of witness tampering and lying to Congress about his pursuit of Russian-hacked emails...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'VERY INTIMIDATING'</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191115154338-5tai2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 7-'Very intimidating' - Trump launches Twitter attack on witness during impeachment testimony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay employee says salary halved to be even with 'females in office'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/15/gay-employee-salary-halved-even-females-office-new-york-discrimination-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man claims in lawsuit against New York events company that employers sought to degrade him after they learned he was gay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Putting On 'Game Face' Improves Performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/competitive-edge-putting-on-a-game-face-can-improve-performance-stress-recovery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most people consider these gritty stares as nothing more than a side effect of preparing for in-game play, is it possible that putting on a game face actually helps us perform better?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video showing teen with no arms or legs being tackled and pinned by deputy prompts investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Video-showing-teen-with-no-arms-or-legs-being-14837578.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shirtless 15-year-old screams as he lies facedown on the kitchen floor of his group home in Tucson, Arizona. He has no arms or legs, so he can't flee or fight back. A sheriff's deputy at least twice his size is crouching over him and pinning him to the ground, using his body weight to restrain the quadruple amputee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TORCHES WITNESS IN REAL-TIME</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/trump-attacks-marie-yovanovitch-in-real-time-during-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump attacked former U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch in real time as she testified in the Trump impeachment inquiry, denigrating her career as a diplomat and asserting h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House releases memo of Trump call with Ukraine Zelenskiy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/15/trump-releases-transcript-of-april-call-with-ukraine-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congratulatory phone call was three months before the July 25 call, which sparked the House impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAYLOR SWIFT BANNED FROM PLAYING OLD HITS?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/big-machine-records-denies-taylor-swift-claims-scott-borchetta-scooter-braun-1203406009/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED: In a statement issued early Friday morning, Big Machine Records denied Taylor Swift’s claims that they are blocking the use of her music. Swift had said in social media posts late Thursday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight from London to Sydney breaks 2 world records...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/878650/flight-from-london-sydney-breaks-2-world-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a milestone decades in the making. On Friday, a Qantas airplane loaded with 100 metric tons of jet fuel flew 11,060 miles from London to Sydney, nonstop. The journey lasted 19 hours and 19 minutes, and shattered two records, becoming the longest commercial airline passenger flight for both distance and duration, CNN reports. The new Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner departed from Heathrow Airport at 6 a.m. Thursday morning, and flew over Germany, Russia, Poland, Belarus, Kazakhstan, China, the Philippines, and Indonesia. This was a test flight, and while the plane can hold up to 256 people, there were just 50 on board. All passengers were outfitted with monitors, and researchers from Australia's Charles Perkins Centre will study how sleep patterns, movement, and food consumption on an extremely long flight affect a person's health. The last time Qantas attempted to fly this route without stopping, it was 1989. The airline used a Boeing 747, ripping out most of the seats and loading the plane with as much fuel as possible, even towing it to the runway in order to conserve gas, CNN reports. "Flying nonstop from the east coast of Australia to London and New York is truly the final frontier in aviation, so we're determined to do all the groundwork to get this right," Qantas CEO Alan Joyce said. Qantas is hopeful it can start offering nonstop flights from London to Sydney and vice versa in 2022. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Faces Probe on Campaign Finance, Lobbying Breaches...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/giuliani-faces-u-probe-campaign-000039292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Rudy Giuliani, President Donald Trump’s personal lawyer, is being investigated by federal prosecutors for possible campaign finance violations and a failure to register as a foreign agent as part of an active investigation into his financial dealings, according to three U.S. officials.The</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
