<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell 'boasted' about oral sex with George Clooney...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12340128/ghislaine-maxwell-schoolgirl-oral-sex-george-clooney-virginia-giuffre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell boasted about performing an alleged sex act on George Clooney and “giggled like a schoolgirl”, Virginia Giuffre has claimed. The sensational claims were made in the ma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOOKS: RUSSIA WANTS TRUMP; CHINA WANTS BIDEN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/07/politics/2020-election-russia-china-iran/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US intelligence community's top election security official said in a statement Friday that China "prefers" an outcome where President Donald Trump is not reelected in November and Russia is working to denigrate former Vice President Joe Biden's White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released from jail at height of pandemic, rape suspect kills accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/crime-law/2020/08/06/released-jail-height-pandemic-alexandria-rape-suspect-allegedly-killed-his-accuser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ibrahim Bouaichi had been in jail since October on rape and abduction charges. But he was released in April, and is now charged with killing his accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-ANGELS employee charged in pitcher's fatal opioid overdose...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/former-l-angels-employee-charged-pitcher-tyler-skaggs-fatal-opioid-n1236179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyler Skaggs was just 27 when he was found dead in his hotel room, as his team prepared to play the Texas Rangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado 'recon' teams quietly monitor mask wearing...</title>
      <link>https://coloradosun.com/2020/08/06/mask-wearing-compliance-surveys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coloradosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tri-County Health Department has been dispatching volunteers to conduct mask surveys since April. Now Boulder and Gunnison counties are starting their own coronavirus recon missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman is 1st in US to get 2nd face transplant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4cb2c94741618736fc91f2a51899b458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — For the second time in a decade, a New Hampshire woman has a new face. Carmen Blandin Tarleton, whose face was disfigured in an attack by her ex-husband, became the first...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Media Led Great Racial Awakening...</title>
      <link>https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/media-great-racial-awakening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tabletmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Years before Trump’s election the media dramatically increased coverage of racism and embraced new theories of racial consciousness that set the stage for the latest unrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will curtain fall on Broadway for good?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/covid-19-knocked-actors-broadway-stage-are-lights-dim-forever-n1235957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have to pave a new way forward, because this industry is not ever going to be the same," one actor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL owner Dan Snyder files $10M lawsuit over false sex trafficking stories...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/511056-nfl-owner-dan-snyder-files-10m-lawsuit-over-false-sex-trafficking-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indian-based website has since taken down the stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norwegians Told to Avoid All Foreign Travel... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/norwegians-told-to-avoid-all-foreign-travel-as-virus-surges/ar-BB17GG9o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muddy Data Causes Some States to Undercount...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/muddy-virus-data-causes-some-us-states-to-undercount-cases/ar-BB17FNeL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire hedge fund chief Paulson to host big-money Hamptons fundraiser..</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/trump-fundraiser-to-be-hosted-by-billionaire-john-paulson-in-hamptons.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tickets for the Trump dinner event are priced up to $500,000 per couple, an invitation says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii reinstates restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/hawaii-reinstates-coronavirus-restrictions-theres-no-question-that-the-virus-is-surging.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There is no question that the virus is surging in our state, and I know that many are worried about their health," Hawaii Gov. David Ige said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US tops 2,000 covid deaths in 24 hrs for first time in three months...</title>
      <link>https://in.news.yahoo.com/us-records-more-2-000-023800892.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time the US recorded more than 2,000 deaths in 24 hours was on May 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Londoners Are Refusing to Return to the Office...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-londoners-refusing-return-office-091311966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Britons are lagging Europe in the march back to the office, but the U.K.’s status as the standard-bearer for WFH could be hard to sustain. Only 34% of U.K. office workers are working in their normal location, according to a recent survey by analysts at Morgan Stanley. In France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JULY JOBS: +1.76 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0aca194f0f4870b01280049ca567a87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States added 1.8 million jobs in July, a pullback from the gains of May and June and evidence that the resurgent coronavirus has weakened hiring and the economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah protesters face charges with life sentence?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e660cd8c172fca5cd49e703d74f92fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Some Black Lives Matter protesters in Salt Lake City could face up to life in prison if they’re convicted of splashing red paint and smashing windows during a protest, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump long has relied on nondisclosure deals to prevent criticism. That strategy may be unraveling... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-long-has-relied-on-nondisclosure-deals-to-15466258.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Donald Trump has relied on broadly worded nondisclosure agreements as a powerful weapon against anyone who would say something critical of him. Among those who have signed agreements are a porn star, two ex-wives, contestants on "The Apprentice," campaign workers and business associates.  But this key element of Trump's corporate and political strategy has shown signs of unraveling, even as his campaign spends heavily to enforce such agreements. He and his allies recently have lost initial rounds in legal battles to stop damaging books by former top White House officials and his niece Mary L. Trump.  Now, in one of the most sweeping efforts by a former associate to undo nondisclosure agreements, the Trump campaign's former Hispanic outreach director last week filed her latest effort in a class-action suit to void all such campaign contracts. She says they are so broad that they deny individuals their First Amendment right to say anything critical of the president - even as he routinely takes to Twitter to mock and deride his critics.  In a motion for summary judgment in the case, the former campaign worker, Jessica Denson, said the campaign sought a $1.5 million claim against her for violating an NDA. She said that came after she filed a lawsuit alleging sex discrimination by campaign officials. (That separate case is ongoing.)  "These NDAs are representative of the levers of fear that this campaign and administration wield over people," Denson told The Washington Post. "And if this lever of these NDAs is lifted, it is significant not only for the direct effect it has on people who have signed it, but for a general environment of people who are afraid to speak out."  Under her agreement, Denson was not allowed to disparage Trump during her time with the campaign "and at all times thereafter," and she cannot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans Increasingly Turn to Robots for Interaction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/08/will-covid-19-spur-new-robot-friends-and-helpers/167531/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socially assistive robots interact with people and can perform household chores, accomplish health care tasks, and offer emotional support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US tops 2,000 covid deaths in 24 hrs for first time in three months...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/us-tops-2-000-deaths-in-24-hours-for-first-time-in-three-months-johns-hopkins-01596761106?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has recorded more than 2,000 coronavirus deaths in 24 hours, the highest number of daily fatalities in three months, Johns Hopkins University's real-time tally showed Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report Satisfies Everyone and No One...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jobs-report-satisfies-everyone-no-144344472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Investors who expected that the July jobs report would compel congressional officials to avoid a collapse in negotiations on a new coronavirus relief bill were met instead with data that seems likely to entrench Democrats and Republicans in their positions. Just consider the headline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap Between Black and White Widens to Pandemic High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gap-between-black-white-unemployment-143021223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The gap between Black and White joblessness widened slightly in July, indicating the economic recovery continues to be uneven along racial lines even though labor-market conditions are improving across the board.The gap, which is now at its widest in the pandemic era, rose to 5.4 percentage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's scorn of Saudis is warning shot after Trump's embrace...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-scorn-saudis-warning-shot-080002789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Arabia reveled in Donald Trump’s decision to make the kingdom his first overseas destination as president. It will have to decide how welcoming to be for Joe Biden if he wins the White House in November.Trump’s May 2017 visit was marked by claims of $100 billion in arms sales, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TIGHTENING?</title>
      <link>https://cookpolitical.com/analysis/national/national-politics/polling-imperfect-its-bad-news-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cookpolitical.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching politics is an addiction, in which an assortment of websites provides hourly fixes, particularly in the form of poll aggregates and models like RealClearPolitics and FiveThirtyEight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We cannot stop people': 250,000 expected at SDakota motorcycle rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/We-cannot-stop-people-250-000-are-expected-at-15465630.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials are still warning against even small gatherings, and states with relatively low spread are ordering visitors from hot spots to self-quarantine.  But come Friday, about 250,000 people from across the country are still expected to start descending on a roughly 7,000-person community in South Dakota for one of the biggest motorcycle rallies in the world, a 10-day extravaganza so deeply rooted that Sturgis calls itself the City of Riders.  The mayor of Sturgis says there's not much to do but encourage "personal responsibility," set up sanitation stations and give out masks - though face coverings won't be required.  "We cannot stop people from coming," Mayor Mark Carstensen said Thursday on CNN.  Worried residents, however, say officials should have canceled the Sturgis Motorcycle Rally in a state where Republican Gov. Kristi Noem resisted stay-at-home orders and mask rules - and last month welcomed another mass event, President Donald Trump's Fourth of July weekend speech at the foot of Mount Rushmore. A city survey found that more than 60 percent of Sturgis residents wanted the event postponed, the Associated Press reported.  "This is a huge, foolish mistake to make to host the rally this year," Sturgis resident Linda Chaplin warned city counselors earlier this summer, as a debate raged, according to the AP. "The government of Sturgis needs to care most for its citizens."  "My grandma is absolutely terrified because she has diabetes and is in her 80s and has lupus," another resident told CNN. "If she gets it, it's a death sentence."  But the spectacle in South Dakota's Black Hills is hugely important to the local economy, bringing in $1.3 million in city and state tax revenue last year, according to the Argus Leader. A mayor's letter overviewing Sturgis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: 'This May be Last Time You'll See Me for While'...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/08/07/trump-this-may-be-the-last-time-youll-see-me-for-a-while/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No joke: Comedians could fall foul of Scottish hate crimes proposal...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807135551-4zmmh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-LGBT/ARTS:No joke: Comedians could fall foul of Scottish hate crimes proposal, lawyers warn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAP RAUNCH...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/music/cardi-b-megan-thee-stallion-release-wap-song-music-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cardi B and Megan Thee Stallion have released their new song 'WAP' and its music video. Look and listen here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seth Rogen Israel comments highlight fraught diaspora ties...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cd8614d0afeee761ae5dd9ba0b518f7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — It began as a lighthearted conversation between two Jewish comedians, riffing on a podcast about the idiosyncrasies of their shared heritage. But after talk turned to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime presidential adviser Scowcroft dies at 95...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/42daf34201cc29aceb84983cca227880</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Brent Scowcroft, who played a prominent role in American foreign policy as national security adviser to Presidents Gerald Ford and George H.W. Bush and was a Republican voice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Loomer About to Get Little Closer to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/right-richter-laura-loomer-is-about-to-get-a-little-closer-to-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fringe Trumpworld personality has tried to restyle herself this cycle as a less obviously hateful Republican candidate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carefree youths fuel global rise in infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200807-carefree-youths-fuel-global-rise-in-virus-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carefree youths fuel global rise in virus infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New polls show tight races for Graham, McConnell...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/510904-quinnipiac-poll-shows-competitive-senate-races-in-maine-south-carolina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New polls by Quinnipiac University show Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) and Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) in tight races.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETTING MARKETS FAVOR BIDEN</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807121115-44a9z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/GAMBLING-GMF (GRAPHICS):Betting markets favor Biden over Trump, but odds narrow in U.S. race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury Miami High-Rise First To Use COVID-Killing Robot...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/08/06/downtown-miami-luxury-high-covid-killing-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Downtown Miami luxury high-rise is now home to a COVID-killing robot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beirut Explodes in Violence; Protesters Gassed After Deadly Blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/beirut-explodes-in-violence-after-deadly-blast-with-riots-and-tear-gas-in-the-rubble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anguish has turned to anger in the Lebanese capital with police using tear gas on protesters out on the streets to demand transparency over deadly port explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 'fast radio burst' detected closer to Earth than ever before...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/fast-radio-burst-magnetar-milky-way.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most FRBs originate hundreds of millions of light-years away. This one came from inside the Milky Way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top figure in modern Judaism dies in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200807-top-figure-in-modern-judaism-dies-in-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top figure in modern Judaism dies in Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris raves draw crowds as virus shutters nightclubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200807-paris-raves-draw-crowds-as-virus-shutters-nightclubs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris raves draw crowds as virus shutters nightclubs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JULY JOBS: +1.76 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/jobs-report-july-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total nonfarm payroll increased of 1.763 million for the month. The unemployment rate fell to 10.2%, also better than the estimates from economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Ad slump hits media jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/advertising-slump-during-virus-crisis-hits-media-jobs-01596797407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media redundancies, partial layoffs and managerial wage cuts are on the rise as advertising markets implode, despite customers showing an ever stronger appetite for information on the coronavirus crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After first spared, rural California now ravaged...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-being-spared-rural-california-120002879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus is now hitting California&amp;#39;s Central Valley the hardest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'culture of violence' alleged by LAPD SWAT whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/inside-the-culture-of-violence-alleged-by-lapd-swat-whistleblower/article_7ad66c68-e790-506f-b1dd-e1069f3fc7e5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — After assessing the hilly terrain around a Sunland house where a homeless man had holed up one morning in May 2017, the Los Angeles Police Department's heavily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden VP race highly fluid days before expected pick...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/510936-biden-vp-race-is-highly-fluid-days-before-expected-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before Joe Biden is set to announce his running mate, Democrats including confidants of the former vice president say the race is fluid, with different candidates gaining or losing momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, losing grip on GOP, wields less influence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-losing-grip-gop-wields-110037157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than three months before election day, President Trump is losing his iron grip on congressional Republicans and is facing pushback on multiple fronts, from delaying the election to false claims about mail-in voting leading to widespread fraud, that show his weakened status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Wistful Age, Farmers Find New Angle: Chore TV...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/07/in-a-wistful-age-farmers-find-a-new-angle-chore-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEACHAM, Vt. — The sweet smell of hay rose off the earth on a recent evening, as Morgan Gold strode</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to U.S. Visitors: Please Don't Sneak Across Border...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/07/canada-to-u-s-visitors-please-dont-sneak-across-the-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was packing for my road trip from Colorado to Alberta, Canada, when the text came in from a gentleman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Trump Blew Up More Than Just TIKTOK and WECHAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2020-08-07/trump-s-bans-on-tiktok-wechat-could-hit-u-s-tech-giants-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackout hits large area of NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/07/power-outage-hits-large-area-of-manhattan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A widespread power outage left about 130,000 customers in darkness across a large area of Upper Manhattan early Friday, a Con Edison spokesman said. Three networks in the utility’s transmissi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border agents unearth 'most sophisticated smuggling tunnel in history'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e759e3542d183822decd8979d341a814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — An incomplete tunnel found stretching from Arizona to Mexico appears to be “the most sophisticated tunnel in U.S. history," authorities said. The tunnel intended for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House candidate selling anti-China face masks. Asian Americans say they incite racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-GOP-House-candidate-in-Va-is-selling-15465262.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a selfie by Virginia Del. Mark Cole that first caught Sookyung Oh's eye.  Cole, R-Fredericksburg, tweeted an image showing off a bright red face mask he said he'd purchased from the congressional campaign of Del. Nick Freitas, R-Culpeper.  "COVID-19, 'MADE IN CHINA," it read.  Oh, who is Virginia director of the National Korean American Service &amp; Education Consortium Action Fund, said that she and other Asian American community leaders were "shocked" to find the masks for sale as campaign merchandise.  "He's literally financing his campaign with a tactic that has been shown to exacerbate anti-Asian racism," Oh said of Freitas, a libertarian-leaning Republican who is running against first-term Democratic Rep. Abigail Spanberger in central Virginia's largely rural 7th district.  In an open letter issued this week, the NAKASEC Action Fund called on Freitas's campaign to stop selling the "Made in China" face masks, saying the merchandise is another example of anti-China political rhetoric that has put Asian Americans at risk of discrimination during the coronavirus pandemic.  Some of the rhetoric has come from President Donald Trump, who routinely refers to the deadly virus as the "China virus" and has also outraged his critics by calling it the "Kung flu."  A number of Asian American community organizers and two Asian American lawmakers from Virginia, Dels. Sam Rasoul, D-Roanoke, and Kathy Tran, D-Springfield, signed onto the statement.  "Blaming China for the COVID-19 crisis in the United States has led to a sharp increase of racially motivated attacks and discrimination against people of Chinese descent and others perceived to be of Chinese descent," the statement said, citing incidents in which Asian Americans have been spit on, cursed at or assaulted.  "Nick...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TIGHTENING?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-campaign-chief-sees-bounce-after-virus-briefings-revived/ar-BB17F6rm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain denies suffering second virus wave as cases mount ...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-08-spain-denies-virus-cases-mount.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's health ministry on Thursday denied that the country is facing a second wave of COVID-19 infections, despite a spike in cases of the virus in recent days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins switches to virtual fall semester...</title>
      <link>https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/08/06/university-moves-undergraduate-instruction-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hub.jhu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students urged to stay home due to resurgence of COVID-19; JHU increasing financial aid and other supports to offset pandemic's burden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye admits he wants President reelected in interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1268485/kanye-west-campaign-president-joe-biden-trump-reelection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West has apparently admitted to running a spoiler campaign to take away votes from Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden. In an interview with Forbes via text message, the rapper claimed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools begin opening, parents on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Virus-keeps-spreading-as-schools-begin-to-open-15465493.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Miss. - Even before President Donald Trump admonished his top coronavirus adviser for saying the country was entering a "new phase" of widespread infection, patients at Mississippi's only Level 1 trauma hospital were already on a wait for ICU beds.  "Our ICUs have been full for weeks," Dr. LouAnn Woodward, a vice chancellor at the University of Mississippi Medical Center in Jackson said Thursday. "It's a very acute issue we're facing here."  Mississippi, now experiencing the country's highest rate of positive tests, is emblematic of the pandemic's new reality. The virus is no longer principally an urban problem: It is present throughout every state, and those infected often don't know it, leading to what top public health officials call "inherent community spread."  This has proved true for Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine, a Republican, who learned he was positive for covid-19, the disease caused by the novel coronavirus, when he was tested Thursday morning in advance of a planned meeting with Trump. Trump went ahead with his visit to a Whirlpool plant; DeWine, the second governor known to have contracted the virus, went into self-isolation.  The situation in Mississippi is unfolding as well in other largely rural parts of the country, including in Alabama, South Carolina and California's Central Valley, places where so much viral material is circulating that when people get infected, many are unsure when or how it happened - so the outbreaks cannot be easily traced and contained.  State health officials in Alabama, for instance, say they are starting to see the impact of a mask mandate imposed two weeks ago. But some worry the dramatic spread might be attributable to people giving up on testing, as results can take days or weeks to come back.  "My fear is if we don't see...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GREED, ABUSE AND BRAZEN ILLEGALITY'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/new-york-attorney-general-letitia-james-files-lawsuit-dissolve-nra-n1236009</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James said last year that an investigation of the NRA was underway, part of her campaign promise to dig into the group's not-for-profit status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities go to extremes... </title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/cities-go-to-extremes-with-coronavirus-quarantine-crackdowns-checkpoints-power-shutoffs-steep-fines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the daily number of coronavirus cases in the United States still hovering at about 50,000 and American deaths from the disease approaching 160,000, cities across the country are taking increasingly severe measures to force the curve of the outbreak downward -- including power shutoffs, fines and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model forecasts 300,000 US covid deaths by Dec 1...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806221829-76we1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-University of Washington forecasts 300,000 U.S. COVID-19 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine 'checkpoint' opens at NYC's Penn Station...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806190446-nql9u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NEW YORK-QUARANTINE (TV, PIX):Quarantine 'checkpoint' opens at New York City's Penn Station to enforce travel rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance Standoff Over 'Smart' Streetlights...</title>
      <link>https://myfintale.com/business/in-san-diego-smart-streetlights-spark-surveillance-reform/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;myfintale.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this article A homicide detective looked up from the scene of a fatal shooting in San Diego’s Gaslamp District in August 2018 and saw [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge nixes Trump bid to delay suit from woman alleging rape...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/judge-nixes-trump-bid-delay-230247652.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York judge knocked down President Donald Trump&amp;#39;s bid to delay a lawsuit from a woman who accused him of rape, ruling in a decision released Thursday that the presidency doesn&amp;#39;t shield him from the case. Pointing to a recent U.S. Supreme Court ruling that the president isn&amp;#39;t immune</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In devastated Beirut, French leader offers comfort and a hug...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fdfa749a9ef0c29ed875c7dd63916e81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — It was one of the most powerful moments of Emmanuel Macron’s lightning visit to devastated Beirut: confronted by a distraught woman in a sea of enraged residents, the French leader...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W. Bush pays tribute to immigrants in new book...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f731fda15d2f91dcbdca160bc6be2b89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A new book by former President George W. Bush will highlight an issue which now sets him apart from many of his fellow Republicans — immigration. Crown announced Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims Biden opposes God...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a3c57cdcf8e44755d15930b29c660e36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — President Donald Trump billed his trip to Ohio Thursday as a chance to promote economic recovery, but he quickly pivoted to a deeply personal attack on Joe Biden, even questioning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress urges Postal Service to undo changes slowing mail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a291ebc31c5638aa5a9adafc2ff2b430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Lawmakers from both parties are calling on the U.S. Postal Service to immediately reverse operational changes that are causing delays in deliveries across the country just as big...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boomerang?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/20bd8464759422fd2df7100488f6be7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Kanye West's unlikely White House bid is getting help qualifying for presidential ballots in key states from Republicans around the country, fueling suspicions he's being pushed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misery Ranking Will Show USA Getting Worse Versus Rest of World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/misery-ranking-will-show-us-getting-worse-versus-rest-of-world/ar-BB17DrwR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: Daughter claims mom Kellyanne had her 'ARRESTED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12334875/claudia-conway-donald-trump-idiot-twitter-lawyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLAUDIA Conway claimed that her mom Kellyanne had her “arrested” in a TikTok video after she said that she “needs a lawyer.” One viewer claimed that the teenager went live o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Zuckerberg Fortune Surpasses $100 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2020/08/06/news/facebook-founder-mark-zuckerbergs-fortune-surpasses-100b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capturing rescue in Beirut...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-lebanon-security-blast-survivor-wider-idUSKCN25232S?taid=5f2c78b1df732d0001466633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When he first felt the ground shaking, Reuters photographer Mohamed Azakir thought Beirut had been struck by an earthquake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign aide admits killing Arkansas Senator...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8601615/Campaign-aide-admits-killing-Arkansas-Senator-Linda-Collins.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Lynn O'Donnell, 49, pleaded guilty on Thursday to first-degree murder and abuse of a corpse in the June 2019 death of former Arkansas Senator Linda Collins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Port worker found alive at sea 30 hours after explosion...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/06/beirut-port-worker-found-alive-at-sea-30-hours-after-explosion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bloodied Amin al-Zahed was admitted to the Rafic Hariri University Hospital after being pulled out of the Mediterranean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside San Fran restaurant's 'quarantine bubble'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/hashiri-quarantine-bubble-igloo-patio-dining-covid-15464405.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As restaurateurs continue to seek creative solutions to serve their clientele during the pandemic, a first-of-its-kind outdoor dining experience has made its way to downtown San Francisco.  Three seven-foot-tall translucent domes dotted the pavement of the Mint Plaza in SoMa on Wednesday evening, where a handful of customers at Sushi Hashiri were escorted inside to enjoy a meal -- and a rather unusual patio seating arrangement.  Intrigued by restaurants in Amsterdam and Japan that had implemented similar greenhouse-style structures, manager Ken Matsuura decided to test out the concept at his own restaurant.  "We hadn't seen any other Bay Area restaurants doing it, so why not be the first?" he told SFGATE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens arrested after jumping Mar-a-Lago wall with 'mini AK-47', loaded magazine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8597613/Police-3-teens-inadvertently-jump-wall-Mar-Lago.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three teenagers fleeing police while carrying a semiautomatic gun in a backpack jumped a wall at President Donald Trump's Mar-a-Lago resort, but probably didn't know that's where they were.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada allowing terminally ill patients to use psychedelic mushrooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/06/world/canada-psychedelic-mushrooms-cancer-therapy-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian government will allow four patients with incurable cancer to receive psilocybin therapy, which uses the drug found in the so-called "magic mushrooms" or "shrooms," to ease their end-of-life distress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commission rejects request for 4th face-off...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/06/commission-rejects-trump-request-for-4th-presidential-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Commission on Presidential Debates on Thursday rejected President Trump’s request that it schedule a fourth presidential debate. Trump attorney and former New York Mayor Rudy Giuliani req…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew's alleged 'puppet fetish' revealed...</title>
      <link>https://knewz.com/prince-andrew-victim-puppet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knewz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York faces fresh allegations in newly released court documents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE shines in pandemic with $2 trillion value on horizon...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/apple-shines-pandemic-trillion-horizon-72217125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early in 2020, Apple appeared to be caught in a horrible bind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope appoints 6 women to top roles on Vatican council in progressive step...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/06/pope-appoints-six-women-to-top-roles-on-vatican-council-in-progressive-step</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Labour minister Ruth Kelly is among the women who will oversee Vatican finances and address its cashflow problems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCUNIVERSAL TV Shake-Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/nbcuniversal-tv-shake-up-nbcs-paul-telegdy-frances-berwick-oversee-networks-1306249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conglomerate is searching for an executive to oversee a new entertainment programming unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA lifts advice to avoid all foreign travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200806-us-lifts-advice-to-avoid-all-foreign-travel-due-to-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US lifts advice to avoid all foreign travel due to pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Giving Patients $1,250 Stipend To Stay Home After Diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/08/05/alameda-county-offering-1250-stipend-to-help-covid-19-patients-during-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alameda County hopes to slow the spread of COVID-19 by helping families that face a sudden financial crisis when a test comes back positive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
