<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Woman sentenced to 30 years for taking, sharing nude photos of 1-year-old...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article245498850.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No denial from Mattis...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-allegations-leave-military-leaders-off-15544501.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Senior and former military leaders appeared to struggle Friday with how to respond to a report that President Donald Trump disparaged U.S. service members killed in combat as "losers," as the president attacked the allegations as "fake news."  The article elicited an array of reactions amid Trump's history with the military, which includes mocking Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz., for being captured in Vietnam, belittling the parents of an Army officer killed in Iraq, and dismissing brain injuries suffered by U.S. troops in an Iranian ballistic missile strike as "headaches."  The report in the Atlantic, published late Thursday, focused in part on a presidential visit to Arlington National Cemetery on Memorial Day in 2017 and a canceled visit to the Aisne-Marne American Cemetery outside Paris in 2018.  In the first example, according to the magazine, Trump allegedly said, "I don't get it. What was in it for them?" while standing with retired Marine Gen. John Kelly at the grave of Kelly's son, Robert, who was killed in Afghanistan. At the time, Kelly was homeland security secretary.  In the second, the Trump administration canceled the visit to the cemetery in France in bad weather when helicopter travel was questionable and Trump seemingly dismissed the World War I veterans who are buried there.  "Why should I go to that cemetery?" Trump said, according to the report. "It's filled with losers."  The president vehemently denied the report, attacking the Atlantic as a "third-rate magazine" and criticizing Kelly for not doing a good job as his former chief of staff.  "This man was totally exhausted. He wasn't even able to function in the last number of months," Trump said. He added that he did not know whether Kelly served as a source for the Atlantic's story, "but it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland on edge after suspect in weekend killing is fatally shot by police... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Suspect-in-Portland-slaying-is-killed-during-15542831.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. - Eyewitnesses and video footage gave police investigators murky accounts of the fatal shooting of a far-right activist here a week ago, according to newly unsealed court documents that shed new light on the politically charged incident but offer little in the way of definitive answers.  Investigators interviewed at least five people who saw some portion of the shooting of 39-year-old Aaron "Jay" Danielson and reviewed video footage, according to an arrest affidavit unsealed Friday, but their accounts stopped far short of providing a cohesive narrative.  Police said they ultimately came to believe Danielson was shot by a far-left activist, 48-year-old Michael Forest Reinoehl. But Reinoehl claimed publicly that he acted to defend himself and others, while a man who was with Danielson said his friend was targeted for a hat he wore bearing the insignia of the far-right Patriot Prayer group.  Reinoehl was shot and killed by law enforcement officers as they tried to arrest him Thursday.  The affidavit is likely to do little to cool the tension gripping Portland. Dueling demonstrators are expected in the region in the coming days, as a racial justice protest is set for Saturday and a pro-Trump event honoring Danielson is planned on Monday.  Oregon Democratic Gov. Kate Brown said at a press briefing Friday that she remained concerned about more violence and urged calm.  "There needs to be a community-wide effort to stop the violence," she said. "Because the violence must stop. Period."  Portland has seen more than three months of consecutive protests against police brutality, some of them descending into destruction and mayhem. But the tension intensified a week ago when a caravan of Trump supporters drove through the city in trucks, sparking skirmishes with those...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One man's battle shows why covid and obesity are such toxic mix... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/one-man-s-battle-shows-why-covid-19-and-obesity-are-a-toxic-mix/ar-BB18IMXH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Fallout After President Reportedly Insulted Dead Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-faces-election-fallout-after-reportedly-insulting-dead-troops/ar-BB18IwSU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen: Trump Would Do Anything to Win, Even 'Starting a War'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michael-cohen-trump-would-do-anything-to-win-even-going-so-far-as-to-start-a-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump lawyer Michael Cohen sat down with NBC News' Lester Holt for an interview ahead of the release of his book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop receives life-saving transplant  -- from woman he jailed...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/she-saved-my-life-police-officer-receives-life-saving-transplant-from-woman-he-put-in-jail-8-years-ago</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jocelynn James, a recovered drug addict and former member of “Franklin’s Most Wanted,” saved the life of the police officer who put her in jail nearly a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman suffers severe burns after hand sanitizer on skin catches fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/round-rock-mother-suffers-severe-burns-after-hand-sanitizer-starts-house-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her home has dozens of hand sanitizers and cleaning products because one of her daughters has a compromised immune system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom says SOUTHWEST AIRLINES kept serving alcohol to drunken man who groped her daughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/airlines/2020/09/04/texas-mom-says-southwest-airlines-kept-serving-alcohol-to-a-drunk-man-who-groped-her-teen-daughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas mother is suing Southwest Airlines after she said her teen daughter was sexually assaulted by an intoxicated passenger who was sold three beers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorothy Parker's ashes exhumed from longtime Baltimore resting place. But moved where?</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-dorothy-parker-ashes-exhumed-20200904-u5t6rvfzjjf2fc4qgbniqcbma4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 30 years in her Baltimore resting place, the ashes of famed Jazz Age writer Dorothy Parker are gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION KICKOFF: VOTING BEGINS!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-vote-mail-begins-white-205036956.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US election is officially open: North Carolina on Friday launched vote-by-mail operations for the November 3 contest between President Donald Trump and Democrat Joe Biden, which is getting uglier by the hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team pushes social media limits...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-team-pushes-social-media-011145049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A message saying you &amp;quot;won&amp;#39;t be safe&amp;quot; in Joe Biden&amp;#39;s America. The former vice president shown &amp;quot;sleeping&amp;quot; during a television interview. Biden &amp;quot;hiding&amp;quot; -- alone -- in his basement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Tehran months away from nuke weapon...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-caught-stockpiling-enriched-uranium-needed-for-bomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has evidence that Iran is stockpiling enriched uranium, the key component in a nuclear weapon, in direct violation of international restrictions on Tehran’s use of the fissile material.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat of power outages...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-blackout-risk-rising-record-213737225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Another round of record-breaking heat hangs over California just weeks after searing temperatures pushed its electric grid to the brink, temporarily knocking out power to millions.Temperatures are forecast to top 100 degrees Fahrenheit (38 Celsius) across the state and reach as high as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing launches secret spacecraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/4/china-launches-reusable-robotic-spacecraft-mimics-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Friday launched a reusable spacecraft that appears to be Beijing’s answer to the secretive U.S. X-37 space plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  DUTY, HONOR, COUNTRY</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/biden-camp-seizes-on-trumps-reported-military-scorn-says-we-understand-trumps-soul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Service members “have asked us if the president is simply waiting for them to die,” Rep. Conor Lamb, a former Marine and a Biden ally, said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Americans Who Died in War 'Losers', 'Suckers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/09/trump-americans-who-died-at-war-are-losers-and-suckers/615997/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has repeatedly disparaged the intelligence of service members, and asked that wounded veterans be kept out of military parades, multiple sources tell The Atlantic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS CONFIRMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/09/04/shocker-fox-newss-jennifer-griffin-confirms-atlantic-magazine-story-about-trump-disdain-for-military-and-mccain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News National Correspondent Jennifer Griffin says she has confirmed with two sources the gist of the Atlantic magazine story about Donald Trump’s disdain of the military and John McCain. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political party biggest factor in whether state has mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/newslocalpolitics/governors-political-party-is-biggest-factor-in-whether-a-state-has-imposed-mask-mandate-study-finds/ar-BB18GK82?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIA Soldiers Deserved Their Fate?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/washington-post-adds-new-reporting-trump-believes-vietnam-veterans-are-losers-and-mia-soldiers-deserved-their-fate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post confirmed and added to the Atlantic's reporting that President Donald Trump denigrated U.S. soldiers killed or captured in war, citing unnamed sources that included a "former senior administration official."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS KELLY SOURCE?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-john-kelly-troops-atlantic-chief-staff-white-house-a9706321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan downs Chinese fighter jet?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1331289/China-plane-crash-Taiwan-shoot-fighter-jet-world-war-3-missile-defence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN has been forced to publicly reject claims it shot down a Chinese military jet, after speculation spiralled out of control on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG'S CLAIMS ROIL DC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edf5d17c4d41cfb69117f0cf97ef6ac6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump defended himself Friday against accusations that he mocked American war dead as his Democratic rival, Joe Biden, intensified efforts to frame the election...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling versions of reality define fall campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/780b2edfd25af18c0107ee382356194f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — On the campaign trail with President Donald Trump, the pandemic is largely over, the economy is roaring back, and murderous mobs are infiltrating America's suburbs. With...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal border crossings surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/4/illegal-border-crossings-surge-coronavirus-fades-d/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents nabbed nearly 50,000 illegal immigrants along the southern border in August, marking the worst month in a year as the clampdown that had accompanied the coronavirus pandemic begins to fade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Dismisses 11 Students Who Gathered in Same Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/news/world/us/2020/09/04/northeastern-dismisses-11-students-who-gathered-in-same-room.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON - Northeastern University said Friday it has dismissed 11 freshman students for the fall semester for violating campus social distancing guidel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWELL:  Recovery To Take Long Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/09/04/909627932/feds-jerome-powell-jobless-rate-better-than-expected-recovery-to-take-a-long-tim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with NPR, Powell says it may take years before the economy has fully recovered. He says practicing social distancing and wearing masks is essential for the economy to rebound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's brother made $8 million selling TESLA shares -- days before buying them...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musks-brother-kimbal-made-more-than-8-million-selling-tesla-stock-2-days-before-he-bought-them-2020-09-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s younger brother, Kimbal, appears to have made more than $8 million on Tesla’s stock this week, as he exercised options to buy the stock, two days...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prof pretending to be black 'only confessed when black colleagues exposed her'
...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1422051/jessica-krug-george-washington-university-black-professor-exposed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PROFESSOR of African history who pretended to be black has only confessed because “black colleagues exposed her fake background.” Jessica A Krug – a 38-year-old white professor …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mad dash -- for Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2020/09/03/texas-president-trump-bus-tour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's reelection campaign launched a bus tour of the state Thursday, though surrogates said — strenuously — that they still don't see Texas in play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel crisis hits new milestone...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/hotel-crisis-coronavirus-economy-travel-556b1f8d-9a12-4555-8a94-a790d78f9bd3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic-era travel drought has continued through major holiday weekends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers reveal true scale of megalodon shark for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/sep/03/researchers-reveal-true-scale-of-megalodon-shark-for-first-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK study shows dorsal fin of prehistoric mega-fish was similar height to adult human</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth floods across Mexico border during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/mexico-border-meth-coronavirus-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though we’re in the middle of a pandemic, CBP officers say meth seizures have nearly doubled this year compared to last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University Offers Course on 'How to Overthrow the State'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2020/09/03/washington-and-lee-university-offers-course-on-how-to-overthrow-the-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington and Lee University in Lexington, Virginia, is offering a course entitled "How to Overthrow the State," which includes encouraging students to engage in "producing a Manifesto," and "writing a persuasive essay on rewriting history and confronting memory."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 in 10 voters say civil unrest a key issue...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/515128-over-90-percent-say-civil-unrest-will-be-key-issue-in-presidential-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vast majority of voters in a new Harvard CAPS-Harris poll released exclusively to The Hill say they believe civil unrest will be an important issue in the November election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not again! Sailors on U.S. aircraft carrier test positive for COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2020/09/04/sailors-test-positive-for-covid-19-on-carrier-uss-ronald-reagan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small group of sailors tested positive for COVID-19 last week while underway aboard USS Ronald Reagan (CVN-76) following a port call in Guam, Navy officials confirmed to USNI News on Friday. The unspecified number of the crew tested positive for the virus while the carrier was underway on Aug. 27, according to a 7th …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creepy 'Geofence' Finds Anyone Who Went Near a Crime Scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/creepy-geofence-finds-anyone-near-crime-scene/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police increasingly ask Google and other tech firms for data about who was where, when. Two judges ruled the investigative tool invalid in a Chicago case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Falwell mixed personal finances with his university's...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-falwell-legacy-insight/how-jerry-falwell-jr-mixed-his-personal-finances-with-his-universitys-idUSKBN25V27L</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After parting ways with President Jerry Falwell Jr in the wake of personal scandals, Liberty University has hired a firm to investigate “all facets” of Falwell’s tenure, including the school’s financial and real estate operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER Fort Hood soldier DIES; 28th this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8698891/Fort-Hood-soldier-dies-collapsing-Texas-base.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pvt. Corlton L. Chee, 25, died Wednesday after he collapsed following physical fitness training on August 28, Fort Hood officials said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead man' indicted for stealing $500K from COVID-19 help funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2020/09/03/metro/dead-man-andover-indicted-stealing-500k-covid-19-help-funds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Andover man whose alleged staged suicide failed to keep him out of custody is now facing charges in Rhode Island that could send him to prison for up to 30 years. He allegedly tried to scam $500,000 in federal COVID-19 relief loans, federal prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat of power outages...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/newsom-declares-state-of-emergency-as-california-faces-historic-heat-threat-of-power-outages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With scorching temperatures set to sear California through Labor Day weekend, Gov. Gavin Newsom issued an emergency proclamation aimed at shoring up the state’s energy capacity and staving off the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House to vote on marijuana legalization for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/09/04/marijuana-house-vote-federal-legalization-first-time/5678068002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's about time," Rep. Jerry Nadler told USA TODAY, calling it a "historic vote" although its future in the GOP-led Senate appears fraught.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive mystery holes appear in Siberian tundra...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/04/world/craters-tundra-siberia-trnd-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dramatic 30-meter (100-feet) deep hole in Western Siberia is the latest of several to have formed in the region since 2014. Scientists think the craters are formed by an explosive buildup of methane gas but there is still a lot they don't know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure on FDA for coronavirus silver bullet ahead of Election Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/03/politics/white-house-fda-coronavirus-vaccine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a persistent polling deficit and a struggling economy, President Donald Trump has cranked up pressure on administration health officials to expedite work both on a coronavirus vaccine and on treatments that might signal to voters there is an end in sight to the life-altering pandemic that has imperiled his reelection prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK 2015...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2015/07/18/donald-trump-says-mccain-is-not-a-war-hero-and-a-loser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This dumb diatribe might have Trumped them all. Donald Trump on Saturday said there was nothing heroic about the 5¹/₂ years Sen. John McCain spent in a North Vietnamese POW camp — souring even his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ankara Warns West It Will Continue to Shop Around for Missiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/turkey-warns-west-it-will-continue-to-shop-around-for-missiles/ar-BB18GRFG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raging Campus Outbreaks Send Students Home... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/careersandeducation/raging-campus-outbreaks-send-students-home-across-the-us/ar-BB18IkAh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia working to undermine confidence, DHS warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Russia-is-working-to-undermine-confidence-in-15542913.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is seeking "to undermine public trust in the electoral process" by spreading false claims that mail-in-ballots are riddled with fraud and susceptible to manipulation, according to a new intelligence bulletin by the Department of Homeland Security.  Many of the claims made by Russian sources are identical to repeated, unsupported public statements aired by President Donald Trump and Attorney General William Barr, who have said that mailed ballots aren't trustworthy while warning of the potential for rampant fraud in November's elections.  Homeland Security's intelligence office has assessed that Russian actors "are likely to promote allegations of corruption, system failure, and foreign malign interference to sow distrust in Democratic institutions and election outcomes," the bulletin states. Russia spreads these claims through a network of state-controlled media, proxy websites and social media trolls, it adds.  The document doesn't identify any of those media sources by name. But current and former officials who have seen it said the assessment is based in part on classified intelligence about the Russian government's efforts to interfere with the 2020 elections, in a repeat of its operations four years ago, which intelligence agencies have unanimously concluded were designed to help Trump win.  The intelligence on Russian efforts to undermine voting-by-mail has been assessed as credible and was deemed important enough to share in an unclassified form on Thursday with state and local officials so that they can take steps to protect elections from manipulation, the current and former officials said. They spoke on the condition of anonymity because the information was not intended to be shared publicly.  The bulletin doesn't cite any particular statements by Trump, Barr or other U.S. officials, but it states that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Pandemic Has Taught 'Greatness of Science, but Also Its Limits'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/health/2020/09/04/pope-francis-pandemic-has-taught-the-greatness-of-science-but-also-its-limits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis declared Friday that the coronavirus pandemic has revealed both the greatness and the limits of science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg sees civil unrest if results trickle in...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/zuckerberg-facebook-election-axios-on-hbo-c719ad86-8ab8-43d6-a491-620dc16a3a3d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with "Axios on HBO," the Facebook CEO says the platform will do everything it can not to contribute to tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WARNS NO VAX UNTIL NEXT YEAR</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tempers-quick-vaccine-hopes-162152624.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization said Friday it did not expect widespread immunisation against the novel coronavirus until mid-2021, tempering hopes just as research revealed encouraging early results from a Russian vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon orders STARS AND STRIPES newspaper to shut down...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2020/09/04/trump-and-stars-and-stripes-attacking-american-icon-column/5706859002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump wants to pull funding from Stars and Stripes, a newspaper for American troops that began in the Civil War and has been serving our soldiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS MODEL:  DEATHS DOUBLE BY JAN.</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/04/key-coronavirus-forecast-predicts-over-410000-total-us-deaths-by-jan-1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are facing the prospect of a deadly December,"Â Dr. Christopher Murray, director of IHME, said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiz the Law, born in New York and raised in Kentucky, carries dreams of two farms in Derby...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Tiz-the-Law-born-in-New-York-and-raised-in-15542861.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE - Among the 14 states and two foreign countries that have bred foals who have become Kentucky Derby winners, Kentucky leads 111-6 over second-place Florida, 111-4 over third-place California and Virginia (unless one counts Secretariat more than once), and 111-1 over New York, leads that do seem insurmountable during our lifetimes. Yet if lopsided favorite Tiz the Law were to win the 146th Kentucky Derby on Saturday, New York would narrow its score to 111-2, and that would be something.  It's always something when somebody on hoofs who did not join the world in Kentucky joins the winner's circle at the Derby. It has happened only 34 times out of 145 since 1875, and only once in the last 15 runnings - in 2014, with the pixie-dust story arc of that Californian named California Chrome. So it just figures that even if Tiz the Law sustains his dominance of 2020, it would flatter New York . . . and Kentucky.  He was conceived in Kentucky, in Versailles.  His late mom traveled to New York, part of a general cooperation between two farms.  He joined all the earthly beings as a Bay horse with a big blaze on March 19, 2017, in New York.  He lived 90 days there per agreement, then returned to Kentucky to grow up, not to mention relish the equine pool at Twin Creeks Racing Stables in Versailles.  He returned to New York for sale as a yearling in August 2018.  That means two sets of farm people in two different states have watched him win the Belmont Stakes in June and the Travers in August with the mixtures of pride and wonder and happy disbelief. They know that for all the consuming toil they exert, having something like this happen in life borders on the farcical.  "A lot of times when it seems like nothing works in our business," said Becky Thomas, the owner of Sequel, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Model Now Predicts 410,000 Deaths By Year End...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/breaking-top-coronavirus-model-now-predicts-410000-u-s-deaths-by-years-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key predictive model used by the White House coronavirus task force now predicts the U.S. death toll could likely be 410,000 by January 1, 2021 — and up to 620,000 if the U.S. pursued a "herd immunity" strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing launches secret spacecraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8698169/China-carries-secretive-launch-reusable-experimental-spacecraft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long March-2F carrier delivered the spacecraft into orbit from Jiuquan Satellite Launch Centre in northwestern Chinese region Inner Mongolia, reported state media Xinhua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police hunt car that drove into BLM protesters in Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/sep/04/new-york-police-car-times-square</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shows car moving through crowd with horn blaring as protesters scramble to get out of the way</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Supply Chain Issues'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/postal-chiefs-say-supply-chain-issues-risk-your-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Despite the heroic efforts ...the reality is, that’s going to be a difficult situation for that voter to have their vote counted,” one official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Test Can Predict Psychotic Disorders Years Before Develop...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/blood-test-can-predict-psychotic-disorders-psychosis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have developed a potentially game-changing way to predict if a person is at risk of psychosis years down the line: a blood test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER SURGE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/04/labor-day-weekend-will-set-the-course-for-the-coronavirus-this-fall.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current outbreak in the U.S. combined with the holiday weekend have the makings of what Vanderbilt University infectious disease specialist Dr. William Schaffner described as an "accelerator weekend."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Casinos Desperate for More Quarters...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/coin-shortage-for-slot-machines-leaves-casinos-offering-freebies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americaâ€™s Casinos Are Desperate for More QuartersÂ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired general torches president: 'You're no patriot'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/515099-retired-general-torches-reported-trump-comments-on-military-youre-no</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A retired Army general on Thursday night went viral for his scathing response to a report that President Trump made</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catwalk shows to return for London Fashion Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200904-catwalk-shows-to-return-for-london-fashion-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catwalk shows to return for London Fashion Week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People can control own happiness...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bryanrobinson/2020/09/03/can-you-control-your-happiness-new-study-gives-a-scientific-backed-answer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a world where happiness is in short supply, a new study shows your happiness might be more in your control than you think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION KICKOFF: VOTING BEGINS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/04/politics/2020-election-north-carolina-ballots-mail/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ballots are on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECONOMY ADDS 1.4 MILLION JOBS IN AUGUST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/04/jobs-report-august-2020-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key model predicts 400,000 deaths in USA by January...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/515090-key-model-predicts-400000-coronavirus-deaths-in-us-by-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key forecasting model often cited by experts and used by the White House has revised its prediction of COVID-19 deaths in the U.S., now estimating a peak of 410,451 by January 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside intense gunbattle...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/04/suspected-protest-shooter-michael-reinoehl-had-gun-when-killed-by-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Antifa-supporting security guard wanted in the killing of a right-wing protester in Portland fired “40 or 50” rounds from an assault rifle at cops before he was shot to death Thursday in Washin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCHESTER ERUPTS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/04/2-cops-hurt-at-rochester-protest-over-daniel-prudes-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Rochester cops were injured and eight people arrested early Friday after a protest by over 200 demonstrators demanding justice for Daniel Prude — who suffocated while in police custody — descen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic politicking: Dems at laptops. GOP at door...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9b1ac944e8e759de99ced3a5ff90022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REEDSBURG, Wisconsin (AP) — At a family dining table in tiny Reedsburg, Wisconsin, Arlene Ketchpaw chatted with a half-dozen Sauk County Democrats about how to win over voters, her fellow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for survivor in Beirut rubble grips grieving nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d3b47ab57c9b319f62800b22fbe3d5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Rescue workers used cranes, shovels and their bare hands in search operations that resumed early Friday in the rubble of a building that collapsed last month in Beirut’s catastrophic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors ready for big market moves as election nears...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-volatility-analysis/2016-all-over-again-investors-ready-for-big-market-moves-as-us-election-nears-idUSKBN25V1EW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Market volatility is back - and investors expect more wild swings in the coming weeks and months as the U.S. presidential election closes in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots will be 'as important as phones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/humans-wont-able-live-without-22627877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVES: The author of new book Sex Robots &amp; Vegan Meat has talked Daily Star Online through her new book. In it, she spoke to one sex doll owner who thinks dolls will become as important as mobile phones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urinating woman seen 'performing sex act' on NYC street...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8690571/Woman-seen-performing-sex-act-man-New-York-City-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A photo has emerged showing a woman crouching down while apparently performing oral sex on a shirtless man near W 79th Street and Broadway around 9pm on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech stocks smashed... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/03/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech stocks remained weak a second day. Futures for the tech-heavy Nasdaq-100 lost 0.5%</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of workers expect 'retirement' to include job...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/03/many-workers-expect-their-retirement-to-include-a-job-survey-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half (54%) of workers say they anticipate their golden years to include a job â€” an expectation that's even more pointed among among baby boomers (59%) and Generation X (60%).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ankara Warns West It Will Continue to Shop Around for Missiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/turkey-warns-west-it-will-continue-to-shop-around-for-missiles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey Warns West It Will Continue to Shop Around for Missiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Gov: 4,000-Person Social-Distancing Taskforce Needed Before Allowing Indoor Dining...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/09/03/andrew-cuomo-says-4000-person-nypd-social-distancing-taskforce-needed-before-hell-allow-indoor-dining-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City restaurants have been excluded from the reopening of dining rooms in the rest of the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frenchman to livestream death in right-to-die case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frenchman-livestream-death-die-case-093453632.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Frenchman who is suffering from an incurable condition said Friday he plans to livestream his death on social media as he refuses to take food, drink or medicine after President Emmanuel Macron turned down his request for euthanasia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCarolina kicks off mail voting as requests spike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3c98948c51cfdb2f23186e77f87ebb24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH (AP) — Mail balloting in the presidential election is set to begin Friday as North Carolina starts sending out more than 600,000 ballots to voters — responding to a massive spike in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Record heat expected in West...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/record-heat-expected-labor-day-weekend-west/story?id=72812988</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several excessive heat warnings and advisories have already been issued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA beat down...</title>
      <link>/https://www.marketwatch.com/story/teslas-stock-falls-on-course-for-longest-losing-streak-since-march-2020-09-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordics welfare model limits economic damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200903-nordics-welfare-model-limits-corona-economic-damage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nordics welfare model limits corona economic damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal task force kills Portland shooting suspect at arrest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f0418fd4a37be8d9b6953c8359109587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LACEY, Wash. (AP) — A man suspected of fatally shooting a supporter of a right-wing group in Portland, Oregon, last week after a caravan of Donald Trump backers rode through downtown was killed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions flare across Mediterranean as world powers manuver...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/2/russia-turkey-israel-vie-mediterranean-resources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow is eyeing a possible military base along the oil-rich shores of Libya. China is seeking investment deals across the region. Turkey is clashing with NATO partner Greece over drilling rights and militarized islands. Newly discovered offshore natural gas deposits have nations scrambling to stake their claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Parties Hit Greek Islands!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1416754/boozy-brits-zante-coronavirus-parties-greece/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ZANTE has become a new coronavirus hotspot as Brit super-spreaders shun masks, cram onto packed flights, and party like there isn’t a pandemic. Shameless tourists booze were pictured “F*** Co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privately built border wall will fail, engineering report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2020/09/02/texas-private-border-wall-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report, set to be filed in federal court this week, confirms reporting from ProPublica and The Texas Tribune that found portions of the wall were in danger of overturning if not fixed due to extensive erosion just months after it was built.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake rattles Florida-Alabama line...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/weather/2020/09/03/an-earthquake-hit-florida-on-thursday-how-often-does-that-happen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were no injuries or damage reported from the quake Thursday, though a lot of people reported feeling it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People can control own happiness...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bryanrobinson/2020/09/03/can-you-control-your-happiness-new-study-gives-a-scientific-backed-answer/#101636135f56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a world where happiness is in short supply, a new study shows your happiness might be more in your control than you think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle sues agency over paparazzi pics of her walking dogs with Archie...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/meghan-markle-sues-agency-over-22625091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duchess of Sussex claims her privacy was breached when the snaps were taken in Vancouver in January, and has launched legal action against agency Splash News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Production Halted...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/robert-pattinson-coronavirus-batman-1234758442/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED: Robert Pattinson has tested positive for coronavirus, prompting “The Batman” to suspend filming in the United Kingdom days after it went back into production, according to a so…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr Unsure If Illegal...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/935580/attorney-general-barr-wont-agree-illegal-vote-twice-trump-urged-claims-ignorance-state-laws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump twice on Wednesday urged supporters in North Carolina to vote two times in the presidential election, once by mail and then again in person, ostensibly to test his unsubstantiated claims that mail-in voting will be rife with fraud. 'Intentionally voting twice is illegal, and in many states, including North Carolina, it is a felony,' The Washington Post notes. Attorney General William Barr either does not know that or he was just being coy in an interview Wednesday evening with CNN's Wolf Blitzer. 'I don't know what the law in the particular state says' -- Wolf Blitzer has to explain to the Attorney General of the United States that it's actually illegal to vote twice pic.twitter.com/ytDfzZoZV6 â€” Aaron Rupar (@atrupar) September 2, 2020 Blitzer read Barr what Trump had said, and Barr suggested Trump was just 'trying to make the point that the ability to monitor this system is not good.' Blitzer pointed out that if anyone followed Trump's advice, they would be breaking the law, and Barr responded, 'I don't know what the law in the particular state says.' He added he's not sure if it is illegal to vote twice in any state, then claimed that widespread mail-in voting 'is very open to fraud and coercion, is reckless and dangerous, and people are playing with fire.' 'Multiple studies have debunked the notion of pervasive voter fraud in general and in the vote-by-mail process,' The Associated Press reports. The Post noted that its own analysis of mail-in voting in three states where it is the primary means of casting ballots found 372 possible cases of double voting or other fraud out of 14.6 million ballots mailed in for the 2016 and 2018 elections, a potential fraud rate of 0.0025 percent. If you try out Trump's idea in real life, you will either be blocked from voting in person or your mail-in ballot will be 'spoiled,' Patrick Gannon, spokesman for the North Carolina State Board of Elections, told The New York Times. He suggested that if you are worried about your mail-in ballot, rather than commit felony vote fraud, track its progress on the board's website. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab nations resist normalizing ties with Israel...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/despite-pressure-trump-arab-nations-174257880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Besides UAE, no other Arab nation has said it is willing to take the long-shunned leap to accept and recognize Israel as a legitimate Mideast neighbor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems request Hatch Act probe of Republican convention...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8fe0746f4db1030220f6114a0a97a485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats on the House Oversight Committee are seeking an investigation into what they call repeated violations of the federal Hatch Act by members of the Trump administration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskless Trump mocks way Biden wears mask...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d093d8fefee24b97f449f83d405c9dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the 2020 presidential campaign (all times local): 7:45 p.m. President Donald Trump is mocking his Democratic rival for letting his mask hang off his ear...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
