<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Suspense builds ahead of major Pentagon report...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/may/21/ufos-go-mainstream-suspense-builds-major-pentagon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon-to-be-President Jimmy Carter in 1973 went public with a claim he had seen a UFO years earlier in the skies above rural Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Bizarre Encounter With Mysterious 'Highly Modified' Drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/40724/border-patrol-helicopter-had-bizarre-encounter-with-mysterious-highly-modified-drone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mystery drone flew up to 14,000 feet and was tracked for over an hour. Now the FBI is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Black Lives Matter activist shot in London following 'numerous death threats'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/British-Black-Lives-Matter-activist-Sasha-Johnson-16198570.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON - A British Black Lives Matter activist is fighting for her life after being shot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey set for return to movies with paedophilia drama...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/may/24/kevin-spacey-return-italian-paedophilia-drama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor, who has been the subject of multiple sexual misconduct allegations, is to play a detective in Franco Nero’s film about a man wrongly suspected of child abuse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This $68 billion Australian city wants to become next Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/24/springfield-australian-smart-city-wants-to-be-the-next-silicon-valley.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The world has learned a lot from Silicon Valley," Greater Springfield's founder told CNBC. "We said: that's 85 years old. Let's design the latest version."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTAGION WATCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/mainstream-markets-shrug-at-volatile-1-trillion-crypto-rout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mainstream Markets Shrug at Volatile $1 Trillion Crypto Rout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Matter activist critical after shot in head...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-57223755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sasha Johnson is being treated in intensive care after being shot in the head, her party says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 close to agreement on taxation of world's largest companies...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210524054158-8alai</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G7-SUMMIT/TAX (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-G7 is close to agreement on taxation of world’s largest companies - FT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Roman Protasevich?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/23/who-is-roman-protasevich-the-captive-journalist-in-belarus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has all of the elements of a Jason Bourne plot: A commercial flight carrying a dissident journalist is intercepted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto back? O'Rourke mulling bid for TX gov...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-texas-election-2020-campaign-2016-government-and-politics-1d2fcef28c9d9a00c33500845136bda1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — There’s no road trip, no soul searching. No beard or blogging. But Beto O’Rourke is making a political life decision again. Three years after becoming Democrats’ breakout star out of Texas, and a year removed from crashing back to Earth in a short-lived presidential run, O’Roukre is again weighing another campaign — this time for governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGS TO SNIFF FOR COVID AT AIRPORTS?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/study-shows-dogs-can-detect-covid-positive-arrivals/ar-AAKiYeM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogs can be trained to detect more than 90 percent of Covid-19 infections even when patients are asymptomatic, according to research published Monday, which authors hope could help replace the need to quarantine new arrivals. - 'Important start' - Authors of the research, which has yet to be peer-reviewed, said they hoped it could eventually replace the need for travellers to quarantine -- which necessarily disrupts every arrival even though the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More anti-semitic attacks in USA; Calls for forceful response...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98who-e2-80-99s-out-protecting-us-e2-80-99-spate-of-anti-jewish-attacks-in-the-us-draws-calls-for-more-forceful-response/ar-AAKj06p?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen antisemitic incidents, including several physical attacks that led to injuries, have been reported since fighting erupted in Israel and Gaza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin prices tumble 50% from peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bitcoin-prices-tumble-50-from-peak-and-mark-cuban-calls-the-crypto-crash-the-great-unwind-11621790964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin prices on Sunday afternoon are in free fall anew, with the world's No.1 crypto spiraling down more than 50% from a peak in around the middle of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,500 rowdy teens storm Southern California beach to attend TIKTOK star's birthday...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9610195/Viral-video-drew-hundreds-California-party-150-arrested.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Southern California said an 'unruly' crowd of at least 2,500 teens hurled fireworks, bottles, and rocks at officers in Huntington Beach on Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER OF GOLD?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/23/bitcoin-resumes-selloff-over-weekend-briefly-falls-below-33000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bitcoin sell-off continued Sunday following a roller-coaster week of trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Ponders Zero-Spectator Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsmax.com/newsfront/japan-olympics/2021/05/23/id/1022456/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a year of empty bleachers and fake crowd noises, sports fans are returning to stadiums around the world. But the one arena where they might not be welcome is the biggest event of all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's Osaka city crumples under covid onslaught...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210523235150-h4422</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN-OSAKA (PIX, TV):No one's safe anymore: Japan's Osaka city crumples under COVID-19 onslaught</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global aviation stunned...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210523212916-edhjf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELARUS-POLITICS/ICAO (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Global aviation stunned by Belarus jetliner diversion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Travel Will Require Picking Your Way Through a Maze of Border Rules...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/lifestyle/destination-of-the-week/summer-travel-will-require-picking-your-way-through-a-maze-of-border-rules-7326876/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unvaccinated could potentially get in too if the US is added to an EU “white list” that currently features eight countries, including New Zealand and Israel, with low Covid-19 rates.travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE FOR THE AGES:  Mickelson wins PGA at 50...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-29ac515b828badcd4f09c2b67804e874</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIAWAH ISLAND, S.C. (AP) — Phil Mickelson has delivered so many thrills and spills over 30 years of pure theater that no one ever knows what he will do next. His latest act was a real stunner: A major champion at age 50.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belarus scrambles fighter to force airliner to land, arrests opponent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-belarus-technology-business-government-and-politics-66ed27d88963aaf10c9f595433ac14fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VILNIUS, Lithuania (AP) — A prominent opponent of Belarus' authoritarian president was arrested Sunday after the airliner in which he was traveling was diverted to the country after a bomb threat, in what the opposition and Western officials denounced as a hijacking operation by the government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO sightings went from joke to national security worry in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-ufo-sightings-went-from-joke-to-national-security-worry-in-washington/ar-AAKiHOp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of national intelligence is expected to unveil an unclassified report next month on everything government agencies know about UFOs, including scores of unusual sightings by military pilots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a scary time' for LA Jews as attacks bring heightened security, anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scary-time-l-jews-attacks-134010403.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remi Franklin, a jujitsu practitioner and security volunteer, stood guard on La Brea Avenue on Saturday afternoon as the neighborhood's highly visible Orthodox Jewish population made their way home from Shabbat services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAZI SYMBOLS</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15038309/palestine-protest-london-flares-burn-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-Semitic chanting and posters, along with Nazi symbols have marred pro-Palestine protests across the country with the Israeli flag being burned in a central London demo. The Met Police confirme…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Antisemitic attack outside LA sushi restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/man-arrested-in-suspected-antisemitic-attack-outside-la-sushi-restaurant-police-say/ar-AAKh1ze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was arrested on suspicion of assault with a deadly weapon, and investigators believe the crime was motivated by hate, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coke Snorting During Live EUROVISION Broadcast?!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-eurovision-song-contest-winner-under-investigation-for-allegations-he-snorted-cocaine-on-live-television/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Italian band called Maneskin is denying charges that a live broadcast of the Eurovision song contests showed band members snorting drugs from a table. The video, which is embedded above, appears to show a band member dropping his head to a table during a live shot, though no drugs are visible in the shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs 97% effective in detecting Covid in human sweat...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/dogs-97-effective-in-detecting-covid-19-in-human-sweat-according-to-french-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French study reported the canines are highly effective in detecting COVID-19 in human perspiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek owners protest mandatory sterilization of pets...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/greek-dog-owners-protest-mandatory-sterilization-of-pets/19692056/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several hundred dog owners and their pets gathered Sunday outside Greece’s Parliament in protest against a draft law that will make sterilization of household pets — especially cats and dogs — mandatory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing mystery of suspected energy attacks draws concern...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-government-and-politics-51ebd4f82664aacc5394c1863cd6a5f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration is facing new pressure to resolve a mystery that has vexed its predecessors: Is an adversary using a microwave or radio wave weapon to attack the brains of U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fueled eating disorder surge in teens, adults...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-pandemics-lifestyle-eating-disorders-health-27c9d5680980b1452f7e512db4d9f825</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many hospital beds are full. Waiting lists for outpatient treatment are bulging. And teens and adults seeking help for eating disorders are often finding it takes months to get an appointment. The pandemic created treacherous conditions for eating disorders, leading to a surge of new cases and relapses that is not abating as restrictions are loosened and COVID-19 cases subside in many places, doctors and other specialists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor, rich: All are on their own...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-coronavirus-pandemic-health-f291b00195967277a6ea1ca0ec5a1c8b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — For the family of the retired diplomat, the terror struck as they tried desperately to get him past the entrance doors of a private hospital. For the New Delhi family, it came when they had to create a hospital room in their ground-floor apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia-like pro-Palestinian gangs attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/militia-like-pro-palestinian-gangs-attack-jews-across-us-west-analysis-668824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The militia-style of ISIS, now under the Hamas banner, appears to have come to more western countries under the guise of pro-Palestinian activism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider to 'expose' country music 'hypocrites' in new book...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/05/23/music-insider-to-expose-country-music-hypocrites-in-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Atlantic Records exec Dorothy Carvello — who penned a tell-all about rampant sexism in the music biz — has set her sights on Nashville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian cable car plunges to the ground, killing at least 9...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-84672bf7fcd99f103587cc3862b49dcc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — A mountaintop cable car plunged to the ground in northern Italy on Sunday, killing at least nine people and sending two children to the hospital, authorities said. A photo of the wreckage taken by Italy's fire squad showed the crushed and crumpled remains of the cable car in a clearing of a thick patch of pine trees near the summit of the Mottarone peak overlooking Lake Maggiore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country China 'quietly' invading...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/asia/beijings-new-power-play-involves-shocking-bhutan-land-grab/news-story/03fad943250e2a2421479f9a21a9c884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early April, the Chinese welcomed a delegation of international visitors to the city of Kunming in Yunnan province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The coming sexual counterrevolution...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/topic/sexual-counterrevolution-liberation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sexual revolution sought to ease the burden of shame and social constraint — especially for women. Yet if we listen to its inheritors,</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
