<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Outsider' Buttigieg plays skillful inside game, positioning himself for future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/outsider-buttigieg-plays-a-skillful-inside-game-positioning-himself-for-the-future/ar-AANjOcY?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biking with Republicans. Tacos with AOC. Buttigieg is deftly using the infrastructure talks to quietly build a network, potentially laying the groundwork for his political future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Inherited Deal Cut By My Predecessor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/i-inherited-a-deal-cut-by-my-predecessor-biden-issues-statement-on-afghanistan-as-taliban-control-spreads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden issued a statement on Sunday regarding the deteriorating situation in Afghanistan, reaffirming his administration’s plans and placing blame on the plan he “inherited from [his] predecessor,” former President Donald Trump, and the inability of the Afghan military to hold their own country. Biden began the statement by describing how he and his […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN'S SPOILS OF WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9894251/Rampant-Taliban-ransack-palatial-home-Afghan-warlord-ally-General-Dostum.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insurgents tightened their grip on Afghanistan on Saturday by capturing Mazar-e-Sharif - a large, heavily defended city in the north of the country - in a major setback for the government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why conservatives depend on memes...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/08/why-the-left-cant-meme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Woke comedy' will never compete with the despair of the online Right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From hubris to humiliation:  America's warrior class contends with abject failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/from-hubris-to-humiliation-america-e2-80-99s-warrior-class-contends-with-the-abject-failure-of-its-afghanistan-project/ar-AANk1Z0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington’s policymakers reflect on the Afghan collapse after two decades of hollow nation-building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Daily Death Toll Nearly Doubles in Two Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-daily-death-toll-from-covid-19-almost-doubles-in-two-weeks/ar-AAMrNBT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news and guidance on the state of the COVID-19 pandemic across New England and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mounting lawsuits, federal government challenge DeSantis, Abbott bans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mounting-lawsuits-federal-government-challenge-desantis-abbott-bans-on-mask-mandates/ar-AANkmA5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican governors have argued it should be up to individuals to decide if they want to wear masks, which protect others against the spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled Newsom warns Dems to wake up!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/embattled-california-gov-newsom-facing-recall-election-says-it-s-time-for-democrats-to-wake-up/ar-AANk2mt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Republicans motivated, Newsom says the threat of the recall is real unless Democrats start to take the election seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Seniors Hospitalized With Covid as Much as in January...</title>
      <link>https://www.luxtimes.lu/en/world/pandemic-florida-seniors-hospitalised-with-covid-as-much-as-in-january-6117eed4de135b9236a47575</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.luxtimes.lu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vast majority of those hospitalised are unvaccinated, hospital chiefs say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel recalls envoy as Poland adopts law on WWII claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/8/14/israel-furious-as-poland-signs-law-to-limit-property-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel recalls its top diplomat to Poland after president approves bill curbing World War II-era restitution claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO 'RESPECT':  Critics Call Out Clichés in Aretha Franklin Biopic...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/08/13/respect-reviews-critics-weigh-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many critics are praising Jennifer Hudson's performance in Aretha Franklin biopic 'Respect,' but others are questioning the storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ORDERS 5,000 TROOPS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-increases-us-deployment-afghanistan-200126823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Saturday doubled down on his decision to withdraw US forces from Afghanistan despite the Taliban's rapid advances, but pledged to send more troops to evacuate civilians and warned the insurgents not to threaten that mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion, disappointment and anger...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/many-u-veterans-fall-afghanistan-110008966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retreat of U.S. troops and advance of the Taliban leave veterans of the Afghanistan war conflicted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3CsZfNKbjGc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Behold Barack Antoinette...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/14/opinion/barack-obama-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He hated politics. But he loves post-politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ORDERS 1,000 TROOPS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-joe-biden-middle-east-evacuations-kabul-8ec855b3f943dafe80d3d3ca6b0953f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden authorized on Saturday an additional 1,000 U.S. troops for deployment to Afghanistan, raising to roughly 5,000 the number of U.S. troops to ensure what Biden called an “orderly and safe drawdown” of American and allied personnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain flirts with record heat; 16 Italy cities on red alert...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-science-health-environment-and-nature-heat-waves-645440b90a8cfb48f9e728b28fe7408b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain endured its hottest day of the year Saturday, with temperatures topping 46 degrees Celsius (115 F), while authorities in Italy expanded the number of cities on red alert for health risks to 16 as a heat wave engulfed Southern Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tap Dancing With Trump: Lindsey Graham Quest for Relevance...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/tap-dancing-with-trump-lindsey-grahams-quest-for-relevance-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindsey Graham’s moment, it seemed, came on the evening of Jan. 6. With crews still cleaning up the blood and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France sees fifth weekend of protests against Macron health pass...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210814-france-sees-fifth-weekend-of-protests-against-macron-covid-pass</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France sees fifth weekend of protests against Macron Covid pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YALE researchers say social media outrage machine has biggest influence on moderate groups...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90665826/yale-researchers-say-social-medias-outrage-machine-has-the-biggest-influence-on-moderate-groups</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tracking Twitter users over time, researchers found that those who racked up engagement after showing moral outrage were more likely to keep doing so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/fred-could-become-tropical-storm-as-it-aims-for-florida/999250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Rainstorm Fred threatens to restrengthen while bringing a wide variety of impacts to portions of Florida through the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Storm Intensifies; May Follow Similar Path...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2021-08-14-tropical-storm-grace-forms-south-florida-in-the-cone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Grace will soon bring gusty winds and heavy rain to the islands of the Caribbean. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As America exits, history repeats self...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/567790-as-america-exits-history-repeats-itself-in-afghanistan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With so much going wrong in Afghanistan, now is hardly the time to be in any way optimistic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Wall St Most Bullish on Stocks in Two Decades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wall-street-most-bullish-stocks-121500623.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s been two decades since Wall Street analysts were this upbeat.About 56% of all recommendations on S&amp;P 500 firms are listed as buys, the most since 2002. It’s one more data point that shows the extent of the euphoria sweeping markets after a blockbuster earnings season.While analysts are historically a bullish bunch, they’re turning even more optimistic in the face of relentless stock-market gains and corporate earnings that topped even the highest expectations. For all the con</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militant Sweep Follows Years of Miscalculations...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/taliban-sweep-in-afghanistan-follows-years-of-u-s-miscalculations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden’s top advisers concede they were stunned by the rapid collapse of the Afghan army in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus claims more young as deaths climb yet again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-5e56dc3f817e3eaca1f48511c3be8549</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A young mother had just celebrated her first wedding anniversary and was one of six members of a Jacksonville church to die over a 10-day span. Another Florida woman had just given birth to her first child, but was only able to hold the newborn girl for a few moments before dying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE MARINES ARRIVE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/rush-troops-kabul-tests-bidens-withdrawal-deadline-79455160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fresh contingent of Marines have arrived in Kabul as part of a 3,000-troop force intended to secure an airlift of U.S. Embassy personnel and Afghan allies as Taliban insurgents approach the outskirts of the capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-death Experiences Can Scar Animals for Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/08/wild-animals-ptsd/619736/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans may not be the only creatures who get PTSD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin alarmed over 'unprecedented' natural disasters in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/08/14/putin-alarmed-over-unprecedented-natural-disasters-in-russia-a74788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin on Saturday said the scale of natural disasters that have hit Russia this year has been "absolutely unprecedented".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney lockdown fines increased to $3,700, stay-at-home extended...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/567857-sydney-lockdown-fines-increased-to-3700-stay-at-home-extended</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Sydney and its home state of New South Wales will now face fines of up to $3,700 for violating coronavirus stay-at-home orders, which were extended Saturday following a record number of daily COVID-19 i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapon seizures 'massive boon' as cities fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210814-weapon-seizures-massive-boon-for-taliban-as-cities-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weapon seizures 'massive boon' for Taliban as cities fall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Wall St Most Bullish on Stocks in Two Decades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wall-street-most-bullish-stocks-121500623.html#:~:text=(Bloomberg)%20%2D%2D%20It's%20been%20two,buys%2C%20the%20most%20since%202002.</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s been two decades since Wall Street analysts were this upbeat.About 56% of all recommendations on S&amp;P 500 firms are listed as buys, the most since 2002. It’s one more data point that shows the extent of the euphoria sweeping markets after a blockbuster earnings season.While analysts are historically a bullish bunch, they’re turning even more optimistic in the face of relentless stock-market gains and corporate earnings that topped even the highest expectations. For all the con</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Behold Barack Antoinette...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/behold-barack-antoinette/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Jay Gatsby gave big, lavish, new-money parties at his sprawling mansion on the water because he wanted to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska hit by 6.9 mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3473187/alaska-earthquake-news-magnitude-7/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge earthquake struck the Alaska peninsula on Saturday morning, the European-Mediterranean Seismological Centre (EMSC) reported. The quake registered a magnitude of 6.9 on the Richter scale and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens Cash in on NFT Art Boom...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/teens-cash-in-on-the-nft-art-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last fall, Randi Hipper decided to, as she put it recently, “go in-depth with the crypto space.” After hearing about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan president appeals for help as Taliban close in on capital...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/567855-afghanistan-president-appeals-for-help-as-taliban-close-in-on-capital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghan President Ashraf Ghani is calling on the international community to aid in the country’s fight against the Taliban, which has closed in on Kabul as fears grow that the capital could soon be overrun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN MARCH ON KABUL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-taliban-f600d6faf28e9c2ccb454ad176987b19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban seized two more provinces on Saturday and approached the outskirts of Afghanistan's capital while also launching a multi-pronged assault on a major northern city defended by former warlords, Afghan officials said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
