<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL WATCH GULF...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/121154.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAnon spreads across globe, shadowing COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/516102-qanon-spreads-across-globe-shadowing-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The QAnon movement is spreading around the world, turning an outlandish conspiracy theory revolving around President Trump into one of the nation’s most dangerous exports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran executes wrestler who Trump, others urged country to spare...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/516123-iran-executes-wrestler-who-trump-urged-country-to-spare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has reportedly executed a wrestler accused of murder after President Trump asked authorities to spare him from the death penalty, according to the country’s state TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY VALLEY  HEARTBREAK</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Half-a-million-Oregonians-more-than-10-percent-15559123.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAPPY VALLEY, Ore. - Wildfires across the West Coast have killed at least 19 people in California and have ravaged more than a million acres of land in Oregon, where dozens of people were missing and tens of thousands of residents evacuated their homes amid some of the most dangerous air conditions in the world.  Oregon officials said they believe the wildfires could have claimed numerous lives because of how many structures have burned, but they said a death toll is unclear as they began to survey the destruction. Fires continued to rip through more than 1,500 square miles in the state on Friday.  "We know we're dealing with fire-related death, and we're preparing for a mass fatality incident based on what we know and the number of structures that have been lost," said Andrew Phelps, director of Oregon's Office of Emergency Management. Phelps said he could not confirm how many deaths had occurred from the fires, but a state-run dashboard recorded at least five fatalities.  After days of high temperatures and dry winds, cooler weather on Friday allowed firefighters to begin to contain some of the 16 fires across the state. But they had barely begun to make headway when dense smoke limited firefighters' ability to fly, said Doug Grafe, chief of fire protection for the Oregon Department of Forestry. Eight of the 16 fires will be on the map until fall rains arrive, Grafe said.  A cluster of fires grew dramatically across a swath of 56 miles southeast of Portland, burning about 440,000 acres in an area of the state unaccustomed to wildfires of this magnitude, Grafe said. A blanket of smoke covered the sky even in downtown Portland, where officials opened up the Oregon Convention Center for evacuees.  "We have not seen the likes of this fire in this state, this integrated with our communities, ever before," Grafe said. "We...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mx_RZIPC3M0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani claims 'no reason to believe' his Ukraine contact is spy despite sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-giuliani-ukraine-russian-spy-trump-20200911-2xllriyagzgthpbje2hyopcunm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Americans commemorated the 19th anniversary of 9/11, NYC's former mayor talked about his active dislike for de Blasio and Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL WATCH MIAMI...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/112055.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump made promise to save coal in 2016. He couldn't keep it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/trump-made-a-promise-to-save-coal-in-2016-he-couldnt-keep-it/ar-BB18Gm7N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN to Televise 'Black National Anthem'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2020/09/10/espn-to-televise-protesting-players-and-singing-of-black-national-anthem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The players have said they will protest and, if they do, ESPN says they will televise it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE '75% CHANCE OF WINNING'...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-election-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest forecast of the 2020 presidential election between President Donald Trump and Joe Biden by Nate Silver’s FiveThirtyEight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of San Quentin inmate who contracted virus files wrongful death claim...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/family-san-quentin-inmate-contracted-032703943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family of San Quentin inmate dead after getting COVID-19 files death claim cites transfer of infected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising deaths and lost hope...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-staggering-fire-toll-record-110053322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With months of fire season ahead, blazes across California explode in size, taxing resources. Ten are reported dead in fire sweeping Butte and nearby counties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of structures destroyed in CA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/10-killed-californias-deadliest-blaze-184704800.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The North Complex fire near Oroville in Butte County is now blamed for 10 deaths, placing it among the deadliest wildfires in state history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials battle online misinformation along with wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d294693de30f859f6c028122fd99bf11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Emergency responders in the Pacific Northwest are fighting misinformation along with raging wildfires as people spread unsubstantiated social media posts blaming coordinated groups...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL players booed as racial justice stand sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/561c74297aef243e58ac573afe4d8e26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — The NFL’s new stance encouraging players to take a stand against racial injustice got its first test as some fans of the Super Bowl champion Kansas City Chiefs booed during...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OREGON SCORCHED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/429f97bdf66aaa28a4dd43879a412503</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — Hundreds of firefighters battled two large wildfires Friday that threatened to merge near the most populated part of Oregon, including the suburbs of Portland, and the governor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Sperm Donor. 36 Children. Mess of Lawsuits...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/09/sperm-donor-identity-mental-health/616081/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents thought Donor 9623 was a genius who spoke four languages, not a college dropout with a criminal record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie theaters rushed to reopen, but now no blockbusters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/11/coronavirus-movie-theaters-rushed-to-reopen-blockbusters-were-pushed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With "Wonder Woman 1984" pushed to winter, the next Hollywood blockbuster won't hit theaters until "Black Widow" arrives in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing 'I love you' from owner makes pups' heart rate skyrocket 46%...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/life/pets/article/Hearing-I-love-you-from-their-owner-makes-pups-15556764.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you ever wondered how strong your furry friends' love is for you, here's your answer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids dodge teachers with fake glitch...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/education/2020/09/10/detroit-problems-online-learning-remote-teaching/5756638002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online learning in schools has been marked by technical glitches and student pranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans furious Mueller team wiped phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/republicans-demand-answers-on-muellers-team-wiping-phones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressional Republicans demanded answers on Friday as to whether there “was a widespread intentional effort” to wipe the mobile devices of multiple people on former Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s team during the Russia probe, and suggested this could amount to "anticipatory obstruction of justice."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cougar inbreeding causing crooked tails, undescended testicles
...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8723383/Cougar-inbreeding-California-causing-undescended-testicals-crooked-tails.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cougars in Southern California are exhibiting kinked tails and undescended testes, signs of poor genetic diversity that could render them extinct within a few decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Busted For Throwing Party Admit To Having COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/miami-university-covid-positive-students-party-police-cam-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"How many other people have COVID?" The officer asked. "They all do," the student replied, gesturing toward his housemates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False rumors 'inundate' officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/blogs-trending-54121992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deluge of misinformation about fires in Oregon prompted local officials to debunk rumours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo wife assigned State Dept. tasks on private email...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article245664835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President will put down 'INSURRECTION' if declared winner and riots break out...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8723181/Donald-Trump-says-INSURRECTION-opponents-threaten-riots-election-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is vowing to 'put down' any 'riots' that occur among opposition 'within minutes' should he be declared the winner on Election night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor resigns from Russia probe amid concerns over Barr pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/news/connecticut/hc-news-john-durham-dannehy-resignation-20200911-20200911-xcsapnq7g5e63kvtw5aqi7cv34-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutor Nora Dannehy, a top aide to U.S. Attorney John H. Durham in his Russia investigation, has quietly resigned from the probe - at least partly out of concern that the investigative team is being pressed for political reasons to produce a report before its work is done, colleagues said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Reilly gets new radio show...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/11/bill-oreilly-gets-new-show-on-radio-station-owned-by-trump-ally.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News host Bill O'Reilly is getting a new show on a station that's owned by one of President Donald Trump's allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Nap Sued for Alleged Sex Assault in 80s...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/be-a-good-boy-lawsuit-graphically-accuses-fox-news-star-andrew-napolitano-of-sexual-assault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAUDI NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/trump-admin-optimistic-saudi-arabia-could-be-next-to-make-peace-with-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House senior adviser Jared Kushner hinted on Friday that Saudi Arabia could be the next Arab nation to reach a historic peace agreement with Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside OXFORD Saga: From Wild Hype to Sobering Reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/09/11/inside-oxford-coronavirus-vaccine-saga-412208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once hailed as the world’s best hope, the Oxford/AstraZeneca vaccine trial hits a bump in the road—and that might be good news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOTING FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2020/09/hundreds-fear-looting-try-to-push-through-oregon-wildfire-roadblocks-fire-official-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;300 people in Central Oregon tried to push through roadblocks Wednesday on highways near Sisters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top School District Running Empty Buses...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/fairfax-county-is-running-empty-school-buses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The way states, municipalities, and other public authorities are putting off the day of tightening up their budgets is a marvel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: CA Police Surrounded, Attacked After Responding To Violent Sideshow...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/09/11/sacramento-police-surrounded-violent-sideshow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hostile crowd can be seen throwing rocks and fireworks during the incident on August 30th.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Keeps Proving Deadly to Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/09/11/the-covid-19-pandemic-keeps-proving-deadly-to-liberty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the pandemic rages on, nominally free countries are sliding down a path blazed by authoritarian regimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Bahrain agrees to normalize relations with Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/trump-expected-to-announce-historic-bahrain-israel-normalization-agreement-641961</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu says the agreement marks a "new era of peace."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China wants TIKTOK closed rather than forced U.S. sale...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-china-bytedance-tiktok-exclusive/exclusive-china-would-rather-see-tiktok-u-s-close-than-a-forced-sale-idUKKBN2622L6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing opposes a forced sale of TikTok's U.S. operations by its Chinese owner ByteDance, and would prefer to see the short video app shut down in the United States, three people with direct knowledge of the matter said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter: My son smoked pot with Willie Nelson on White House roof...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/11/jimmy-carter-my-son-smoked-pot-with-willie-nelson-on-white-house-roof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Jimmy Carter admits in a new documentary that one of his sons smoked pot with Willie Nelson on the roof of the White House. Carter, 95, was asked about the legendary country croone…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towns emptied, confusion spreads...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/never-seen-anything-oregon-towns-154850982.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Molalla and other western towns, fear, uncertainty and disinformation gripped residents as hundreds of thousands in the state evacuate * US wildfires in the west – follow live updatesHundreds of thousands of people in Oregon were ordered to leave their homes on Thursday as wildfires encroached on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Stephen Hawking was wrong about A.I. killing humans [says robot]...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/stephen-hawking-was-wrong-about-ai-killing-humans-says-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A robot pens an article and declares that artificial intelligence is our friend. But of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIPPING:  Musk plans to send humans to Mars in next 48 months?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1456612/elon-musk-plans-for-mars-timeline-spacex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has a timeline of when he hopes to send humans to Mars. The ultimate goal is for his SpaceX company to put a person on the Red Planet by 2024 and build a self-sustaining city by 2050. Spa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France says crisis 'worsening'...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2020/09/11/france-set-to-announce-stricter-measures-to-combat-covid-19-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases are rising in France but the government has yet to severely limit movement or gatherings in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson airs more leaked tapes of Cohen's secret CNN conversations...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/What-s-up-with-Tucker-Carlson-s-leaked-tapes-of-15558076.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the last two weeks, viewers of Tucker Carlson's Fox News opinion show have been treated to what his news colleagues might consider a significant scoop: leaked audio recordings of CNN heavyweights, including anchor Chris Cuomo and President Jeff Zucker, speaking candidly with former Trump fixer Michael Cohen.  Cohen has said publicly that he does not know how the recordings made their way into Carlson's hands. On Twitter, he stated that the only people who possess the tapes beside himself are President Donald Trump, the Trump Organization and the Department of Justice, adding that "I did not give this recording or authorization for its use to @FoxNews or anyone." (A Fox News spokesperson said that the network does not reveal its sources.)  While the origin of the tapes is still shrouded in mystery, what's clear is that Carlson has relished the chance to use them to bash CNN over the head, part of a long-running - and seemly intensifying - war with the network that once employed him. And if it seems like a curious diversion for a political pundit during a busy election season, Carlson's CNN fixation broadly aligns with the Trump campaign's media-bashing strategy.  CNN has declined to comment on the content of the tape recordings. Network officials see the tapes as part of a concerted effort by Trump-boosting conservatives to attack critics of the president and have chosen not to engage with any of the drip-drip revelations. (Conservative consultant Arthur Schwartz, who has described himself as "basically a [expletive] troll on Twitter," has heavily promoted the leaks on social media.)  The release of the tapes seems timed to undermine the rollout of Cohen's tell-all book, "Disloyal," which has brought the onetime press antagonist to MSNBC and Don Lemon's CNN show for promotional interviews.  After teasing the tapes on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Michigan Hosting Racially Segregated Events...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2020/09/10/u-of-michigan-dearborn-hosts-racially-segregated-bipoc-and-non-poc-cafes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Michigan Dearborn hosted racially segregated events on Tuesday, one for "Non-POC," and the other for "BIPOC" (Black, Indigenous, and People Of Color) students. During the two racially segregated "cafes," the groups were encouraged to "discuss their experience as students on campus." The university now says that it "sincerely regrets" describing the cafes as "Non-POC" and "BIPOC" events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Riots Break Out in Bogotá After Police Kill Cab Driver Who Violated Quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2020/09/10/colombia-seven-dead-hundreds-injured-as-rioters-burn-dozens-of-police-stations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTÁ, Colombia — At least seven people have died and hundreds were injured during anti-police riots in the Colombian capital of Bogotá.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: America's spiritual exhaustion...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/936846/lol-nothing-matters-does</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On our collective exhaustion with the Trump era</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff's futuristic program to stop crime -- before it happens... </title>
      <link>https://projects.tampabay.com/projects/2020/investigations/police-pasco-sheriff-targeted/intelligence-led-policing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC To Fine Subway Passengers $50 for Bare Face...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/09/10/mta-face-covering-fine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting Monday, Sept. 14, riders who are not wearing a face covering can be hit with a $50 fine, CBS2's Marcia Kramer reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Sports Industry Favorability Tumbles...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/319256/farming-rises-sports-tumbles-industry-ratings.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public images of several U.S. business and industry sectors have shifted amid the pandemic and other key events of 2020. Positive ratings of healthcare and sports have changed the most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singing 'May Be Worst Thing You Can Do'... </title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/singing-easiest-way-spread-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study reveals loud and consonant-rich singing spreads aerosols and other droplets into the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems build big edge in early voting...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/10/democrats-early-voting-lead-412106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far more Democrats than Republicans are requesting mail ballots in key battleground states, including voters who didn't participate in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicides Among Kids, Young Adults Soaring...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/suicides-among-us-kids-young-adults-jumped-57-in-past-decade/ar-BB18ViMs?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts Blast NYC Restaurant As Dangerous...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/red-lights-flash-as-new-york-speeds-to-open-restaurants-for-indoor-dining-141308649.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON--Arthur Avenue in the Bronx is one of New York’s great culinary thoroughfares, long regarded as the city’s “true” Little Italy, both tastier and more authentic than its heavily touristed counterpart in Lower Manhattan. Like every other segment of New York’s restaurant industry, Arthur Avenue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLPHINS Won't Take Field For National Anthem...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/09/10/miami-dolphins-stay-inside-national-anthem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Miami Dolphins have announced players will not be on the field for the national anthem in Sunday's season opener.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASH:  NFL Ratings Drop Double Digits In Season Opener...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/nfl-ratings-down-season-kickoff-kansas-city-chiefs-coronavirus-houston-texans-nbc-1234575251/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the coronavirus pandemic still raging across America, this year’s NFL season opener was as different as night and day in many ways from the 100th season kickoff in 2019. For one thing, as reig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stadium Installing 'Disinfecting Doorways' To Clean Concertgoers...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/09/11/seatgeek-stadium-installing-new-disinfecting-doorways-for-concert-crowds-could-top-5500-fans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS 2’s Lauren Victory looks at the high-tech devices at the doors of SeatGeek Stadium that are supposed to help keep you COVID-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Watching TV While Eating Prevents From Realizing Full...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/snack-caution-watching-tv-prevents-realizing-when-full/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activities which require lots of attention trick many participants into overeating, even if they were somewhat full beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals, nursing homes fail to separate patients, putting others at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.modernhealthcare.com/safety-quality/hospitals-nursing-homes-fail-separate-covid-patients-putting-others-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modernhealthcare.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Brady vs. Brees -- QB matchup for the ageless...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29836388/battle-goats-why-tom-brady-drew-brees-matchup-seen-before</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their rivalry has spanned four decades. Now they'll make history in the first matchup of starting QBs over 40. How did they get here, and what's in store?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lachlan Murdoch: FOXNEWS will continue growth whether Biden or Trump win...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/515996-lachlan-murdoch-fox-news-will-continue-growth-whether-biden-or-trump-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lachlan Murdoch says Fox News Media will continue to grow regardless of who wins the next presidential election between President Trump and Democratic nominee Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Pence together at NYC 9/11 ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/515998-biden-pence-cross-paths-at-nyc-9-11-ceremony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden and Vice President Mike Pence exchanged pleasantries on Friday in a rare face-to-face meeting when both men attended a ceremony to honor the lives lost in the September 11, 2001, terrorist attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems' Weird Obsession With Scapegoating Susan Sarandon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/democrats-weird-obsession-with-scapegoating-susan-sarandon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar-winning actress and leftist has come under fire from centrist Democrats—including Soledad O’Brien—for not kissing the ring of Joe Biden. Why the outrage?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Brady vs. Brees -- QB matchup for the ageless...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/sports/bucs/2020/09/11/tom-brady-vs-drew-brees-a-quarterback-matchup-for-the-ageless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bucs and Saints' future Hall of Famers will become the first over-40 quarterbacks to meet in an NFL game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no contact and substantial space, Getaway's tiny houses were ahead of their time...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/travel/article/With-no-contact-and-substantial-space-Getaway-s-15559310.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Getaway, the tiny houses are separated by at least six times the recommended amount of social distancing space. Check-in is contactless, and all communication with the staff is conducted by text or phone. There are no communal facilities, and the amenities are within maskless reach. I could satisfy my hankering for, say, s'mores and "Walden" by the fire without leaving my protective bubble. Most important, I would be exposed to more spiders than people - an advantage during a pandemic.  "Getaway is naturally about socially distancing," said Jon Staff, who founded the company with his Harvard pal, Pete Davis. "No part of the business was about hanging out with other people."  The mod cabins are built for our current reality, even though they date from a simpler time: 2015. Staff and Davis, who has since left the company, created the retreat for overworked urbanites tethered to technology. Turns out the pro-nature, anti-social model is a perfect fit for a global health crisis, too.  While hotels struggle to recover - occupancy rates are still under 50% - Getaway is thriving. The company, which operates the cabins at 12 locations in nine states, reported a 99% occupancy rate in July and August and a 260% spike in bookings from May through July. Most of the outposts are more than 90% full through October; the Shenandoah Valley property, where I recently stayed, is at 99.8%.  The Getaway colonies are no more than a two-hour drive from such major urban centers as D.C., New York, Dallas and Los Angeles - a common round-trip commute for many city folk. Each property contains about 30 to 50 structures on double-digit acres of sylvan land. The company plans to open No. 13, in New York's Adirondacks, by the end of this year as well as expand some outposts. For example, the Virginia property will unveil nine two-person cabins...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
