<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Major League Baseball tix going biometric...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90201535/major-league-baseball-tickets-are-going-biometric-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pilot program will bring biometrics to select stadiums later this season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHERIFF JOE TARGETED...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/07/12/exclusive-sheriff-joe-sacha-baron-cohen-duped-me-posing-finnish-comedian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking in a Breitbart News interview, Joe Arpaio, the former Sheriff of Maricopa County, Arizona, detailed allegedly being duped into an interview with Sacha Baron Cohen, who Arpaio says posed as a famous comedian from Finland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama loses 2,346,119 fake TWITTER followers so far...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/obama-loses-2-million-followers-in-twitters-crackdown-on-fake-accounts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter’s purge of locked accounts hits the ex-president’s social media hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Havilland's 'FEUD' Petition Denied By CA Top Court; SCOTUS Next?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/olivia-de-havilland-feud-california-supreme-court-petition-denied-1202425561/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Nine days after Olivia de Havilland turned 102, the California Supreme Court has rejected the two-time Oscar winner’s desire to have them review her feud with FX Networks and Ryan Murphy…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend of reporters leaking to FBI...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/12/journalists-source-fbi-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I shared a copy of the dossier'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM SEN: 'WILD-EYED' RACE TO LEFT DANGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2018-07-12/sen-chris-coons-democrats-need-to-abandon-wild-eyed-race-to-left</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ghost' particle found mile beneath Antarctica...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/07/12/let-light-ghost-particle-found-mile-beneath-antarctica-holds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secrets of the origins of light are set to be unlocked by the discovery of an elusive &amp;ldquo;ghost&amp;rdquo; particle a mile beneath Antarctica, scientists have announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Destroyed Proof of Life On Mars?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/science/space/news/2018-07-12-mars-proof-of-life-organic-material-curiosity-rover-nasa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evidence of life on Mars possibly burned up by NASA decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping man shocked as BOA CONSTRICTOR falls from ceiling in New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Snake-Boa-Constrictor-Falls-Ceiling-Sleeping-New-York-Man--487975391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A central New York man got a rude awakening when a large snake fell from his bedroom ceiling and landed on him while he slept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear as social giant labels Russians as 'interested in treason'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jul/11/facebook-labels-russian-users-as-interested-in-treason</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firm removes category, which affected 65,000 people, from ad tools, following safety fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moviegoer stabbed during fight over seat at 'PURGE' screening...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/patron-stabbed-at-purge-screening-194065</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 11--As patrons awaited the start of the latest blood-soaked “Purge” movie, a dispute over a reserved seat ended with a Texas man plunging a knife six inches into the abdomen of a fellow moviegoe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ted Koppel Was Duped...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-sacha-baron-cohen-duped-ted-koppel-his-showtime-show-1126560</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran broadcaster, who was tricked into an interview (but didn't sign a release), explains how it happened to him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ APPEALS AT&amp;TTIMEWARNER MERGER</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/justice-department-will-appeal-time-warner-att-merger-approval-dow-j.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man injured in 'knife attack' by multiple people' on busy NYC street...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5947839/Man-reportedly-stabbed-multiple-people-Manhattan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was injured in broad daylight on a busy street in Greenwich Village on Thursday. A 911 caller told police that several people were involved in the 1.30pm stabbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROY MOORE:  EMBARRASSED AND HUMILIATED...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/jul/12/sacha-baron-cohen-sarah-palin-who-is-america-tv-show-veteran-response</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian responds on Twitter after the ex-Alaska governor called him ‘evil, exploitative and sick’ for duping her for his new show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIZZA HUT Expands Beer Delivery...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/05/08/pizza-hut-expands-beer-delivery-experiment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest attempt at flying car...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-44805697</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A previously unknown Northern California company says it has made a flying car just about anyone can pilot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad tried to revive baby by shocking with extension cord...</title>
      <link>http://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2018/jul/11/van-buren-man-charged-in-infant-s-death-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arkansasonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 19-year-old man is scheduled to go before a Crawford County circuit judge today, charged with smothering his infant daughter then trying to revive her by shocking her with a live extension cord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing shortage warning of price bubble?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/the-housing-shortage-may-be-turning-warning-of-a-price-bubble.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supply of homes for sale in the second quarter of 2018, the all-important spring market, rose at three times the rate of the same period last year, according to Trulia, a real estate listing and research company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burglar Breaks Into 'Escape Room'; Calls 911 When Can't Escape...</title>
      <link>http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/burglar-escape-room-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say a burglar in Washington state got more than he bargained for when he broke into an "escape room" and (ironically) couldn't escape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Budget Deficit Narrowed to $74.86 Billion in June...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-budget-deficit-narrowed-to-74-86-billion-in-june-1531418402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government’s budget deficit narrowed in June compared with a year earlier. Spending and revenue collection both fell, including a large drop for corporate-tax receipts in the wake of federal tax cuts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARACTER REBUTS PALIN...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/sarah-palin-sacha-baron-cohen-showtime-series-1202425392/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen isn’t done with former Alaska governor and vice presidential candidate Sarah Palin. Billy Wayne Ruddick, Jr, PhD, his character from the new Showtime series, Who Is America?…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX SCORES MOST EMMY NOMINATIONS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/12/netflix-vs-hbo-emmy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix just toppled HBO from its Emmy nomination throne. For the first time ever, the streaming service garnered more Emmy…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  People Dumber During Heat Wave...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/07/12/heat-waves-brains-slower-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at Harvard University have discovered that a person's brain works 13 percent slower when it has to operate in extreme heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen Purchases $6.7 Million NYC Apt...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-purchases-new-york-city-apartment-for-6-7-million-1531410460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s former personal lawyer financed the purchase with a mortgage from the developers, according to public records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient 'Iceman' shows signs of well-balanced last meal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/41791b87470743128bebe778f45d9c0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Talk about a paleo diet. Scientists have uncovered the last meal of a frozen hunter who died 5,300 years ago in the Alps.        The stomach contents of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSTLE owner wins GAWKER auction for $1.35 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/bustle-owner-goldberg-wins-auction-gawker-com-1-170720649--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - U.S. entrepreneur Bryan Goldberg, the owner of websites Bustle, Elite Daily and The Zoe Report, has prevailed in the bankruptcy auction for Gawker.com with a $1.35 million bid, people familiar with the matter said on Thursday. The sources asked not to be identified ahead of an official announcement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First legal sportsbook opening on NFL stadium grounds...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/chalk/story/_/id/24077347/fanduel-open-sportsbook-meadowlands-racetrack-new-jersey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FanDuel announced it will open a 5,300-square-foot sportsbook Saturday at the Meadowlands Racetrack in New Jersey, on the same property as the stadium where the New York Giants and Jets play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGES DROPPED</title>
      <link>http://www.wrdw.com/content/news/Lawyer-Stormy-Daniels-arrested-at-Ohio-strip-club-487999521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wrdw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porn actress Stormy Daniels was arrested at an Ohio strip club and accused of letting patrons touch her in violation of a state law, and her attorney said Thursday she was set up in a sting operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGES DROPPED</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/MichaelAvenatti/status/1017450331297533952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I am pleased to report that the charges against my client @stormydaniels have been dismissed in their entirety (below motion was just granted). I want to thank Joe Gibson &amp;amp; his colleagues at the prosecutors ofc for their professionalism starting with our first call early this am.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORN STAR ARREST PART OF LARGER TRAFFICKING INVESTIGATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.lancastereaglegazette.com/story/news/crime/2018/07/12/stormy-daniels-arrested-ohio-strip-club-pickerington-woman/779011002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lancastereaglegazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brittany Walters, of Pickerington, was one of three charged with illegal sexually oriented activity in a sexually oriented business by Columbus Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Releases Letter From Kim...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/12/kim-jong-un-letter-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort moved to Alexandria jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/12/paul-manafort-alexandria-jail-715378</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online records from the Northern Neck jail show Manafort was checked out of that detention center at 12:32 A.M. Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX SCORES MOST...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/awards/game-of-thrones-saturday-night-live-westworld-emmy-nominees-1202871447/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a year off, “Game of Thrones” has returned to Primetime Emmy Award contention in a big way. The fantasy epic drew 22 nominations Thursday, the most for any series — edging out NBC…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-TV Shows Sweep Competition... </title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/07/12/emmy-nominations-this-is-us-blackish-only-network-nominees-cbss-showtime-blanked-non-tv-shows-sweep-competition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once there was a time when people in the TV business complained that HBO and Showtime were taking the Emmys away from network TV. Now the Emmys belong to shows that aren’t even on TV or cable…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tense Hill Hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/strzoks-house-judiciary-hearing-plunges-into-absolute-chaos-as-lawmakers-exchange-heated-barbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok Swears:  My work never tainted by political bias...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fbi-agent-never-tainted-political-bias-080213902--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An FBI agent whose anti-Trump text messages fueled suspicions of partisan bias told lawmakers Thursday that his work has never been tainted by politics and that the intense scrutiny he is facing represents "just another victory notch in Putin's belt."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't kiss the queen!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/royal-etiquette-trumps-visit-dont-kiss-queen-151224009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — President Donald Trump is coming to Britain fresh from a confrontational NATO summit that featured stinging criticism of America's closest allies, but he's likely to tone down that stance when he takes tea Friday with Britain's Queen Elizabeth II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STORMS LONDON...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6760773/donald-trump-slams-theresa-mays-chequers-plan-for-brexit-saying-i-dont-know-if-thats-what-they-voted-for/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has landed in Britain for his first official visit – and declared that the people of the UK “like me a lot”. The President arrived at Stansted Airport near London on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMMY Nominations: The List...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2018-emmy-nominations-live-updating-1110785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The Handmaid's Tale's' Samira Wiley and 'New Amsterdam's' Ryan Eggold are set to make the announcement starting at 8:25 a.m. PT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems struggle with unity... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/396589-dems-struggle-with-unity-amid-leadership-tensions </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are struggling to show a united front as the shocking ouster of their Caucus chairman rekindles tensions about the future of the party — and who is best suited to lead it into the crucial 2020 cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL FOR MUSK...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2018-07-12/how-tesla-s-model-3-became-elon-musk-s-version-of-hell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can he deliver?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ocasio-Cortez drama; Accuses rival of pushing 3rd party...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/speedreads/784415/alexandria-ocasiocortez-accuses-defeated-democratic-primary-opponent-stubbornly-running-thirdparty-challenge-against</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Joseph Crowley (D-N.Y.) was stunningly defeated in last month's Democratic primary in New York by progressive phenom Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez. At the time, he put on a good face, even playing "Born to Run" for her after she'd sealed the spot. But things might not be so friendly beyond the Bruce Springsteen covers, and now Ocasio-Cortez is accusing Crowley of mounting a third-party challenge against her: .@repjoecrowley stated on live TV that he would absolutely support my candidacy.Instead, he’s stood me up for all 3 scheduled concession calls.Now, he’s mounting a 3rd party challenge against me and the Democratic Party- and against the will of @NYWFP.https://t.co/Xvb6Jk8N8q — Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (@Ocasio2018) July 12, 2018 New York has a quirky third-party system, which can allow unsuccessful major party candidates like Crowley to be the nominee for a smaller party and therefore still appear on the general election ballot. This was most recently highlighted by Ocasio-Cortez winning a district she didn't even run in as a write-in for the Reform Party. Likewise, Crowley won the Working Families Party line in New York's 14th District, where he lost the Democratic nomination to Ocasio-Cortez. It had been expected that Crowley would vacate the spot and support his fellow Democrat in the race: Bill Lipton, state director of the Working Families Party, said he immediately reached out to Mr. Crowley's campaign to request that he vacate the line. To Mr. Lipton's chagrin, his campaign declined; Mr. Crowley will remain on the ballot in November. "You'd think that given the moment we're in," said Mr. Lipton, "that Democratic leaders would want to help progressive forces to unite." [The New York Times] Crowley's campaign sidestepped a question about why they are remaining on the ballot. "Joe Crowley is a Democrat," a spokeswoman told the Times. "He's made clear he is not running for Congress and supports the Democratic nominee in NY-14." Update 9:51: Crowley responded to Ocasio-Cortez's accusation on Twitter, writing: "Alexandria, the race is over and Democrats need to come together. I've made my support for you clear and the fact that I'm not running. We've scheduled phone calls and your team has not followed through. I'd like to connect but I'm not willing to air grievances on Twitter." Jeva Lange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY DROIDS:  Sex robot makers blasted over sick 'family friendly' love doll designs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6760656/sex-robots-family-friendly-dolls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SEX robot with a “family mode” that dials down her dirty talk has been blasted as “profoundly damaging” for kids by academics. The controversial droid named Samantha went …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The World Needs More Cowboys' slogan for University of Wyoming called SEXIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article214680825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Wyoming is drawing criticism after school staff thought the new $500,000 UW slogan — "The World Needs More Cowboys" — was sexist. Women and Twitter users are defending the college and say the word "cowboy" is inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump as popular as Obama in middle of first term...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article214749845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A poll from Pew Research Center found 44 percent of people say Obama has done the best or second best job, with Clinton in second with 33 percent and Reagan third with 32 percent. Trump, at 19 percent, matches Obama in middle of first term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scuba diver finds iPhone lost at sea -- after text lights it up...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/scuba-diver-finds-iphone-lost-12898742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incredibly the device still had more than 80% of its charge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University moving desecrated US flag to art museum...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Kansas has moved a paint-spattered American flag from a prominent flagpole to a publicly-funded art museum on the same campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Could Dems Nominate Maxine Waters for President?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailynews.com/2018/07/11/could-democrats-nominate-maxine-waters-for-president-answer-yes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the Democratic side of the aisle, I challenge you to find a politician or media personality who has better expressed the anger, frustration and rage of the “Resistance” better than Maxine Waters…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posed as Trump Voter with 'Bullet' Necklace and 'INFOWARS' Stickers...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/07/12/exclusive-sacha-baron-cohen-posed-as-disabled-veteran-trump-voter-with-bullet-necklace-and-infowars-stickers-in-palin-prank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen "pretended to be a disabled veteran from Kentucky" in a disguise "meant to mock Trump voters by making them seem ignorant and offensive," a source close to Palin told Breitbart News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Peter Strzok Breaks Silence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5cd36c766cf14f548bdaf050d1393d98/FBI-agent:-My-work-has-never-been-tainted-by-political-bias</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An FBI agent whose anti-Trump text messages fueled suspicions of partisan bias will tell lawmakers Thursday that his work has never been tainted by politics and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complications and controversy of Nick Loeb's pro-life 'ROE v. WADE' movie...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/movies/ny-ent-nick-loeb-roe-v-wade-20180710-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Loeb’s polarizing, pro-life “Roe v. Wade” movie faced an onslaught of challenges practically from the get-go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Joy Reid ratings drop 20% after blog hacking controversy?</title>
      <link>http://contemptor.com/2018/07/11/msnbcs-am-joy-has-lost-over-20-percent-of-its-audience-following-blog-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;contemptor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been almost three months since a slew of homophobic and culturally insensitive posts from MSNBC host Joy Reid's old blog were unearthed, resulting in a lengthy controversy that embroiled the Re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'exotic' tick clones self; 'Aggressive biter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article214748110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A species of East Asian tick has found its way to N.C. The U.S. Department of Agriculture reports it found the Longhorned tick on an opossum in Polk County and fears the bug will spread quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaginal Rejuvenation  Latest Cosmetic Trend to Hit Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/vaginal-rejuvenation-is-latest-cosmetic-trend-hit-hollywood-1126442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data is in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump arrives in 'hot spot' Britain, questioning May's Brexit plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-arrives-hot-spot-britain-questioning-mays-brexit-130316893--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump arrived in "hot spot" Britain on Thursday after casting doubt on Prime Minister Theresa May's plans for leaving the European Union and with protests planned across the country where he says the people like him a lot. After a NATO summit where he provoked a crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever color X-ray on human...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/first-ever-colour-x-ray-human-005837590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand scientists have performed the first-ever 3-D, colour X-ray on a human, using a technique that promises to improve the field of medical diagnostics, said Europe's CERN physics lab which contributed imaging technology. The new device, based on the traditional black-and-white X-ray, incorporates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans are starving, but the country still sends crude to Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article214635335.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan oil production is dropping rapidly and the government has no money to buy food, medicines or consumer goods, but there's one item the socialist regime of Nicolas Maduro does not appear willing to sacrifice at all: oil subsidies to Cuba</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN LOBBIES FACEBOOK TO SHUT DOWN ALEX JONES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/cnn-lobbies-facebook-to-shut-down-infowars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media giant admits it down ranks Infowars content</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/economy/jobless-claims-plunge-to-214-000-lowest-since-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New applications for unemployment insurance benefits dropped 18,000 to 214,000 in the first week of July, the Department of Labor reported Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Lopez uses water bottle to pretend to urinate on Trump's star in Hollywood...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/07/12/george-lopez-uses-water-bottle-to-pretend-to-urinate-on-trumps-star-in-hollywood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian George Lopez was recently seen in a TMZ video emptying a small water bottle onto President Donald Trump’s star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame, acting as though he was urinating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FONDLED UNDERCOVER OFFICERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.10tv.com/article/police-stormy-daniels-grabbed-backside-undercover-columbus-officer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adult film actress Stormy Daniels was arrested in Columbus, Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Tebow get called to Majors?</title>
      <link>https://www.app.com/story/sports/baseball/2018/07/11/improving-tim-tebow-its-now-never/764001002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.app.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Tebow's recent play has opened many eyes as the 30-year-old could see a call-up this season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trash piles up in USA as China closes door to recycling...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/trash-piles-us-china-closes-door-recycling-doc-17h4mx1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto raises $10.4M, keeping flush his bid to upset Cruz...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/orourke-raises-10-4m-keeping-flush-bid-upset-024154414--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Democratic U.S. Rep. Beto O'Rourke says he raised more than $10.4 million over the past three months, putting him on track to again outpace U.S. Sen. Ted Cruz, whom he's trying to upset in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masquerade As Vet Felony?</title>
      <link>http://www.kxl.com/listen-karen-straughan-was-sacha-baron-cohens-masquerade-as-a-vet-funny-or-a-felony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen, the comedian and actor known for “Borat” and other roles in Hollywood …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The online battle for truth...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/online-battle-truth-doc-17h6381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World oil supply risks being 'stretched to limit'...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180712-world-oil-supply-risks-being-stretched-limit-iea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riding migration backlash, Sweden's political pariah looks to end isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sweden-election-swedendemocrats-newsm/riding-migration-backlash-swedens-political-pariah-looks-to-end-isolation-idUSKBN1K20HJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM/VISBY, Sweden - Once denounced as neo-fascists, Jimmie Akesson's Sweden Democrats look poised to translate more voter-friendly nationalist policies into big electoral gains in a country long famed for liberal tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF OF AMERICANS TRYING TO LOSE WEIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/12/nearly-half-of-americans-trying-to-lose-weight-cdc-data-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly Half of Americans Trying to Lose Weight, CDC Data Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Peter Strzok to Break Silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fbis-peter-strzok-to-break-his-silence-1531387800 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI agent censured for sending anti-Trump text messages while he helped lead investigations into Hillary Clinton and President Trump will break his public silence Thursday in testimony before Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO ALLIES AGREE TO INCREASE DEFENSE SPENDING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/trump-says-nato-allies-have-agreed-to-increase-their-defense-spending-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGED WITH SEX OFFENSES...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/stormy-daniels-arrested-strip-club-charged-sex-offenses-n890791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Michael Avenatti says the adult film star was arrested after a customer touched her in a non-sexual manner during a performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
RARELY ENFORCED LAW?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/07/12/columbus-has-rarely-used-2007-bill-that-protects-strippers-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was unclear early Thursday exactly what charges, if any, porn star Stormy Daniels may face following her arrest at an Ohio strip club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORMY DANIELS ARRESTED IN OHIO... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/stormy-daniels-arrested-in-columbus-ohio-while-performing-avenatti.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels, the porn star who has made headlines for an alleged affair with Donald Trump, was arrested in Columbus, Ohio, according to her attorney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPA JOHN'S chairman resigns after using racial slur...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/10/papa-johns-founder-john-schnatter-resigns-as-chairman-of-company-boar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Papa John's founder John Schnatter has resigned as chairman of his company's board after admitting and apologizing for using the N-word during a May conference call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADIO HOST DUPED...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/11/joe-walsh-sacha-baron-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former congressman and radio host claims Sacha Baron Cohen duped him with fake award ceremony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Thailand cave rescue to be turned into Hollywood movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/thailand-cave-rescue-turned-hollywood-movie-003908190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mission to rescue 12 boys and their soccer coach from a Thai cave is to get the Hollywood treatment in a movie announced by faith-based production house Pure Flix. Managing partner Michael Scott, who lives in Thailand and was at the rescue site in Chiang Rai as the boys were being pulled to safety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Battling Fake Accounts, TWITTER to Slash Millions of Followers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/11/technology/twitter-fake-followers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter will begin removing tens of millions of suspicious accounts from follower numbers, signaling a major new effort to fight fraud and restore trust on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW CBSSHOWTIME SERIES CREATES CHAOS...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/sarah-palin-dick-cheney-bernie-sanders-duped-sacha-baron-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin, who is enraged that Sacha Baron Cohen “duped” her on his new show, is apparently not the only politician who's fallen prey to the comedian's humor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SACHA BARON COHEN PROBES CHELSEA CLINTON'S 'SEX CHANGE' OPERATION!</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/11/sarah-palin-sacha-baron-cohen-interview-chelsea-clinton-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin recently revealed she was “duped” by actor Sacha Baron Cohen, who disguised himself as a disabled U.S. veteran to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEF OF IRRITATION</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/onpolitics/2018/07/11/john-kelly-upset-breakfast/777505002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of news outlets, including the Post, speculated that Kelly's body language was related to the remarks Trump was making at the time about Germany being "totally controlled by Russia."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great white shark makes U-turn off Carolinas coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/technology/article214731770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A great white shark made a sharp U-turn off the coast of the Carolinas and is headed south again in deeper water. OCEARCH researchers have seen this before, and think they might know why why sharks behave this way: They're pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh Spends Evening Feeding Homeless...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/11/kavanaugh-feeds-homeless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is really touching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED snubs mediation, sends anti-Trump dossier lawsuit to trial...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/11/buzzfeeds-ben-smith-mediation-snub-sends-dossier-l/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first face-to-face encounter between anti-Trump dossier publisher Ben Smith and one of its targets, Russian entrepreneur Aleksej Gubarev, was set to happen last month in a New York City law office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY, COMCAST Raise Stakes in Battle for FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/disneys-71-billion-bid-for-fox-is-now-worth-90-billion-1531316559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s official: The battle for 21st Century Fox assets moved across the Atlantic with dueling bids for satellite-TV provider Sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese urged to 'eat a bug, save a tree' as cicada threaten greenery...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2154855/chinese-citizens-urged-eat-bug-and-save-tree-summer-cicada-glut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An official is hoping to start a trend for chomping on chirpy insects in a bid to stop them devastating willow and cherry blossom trees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest Tools Outside Africa Found, Rewriting Human Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/07/news-china-human-tools-africa-shangchen-hominin-paleoanthropology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New evidence suggests that our ancient cousins left the continent much earlier than thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA-Bron: NBA Star In Talks to Star In Comedy...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/lebron-james-new-movie-body-swapping-comedy-1202863347/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James, scribe Steve Mallory, and James’ SpringHill Entertainment have sold an untitled comedy pitch to Paramount Players, with the NBA icon in early talks to star. SpringHill and Mallo…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
