<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma jail inmate shot, killed after hostage situation...</title>
      <link>https://www.oklahoman.com/story/news/2021/03/27/detention-officer-taken-hostage-at-oklahoma-county-jail/7032275002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oklahoman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A detention officer was taken hostage Saturday at the Oklahoma County jail, according to multiple reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK freezes Maduro's page for 'COVID misinformation'...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comaljazeera.com/news/2021/3/27/facebook-freezes-maduro-page-over-covid-misinformation-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comaljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58 minutes of terror: How the Boulder shooting unfolded...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2021/03/27/boulder-shooting-king-soopers-58-minutes-how-unfolded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In just under an hour, a gunman terrorized the large Boulder grocery store, killing 10 people and shattering both a tight-knit workplace and a larger community’s sense of security around an e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused gunman Ahmad Al Aliwi Alissa was 'laughing' during massacre...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/27/ahmad-al-aliwi-alissa-was-laughing-during-boulder-shooting-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The accused gunman in Monday’s mass shooting in Boulder was “laughing” as he murdered 10 people and terrorized shoppers inside a King Soopers grocery store, police and a witness said.  “We cou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccines haven't cured loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-new-york-coronavirus-pandemic-herkimer-medicaid-5e3ba59ec814a94b55cf86b56e84c54c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HERKIMER, N.Y. (AP) — Vaccines have begun saving lives in New York's nursing homes, but they haven't yet cured another crisis caused by the pandemic: loneliness. Persistently high rates of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago suburb began reparations with housing grants. Now national nonprofit wants to give cash payments to targeted residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/chicago-suburb-began-its-reparations-with-housing-grants-now-a-national-nonprofit-wants-to-give/article_72864758-b5a2-5b27-89dd-74314726e10e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — A national nonprofit is launching a cash payment pilot program for a small group of Evanston residents in an effort to show city leaders how a similar reparations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising case counts in young test vaccine strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/rising-covid-19-case-counts-in-the-young-test-us-vaccine-strategy/article_908a92b8-ff84-528b-9233-0daa2346e2a7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has spent months trying to vaccinate those most at-risk of severe illness from COVID-19, from health-care providers and the elderly, to essential workers and those with other underlying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birx shares chilling conclusion as America arrives at moment of introspection...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/27/politics/covid-war-deaths-preventable/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US may finally be getting a handle on the coronavirus pandemic, but for so many Americans, it's too late, and that disconnect is raising fresh questions about why the US couldn't have done more earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen Interview From CBS Will Debut on PARAMOUNT Plus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cbs-sunday-morning-special-the-woody-allen-interview-premieres-march-28-on-paramount-plus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special will feature interviews with Allen, Dylan Farrow, and an exploration of whether controversial acts diminish an artist's legacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of patients in intensive care in France rises again...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210327162423-4fwek</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE (URGENT):Number of COVID-19 patients in intensive care in France rises again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depression, tiredness, stress have led to less sex...</title>
      <link>https://extra.ie/2021/03/27/must-see/sex-survey-depression-tiredness-stress-ageing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;extra.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depression, tiredness and stress have led to fewer people having sex, a new survey has found. Around 12% of those surveyed by sexual wellness brand LELO have not had an intimate experience in over three years. The Sex Census put together by LELO found that although the pandemic has obviously hindered some people's sex lives, other factors have also come into play. However, 76.5% of people in couples reported not having more sex than usual despite spending lockdown with their partner back in April 2020. The most common factor that has stopped people from having sex is tiredness with 35.7%</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'COVID Shame' Keeping People From Telling Others When Infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-shame-reporting-infections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trust in government, or lack thereof, appears to be a key factor in deciding to keep a COVID diagnosis secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Just 8% Of Americans Fully Rested; Average Just 5 Hours!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-not-rested-after-night-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty-one percent agree that the vicious political and pandemic news cycles have caused them to lose sleep over the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Say Pandemic Stress Ruined Sex Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/2020-pandemic-stress-ruined-sex-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Be aware':  Pentagon target list for extremist infiltrators -- right and left...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/27/military-extremism-target-list-478200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An internal "training module" singles out a range of groups, ideologies and symbols seen as primary insider threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Weinstein accuser claims he told her to 'pretend he was Zac Efron' then bloodied his genitals...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/03/27/new-harvey-weinstein-accuser-says-she-bloodied-his-genitals-fighting-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman has stepped forward to accuse Harvey Weinstein of “attempted rape” inside a Beverly Hills hotel room — and claims she bloodied his genitals as she desperately fought him off, ac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities worldwide turn off lights to mark Earth Hour...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cities-worldwide-turn-off-lights-163708271.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cities around the world were turning off their lights Saturday for Earth Hour, with this year's event highlighting the link between the destruction of nature and increasing outbreaks of diseases like Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden betting on bigger government. Pandemic may be helping him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-is-betting-on-bigger-government-the-pandemic-may-be-helping-him/ar-BB1f1Npf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is adding to a massive expansion in government spending, hoping that public resistance to more spending has eased as the pandemic exposes untreated problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What curfew??</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9408611/Massive-crowds-continue-gather-Miami-despite-8pm-restrictions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worries about renewed Covid-19 outbreaks prompted Miami officials to enact a nighttime curfew following an infusion of rowdy 'spring breakers' that have frustrated locals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's Famous Evangelical Preacher, but His Kids Wish He'd Pipe Down...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/27/hes-a-famous-evangelical-preacher-but-his-kids-wish-hed-pipe-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rev. Rick Joyner is a famous evangelical leader who has called on Christians to arm themselves for an inevitable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZIL NIGHTMARE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brazil-rio-de-janeiro-jair-bolsonaro-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-63e897b16e4767d436916616796b6e60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Brazil currently accounts for one-quarter of the entire world’s daily COVID-19 deaths, far more than any other single nation, and health experts are warning that the nation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we heading for post-pandemic 'Roaring 2020s,' with parties and excess?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/are-we-heading-for-a-post-pandemic-e2-80-98roaring-2020s-e2-80-99-with-parties-and-excess/ar-BB1f1DWI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the celebrations begin, however, there probably will be some trepidation as people adjust to their newly restored freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuck ship blocking Suez budges for first time!</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/stuck-tanker-blocking-suez-canal-budges-for-the-first-time-663348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should the efforts fail, the US Navy is willing to send help if Cairo asks for it • each hour the Suez Canal does not operate costs $400 million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of animals stuck in hulls...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/middle-east/stuck-in-suez-canal-thousands-of-animals-packed-tight-in-ship-hulls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given the Europe-to-Saudi Arabia itinerary, they are most likely carrying sheep.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Tale of Love and Death Stands to Rouse House of GUCCI...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/a-dark-tale-of-love-and-death-stands-to-rouse-the-house-of-gucci/ar-BB1f18xb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gucci is all too familiar with falling in and out of love. The Italian label’s relationship with consumers has long traced the arc of wild infatuation followed by languishing interest, before a new creative mind rekindles the romance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY launches first 'vaccine passports'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/03/26/covid-vaccine-passports-new-york-first-vaccination-proof-system/6976009002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's new Excelsior Pass is part of a growing but disjointed effort to provide vaccine 'passports' or  certifications useful for safe gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two killed, eight injured in Virginia Beach shooting incidents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/27/us/virginia-beach-shootings/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people are dead and at least eight injured after shootings near the oceanfront in Virginia Beach, Virginia, police said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany warns third wave could be worst...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210326100438-5an3p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Germany warns third coronavirus wave could be the worst so far</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, With $400 Billion Iran Deal, Could Deepen Influence in Mideast...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/27/china-with-400-billion-iran-deal-could-deepen-influence-in-mideast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China agreed to invest $400 billion in Iran over 25 years in exchange for a steady supply of oil to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain gives 4-day week a try...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/madrid-coronavirus-pandemic-europe-spain-economy-fefbe45308a168ee0d072c6176a1cffc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — After years of waiting tables, Danae De Vries is one step closer to achieving her lifetime dream of becoming a theater coach. Ironically, she owes that to the pandemic. It was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 attend rock concert in Barcelona...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-health-coronavirus-pandemic-barcelona-music-75d9bc234b0a15735871a7cf0d28b25b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA, Spain (AP) — Five thousand music lovers are set to attend a rock concert in Barcelona on Saturday after passing a same-day COVID-19 screening, to test its effectiveness in preventing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suez Canal crisis deepens as hopes to free giant ship hinge on tide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/hopes-for-blocked-suez-canal-hinge-on-rising-tide-potentially-freeing-ship/ar-BB1f1Hrn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of ships trapped in a massive maritime traffic jam grew on Saturday as efforts to free the Ever Given continued for a fifth day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow tests 'unstoppable' nuke...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/brit-spy-plane-spots-vladimir-23799550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British spy plane has confirmed Russia has completed its initial test of Putin's new 'unstoppable' missile which experts believe is able to target US cities in the event of nuclear conflict.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
