<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>What's the Rush? Power of Slow Morning...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/whats-the-rush-the-power-of-a-slow-morning-11546958541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an antidote to our tech-obsessed society, slow-morning practitioners wake up early to meditate, read, exercise or do nothing at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Digisexuals' ditch dating; Turn to sex dolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7962025/sex-dolls-better-than-real-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUNGING on a sofa in a leather corset and holding a can of beer, Kristal is Nick’s perfect woman.   So she should be, as the truck driver forked out over £6,000 on the silicone sex doll, who…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC MAYOR GUARANTEES HEALTH CARE FOR ALL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/NYC-Health-Care-Guarantee-Mayor-de-Blasio-504046171.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will begin guaranteeing comprehensive health care to every single resident regardless of someone's ability to pay or immigration status, an unprecedented plan that will protect the more than half a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Death Rates 25-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64439-cancer-death-25-year-low.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. cancer death rates have declined continuously for the last quarter of a century, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharpshooting all-female squad hunts poachers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/the-brave-ones-zimbabwe-domestic-violence-survivors-trained-sharpshooters-hunt-poachers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abused and disadvantaged women have become Zimbabwe's hidden weapon against poachers who kill elephants and rhinos for their tusks and horns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students hate Trump's immigration quotes, don't realize they're Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;See their reactions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: GINSBURG MISSES SECOND DAY AT SUPREME COURT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/424287-ginsburg-misses-second-day-in-a-row-at-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was absent from the Supreme Court bench for the second day in a row on Tuesday.Chief Justice John Roberts noted Ginsburg’s absence when the justices took their seats for the second time in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery shrouds Manafort case...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/424281-mystery-shrouds-manafort-case-as-attorneys-appear-to-miss-key</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for President Trump’s former campaign chairman Paul Manafort appear to have missed a court-ordered deadline to reply to special counsel Robert Mueller’s accusations that Manafort breached a plea agreement by lying to federal pr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networks plan to carry rebuttal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/424290-networks-plan-to-carry-dem-response-to-trump-primetime-address</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most major broadcast networks indicated Tuesday they plan to carry the Democratic response to President Trump's primetime address from the Oval Office on the partial government shutdown and the situation at the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,500-a-month doggy daycare prompts growls in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jan/08/dog-daycare-san-francisco-doggy-style</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doggy Style, whose top-tier membership requires $7,500 fee, sparks backlash amid housing crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Confused' 86-year-old beat husband to death with cane...</title>
      <link>https://www.pnj.com/story/news/2019/01/07/police-86-year-old-florida-woman-beat-husband-death-walking-cane/2501771002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pnj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 86-year-old woman has been arrested on suspicion of murder for allegedly beating her 89-year-old husband to death with a walking cane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS OVAL OFFICE ADDRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cb9df4c458e647db9866ffa4c0db1fa2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump will argue to the nation Tuesday night that a "crisis" at the U.S.-Mexico border requires the long and invulnerable wall he's demanding before ending a partial government shutdown that has hundreds of thousands of federal workers fearing missed paychecks on Friday. Trump's first Oval Office speech will be followed by a Thursday visit to the southern border to highlight his demand for a barrier. White House press secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders tweeted that he will "meet with those on the front lines of the national security and humanitarian crisis."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron facing mountain of challenges in new year...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0984f26a923e445287cf59b64f9f43da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French President Emmanuel Macron is facing a mountain of challenges in the new year — starting with yellow vest protesters who are back in the streets to show their anger against high taxes and his pro-business policies that they see as favoring the wealthy rather than the working class. Once Europe's rising star, Macron is now fighting to save his image and his vision for transforming France's welfare state and economic model. Here's a look at three major issues he will need to tackle in 2019: YELLOW VEST CRISIS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Most Democrats identify as liberals for first time...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/424280-most-democrats-identify-as-liberals-for-first-time-gallup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Democrats now identify as liberal rather than moderate or conservative, a Gallup poll released Tuesday found, marking the first time since the polling giant began asking the question in the 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELTDOWN: Woman flips out at airport, calls JETBLUE worker 'rapist'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/08/woman-flips-out-at-airport-calls-jetblue-worker-a-rapist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This irate woman screamed until she was JetBlue in the face — but she still wasn’t allowed to board her flight. Viral video posted Monday on Instagram shows the unnamed passenger hurling insults an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Teacher Smears Feces On Tables, Grills At Principal's Party...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/01/07/florida-teacher-human-feces-principals-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida substitute teacher is accused of spreading human feces on tables and grills at a park where a principal was set to host a birthday party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone uncomfortable legal limbo persists...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-adviser-roger-stone-uncomfortable-legal-limbo-persists/story?id=60220161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the waning weeks of 2018, longtime GOP operative Roger Stone told reporters he believed he could be indicted and become the next target of Robert Mueller's probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS said to ask bankruptcy judge to liquidate... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sears-bankruptcy-liquidation-exclusiv/exclusive-sears-to-ask-bankruptcy-judge-to-liquidate-sources-idUSKCN1P218J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears Holdings Corp will ask a bankruptcy judge on Tuesday if it can proceed wit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.4 MAG QUAKE STRIKES OFF JAPAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-japan-earthquake-large-64-13828696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquake was 24 miles deep and centred 116km south southeast of Kagoshima in Japan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nude restaurant closes after 15 months due to lack of customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6568949/Pariss-NAKED-restaurant-closes-15-months-lack-customers.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'naturel, which opened in November 2017 with the promise of a discreet Parisien dining room where guests eat naked, will close in February this year after failing to attract customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family says US Navy veteran held for months in Iranian prison...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/424272-family-says-us-navy-veteran-has-been-held-for-months-in-iranian-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of a U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science races against tick-borne virus...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-01-science-tick-borne-virus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two groundbreaking discoveries by USC researchers could lead to medications and a vaccine to treat or prevent a hemorrhagic fever transmitted by a new tick species before it spreads across the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect, 20, held over massive politician data hack...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/suspect-20-held-over-massive-german-politician-data-084921899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police said Tuesday they have arrested a 20-year-old suspect in the case of private data stolen from hundreds of politicians, including Chancellor Angela Merkel, and published online. "The prosecutor's office in Frankfurt, the Central Office for Fighting Internet and Computer Crime and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warehouses Test New Breed of AI Robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/warehouses-test-a-new-breed-of-ai-robots-11546948800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Logistics providers and retailers are using mobile robots to cut down on the number of steps workers take, and deploying AI-aided mechanical arms for more nuanced tasks long deemed possible only for human hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HYUNDAI reveals WALKING car...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/hyundai-reveals-walking-car-concept-13827385</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hyundai believes the car could one day be used by first responders in response to natural disasters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Positive thinking key to healthy old age...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6565563/Is-key-happiness-married.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at University College London questioned more than 7,000 people aged 50 to 90 on how meaningful they felt their life was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Patriarch Warns 'Antichrist' Will Control Humans Through Gadgets...</title>
      <link>https://themoscowtimes.com/news/russian-patriarch-warns-antichrist-will-control-humans-through-gadgets-64060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview, Patriarch Kirill warned against “falling into slavery” to smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kevin Spacey went from megastar to pariah in just over year...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/01/07/how-kevin-spacey-went-from-megastar-to-pariah-in-just-over-a-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just four years ago, Kevin Spacey was standing onstage at the Golden Globes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right leader severely beaten in 'assassination attempt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8142936/german-far-right-leader-severely-injured-after-being-beaten-in-assassination-attempt/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FAR-right German politician has been brutally attacked in an “attempted assassination.” Frank Magnitz, chairman of Germany’s AfD party, was left with a gaping wound in his head after being knocke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't Afford to Lose...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-cant-afford-to-lose-11546909031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of defeat would be higher for President Trump than for Speaker Pelosi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown Weighs on Federal Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/shutdown-weighs-on-federal-workers-11546906831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many federal employees, the uncertainty and stress of the government shutdown is building into a sense of helplessness as they face the prospect of missing their first full paycheck on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMSUNG Echoes APPLE's Gloomy Outlook as Tech Woes Get Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/samsung-electronics-profit-outlook-surprisingly-weak-11546909783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samsung Electronics expects its fourth-quarter operating profit will decline 29%, surprise guidance that fell far below analysts’ estimates and the latest sign of challenges hitting the tech industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMERGENCY DECLARATION?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ap-explains-trump-emergency-build-wall-010333900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is weighing using a national emergency declaration to circumvent Congress and the budget stalemate and force construction of the president's long-promised southern border wall. "We're looking at a national emergency because we have a national emergency," President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some freshmen in Congress say no to their own paychecks...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Some-freshmen-say-no-paycheck-during-shutdown-13515386.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - For a few of the 93 freshman lawmakers sworn in last week, one of their first official acts in Congress was indefinitely delaying their paycheck. In keeping with previous government shutdowns, dozens of lawmakers are voluntarily refusing or donating their pay as long as any part of the federal bureaucracy remains shuttered - and new members are not being shy about joining in. For many, it is a gesture of solidarity with the hundreds of thousands of federal workers and contractors who will be going without their own paychecks until the partial shutdown is resolved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House, Dems even disagree on definition of 'negotiating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/shutdown-day-17-white-house-dems-disagree-definition-negotiating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House shifted into offense Monday in what likely will be a prolonged shutdown battle with congressional Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration case backlog keeps growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/immigration-case-backlog-keeps-growing-as-shutdown-drags-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration attorneys say the delay of court cases can cause financial strain on their clients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking at record low in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-smoking-reduction-benefits-20190107-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new analysis of health data from the 500 largest cities in the country shows that the people who live in neighborhoods with the highest smoking rates are more likely to be poor, less likely to be white, and more likely to have chronic heart or lung diseases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  DALLAS MORNING NEWS lays off dozens...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/the-dallas-morning-news/2019/01/07/dallas-morning-news-lays-43-company-struggles-revenue-declines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the newspaper industry struggles to stem declines in revenue, The Dallas Morning News on Monday laid off 43 employees in its newsroom and other...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2019: TV rolls ups, disappears...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/06/lg-rollable-4k-oled-tv-launching-this-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LG announced a new TV that rolls away when you don't want to watch it at CES 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 20% of households pay 88% of federal income taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/top-20-households-pay-88-federal-income-taxes-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Eye 33% Corporate Rate Hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/dems-eye-33-corporate-rate-hike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman dies from rabies after bitten by dog...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/virginia-woman-dies-rabies-dog-yoga-retreat-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention have confirmed that a Virginia woman who died in 2017 contracted rabies from a dog bite in India. The Daily Progress reports the CDC released a report on Friday cautioning travelers to get the rabies vaccine. The 65-year-old was bitten on the hand during a yoga retreat. She began experiencing pain six weeks later, and eventually tested positive for rabies. She'd never been vaccinated against the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Reporters Ejected...</title>
      <link>https://californiaglobe.com/governor/two-reporters-ejected-from-newsom-inauguration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californiaglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS OVAL OFFICE ADDRESS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bdec60db69df4a5d85354d34368c494c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With no breakthrough in sight, President Donald Trump will argue his case to the nation Tuesday night that a "crisis" at the U.S.-Mexico border requires the long and invulnerable wall he's demanding before ending the partial government shutdown. Hundreds of thousands of federal workers face missed paychecks Friday as the shutdown drags through a third week. Trump's Oval Office speech — his first as president — will be followed by his visit Thursday to the southern border to highlight his demand for a barrier. White House press secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders tweeted that he will use the visit to "meet with those on the front lines of the national security and humanitarian crisis."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's unpredictable negotiating style faces test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f9819be53814017ac26971438c618ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The partial government shutdown is spotlighting the limitations of President Donald Trump's erratic negotiating style. With the impasse over Trump's demand for border wall funding dragging into a third week, the president's zigzag tactics and messaging have angered Democrats and frustrated even some Republicans struggling to help find him an off-ramp. And while Trump's blend of bluster and bullying is hardly new — and at times can produce results — his self-professed dealmaking skills are now facing a bigger test against newly empowered Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heathenry gains a foothold in U.S. military...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2019/01/07/heathens-hold-religious-services-rooted-in-norse-paganism-aboard-aircraft-carrier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The faith rooted in Norse myths is experiencing a resurgence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un Fourth Visit In Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/kim-jong-un-lands-in-china-for-his-fourth-visit-in-a-year-11546909773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un arrived in China—North Korea’s main backer, as he sends mixed signals to the U.S. about his willingness to give up his nuclear weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULLED OVER FOR SPEEDING ON WAY HOME...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/07/kevin-spacey-pulled-over-speeding-after-court-arraignment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey walks out of court, and gets pulled over for speeding hours later. Seriously ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Biden Bid Most Divisive Thing For Field...</title>
      <link>https://www.esquire.com/news-politics/politics/a25782295/joe-biden-2020-democrats-divisive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.esquire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president's track record in Congress puts him on the wrong side of every issue that currently energizes his political party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Untested' Kamala Readies Publicity Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/07/politics/kamala-harris-new-book-tour/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a new memoir set to publish Tuesday, the 2020 spotlight shifts this week to Sen. Kamala Harris as she embarks on a book tour in advance of an expected presidential announcement this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive cultural extermination campaign against Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/global-opinions/china-has-launched-a-massive-campaign-of-cultural-extermination-against-the-uighurs/2019/01/07/efe03c9c-12a4-11e9-b6ad-9cfd62dbb0a8_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Vocational training” is basically just cultural extermination under a less-horrific name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON most valuable US company for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2019/01/07/amazon-tops-microsoft-as-most-valuable-us-company/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The repositioning has been triggered by mounting concerns that the Trump administration’s trade war with China and rising interest rates will bog down the worldwide economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Death Penalty for Scientist Who Created Gene-Edited Babies?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chinese-scientist-who-created-crispr-babies-could-face-1831553751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British geneticist is worried that He Jiankui—the Chinese scientist responsible for the birth of genetically modified human twins—could face the death penalty for corruption and bribery charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO SOLO ROAD TRIP TO MEET VOTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/beto-orourke-plans-solo-road-trip-to-meet-democratic-voters-outside-texas-11546900932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O’Rourke is asking aides to create an itinerary for a solo road trip outside Texas where he would ‘pop into places’ such as community colleges, as he considers whether to enter the 2020 Democratic presidential primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil gang rampage challenges Bolsonaro security strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-violence/brazil-gang-attacks-challenge-bolsonaros-security-strategy-idUSKCN1P11YS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Criminal gangs on a rampage in northeast Brazil are posing an early security tes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Promobot' struck, 'killed' by self-driving TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6566655/Oops-Autonomous-robot-struck-killed-self-driving-Tesla-Las-Vegas-ahead-CES.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla has found itself the cause of yet another self-driving car accident – and this time, its victim was a $2,000-per-day rentable humanoid robot. Promobot says the damage to its bot is likely irreparable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison commissaries offer AMAZON-like goods, rack up $17M sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/expo/news/g66l-2019/01/8e8ac092fe8811/oregons-prison-commissaries-of.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state operates its own version of big box stores for its inmate population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asks followers to help make bribery jokes...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Netanyahu-asks-Twitter-followers-Help-me-make-bribery-jokes-576643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In reference to the power-duo of Israeli television Rotem Sela and Assi Azar, a user claimed that Bribery without money is like the famous model and actress Sela having to work without the Azar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers grounded with dead body for 2 HOURS after passenger dies on board...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6566739/Plane-passengers-left-grounded-dead-body-TWO-HOURS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ANZ80 flight from Hong Kong was diverted to Cairns Airport at 2.30am on Monday morning after the man died due to an unknown medical emergency. It waited at Cairns for two hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Black Man Dies in Home of West Hollywood Dem Donor...</title>
      <link>https://www.advocate.com/crime/2019/1/07/another-black-man-has-died-home-democratic-donor-ed-buck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.advocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ski resort evacuated as heavy snow blankets...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/ski-resort-evacuated-thousands-stranded-142144984.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy snowfalls have left large areas of the Austrian and Bavarian Alps paralysed, with more than 2,000 people trapped in villages and ski resorts cut off from the outside world. Five people have been killed, and another two are missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 cops in 'love rectangle' stripped of guns so won't kill each other...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/07/4-cops-in-love-rectangle-stripped-of-guns-so-they-wouldnt-kill-each-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NYPD sergeant cheated on his cop girlfriend with a fellow officer — whose husband is also on the job — and the bosses took away all their guns so they wouldn’t kill each other,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows 'Sanctuary To All Who Seek It'...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/07/gavin-newsom-california-governor-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Jerry Brown is passing his title to fellow Democrat Gavin Newsom, who was sworn in Monday as California's 40th governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How China Flexes Political Muscle to Expand Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-china-flexes-its-political-muscle-to-expand-power-overseas-11546890449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secret discussions show how China uses its political and financial clout to bolster its position overseas, especially for its “Belt and Road” infrastructure project. Malaysian’s new leader has since put the deal on hold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Gov. Newsom immediately challenges Trump at inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/Gov-Gavin-Newsom-governor-inaugural-speech-brown-13514913.php?t=6c49ce5a9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO - Gavin Newsom took the oath as California's 40th governor Monday and instantly challenged President Trump, promising a "progressive, principled" administration that will counter "corruption and incompetence" in the White House. "It is up to us to renew the California dream for a new generation. And now more than ever, it is up to us to defend it," Newsom said. "But there is an administration in Washington hostile to California's values and interests." The former San Francisco mayor painted a picture of California as a virtual "nation-state," one that will push beyond the strictures proposed by the GOP leaders in Washington toward a more progressive future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Refunds To STILL Be Sent Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/07/white-house-official-says-tax-refunds-will-be-sent-out-despite-government-shutdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 12 percent of IRS staff are expected to continue working through a shutdown, according to the agency's plan, which means certain functions such as answering taxpayer questions would be curtailed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Draft Beto' effort builds momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/07/orourke-south-carolina-nevada-boost-1085236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O’Rourke is getting a significant lift in the early nominating states of South Carolina and Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vet issues alert as nasty dog virus sweeps UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1068363/dog-virus-warning-uk-dog-news-pet-illness-bacterial-infection-gastroenteritis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VET has warned dog owners of a painful bacteria infection spreading rapidly across the UK, urging pet lovers to take care of their animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic mushroom legalization gets closer in Denver...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/01/07/denver-magic-mushrooms-legalization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists who hope to make Denver the first U.S. city to decriminalize psychedelic mushrooms plan to turn in ballot petitions Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Kelly allegedly posts sex tapes of accuser to discredit rape claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6566331/R-Kelly-allegedly-posts-sex-tapes-accuser-site-launched-camp-discredit-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook page, whose name is not being revealed, was created on Sunday, and by Monday afternoon there was an announcement that video had been posted online of one accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 'dramatic statement,' Netanyahu says he was refused chance to confront accusers...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-january-7-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement authorities say investigations against PM were carried out 'professionally and thoroughly... only according to professional considerations'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Hearing Loss Linked To Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-hearing-loss-linked-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elderly people suffering from hearing loss are more likely to experience symptoms of depression, and the greater the degree of hearing loss, the more intense those symptoms are, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS OVAL OFFICE ADDRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/breaking-trump-reportedly-seeking-to-address-the-nation-on-tuesday-night-but-networks-reluctant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripper Arrested After Threatening Mass Shooting At Club...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/01/06/florida-stripper-arrested-after-threatening-mass-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another arrest has been made following a shooting threat on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver admits murdering 6 between fares...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/07/uber-driver-admits-to-murdering-six-strangers-between-fares/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KALAMAZOO, Mich. — A man charged with killing six strangers between picking up rides for Uber pleaded guilty to murder on Monday in Michigan. Jason Dalton’s surprise move occurred as lawyers …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/eagles-bears-ratings-nfl-wild-card-golden-globe-sunday-1202530563/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking until the final minutes like it may go into overtime and delay the start of the Golden Globes, last night’s NFL wild card playoff game between the Philadelphia Eagles and Chicago Bears was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu to make 'dramatic announcement'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/82d4bc7a869947c886071bfef325fe70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu says he will deliver a "dramatic announcement" set to coincide with the evening news broadcast. Netanyahu said in statement on Twitter on Monday that he would broadcast a "special announcement to the press." The embattled prime minister's mysterious statement left even veteran political reporters baffled as to its nature. There was speculation it was related to investigations into alleged corruption by Netanyahu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home items getting creepier...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/12787de930564f2cbe8fadfdf63e2e7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — One day, finding an oven that just cooks food may be as tough as buying a TV that merely lets you change channels. Internet-connected "smarts" are creeping into cars, refrigerators, thermostats, toys and just about everything else in your home. CES 2019, the gadget show opening Tuesday in Las Vegas, will showcase many of these products, including an oven that coordinates your recipes and a toilet that flushes with a voice command. With every additional smart device in your home, companies are able to gather more details about your daily life. Some of that can be used to help advertisers target you — more precisely than they could with just the smartphone you carry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns against nationalism -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-diplomats/pope-francis-warns-of-resurgent-nationalism-urges-help-for-migrants-idUSKCN1P115Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis warned on Monday against a resurgence of nationalist and populist m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THURSDAY:  Trump to Visit Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-to-travel-to-southern-border-thursday-sarah-sanders-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump will travel to the U.S.-Mexico border on Thursday in a bid to highlight border security, as he presses Democrats for wall funding amid the protracted standoff that triggered a partial government shutdown now stretching into its 17th day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER CHANNEL Sued For Selling Data Of App Users...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/04/la-sues-weather-channel-illegally-selling-private-data-mobile-app-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data was sold to at least 12 third party websites over the past 19 months, the complaint reads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain testing 'no-deal' scenario as Brexit vote nears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24342b039b64431193bac0d07f7415d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain is testing how its motorway and ferry system would handle a "no-deal" Brexit by sending a stream of trucks from a small local airport to the port of Dover — even as some legislators try to pressure the government to rule out the scenario. The tests began Monday morning and are intended to gauge how severe the disruption would be if Britain leaves the European Union on March 29 without an agreed-upon withdrawal deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney in Yankee cap arrested in series of violent NYC sex attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Attorney-Sex-Attack-Manhattan-Pattern-2014-Rashaun-Kelley--503995031.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney has been charged in three sex attacks that took place in Manhattan more than three years ago, the NYPD said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END:  Supreme Court Denies Review of Olivia De Havilland 'FEUD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/supreme-court-denies-review-olivia-de-havillands-feud-lawsuit-1174078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 102-year-old actress has lost her case over a series that she claimed depicted her falsely and unfairly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey Makes First Court Appearance... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-spacey-makes-first-court-appearance-alleged-sexual-assault-1173337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged victim was 18 at the time when he claims the actor assaulted him after getting him drunk at a restaurant on Nantucket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How solitary confinement drove young inmate to brink of insanity...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/how-solitary-confinement-drove-a-young-inmate-to-the-brink/article_62707aa1-d5ec-51cc-b41d-911f58c313cb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — With his mental state deteriorating as he sat in the crushing isolation of solitary confinement, a desperate inmate named Anthony Gay saw a temporary way out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player thinks Goodell plotting against Chargers...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/01/07/russell-okung-thinks-the-league-is-plotting-against-the-chargers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chargers had a chance to take the lead over the Ravens in December, when a holding penalty on Russell Okung backed them up, and they fumbled on the next play. The Chargers had a chance to kneel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAGA LOSES TO GA GA...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/movies/golden-globes-2019-a-star-is-born-snubbed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 76th annual Golden Globes were presented live on NBC at the Beverly Hilton in Beverly Hills, California, on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEYLAND sharply hikes prices; Most expensive pass $1,949!</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2019/01/07/disneyland-2019-ticket-prices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Lando Calrissian once griped: "This deal is getting worse all the time!" Disneyland announced it's significantly hiking its already…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'self-aware' vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cars/news/self-aware-car-launched-ces-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans of the sentient, singing trains in Philip Reeve's Rail Head science fiction tale will be disappointed with Delphi's somewhat overstated exhibit at this year's Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas, the &amp;quot;self-aware car&amp;quot;, although in reality it is much better than the usual sci-fi fantasy fare usually served up at this frenetic early-year event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to crash spacecraft into asteroid in mission to stop strike on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/751994/nasa-news-spaceship-crash-asteroid-deadly-strike-earth-dart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Biggest Bear Says Problems 'Likely to Worsen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/facebook-s-biggest-bear-says-problems-likely-to-worsen-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's Biggest Bear Says Problems â€˜Likely to Worsenâ€™Â in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smarts' creep into everyday products...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/12787de930564f2cbe8fadfdf63e2e7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — One day, finding an oven that just cooks food may be as tough as buying a TV that merely lets you click between channels. Internet-connected "smarts" are creeping into cars, refrigerators, thermostats, toys and just about everything else in your home. CES 2019, the gadget show opening Tuesday in Las Vegas, will showcase many of these products, including an oven that coordinates your recipes and a toilet that flushes with a voice command. With every additional smart device in your home, companies are able to gather more details about your daily life. Some of that can be used to help advertisers target you — more precisely than they could with just the smartphone you carry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Denies Ownership Of Syringes Found In Rectum During Jail Strip Search...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/contraband/syringe-story-stinks-482093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida Man denied ownership of three syringes removed from his rectum during a 4:30 AM strip search at a county jail, according to a criminal complaint. Cops arrested Wesley Scott, 40, early Frida</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
