<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Job openings climb to record 6.9 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-job-openings-climb-to-record-69-million-2018-09-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of job openings in the U.S. climbed to a record 6.9 million in July in a clear sign that a booming economy is entering the second half of the year with a big dollop of momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens to wild horses?</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article218170815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Carolina coastal residents are evacuating ahead of Hurricane Florence, but the wild horses that make their homes on the coast will stay put and might be better prepared than anyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'SNL' makeover rescue EMMYS?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/38f07ad36f9c4d5e8a311ba1eae513b0/Will-a-'Saturday-Night-Live'-makeover-rescue-the-Emmys?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Excited about Monday's 70th Emmy Awards? Probably not. That's an educated guess based on shrinking interest in entertainment's back-slapping ceremonies generall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biblical flooding...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/09/11/hurricane-florence-storm-could-harvey-east-coast-due-floods/1264450002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst impact of monstrous Hurricane Florence could be disastrous, deadly flooding from days of relentless rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President only trusts small group after op-ed, Don Jr. says...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-jr-father-trusts-smaller-group-aides-white/story?id=57735562</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid explosive allegations that some White House officials are actively working against President Donald Trump’s agenda, Donald Trump Jr. told ABC News the number of people in the White House that his father can trust is smaller than he’d like. “I think there are people in there that he can trust,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial biometrics catches another illegal at DC airport...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/illegal-caught-at-airport-using-facial-biometrics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border security officials have caught a second impostor trying to enter the United States using a new facial comparison biometric system. &amp;nbsp;It is the second time in less than three weeks since the cutting-edge technology was deployed at Dulles Washington International Airport in the Washington, D.C. area that someone has been caught.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffes, elephants wander about in snow after freak blizzards hit Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7229712/snow-south-africa-blizzards-desert-giraffes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANIMALS more used to the searing heat have been swanning around in the snow after freak blizzards hit the Savannah. Giraffes, antelopes and elephants were all among the beasts braving the freeze af…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Now Training Politicians On How To Avoid Becoming 'Fake News'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/09/10/fbi-politicians-cybersecurity-fake-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time ever, the FBI is training political candidates in Colorado how to spot people who may want to hijack their identity and spread misinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia: Staged Filming of False Flag 'Chemical Attacks' Has Begun in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-09-11/russian-defense-ministry-says-filming-mock-chemical-attack-has-begun-idlib</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos banning books...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/fahrenheit-2018-amazon-begins-banning-controversial-books/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roosh V's dating advice books memory holed for unspecified offensive content</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Ever Study of Male Fertility Finds 60% Reduction in Sperm Count...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6152735/The-male-infertility-injustice-does-IVF-industry-focus-wholly-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan James, 32, from Kent (pictured with wife Gemma and their child, Phoebe) struggled to conceive with his partner - until a sperm-boosting health regime changed their fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight weeks out: Dems see narrow path to Senate majority...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/405980-eight-weeks-out-dems-see-narrow-path-to-senate-majority</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight weeks out from the midterm elections, both Republicans and Democrats find themselves with a path to a Senate majority. For Democrats, it is a surprising development given this year’s difficult political map: The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDS TOP 130 MPH</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/111151.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's ex-bodyguard challenges Navalny to duel...</title>
      <link>https://themoscowtimes.com/news/russian-national-guard-chief-challenges-navalny-to-a-duel-62843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of Russia’s National Guard has challenged opposition leader Alexei Navalny to a duel and promised to pound him into a ‘juicy steak.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many California marijuana products failing safety tests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2cb04323f9074c1ca28001693f6e2a8a/Many-California-marijuana-products-failing-safety-tests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Nearly 20 percent of marijuana products in California have failed tests for potency and purity since the state started requiring the checks on July 1, a failure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crack pipe' vending machines popping up in New York...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/crack-pipe-vending-machines-found-on-long-island/4202377/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Town of Brookhaven officials and Suffolk Police are trying to figure out who placed three potential crack pipe vending machines, dubbed as pen vending machines, in Coram and Medford.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Producing More of What Eat...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/see-food-why-robots-are-producing-more-of-what-you-eat-1536663744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots that see underpin the future of self-driving cars, humanoid robots and autonomous drones. Right now, they’re serving their apprenticeship sizing up the likes of sausages and frozen pizzas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Trade Center Struggles to Fill Office Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-yorks-world-trade-center-struggles-to-fill-office-space-1536663600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rebuilt One World Trade Center in New York has struggled more than the other towers on the site to fill its 3.1 million square feet of office space. About 20% of the building remains empty four years after it opened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke Plants in Path...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/09/11/preparations-hurricane-florence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With mandatory evacuations already issued for parts of three East Coast states, millions of Americans are preparing for what could become one of the most catastrophic hurricanes to hit the Eastern Seaboard in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bono uses 'devil clown alter ego' to mock Sweden with Nazi salutes during U2 concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6154295/Swedish-election-Anti-immigrant-Sweden-Democrats-votes-party-male-voters.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bono was seen making a Nazi salute on stage during U2's concert in Paris on Sunday, as he mocked the leader of the far-right Sweden Democrats in the wake of the general election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small-business optimism highest level ever; Tops previous record under Reagan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/11/small-business-optimism-surges-to-highest-ever.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tax cuts and deregulation efforts of President Donald Trump and the Republican-led Congress led to more sales, hiring and investment, according to a survey by the National Federation of Independent Business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC officials already urging to prepare for nasty flu season...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/10/cdc-urges-public-to-prepare-for-another-potentially-nasty-flu-season.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC estimates that more than 700,000 people were hospitalized with the flu during last season with epidemic levels of influenza or pneumonia for 16 consecutive weeks. Some 180 children died from the most recent bout of flu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vanished China star last in 'social responsibility' ranking...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/206/vanished-china-star-fan-last-social-responsibility-ranking-doc-1904681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas booming again -- and bracing for next slump...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-financial-crisis2008-lasvegas/las-vegas-is-booming-again-and-bracing-itself-for-next-slump-idUSKCN1LR0YX?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diane Han is trying to leave the Las Vegas of her childhood behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica 'close to war zone' with 57 murders a day...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180911-safrica-close-war-zone-with-57-murders-day-minister</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto: Standing ovation for Redford's acting swansong...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-45480846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar glory possibly beckons for what the Hollywood veteran says is his final acting venture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million+ Flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-storm-florence/more-than-1-5-million-ordered-to-evacuate-as-hurricane-florence-threatens-carolinas-idUSKCN1LR0J6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1.5 million people were ordered to evacuate their homes along the U.S. Atlantic coast as Hurricane Florence, a Category 4 storm and the most powerful to menace the Carolinas in nearly three decades, barreled in on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic Sludge, Lagoons of Pig Manure...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-09-10/add-potential-coal-ash-spills-to-hurricane-florence-s-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America moves closer to cashless society...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/america-moves-closer-to-being-a-cashless-society-2018-09-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cash-free commerce is spreading around the U.S., particularly in restaurants catering to a younger crowd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child who sweats blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/728870/bible-jesus-girl-sweats-blood-mystery-condition-dak-doa-vietnam-gethesmane</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things So Dire in Brazil Millions Refusing to Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/09/11/things-are-so-dire-in-brazil-that-millions-are-refusing-to-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things Are So Dire in Brazil That Millions Are Refusing to Vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>http://www.ssd.noaa.gov/PS/TROP/floaters/06L/html5-rb-short.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ssd.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>http://synoptic.envsci.rutgers.edu/site/radimg/anim_serc.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;synoptic.envsci.rutgers.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British city could be first to quit cigarettes totally...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7226515/bristol-uk-city-quit-cigarettes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRISTOL could be the first place in Britain to completely quit fags. New data suggest the city is on course to have no smokers at all by 2024. Wokingham and York could be next – ciggie-free by 2026…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Found Hanging From Tree Outside Elementary School...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/09/10/teen-found-hanging-outside-maryland-elementary-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 16-year-old girl was found hanging outside a Salisbury elementary school Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Threat for East Coast... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/strengthening-florence-to-pose-serious-threat-to-us-east-coast-later-this-week/70006011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  DETAILED UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/nJYURnnfgWw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;youtu.be&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: http://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Please note that these posts do NOT reflect the official forecasts of the National Hurricane Center, and should not ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child suicide rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/09/10/rising-child-suicide-defy-answers-prevention-month/1197113002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths more than doubled from 2008 to 2016 – and rising numbers of young children visited emergency rooms for suicidal thoughts and attempts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmonaut shows space station hole to calm public...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180910-cosmonaut-shows-space-station-hole-calm-public</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper continues to cheat death...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/music/posts/la-et-ms-post-malone-final-destination-20180910-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Post Malone has had a pretty good year, all things considered. He's scored a No. 1 song, a No.1 album and, increasingly, appears to be cheating death at every turn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst storm EVER outside Florida?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2018/09/hurricane-florence-southeast-danger/569863/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since records began, only 10 major hurricanes have made landfall around the Carolinas. This one has the potential to blow them all out of the water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE becomes most shorted company ahead of iPhone launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/09/10/apple-becomes-shorted-us-company-ahead-iphone-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Short sellers have circled Apple on the eve of the tech giant&amp;rsquo;s highly-anticipated iPhone launch, with the tech giant becoming America&amp;rsquo;s most bet-against company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE: Illegal crossings surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Border-agents-in-South-Texas-saw-increase-in-13219268.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Central American families arrested for entering the United States illegally surged again in August, according to a Trump administration official and Border Patrol agents in South Texas, an increase that comes as the president threatens a government shutdown to extract funding from Congress for a border wall. U.S. Customs and Border Protection is expected to publish the most recent border arrest totals this week, and the numbers will be used to gauge the effect of President Donald Trump's order halting the separation of migrant parents from their children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFOWARS stores thrive online despite Big Tech ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/business/article/As-Alex-Jones-rails-against-Big-Tech-his-13219191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech industry's bans of conspiracy theorist Alex Jones over repeated allegations of hate speech have left intact key elements of his money-making machinery -- digital storefronts that sell apparel, survivalist gear and nutritional supplements. And business, so far at least, appears to be booming. The sites, called Infowars stores after Jones' main conspiracy-themed brand, continue to operate on Twitter and Facebook, both of which have closed other accounts affiliated with Jones. Digital storefronts on these and other digital platforms funnel traffic to a website, Infowarsstore.com, that has not been affected by the industry crackdown on Jones. It had 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navratilova Calls Out Serena over U.S. Open Meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180910-navratilova-serena-even-guys-do-it-its-wrong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot bat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/robat-the-robot-mimics-bats-using-sound-alone-to-navigate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot + bat = a new bot that uses an echo-based sonar system to get around and map new surroundings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg's obsession with ancient Roman emperor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/10/facebook-ceo-mark-zuckerbergs-love-for-augustus-may-give-insight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook CEO's idealization of the ancient Roman emperor, who he says made difficult choices to achieve the greater good, may explain many of his decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mysterious radio bursts' from outer space detected... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7226213/dozens-of-mysterious-radio-bursts-from-outer-space-detected-by-alien-hunting-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN artificial intelligence program hunting for alien life in the universe has picked up dozens of mysterious radio bursts. The Breakthrough Listen has detected 72 new fast radio bursts (FRBs) comin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans turn to breast milk donations as baby formula price soars...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article217586870.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Venezuela, where baby formula can cost more than a month’s wages, women are turning to each other for help feeding their babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Moore takes mic away after Hogg URGES FOREIGN MEDDLING IN ELECTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/35640/watch-david-hogg-makes-fool-himself-canada-michael-ryan-saavedra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Left-wing activist David Hogg made a fool out of himself in Canada late last week while joining leftist Michael Moore for the premiere of his anti-Trump propaganda film "Fahrenheit 11/9."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of elderly Americans hooked on Xanax...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6151275/25-older-adults-use-sedatives-treat-depression-sleep-issues-addicted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study led by the University of Michigan has found that for every 10 extra days a prescription for benzos was written for, long-term use risk among older adults doubled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI officials plotted media leaks before major Trump-Russia revelation...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/09/10/strzok-media-leak-text/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovery of dog saves man from sex-crime conviction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/34e672ffb06d4d229dbe21a52939bf0f/Discovery-of-dog-saves-Oregon-man-from-sex-crime-conviction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — The discovery of a black Lab named Lucy led to the unravelling of a criminal case Monday against an Oregon man who had begun serving a 50-year prison sentence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Unveil Plan to Make Tax Cuts Permanent...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/house-republicans-unveil-plan-to-make-individuals-tax-cuts-permanent-1536615799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republicans have introduced legislation to lock in cuts to individual tax rates beyond 2025, a proposal that will have trouble advancing in the Senate but which sends a signal about GOP priorities ahead of midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryogenics firm sued for freezing man's head instead of whole body...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/09/09/cryogenics-firm-sued-freezing-mans-head-instead-whole-body/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A legal battle is brewing between a US cryogenics facility and the son of one of its clients after the company froze his deceased father&amp;rsquo;s head instead of his entire body, filings seen by The Daily Telegraph show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing murder charge and lawsuit, millionaire's assets held by police commissioner...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article218125040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney for David Jungerman, who is accused of murdering Tom Pickert in Brookside, is opposing a judge’s order putting the suspect’s assets under the control of a Kansas City police commissioner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to crack down on 'chaotic' online religious info...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-religion/china-to-crack-down-on-chaotic-online-religious-info-media-idUSKCN1LQ2QC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has drawn up new draft guidelines to crack down on the "chaotic" and illegal online promotion of religion, the official Global Times reported on Tuesday, part of a tough state campaign to bring religious worship into line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million+ Flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/09/10/hurricane-florence-driving-life-threatening-conditions-toward-east-coast/1253945002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory evacuations were underway Monday in the Carolinas and more are scheduled for Tuesday as Hurricane Florence  strengthened to a Category 4 storm and continued its slow but angry dance toward the East Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAYBOY model sues Avenatti...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/09/10/michael-avenatti-playboy-elliott-broidy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resistance moms hardest hit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple blood test may reveal body's inner clock...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/simple-blood-test-may-reveal-bodys-inner-clock-212154516.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of researchers at Northwestern University said Monday they have designed a blood test that can measure a person's inner body clock within 1.5 hours, an advance that may help personalize medical treatments in the future. The study was published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Braces For Its Own Hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hurricane-olivia-approaches-hawaii-heavy-wind-rain-212127077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hurricane Olivia will likely approach Hawaii as either a high-end tropical storm or a low-end hurricane in coming days, weather forecasters said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Preps for Second Meeting With Kim Jong Un...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-preparing-for-second-trump-meeting-with-north-koreas-leader-1536607841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said it is working to arrange a second meeting between President Trump and Kim Jong Un after the North Korean leader sent a letter requesting one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss America Delivers All-Time Ratings Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/09/10/miss-america-all-time-low-in-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC's broadcast of Sunday night's Miss America pageant capped a ceremony rife with politicization, leading to an all-time low in TV ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSTON CHRONICLE reporter resigns after accused of making up interviews...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/local/article/A-note-from-the-editor-of-the-Houston-Chronicle-13218790.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We ask that you trust us that we've done everything we can to ensure what we've told you is fair and accurate. For that reason, I want to be completely transparent with readers and tell you that we have launched an investigation into one of our own reporter's work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rat yanks DC fire alarm, forces building evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/10/rat-yanks-fire-alarm-forces-building-evacuation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet Fire Alarm Rat. Surveillance footage captured the moment a pesky rodent pulled the fire alarm at a Washington, DC, condominium building, triggering an evacuation. The video, published by NBC W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lava flow seen on restless Alaska volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/lava-flow-seen-restless-alaska-volcano-215723666.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — A lava flow has been spotted on an Alaska volcano that recently became active again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORENCE CHURNS</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Expect-Storm-Surge-15-20-Feet-Landfalling-Category-4-Storm-Carolinas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Florence hits the coast of North or South Carolina as a Category 3 or stronger hurricane, we should expect to see record storm surge heights, with a 15 – 20’ surge very possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booming US economy led to record summer travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/airlines-say-booming-us-economy-led-to-record-summer-travel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major U.S. airlines said Monday that the booming U.S. economy is what led to a record-breaking level of travel over the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Now Has Tooth 'Radios' for Secret Communication...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2018/09/military-now-has-tooth-mics-invisible-hands-free-radio-calls/151145/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of battlefield communications is resting comfortably near your back gums.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Divorce 'Contagious'...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/09/09/study-divorce-may-be-contagious/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People are 75 percent more likely to get divorced if their friend has been divorced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDS TOP 140 MPH</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/102053.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife Julie Chen takes time off from 'TALK'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/julie-chen-wife-departed-cbs-ceo-takes-time-204044190--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV host Julie Chen, the wife of former CBS Corp Chief Executive Leslie Moonves, said on Monday she was taking a few days off from daytime show "The Talk" to spend time with her family. Moonves said the claims against him were untrue. Chen, who married Moonves in 2004, serves as a host and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA approves goal for 100% renewable electricity...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article218128485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Jerry Brown on Sept. 10, 2018, signed Senate Bill 100, which sets a goal for California to get all of its retail electricity from renewable sources like solar and wind by 2045.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But will REMAIN advisor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/les-moonves-remain-cbs-advisor-120-million-payout-pending-investigation-n908166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because of a confidentiality clause, the results of the investigation into allegations against Moonves may never be revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ERA: MOONVES OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/leslie-moonves-departs-cbs-ceo-chairman-financial-package-withheld-pending-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS and Moonves will donate $20 million to one or more organizations that support the #MeToo movement and equality for women in the workplace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Orders Gag, Warns Prosecutors In Maria Butina Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/09/10/646400980/judge-orders-gag-chastens-prosecutors-in-case-of-accused-russian-agent-butina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Tanya Chutkan said both prosecutors and the defense had gone too far in their statements. She declined to release Maria Butina from pretrial confinement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartoonist defends Serena Williams drawing amid 'racist', 'sexist' accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/j-k-rowling-blasts-racist-serena-williams-newspaper-cartoon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famed author J.K. Rowling took to Twitter to call out a cartoonist's "racist" take on Serena Williams' U.S. Open penalties and loss</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran 'Strike Beyond Seas' Vow Heightens Concerns Of Clandestine Ops In USA...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-vows-strikes-outside-borders-beyond-seas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Iranian military leader warned Iran is plotting strikes outside of its own borders and will go "beyond the seas" to carry out attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young and Russian In DC: Paranoid Bosses, Suspicious Landlords, Tinder Woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/09/10/young-russians-washington-dc-219743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington’s young &amp;eacute;migr&amp;eacute; crowd is beginning to feel like they’re living in a spy novel. And they’re the bad guys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAYBOY Club opens in New York, defying #MeToo era...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/10/tone-deaf-playboy-club-opens-in-new-york-defying-the-metoo-era</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Club to open more than 30 years after Hugh Hefner declared Bunnies ‘a symbol of the past’ and 32 years after the city’s original closed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jim Carrey Tells Dems: Say Yes To Socialism!</title>
      <link>https://www.lifezette.com/2018/09/millionaire-jim-carrey-declares-we-have-to-say-yes-to-socialism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'Dumb and Dumber' and 'Bruce Almighty' star appeared on HBO's 'Real Time with Bill Maher' to give some advice to Democrats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Tiger keeper ordered hit on 'Big Cat Rescue' CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.pnj.com/story/news/2018/09/08/joe-exotic-tiger-keeper-arrested-gulf-breeze-murder-plot/1240662002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pnj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tiger keeper nicknamed "Joe Exotic" was arrested in Gulf Breeze for allegedly attempting to put a hit on a South Florida woman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More and more companies scrap college degree requirement for jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/personal-finance/more-companies-dropping-college-degree-requirement-for-new-hires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No diploma? That won’t stop you from getting a job at some major corporations like Google and IBM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ESPN Boss Changes Course, In Lock Step With NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/10/sports/espn-nfl-jimmy-pitaro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy Pitaro pledged a “resetting” of the network’s relationship with the N.F.L., but is reining in talent and placating the league a winning bet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON: International Criminal Court 'Dangerous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/icc-us-john-bolton-international-criminal-court-national-security-advisor-donald-trump-a8531701.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He labels the ICC as a 'freewheeling global organisation governing over people without their consent'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 2/3 Of Teens Prefer To Chat Online Than In Person...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/most-teens-prefer-to-chat-online-than-in-person-survey-finds-1536597971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two-thirds of teens say they would rather communicate with their friends online than in person, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury over art exhibit where public pose for 'beheading' by Jihadi John...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6151783/Fury-beheading-art-exhibition-public-pretend-murdered-Jihadi-John.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artwork, which is part of an exhibition at the Gogbot art and music festival in the Eastern Dutch city of Enschede, features a full-size picture of a so-called Islamic State (IS) terrorist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON: International Criminal Court 'Dangerous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-calls-international-criminal-court-dangerous-165302405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington (AFP) - White House National Security Advisor John Bolton branded the International Criminal Court dangerous and unaccountable Monday, saying it constitutes an assault on US sovereignty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Wipeout Deepens to $640 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/09/10/crypto-wipeout-deepens-to-640-billion-as-ether-leads-declines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cryptocurrency bear market plumbed a fresh 10-month low, led by a slump in Bitcoin’s biggest rival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican promises 'clarifications' to Pope cover-up claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vatican-promises-clarifications-pope-cover-claims-161805683.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis' top advisers say the Vatican is preparing the "necessary clarifications" about accusations that the pope covered up the sexual misconduct of a now-disgraced American cardinal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi arrests man over breakfast video with woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saudi-arrests-man-over-breakfast-video-woman-163727400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi authorities have arrested a foreign hotel worker who appeared in an "offensive" video eating breakfast with a female colleague, the labour ministry said Sunday. The footage, which sparked outrage on social media in the ultra-conservative kingdom, showed the pair sharing a meal at a desk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Motorcycle racing star grabs rival brake at 140mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/7219293/moto2-star-romano-fenati-sacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOTO2 star Romano Fenati has been sacked by his team after grabbing rival’s brake lever at 140mph as they raced side-by-side. The Italian, 22, has had his contract with the Marinelli Snipers Team t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDS TOP 130 MPH</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT1+shtml/101556.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold Cut Case: Deli Worker 'Consumed $9,000 Worth Of Meat'...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/ohio-cold-cut-case-295038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 10--An Ohio supermarket worker could face criminal charges after her employer told cops that she had consumed more than $9000 worth of deli meat during the past five years she has worked fo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copyright Battle in Europe Pits Media Against Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/copyright-battle-in-europe-pits-media-companies-against-tech-giants-1536584852</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new European push to rein in tech giants through copyright legislation is sparking fierce debate and questions about whether the proposed law would accomplish its goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunken British sailors invade Florida, brawl at bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2018/09/09/drunken-british-sailors-are-invading-florida-and-beating-each-other-up-because-why-not/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British sailors from the Royal Navy’s prized new carrier HMS Queen Elizabeth arrived in the northeast Florida port of Jacksonville Beach Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump closes Palestinians' office in DC, citing their refusal to move forward on peace deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/22ab439a410042169cf96b0612fb8e5a/Trump-closing-Palestinian-mission-in-pro-Israel-move</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is closing the Palestinian Liberation Organization's mission in Washington, the latest U.S. blow against the Palestinians and an internati</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO SHAKEUPS: THE MIGHTY ARE FALLING...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ceo-shakeups-les-moonves-jack-ma-departures-dc44e5d4-a061-43a2-82af-1c2db319325b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They're leaving for varied reasons and on different timetables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORENCE CHURNS</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Hurricane-Florence-Rapidly-Intensifying-Likely-Hit-North-or-South-Carolina-Thursday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florence has rapidly intensified into a dangerous Category 3 hurricane, and appears destined to strengthen into a very dangerous Category 4 hurricane by Tuesday as it heads towards the Southeast U.S. Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/tc_guidance/storm.html?tcid=AL06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE MELTDOWN: I say impeachment, impeachment, impeachment, impeachment, impeachment, impeachment, impeachment, impeachment!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/maxine-waters-brags-she-threatens-trump-supporters-all-the-time-wakes-up-in-middle-of-night-thinking-im-going-to-get-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mad Maxine Waters is obsessed with President Trump. The California Congresswoman went after the president while accepting an award from the Stonewall Young Democrats on Saturday in Los Angeles. At one point in the 20-minute speech, she bragged about threatening Trump supporters. ﻿ Speaking about Sen. Dianne Feinstein’s apology to Judge Brett Kavanaugh for the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Malone targeted by home invaders days after car wreck and plane dramas...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7220594/post-malones-house-stormed-by-home-invaders-days-after-rapper-cheated-death-twice-in-plane-drama-and-car-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARMED raiders targeted Post Malone’s luxury San Fernando home attacking one person while screaming the notorious rapper’s name. Cops in California say three men brandishing guns entered…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMILE:  DC Airport Surprises Passengers With Facial-Recognition Boarding...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/09/dulles-airport-surprises-passengers-facial-recognition-boarding/151095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airport officials rolled out the system expecting to increase security and decrease boarding times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW SEASON:  10 Players from 6 Teams Protest, Boycott on Week One...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/nfl-anthem-protests-10-players-6-teams-protest-week-one  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUNDAY NIGHT GAME SLIPS IN RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/09/aaron-rodgers-packers-nfl-ratings-down-donald-trump-sunday-night-football-opener-bears-nbc-miss-america-1202461366/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a score of 17-0 at the halftime against the Chicago Bears in the official Sunday Night Football kickoff of the new NFL season, last night was not a game the Green Bay Packers were supposed t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURT: Obama re-emerges to remind voters why they elected Trump...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/sep/9/obama-reminds-voters-why-they-backed-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just in time to remind America why voters elected Donald Trump president two years ago, ex-President Barack Obama emerged from political exile last week.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
