<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pastor threatens to remove people with face masks from church...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/coronavirus/article253026988.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They will be serving Frosty’s in hell before we shut this place down.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITIZEN app paying to livestream crime scenes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/25/citizen-pays-new-yorkers-25-an-hour-to-livestream-crime-scenes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to make $200 a day in New York City? Rush to the scene of a murder, a three-alarm fire or a traffic accident — then pull out your phone and start filming. That’s the pitch from Citizen, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA,</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/california-vaccine-verification-ca-state-employees-covid-testing-health-care-workers-coronvirus-vaccinations/10910038/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Newsom and California health officials have announced a vaccine verification and testing program that will be implemented for all state employees and health care workers starting in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Expands Vax Studies of Kids 5 to 11...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/pfizer-and-moderna-are-expanding-vaccine-studies-of-kids-5-to-11/ar-AAMzNT9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the urging of federal regulators, two coronavirus vaccine makers are expanding the size of their studies in children ages five to 11 — a precautionary measure designed to detect rare side effects including heart inflammation problems that turned up in vaccinated people younger than 30. Appearing at a televised town-hall-style meeting in Ohio last week, President Biden said that emergency clearance for pediatric vaccines would come “soon.” The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskless city workers will have to wear stickers declaring status...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/montclair-covid-stickers-mask/10909151/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting Monday in Montclair, city workers who choose not to wear a mask must wear stickers that prove they are fully vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodgers plans to play for PACKERS in stunning turn of events...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/26/aaron-rodgers-plans-to-play-for-packers-in-stunning-turn-of-events/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers may remain a Packer, after all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man blames 'imminent Antifa attack' for shooting woman who tore down his Nazi flag...</title>
      <link> http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/antifa-made-me-do-it-726508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 26--Antifa made me do it. That claim is central to the “stand your ground” defense being floated by the Oklahoma man charged with shooting an unarmed woman in the back as she ran from away from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES Warns of Fuel Shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/26/american-airlines-warns-about-fuel-shortages-around-the-country-ask-pilots-to-conserve.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American asked pilots to save fuel due to shortage at certain midsize airports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tobacco CEO sees end to cigarettes in Britain in 10 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/philip-morris-marlboro-britain-496ac5b559d6cfe5b85d56b39f383905</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief executive of the company that makes Marlboro cigarettes was quoted by Britain's Mail on Sunday as saying that the tobacco company foresaw an end to its sales of traditional cigarettes in Britain within 10 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Inside futuristic Bel Air mansion with floating DJ booth and NFT art gallery...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3353980/bel-air-mansion-on-sale-for-88m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MEGA mansion that ‘rivals a seven star resort’ and has its own floating DJ booth and NFT art gallery has gone on sale for $88million. The luxury Bel Air home boasts a glass floor walk…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Accuses Western Media of Intentionally Making Olympians Look Ugly...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2021/07/26/china-accuses-western-media-of-intentionally-making-its-olympians-look-ugly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China complained that Western media outlets were deliberately choosing unflattering photos of Chinese Olympians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAYPAL to block transactions that fund 'hate'?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/paypal-research-blocking-transactions-fund-130316312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PayPal Holdings Inc is partnering with non-profit organisation the Anti-Defamation League (ADL) to investigate how extremist and hate movements in the United States take advantage of financial platforms to fund their criminal activities. The information collected through the initiatives will be shared with other firms in the financial industry, law enforcement and policymakers, PayPal said. Over the years, the San Jose, California-based company has developed sophisticated systems to help prevent illegal activity and flows through its platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heathrow says it'll see even LESS passengers this year than last...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ryanair-says-its-outperformed-low-cost-rivals-easyjet-and-wizz-as-ceo-oleary-attacks-eu-environmental-tax-proposal-11627299153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael O'Leary, the combative chief executive of Ryanair Holdings, couldn't resist taking a dig at its rivals during a presentation on the airline's latest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN: 'Anti-vaxxer lunatics must be stopped from destroying everybody's freedom'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9827167/PIERS-MORGAN-Americas-anti-vaxxers-snatching-covid-defeat-jaws-vaccinated-victory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To win the war on covid, we need to go to war on the anti-vaxxers - shut them down, get them off the airwaves, ban them from social media, and urgently re-educate their brainwashed followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White people have the LOWEST life expectancy of any ethnic group in England...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9826487/White-people-worst-life-expectancy-ethnic-group.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The life expectancy of white Britons in England and Wales was 83.1 years for women and 79.7 years for men, compared with 88.9 for black African women and 83.8 years for men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas firefighter 'kidnapped and murdered' in Cancun...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9826325/Texas-firefighter-Elijah-Snow-dead-mechanical-asphyxiation-Cancun.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elijah Snow, 35, became trapped as he tried to enter the window of a bathroom at a resort about 10 miles from the one where he was staying with his wife, Mexican investigators concluded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13-Year-Old  Wins Gold...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/teen-skateboarder-momiji-nishiya-gold-medal-japan-tokyo-olympic-games/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The girls standing by her side on the podium? Also teenagers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>46-Year-Old Gets Standing Ovation  During Record-Setting 8th Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/oksana-chusovitina-final-olympics-standing-ovation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gymnast has said Tokyo will be her last Olympic Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Box Office Recovery Stalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/what-box-office-recovery-low-points-are-getting-lower-as-covid-anxiety-grows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After big weekends for "F9" and "Black Widow," turnout for genre films like "Old" and "Snake Eyes" seems lower than in years past</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More EU states require passes to enter bars, restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/26/covid-more-eu-states-restrict-venue-access-unvaccinated-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ireland and Italy among those joining France in requiring vaccine passes to enter bars and restaurants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep sleep quest: 11 popular insomnia cures. Do any of them actually work?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/jul/26/my-deep-sleep-quest-i-tried-11-popular-insomnia-cures-do-any-of-them-actually-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In lockdown, insomnia has soared. Our tired, intrepid writer tried a range of remedies – including CBD, deep breathing and lettuce water</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors, nurses, medical groups call for mandatory vax for ALL health workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/leading-medical-groups-urge-mandatory-vaccination-all-healthcare-workers-n1275009</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requiring shots would be "the logical fulfillment of the ethical commitment" to all patients, according to the groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems move to elevate Cheney's role on Jan. 6 commission...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-move-to-elevate-cheney-e2-80-99s-role-on-jan-6-commission-giving-her-prime-speaking-slot-tuesday/ar-AAMzMHa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wyoming Republican will be one of two members of the nine member panel to deliver an opening statement at the committee’s first public hearing Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAITOR! Tom Barrack Heckled As He Enters Federal Courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/traitor-hecklers-scream-at-trump-ally-tom-barrack-as-he-enters-federal-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Barrack was greeted by an assembly of both members of the press and local Brooklyn hecklers as he entered a Federal Court Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM-BUST:  Big losses ahead for markets? Terrifying new forecasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/granthams-terrifying-new-forecasts-11627061555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I've never seen a forecast this bad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  At least 8 dead in 22-car pileup during Utah sandstorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2021/07/25/least-dead-vehicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least seven people were fatally injured in a 20-vehicle accident Sunday on Interstate 15 near Kanosh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Cuban-Americans protest through night outside White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9826323/Cuban-Americans-protest-WH-night-demanding-Biden-end-regimes-crackdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of anti-Cuban government protesters gathered outside the White to pressure Biden to do more to address the communist regime's actions against the people of Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Telling ShotSpotter to Alter Evidence From Gunshot-Detecting AI...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qj8xbq/police-are-telling-shotspotter-to-alter-evidence-from-gunshot-detecting-ai</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in Chicago are being forced to withdraw evidence generated by the technology, which led to the police killing of 13-year-old Adam Toledo earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman Who Thought Had Natural Immunity Infected Second Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/gop-congressman-who-thought-he-had-natural-immunity-gets-covid-a-second-time-this-episode-is-far-more-challenging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Clay Higgins (R-LA) revealed he has contracted Covid-19 for a second time in a statement referring to the virus as a “biological attack” from the Chinese government. “I have COVID, Becca has COVID, my son has COVID,” Higgins said, referring to his wife. “Becca and I had COVID before, early on, in January 2020, […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer Pink backs beach handball team on 'sexist' clothing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-arts-and-entertainment-pink-handball-025c9c9b4a18fbb71f8f1021774e51a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — U.S. pop singer Pink has offered to pay a fine given to the Norwegian female beach handball team for wearing shorts instead of the required bikini bottoms. Pink said she was “very proud” of the team for protesting against the rule that prevented them from wearing shorts like their male counterparts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS: Man who 'killed party-goer and wounded three STONED to death by crowd'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3353005/texas-man-stoned-death-shooting-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN who is suspected of killing one and injuring three was allegedly stoned to death with garden rocks. The brutal killing came after a fight broke out at a party in Fort Worth, Texas on Monday m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mammals Dream About World They're Entering Before Birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mammals-dream-before-birth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"These brain circuits are self-organized at birth and some of the early teaching is already done," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight teens trapped atop New Mexico roller coaster for two hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article253014448.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescuers used a ladder truck to get the teens off the El Bandido coaster at Western Playland Amusement Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Film Festival Unveils Lineup Heavy on Stars, Indie Favorites...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/venice-2021-film-festival-lineup-1234987376/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 78th Venice International Film Festival is looking to out-dazzle Cannes with a 2021 lineup that includes some of the biggest studio films as well as hotly-anticipated indie and arthouse titles.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant rebuffs precautions, wants unvaxxed diners...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/southern-california-restaurant-rebuffs-covid-precautions-wants-unvaccinated-diners/article_dc7c54ab-03c4-5f75-83b9-2f50ac61e704.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — When restaurants across California halted indoor dining as the COVID-19 pandemic took hold in March 2020, Basilico’s Pasta e Vino in Huntington Beach continued to welcome patrons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House says 'long COVID' could qualify as disability...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/564795-biden-admin-says-long-covid-could-qualify-as-a-disability-under-federal-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration on Monday released new guidance to support those experiencing long-term symptoms from COVID-19 as part of a broader effort to recognize the 31st anniversary of the Americans with Disabilities Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: AMERICANS SPLIT ON TRANS ATHLETES...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/poll-public-split-trans-athletes-tokyo-olympics-d9b02e56-ad54-4525-8d41-d95676cdac49.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Olympics will include the largest number of out LGBTQ athletes in the Games' history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio expands jab-or-test directive to all city workers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/26/nyc-expanding-covid-vaccine-or-test-mandate-to-all-city-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio will announce the expansion of the vaccination-or-test mandate to the entire city workforce — all 300,000-plus municipal employees, including the DOE and the NYPD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising Innovations of Pandemic-Era Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/07/the-pandemic-might-have-changed-sex-for-the-better/619553/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many queer people are reimagining their own boundaries and thinking of this reentry period as a time for sexual self-discovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin threatens to hit enemies with 'unpreventable strike'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3351141/putin-threatens-west-enemies-unpreventable-strike-navy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has bragged his war machine can now deliver an “unpreventable strike” against its enemies as he paraded his naval might.  The Russian strongman’s boast comes days af…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors, nurses, medical groups call for mandatory vax for all health workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/doctors-nurses-and-other-health-groups-call-for-mandatory-coronavirus-vaccinations-for-health-workers/ar-AAMzzZM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The statement — signed by 57 medical and health groups, representing millions of workers — represents an increasingly tough stance amid the sluggish pace of national vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA will not lift travel restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210726120031-ti728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAVEL (EXCLUSIVE):EXCLUSIVE-U.S. will not lift travel restrictions, citing Delta variant -official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors, nurses, medical groups call for mandatory vax for all health workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2021/07/26/mandatory-vaccinations-urged-health-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The statement — signed by 57 medical and health groups, representing millions of workers — represents an increasingly tough stance amid the sluggish pace of national vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen X workers may be facing biggest unemployment crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/26/gen-x-workers-may-face-the-biggest-unemployment-crisis-generation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gen Xers, those 45 years and above, may be bearing the brunt of a global unemployment crisis as the pandemic adds to existing challenges, a new report found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin weighs another term as influence peaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/26/manchin-weighs-another-term-as-his-influence-peaks-500648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin said 2018 was his "last campaign for Senate." Now, he says "you never know" about 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dressel big at Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/olympics/story/_/id/31868532/olympics-2021-caeleb-dressel-ready-become-next-big-name-men-swimming-tokyo-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Michael Phelps era is over. As Team USA looks for its next face of men's swimming, it might just want to look over at Caeleb Dressel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer Settles with NEWS OF WORLD Publisher Over Phone Hacking Claims...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/music/news/ronan-keating-phone-hacking-boyzone-news-of-the-world-1235027259/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irish singer-turned-television host Ronan Keating has received “substantial damages” and a public apology from News of the World publisher News Group Newspapers (NGN) over claims his ce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia sees COVID cases climb; Police warn against protest repeat...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-victoria-eyes-covid-19-lockdown-exit-cases-fall-2021-07-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's most populous state reported a rise in new COVID-19 cases on Monday despite a weeks-long stay-at-home order, while police vowed to crack down on any repeat of a anti-lockdown protest which turned violent at the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Holy moly!': Inside TX fight against ransomware hack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-government-and-politics-business-texas-hacking-772675a2a7a095ef6e5caa72fa8ca847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — It was a steamy Friday two Augusts ago when Jason Whisler settled in for a working breakfast at the Coffee Ranch restaurant in the Texas Panhandle city of Borger. The most pressing agenda item for city officials like him that morning: planning for a country concert and anniversary event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican trial opens into financial scandal rocking papacy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-religion-trials-philanthropy-c06e0c5cb6e43a196142dc07675de1df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — A cardinal who allegedly induced an underling to lie to prosecutors. Brokers and lawyers who pulled a fast one over the Vatican No. 2 to get him to approve a disastrous real estate deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least seven killed in 20-car pileup in Utah sandstorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jul/26/killed-in-20-car-pileup-in-utah-sandstorm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several more were in hospital with critical injuries after high winds blew up dust and impaired visibility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusually large meteor lights up Norway...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9825813/Unusually-large-meteor-lights-skies-Norway.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A web camera in Holmestrand, south of Oslo, captured a fireball falling from the sky and erupting into a bright flash lighting up a marina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rookie Bankers Sour on Wall St Pitch of Big Pay and Long Hours...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/26/rookie-bankers-sour-on-wall-streets-pitch-of-big-pay-and-long-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Vince Iyoriobhe joined Bank of America’s investment banking division as a rookie analyst in 2017, he planned to stick</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stinging Rebuke, China Tells U.S. Diplomat Its Rise Can't Be Stopped...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/26/in-stinging-rebuke-china-tells-u-s-diplomat-that-its-rise-cant-be-stopped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Chinese diplomat on Monday bluntly warned the visiting American deputy secretary of state, Wendy R. Sherman, that the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weightlifter wins gold on ONE LEG!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/tokyo-olympics-2020/3348040/weightlifter-li-fabin-flamingo-gold-tokyo-2020-olympics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEIGHTLIFTER Li Fabin blew away the competition in the men’s 61kg weightlifting category using a bizarre ONE-LEGGED lift to win gold at the Tokyo Olympics. Li used a unique stance to correct …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  APPLE AirDrop causes chaos on board packed flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3348557/apple-airdrop-threat-united-flight-passengers-photo-gun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PASSENGERS of a United flight were left terrified due to ”threat on board” after they received a photo of a gun via Apple’s AirDrop. The bizarre incident took place on Thursday wh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron pushes for Israeli inquiry into spyware...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/25/emmanuel-macron-pushes-for-israeli-inquiry-into-nso-spyware-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French president reportedly spoke to Naftali Bennett to ensure ‘proper investigation’ after Pegasus project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They had a date to kill the cow. So I stole her': How vegan activists are saving farm animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/24/how-vegan-activists-are-saving-spains-farm-animals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain may be famous for its love of meat – but sanctuaries across the country are coming to the rescue of its doomed cows, bulls, pigs, sheep and geese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Hospitalized radio host was outspoken skeptic...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2021/07/25/wtn-radio-host-phil-valentine-knows-he-very-sick-covid-19/8086143002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nashville radio host Phil Valentine, who in the past has been skeptical about vaccination against COVID-19, is now hospitalized with the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers link 'heavy wildfire smoke' to increased risk of contracting covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/news/2021/07/25/wildfire-smoke-increased-risk-contracting-covid-19/8086294002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are proposing that there is a link between air pollution and an increased risk of contracting COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump encourages MAGA to boo US women's soccer...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/tokyo-summer-olympics/trump-encourages-gop-crowd-to-boo-u-s-womens-soccer-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Olympics crossed over with a Donald Trump rally Saturday night, as the former president encouraged a hyped-up Phoenix crowd to boo the U.S. Women’s soccer team. The political action committee Turning Point Action sponsored the “Protect Our Elections Rally,” which turned into a wide-ranging attack on fellow Republicans, the military, the press, “woke” culture — and eventually U.S….</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASKETBALL ROBOT STEALS SHOW AT OLYMPICS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/25/scary-looking-robot-steals-the-show-at-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe all Team USA basketball needs is a robot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollution turns Argentina lake bright pink...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pollution-turns-argentina-lake-bright-210112998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lagoon in Argentina's southern Patagonia region has turned bright pink in a striking, but frightful phenomenon experts and activists blame on pollution by a chemical used to preserve prawns for export.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crist rips DeSantis over spike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/broward-charlie-crist-rips-gov-234400087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic gubernatorial hopeful Charlie Crist attacked Gov. Ron DeSantis on Sunday, accusing him of playing Republican presidential politics on the Texas border — while COVID-19 infections are rising and people are dying in Florida. During a campaign appearance in Broward County, Crist pointed to the recent increase in COVID-19 infections, hospitalizations and deaths. “You know what’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California man who mocked vaccine dies of virus...</title>
      <link>https://nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/california-man-who-mocked-covid-19-vaccine-dies-of-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who mocked COVID-19 vaccinations has died at a Los Angeles-area hospital after contracting the virus. Stephen Harmon was 34.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booster shots on horizon...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/commentary-covid-vaccine-booster-shot-pfizer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In today’s pharmaceutical universe, a simple “safe and effective” determination by the Food and Drug Administration to approve a drug can be manipulated to sell products of questionable value. And …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci warns going in wrong direction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-anthony-fauci-masks-70585010748808ce2284cfc19b608e47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — The United States is in an “unnecessary predicament” of soaring COVID-19 cases fueled by unvaccinated Americans and the virulent delta variant, the nation’s top infectious diseases expert said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swimming team does just fine without Phelps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-swimming-entertainment-sports-coronavirus-pandemic-99835fa2a33934f84035d1e7f225366f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Michael Phelps was up in his broadcast seat, a mere observer rather than the driving force of U.S. swimming. No need to fret about what he left behind. The Americans are off to a flying start at the Tokyo Aquatics Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ggymnasts, tired of sexualization, wears 'unitards'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-gymnastics-germany-unitard-7f5adad73b0a75d263b5d3f57c2f9bd0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The team’s outfits looked similar to the others in the room as the arena lights gleamed off crystals crisscrossing their chests and down their crimson and white sleeves. But the German gymnastics team’s new Olympic suits didn’t stop at their hips.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
