<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Men get postpartum depression too...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/men-get-postpartum-depression-too-2018-08-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New dads experience anxiety, loss of sleep and burnout at work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man showers naked in street after water main break...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/2018/08/11/naked-man-showers-outside-after-water-main-breaks-outside-columbus-home/967103002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk about a cheeky solution to his problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artists, fans push music festivals to tackle sex harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bfa5730a5c8e442390dc20260b12f9bd/Artists,-fans-push-music-festivals-to-tackle-sex-harassment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — When Emma Friedman went to her first rock festival at the age of 17, she was so excited to get to see bands she loved in a festival environment. But as she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 ferry workers suspended for pro-Trump flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/2-ferry-workers-suspended-for-week-for-pro-trump-flag/17762648/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials with North Carolina's ferry system have suspended a boat captain and crew member for a week after they hoisted a flag supporting President Donald Trump's re-election on a state-owned ship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting sex in sexagenarian: MADONNA still shocks at 60...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180812-putting-sex-sexagenarian-madonna-still-shocks-60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle plane stealer: 'Just a broken guy, got a few screws loose'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattlepi.com/seattlenews/article/Sea-Tac-airplane-stolen-crashed-13149228.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattlepi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 29-year-old man stole a Horizon Air passenger plane from Sea-Tac International Airport and took off on Friday night, circling the area for a short time and performing stunts while being chased by military jets before crashing near Tacoma.  The unnamed Pierce County man flying the Q400 twin-engine turboprop engaged in a lengthy back and forth negotiation with air traffic control where he mentioned not intending to land the aircraft, before the fiery crash on Ketron Island in North Pierce County, just south of Tacoma. There were reportedly no passengers or other personnel on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposes Cracks in Airport Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/horizon-air-employee-who-crashed-plane-didnt-have-pilots-license-1534018700</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday’s theft of a Horizon Air passenger plane from Seattle’s main airport exposed aviation vulnerabilities that persist even after efforts to enhance security after the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 shot in UK rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/722810/manchester-moss-side-shooting-england-uk-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pickup truck rams into Atlanta strip club...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/truck-rams-into-atlanta-gentlemen-club-police-say/BamNOvjUr8EwpOi4KuIH9O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pickup truck crashing into the front of a gentleman’s club around 1 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA launches historic probe to 'touch Sun'...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180812-nasa-launches-historic-probe-touch-sun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA spacecraft rockets toward sun for closest look yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nasa-spacecraft-rockets-toward-sun-073424219.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A NASA spacecraft zoomed toward the sun Sunday on an unprecedented quest to get closer to our star than anything ever sent before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Laureate V.S. Naipaul Dead at 85...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/nobel-laureate-v-s-naipaul-dies-at-85-1534038869</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;V.S. Naipaul, the Trinidad-born Nobel laureate, died Saturday at his London home, his family said. He was 85. His books explored colonialism and decolonization, exile and the struggles of the everyman in the developing world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bans don't seem to be lessening reach of Alex Jones, INFOWARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mystatesman.com/business/bans-don-seem-lessening-reach-alex-jones-infowars/Xo1jC96JodMuYqZDYMVQjO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mystatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the nation’s largest technology and social media companies have tried to stop Alex Jon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan vows to defy US 'threats' after currency crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-vows-defy-us-threats-currency-crash-131332606.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Recep Tayyip Erdogan vowed Saturday to defy US "threats" over a detained pastor, showing no signs of concessions in a bitter row that has caused the Turkish lira to crash. Relations between the two NATO allies have sunk to their lowest point in decades over a string of issues including</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives call for constitutional intervention last seen 230 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/11/conservatives-call-for-constitutional-convention-alec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers push for ‘constitutional convention’ to restrict federal government – and it’s not as far fetched as it sounds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyprogress.com/racialstrife/unite_the_right/inside-jason-kessler-s-rise-in-white-nationalist-movement/article_0dd0d0d6-9d84-11e8-a196-d711b92783fe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyprogress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. - Jason Kessler needed a friendly media outlet to vent and portray himself as a victim. So he dialed Stormfront Action, a white-nationalist online radio show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane stolen by 'suicidal' employee crashes near Seattle...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6049669/Commercial-airliner-hijacked-Seattle-Tacoma-Airport-say-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 76-seater Horizon Air turboprop Q400 took off at around 8pm, and two F-15 fighter jets scrambled 'minutes later' to intercept it, according to Pierce County Sheriff's Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy security...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3a42449af0f4abc86973f858ab2295d/Heavy-security-as-Charlottesville-anniversary-weekend-opens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. (AP) — Police blocked off streets and mobilized hundreds of officers for the anniversary of white supremacist violence in Charlottesville, Virginia. The secur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY ON  BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/11/with-turkey-crisis-erupting-bankers-gather-for-emergency-talks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan is showing no signs of backing down in a standoff with the U.S. that rattled markets. As investors worry about Turkey sliding toward a full-blown financial crisis, the big question now is how far the pain may spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The September Issue is dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/11/the-september-issue-is-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In years gone by, the September issue was the Super Bowl of fashion magazines. Fat with ads and glossy shoots cherry-picking the best looks of fall — the most important season in the fashion calend…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California super volcano swirling with magma...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1001733/california-volcano-USGS-Long-Valley-Caldera-supervolcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SUPER-VOLCANO in California which erupted with devastating results hundreds of thousands of years ago has a vast reservoir of semi-molten magma measuring a staggering 240 cubic MILES, a new study has suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: 20 shot in night; 'I'm scared to walk to store'...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-chicago-violence20180810-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 18-year-old was shot in the head and killed on the Southwest Side Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlottesville tense...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6049431/Authorities-ban-skateboards-bats-rocks-Charlottesville-rally-GUNS-permitted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is nothing to stop anyone bringing an actual gun, even an AR-15, to Charlottesville - the on-edge Virginia city as it marks the anniversary of last year’s deadly Unite the Right rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Braces For White Nationalist Rally...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/08/11/unite-the-right-2-rally-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Permits for Sunday’s “Unite the Right 2” rally indicated that about 400 demonstrators are expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final call...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6991591/seattle-plane-hijacker-reveals-why-stole-jet-final-call-before-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MECHANIC stole a plane from Seattle airport and joked with air traffic controllers before crashing into an island. The airport employee, 29, “hijacked” the plane before performing stu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chased by fighter jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/video/2018/aug/11/plane-stolen-from-seattle-airport-chased-by-fighter-jets-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plane has been stolen from Seattle-Tacoma international airport by an airline employee and crashed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charity says heat wave put flamingoes in the mood...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/british-charity-says-heat-wave-put-flamingoes-mood-135243122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A British conservation charity says record-breaking temperatures have encouraged a rare flock of Andean flamingos to lay eggs for the first time since 2003.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP Congressman suspends campaign amid insider trading allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/11/ny-gop-congressman-chris-collins-suspends-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Collins was arrested by federal agents Wednesday in Manhattan. Prosecutors accused him of illegal activity related to securities of Australian biotech company Innate Immunotherapeutics, on whose board of directors he served.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glyphosate under fire from San Fran to Sri Lanka...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/glyphosate-under-fire-san-francisco-sri-lanka-132906775.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glyphosate, the world's most widely used herbicide and the active ingredient in Monsanto's weedkiller Roundup, is the subject of fierce controversy all across the globe and is classified by the World Health Organization as "probably" being carcinogenic. A San Francisco court ordered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Town of 11 People, Mysterious Disappearance Turns Neighbor Against Neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/11/world/australia/larrimah-mystery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumors abound in a small outback town. Was Paddy Moriarty fed to a pet crocodile? Or could he have been baked into a meat pie?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight for FOX Local Sports Channels Could Shake Up Broadcasting...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/11/fight-for-fox-local-sports-channels-could-shake-up-broadcasting </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fight for Fox Local Sports Channels Could Shake Up Broadcasting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians involved in murder of Brazilian activist: govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180811-politicians-involved-murder-brazilian-activist-govt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay up or else: Spain warns of online 'sextortion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180811-pay-or-else-spain-warns-online-sextorsion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year in Paris as bad for health as smoking 183 cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180810-year-paris-bad-health-smoking-183-cigarettes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by the European Transport &amp; Environment association published on Friday confirmed that spending a few days in various popular European capitals is equivalent to smoking between one and four cigarettes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane stolen by 'suicidal' employee crashes near Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/701faeff7c7a44ab89b1186f6ffa63be/Plane-stolen-by-'suicidal'-employee-crashes-near-Seattle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATAC, Wash. (AP) — A "suicidal" airline employee stole an empty Horizon Air turboprop plane, took off from Sea-Tac International Airport and was chased by military jets before c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RELENTLESS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cbc36115f3c4dfda26693ffe1a2b5c8/Crews-battle-growing-wildfire-near-homes-in-California</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE ELSINORE, Calif. (AP) — Firefighters worked furiously Friday to keep a Southern California wildfire from burning more homes while crews in the north finally gained ground on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN ROCKET LIFTOFF! NASA GROUNDBREAKING MISSION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3c0d9bcef5904bf3a01717d66250cb3b/Last-minute-technical-problem-delays-NASA's-flight-to-sun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A last-minute technical problem Saturday delayed NASA's unprecedented flight to the sun.        The early morning launch countdown was halted wi</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
