<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Only Cowards And Sadists Support Persecution Of Assange'...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/johnstone-only-cowards-and-sadists-support-persecution-assange</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman doused with gasoline, set afire at TACO BELL...</title>
      <link>https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2019/10/23/tallahassee-police-searching-suspect-after-he-lights-woman-fire-taco-bell/4079126002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tallahassee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TPD has arrested a suspect who allegedly set a woman on fire Wednesday night at a Tallahassee Taco Bell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thirty-nine victims found dead in truck near London were Chinese...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-bodies/thirty-nine-victims-found-dead-in-truck-near-london-were-chinese-idUSKBN1X30OD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 39 people found dead in the back of a truck near London are believed to be C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracks emerging in Trump evangelical support...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/24/trump-evangelical-christian-support-056121</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large, fast-moving wildfire explodes in Sonoma County, prompting evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-23/kincade-fire-sonoma-county-prompts-evacuations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kincade fire is growing rapidly, and nearby residents have been advised to evacuate immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: MAJORITY OF AMERICANS WANT TO RE-WRITE FIRST AMENDMENT TO STOP 'HATE SPEECH'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/poll-majority-of-americans-want-to-re-write-first-amendment-to-stop-hate-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 per cent of Millennials says Constitution 'goes too far' in allowing free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Buying AR-15': MLB probes ump who threatened civil war over impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/MLB-investigates-umpire-who-reportedly-threatened-14558901.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As millions of fans prepared to watch the Washington Nationals obliterate the Houston Astros on Wednesday, a tweet posted by Major League Baseball umpire Rob Drake caught the attention of an ESPN reporter.  "I will be buying an AR-15 tomorrow, because if you impeach MY PRESIDENT this way, YOU WILL HAVE ANOTHER CIVAL WAR!!! #MAGA2020," the Arizona umpire tweeted late Tuesday, ESPN's Jeff Passan reported.  Drake deleted the tweet so quickly that a screen shot had not surfaced by early Thursday. It had accompanied another tweet that said: "You can't do an impeachment inquiry from the basement of Capital Hill without even a vote! What is going on in this country?"  MLB Commissioner Rob Manfred told ESPN the league was "looking into" the tweet referencing President Donald Trump and the House impeachment inquiry. The umpire has since deactivated his Twitter account.  The tweet was the second major off-the-field scandal to hit MLB during its biggest showcase of the year. On Saturday night, Astros Assistant General Manager Brandon Taubman taunted a group of female reporters about a Houston pitcher accused of domestic violence - an incident Sports Illustrated described as "offensive and frightening."  Drake, 50, who has been a full-time MLB ump since 2010, is perhaps best known for a 2011 altercation with St. Louis Cardinals catcher Yadier Molina, who was suspended for five games after bumping him and spraying him with spit. Drake co-founded "Calling For Christ," an umpire training academy in Arizona, where he lives, according to his official MLB profile.  The MLB and Drake did not immediately return a request for comment.  Drake's tweet suggesting violence over Trump's increasing political peril echoed a right-wing talking point that began on the extreme fringes of the political...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Warren opens up 7-point lead over Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/467231-warren-opens-up-7-point-lead-over-biden-nationally-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) has opened up a 7-point lead in the 2020 Democratic presidential primary, according to a Quinnipiac University poll released Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman shoved head-first into subway train...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/24/watch-brute-shoves-woman-head-first-into-subway-train-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shocking video shows a man shoving a woman into a train at a Brooklyn subway station Wednesday night in what appeared to be an unprovoked attack. The man, hopping up and down and screaming “What!…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin could decide race...</title>
      <link>