<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Taxes too high? Lots of Californians think so...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Taxes-too-high-A-lot-of-Californians-think-so-17083064.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With April 15, the traditional tax day, upon us, a new California poll shows that the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save energy and annoy Vlad, Vice-Chancellor says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-61117828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice-chancellor says they should use bikes and lower the thermostat to use less Russian gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental illness may raise risk of breakthrough virus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/prevention-cures/3269827-mental-illness-may-raise-risk-of-breakthrough-covid-19-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Story at a glance Researchers at the University of California, San Francisco looked at data from 263,697 U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs patients who had completed their vaccines and had at lea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How BARNES &amp; NOBLE Went From Villain to Hero...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/15/how-barnes-noble-went-from-villain-to-hero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years on the decline, Barnes &amp; Noble’s sales are up, its costs are down — and the same people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns USA against sending more arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-warns-us-arming-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diplomatic note used the same type of language Moscow has been offering for some time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penthouses in NKorea mainly for the unfortunate few...</title>
      <link>https://www.asiaone.com/asia/north-korea-penthouses-are-mainly-unfortunate-few</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiaone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL - For people in many countries, living in a penthouse is the dream. In North Korea? Not so much. Leader Kim Jong Un keeps building outwardly glamorous high-rise apartment buildings in the capital, Pyongyang, with the latest being an 80-storey skyscraper completed this week. But defectors and other North Koreans say that unreliable elevators and electricity, poor water supply,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Lee privately trashed 'my friend' Ted Cruz in texts to Mark Meadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mike-lee-privately-trashed-my-friend-ted-cruz-s-efforts-to-overturn-the-election-in-texts-to-mark-meadows/ar-AAWgcTg?cvid=e243d1bd1c9d447bbcfe1f9c17e327c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adopts 'poison pill' measure to thwart...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/15/tech/twitter-elon-musk-poison-pill/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter's board of directors has adopted a limited-term shareholder rights plan called a "poison pill" that could make it harder for Elon Musk to acquire the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow sends Washington formal diplomatic note...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/live/2022/apr/15/joe-biden-russia-ukraine-putin-us-politics-live-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow sends Washington ‘formal diplomatic note’ as Psaki says Biden is not planning to go to Ukraine – follow the day’s news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troop losses hit 20,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/5131995/video-ukrainian-vehicle-destroys-russian-tank-donetsk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the astonishing moment a Ukrainian armoured vehicle bravely takes on a vastly more powerful Russian tank in a ferocious firefight – and WINS. The astounding video filmed from a drone …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male porn star 'Sergeant Miles' arrested over Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5130739/porn-star-sergeant-miles-steven-capitol-riot-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PORN star and Iraq war veteran has blasted what he calls a “political witch hunt” after his arrest over the Capitol riot. Steven Miles – known by his stage name Sergeant Miles &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee wins $450K in lawsuit over unwanted birthday party...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/nation-world/national/article260445977.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He told his Kentucky company he did not want a birthday celebration, but they arranged one anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden shakes hands with thin air after North Carolina speech...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/14/biden-shakes-hands-with-thin-air-after-north-carolina-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden was left empty-handed following an address at a North Carolina university Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PUTIN HUMILIATION...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lost-warship-dents-russian-pride-150116721.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's loss of its flagship cruiser Moskva represents a dent in the operational capabilities of the Russian navy and a severe wound to Russian pride at the height of the war against Ukraine, analysts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE TV DECLARES WW3 'HAS ALREADY BEGUN'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/04/15/ukraine-russian-state-tv-warns-world-war-three-has-already-begun-16472787/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin has denied the ship was sunk by Ukraine's military but its propagandists are in meltdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai's covid siege: Food shortages, talking robots, starving animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/interactive/2022/china-shanghai-covid-lockdown-food-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than three weeks, China’s most populous city, Shanghai, has been under strict lockdown orders in an effort to control a coronavirus outbreak, leaving its 25 million residents trapped at home, struggling to feed themselves or get medical help for sick family members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia finds sympathy in Germany's east...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2022/04/15/germany-ukraine-communist-east-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Berlin faces calls to step up its support for Ukraine, attitudes in Saxony show competing pressures on German leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS POLICE VICIOUS IN SHANGHAI</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10721527/Shanghai-rises-against-Communist-Covid-chaos-residents-scuffle-hazmat-suited-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents in Shanghai have scuffled with hazmat-suited police who have ordered them to give up their homes to Covid patients, videos on social media show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK VS HOUSE OF SAUD...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestreet.com/technology/elon-musk-has-a-secret-code-to-silence-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire and one of the powerful Saudi princes are opponents in the fight for control of Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASTER TRAVEL CHAOS: Atlanta Airport terminal evacuated over 'bomb threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5132233/bomb-scare-hartsfield-jackson-airport-atlanta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN airport has been evacuated after a reported bomb threat caused travel chaos for travelers on Easter weekend. Law enforcement quickly evacuated Hartfield Jackson International Airport’s sou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER TWITTER FATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/14/elon-musk-not-sure-hell-be-able-to-buy-twitter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk's comments came hours after a regulatory filing revealed that he offered to acquire Twitter for $54.20 per share, or about $43 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's Black Sea flagship sinks in latest setback...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-kyiv-black-sea-estonia-8ccaa918f813a844321187ed116ff091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The flagship of Russia's Black Sea fleet, a guided-missile cruiser that became a potent target of Ukrainian defiance in the opening days of the war, sank Thursday after it was heavily damaged in the latest setback for Moscow's invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid false 2020 claims, Republican states eye voting system upgrade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-business-voting-campaign-2016-87e5516c1960c1eb0027e8d7c490b811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — For years, Tennessee Democratic Senate Minority Leader Jeff Yarbro’s call to require the state’s voting infrastructure to include a paper record of each ballot cast has been batted down in the Republican-dominated Legislature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid NYPD manhunt, subway shooting suspect ate lunch at KATZ'S Deli, walked in plain view of surveillance cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-subway-shooter-suspect-frank-james-katzs-mcdonalds-timeline-20220415-mdpqdevxzjgc3gvsznvduwt3my-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the NYPD and federal law enforcement scoured the city for the accused Brooklyn subway shooter on Wednesday, the burly suspect took in some of Manhattan’s culinary delights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine scanning faces of dead invaders, then contacting mothers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraine-is-scanning-faces-of-dead-russians-then-contacting-the-mothers/ar-AAWfxx8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feinstein pushes back on accounts she is mentally unfit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/feinstein-pushes-back-on-lawmakers-e2-80-99-accounts-that-she-is-mentally-unfit/ar-AAWfZ90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Mayor Lightfoot playing defense as she gears up for tough reelection campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/politics/ct-lightfoot-election-on-defense-20220414-2y7smof2szgnncunrg5ex7n3xq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As challengers line up to run for Chicago mayor, incumbent dealing with crime, union fights and difficulties forging good political relationships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momentum builds behind three-year degree to lower college costs...</title>
      <link>https://hechingerreport.org/momentum-builds-behind-a-way-to-lower-the-cost-of-college-a-degree-in-three-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hechingerreport.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skepticism about the cost and duration of a higher education drives a need for speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery sarcophagus found in Notre-Dame to be opened...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20220415/mystery-sarcophagus-found-under-fire-ravaged-notre-dame-to-be-opened/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious lead sarcophagus discovered in the bowels of Paris' Notre-Dame cathedral after it was devastated by a fire will soon be opened and its secrets revealed, French archaeologists said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GIRLS' at 10: In Defense of Dunham Genius...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/girls-10-defense-lena-dunham-085332497.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Collection Christophel / AlamyAs someone with a propensity for drama, one of my favorite ice-breaker questions is: “Who is your problematic fave?” In a time when absolutely no one in the public eye is blemish-free, it’s a revealing question. First off, it tells us what a person views as “problematic,” but also what they value and appreciate, to such an extent that they’re willing to overlook certain bad things about their “fave.” Everyone’s boundaries are different.My problematic fave is Lena Du</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising number of Californians say taxes too high...</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/news/taxes-too-high-lot-californians-110022062.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The share of California voters saying their taxes are too high has grown. A new poll comes amid inflation and many in the state feeling economic stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires eye parallel media universe...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/elon-musk-twitter-billionaires-free-speech-social-media-c74547a6-e51d-48fa-b2bd-3d7458f2adb4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech moguls willing to spend big on "free speech" crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANCE GROWS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-covid-lockdown-defiance-5bc6af77-e402-4d58-8616-729c75150679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Videos on social media show citizens scuffling with health workers and screaming in anger from their apartment windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Broken arrow' incident?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10721351/Ukraine-war-Fears-Moskva-warship-carrying-nuclear-weapons-sank.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Moskva - a 600ft Russian warship that sank yesterday in the Black Sea - could have been carrying two nuclear warheads when it went down, experts and analysts have warned today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem donor Buck sentenced to 30 years for fetish deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-los-angeles-86a598d03cfd44b139ad160f8a4f4e53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Ed Buck told his neighbors that the steady stream of young Black men leaving his West Hollywood apartment were social work clients. What really happened behind closed doors, which he referred to as the “gates of hell,” was far more sinister.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will This Warhol Become Most Expensive Artwork Ever Sold?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2022/04/will-this-warhol-become-the-most-expensive-artwork-ever-sold</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When one of the pop artist’s famed portraits of Marilyn Monroe goes to auction next month, some observers think it could fetch up to half a billion dollars. What is it about this particular work that gives it such potential to break the market?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China holds drills around Taiwan as U.S. lawmakers visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/15/china-holds-military-drills-around-taiwan-as-us-delegation-visits.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China said it conducted military drills around Taiwan on Friday, as a U.S. Congressional delegation visited the island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Memo Deepens Mystery of Possible Interstellar Visitor to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/15/military-memo-deepens-mystery-of-possible-interstellar-visitor-to-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early 2014, a dishwasher-size meteor dashed over the shores of Papua New Guinea before sunrise as it burned up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In France election, meaty issue unites Jews, Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-france-europe-paris-marine-le-pen-d77606f09df17415b94c273eb71be489</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — As she cooks lunch and talks politics, Jewish voter Sarah Gutmann has a nasty feeling — of would-be French president Marine Le Pen invading the privacy of her home, reaching directly into her life and the plates of chicken and kosher sausages that she is frying for her husband and their eldest son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Arizona man stuffed 183 animals in freezer, some alive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arrests-lizards-animals-turtles-snakes-20039b4f1dea6cfa24613f11f9d477f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOLDEN VALLEY, Ariz. (AP) — An Arizona man faces animal cruelty charges after 183 dead dogs, rabbits, birds and other animals were found in a freezer, including some that were apparently frozen while alive, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS COLLECT RECORD TAXES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/2121987000000-federal-tax-collections-set-record-through-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government collected a record $2,121,987,000,000 in total taxes through the first six months of fiscal 2022 (October through March), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wolf of Crypto: Belfort Marketing Self as Digital Currency Guru...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/15/the-wolf-of-crypto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH, Fla. — Jordan Belfort was lounging by the pool on a sunny April morning, sipping Red Bull and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Director Airs Concern He Might Turn to Nukes...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/14/c-i-a-director-airs-concern-that-putin-might-turn-to-nuclear-weapons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The director of the C.I.A. said on Thursday that Russian President Vladimir V. Putin’s “potential desperation” to extract</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS POLICE VICIOUS IN SHANGHAI</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10718709/Video-shows-cops-pin-arrest-Shanghai-locals-resist-homes-isolation-hubs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shanghai cops and health officials pinned down residents as they fought attempts to turn their homes into quarantine hubs. Videos circulated on Weibo before being deleted show scuffles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESISTANCE AT COVID CAMPS</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/jenniferatntd/status/1514619855340814337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Shooter Worked for AMAZON, DOORDASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gjgv/frank-james-nyc-subwayshooter-amazon-doordash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank James, accused of opening fire on a New York subway car, railed about working at Amazon in at least one of his hundreds of videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA astronauts not ready for deep space...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/14/nasa-artemis-moon-explorer-astronauts-00025099</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space agency still hasn't developed the training or equipment — even the space suits — needed to live and work on the moon and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To find out where pandemic is headed, look in sewer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/to-find-out-where-the-covid-pandemic-is-headed-look-here-the-sewer/ar-AAWe4eY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry, Meghan finally reunite with Queen amid family feud...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/04/14/prince-harry-meghan-markle-reunite-with-queen-prince-charles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sussexes have seen the Queen — and Prince Charles — together for the first time in more than 2 years, Page Six can confirm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense minister has 'massive heart attack not from natural causes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10718247/Putins-defence-minister-Sergei-Shoigu-massive-heart-attack-not-natural-causes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shoigu, Putin's right hand man and leader of the Russian army for a decade, was a mainstay in the early weeks of the war in Ukraine but recently disappeared from Kremlin briefings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem donor injected 2 men with fatal doses of drugs in sexually deviant pattern...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ed-buck-face-judgment-injecting-120014614.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Buck, once a fixture of West Hollywood's political scene, was sentenced to 30 years for drug and sex crimes that led to the deaths of two men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social-Media Campaign to Label Bucha Massacre 'Hoax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-wages-social-media-campaign-to-label-bucha-massacre-a-hoax/ar-AAWeCvR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, Lies, and UFOs: Pentagon Head of Counterintelligence and Security Ousted...</title>
      <link>https://thedebrief.org/sex-lies-and-ufos-pentagons-head-of-counterintelligence-and-security-ousted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedebrief.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Debrief's two year investigation into the Pentagon's recently ousted chief of counterintelligence, Afghan refugee evacuations, and UAP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Buck sentenced to 30 years for injecting two men with fatal doses of drugs in sexually deviant pattern...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/ed-buck-sentencing-west-hollywood-political-donor/11748027/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Democratic donor Ed Buck was sentenced to 30 years in prison in connection with the overdose deaths of two men in West Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Rose Back: Scores Major Interview with Warren Buffett...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/04/14/charlie-rose-is-back-former-cbs-pbs-newscaster-posts-in-depth-interview-with-warren-buffett</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver repeatedly runs over woman in road rage attack...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/14/driver-repeatedly-runs-over-woman-in-shocking-road-rage-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The harrowing footage captured Tuesday by a witness in Elizabeth shows the moment Vincent Jean, 56, drove his silver Mitsubishi SUV over the 23-year-old victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money for nothing: Receipt for 'invisible art' sells for $1.2M...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2022/apr/14/receipt-for-invisible-art-auction-yves-klein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A receipt written by the French artist Yves Klein auctioned by Sotheby’s in Paris has been hailed as a precursor to NFTs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare on N Train: Inside terrifying Brooklyn subway shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nightmare-on-the-n-train-inside-the-terrifying-moments-during-the-brooklyn-subway-shooting/ar-AAWdoFu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida pastors seek salvation in real estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/apr/14/miami-church-real-estate-first-presbyterian</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As membership plummets, church leaders are looking for new ways to make ends meet. Some congregants say they’re selling out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds cold-blooded execution of MICROSOFT exec...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10718831/Florida-widow-begs-help-finding-husbands-killer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police still have no leads after Jared Bridegan, 33, was gunned down on February 16 when he got out of his family's black Volkswagen Atlas in Jacksonville Beach to move a tire in the road.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
