<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NEW WAVE WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/lockdown-by-stealth-coming-in-as-people-shun-pubs-and-parties-1356747</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People appear to be putting off socialising to save their contacts for Christmas itself, heeding Professor Chris Whitty’s appeal to 'prioritise what matters'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies Try to Run Out Clock on Dems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/16/facing-subpoenas-trump-allies-try-to-run-out-the-clock-on-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — On Tuesday night, as the House prepared to hold Donald J. Trump’s former chief of staff Mark Meadows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area car owners leaving trunks open to avoid forced entry by thieves...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/trunk-open-car-break-in-why-not-to-leave-your/11344070/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaving your trunk open to deter car break-ins? Some auto owners in the Bay Area are trying it, but police warn this is a very bad idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With too few nurses, it won't take much to overwhelm system...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/12/09/with-too-few-nurses-it-wont-take-much-to-overwhelm-hospitals-this-winter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals nationwide are so short-staffed they’re unable to operate at full capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC FORECAST: 15,600 DEATHS PER WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10314687/CDC-issues-grim-forecast-warning-weekly-COVID-cases-jump-55-1-3-MILLION-Christmas-Day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC projects that the U.S. will record up to 1.3 million new COVID-19 cases during the week of Christmas, a 55 percent increase over current totals. It also predicts a sharp death increase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA broadens access to abortion pills as Supreme Court weighs Roe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/16/politics/medication-abortion-fda-supreme-court/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Food and Drug Administration announced Thursday that it is lifting a requirement that patients seeking medication abortion had to pick up the medication in-person, instead allowing pills to be sent by mail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vast study confirms rare heart risk from MODERNA jabbing...</title>
      <link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/overseas/12/17/21/vast-study-confirms-rare-heart-risk-from-moderna-jab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.abs-cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Moderna Covid jab carries a slight risk of usually non-serious heart problems a study of the entire population of Denmark found Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First salt, now SUGAR warnings coming to NYC menus...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/high-sugar-warnings-on-menus-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for high sugar warnings at restaurants in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida couple saw bees coming out of their shower; Massive beehive of 80,000 was in wall!</title>
      <link>https://people.com/pets/thousands-of-bees-found-in-florida-couples-shower-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Removing the insects and the 100 pounds of honey found with them took more than five hours and came at the cost of $800 — which was not covered by insurance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS SEARCH BALDWIN PHONE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/alec-baldwin-shooting-rust-search-warrant-cell-phone-police-halyna-hutchins-1234892657/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost two months after the fatal shooting of Rust cinematographer Halyna Hutchins by Alec Baldwin on the New Mexico set of low budget Western, Santa Fe police want to look at the Emmy winner’s iPh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 heart inflammation cases among young dosed kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/eight-heart-inflammation-cases-seen-174452995.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC had previously said that reporting rates of myocarditis for boys aged 16 to 17 could be more than 69 cases per million second doses administered and around 40 cases per million second doses in boys aged 12-15 years old. The CDC did not say whether it believes there is a link between the myocarditis cases and the vaccine, or disclose the rate of myocarditis in the age group without vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNARD GOLDBERG: Who will abandon FOXNEWS next?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/585791-who-will-abandon-fox-news-next</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Wallace was a Fox News star, someone who believed in the network’s one-time motto of “Fair and Balanced” coverage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL cracks down...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/12/16/nfl-covid-19-protocols-testing-out-masking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is amping up the league&amp;amp;#039;s COVID-19 protocols. Masking is required for everyone, but positive players can test out sooner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC warns NOT to get J&amp;J over blood clot risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10318751/CDC-panel-unanimously-recommends-Pfizer-Moderna-vaccine-instead-J-J.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Americans should be given the Pfizer or Moderna mRNA vaccines instead of the Johnson &amp; Johnson shot, U.S. health advisers recommended Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy begins kicking out 5,731 sailors; Army prepares to ax 3,800 soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10317305/Army-says-nearly-98-got-COVID-19-vaccine-deadline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Navy and Army each say 98% of their active-duty members have gotten at least one dose of COVID vaccine, but the last 2% have refused to comply with the order and will be discharged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court 'packing' commission member says adding justices dangerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10317471/Member-Bidens-Supreme-Court-packing-commission-says-adding-justices-dangerous-democracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of President Biden's Supreme Court commission broke ranks on Thursday to warn that increasing the number of justices would have a dangerous impact on justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ashley Biden Diary Made Its Way to 'VERITAS'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/16/how-ashley-bidens-diary-made-its-way-to-project-veritas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the final two months of the 2020 campaign, President Donald J. Trump, his grip on power slipping because of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaverse has groping problem -- already...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/12/16/1042516/the-metaverse-has-a-groping-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was sexually harassed on Meta’s VR social media platform. She’s not the first—and won’t be the last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC recommends others over J&amp;J due to clots...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/16/cdc-panel-prefers-pfizer-moderna-vaccines-over-jj-due-to-rare-blood-clot-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC has confirmed 54 cases of people developing blood clots and showing low blood platelet levels following J&amp;J vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Striking' jab resistance in variant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/16/columbia-university-finds-omicron-vaccine-resistance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study out of Columbia University says the Omicron variant is “markedly resistant” to vaccines and boosters might not do much to help, spelling bad news for the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cyber mercenaries' using FACEBOOK to spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211216-meta-targets-cyber-mercenaries-using-facebook-to-spy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook parent Meta announced Thursday the shutdown of some 1,500 accounts tied to "cyber mercenary" companies accused of spying on activists, dissidents and journalists worldwide on behalf of payin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parscale Probed...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/brad-parscale-says-jan-6-161701536.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom BrennerThe Jan. 6 Committee now appears to be looking into former Trump campaign manager Brad Parscale, with Parscale telling The Daily Beast late Wednesday night the committee investigating the attack on the Capitol had subpoenaed his phone records from November through January.Parscale said he had received a notice from his phone carrier earlier in the day and “just agreed.”“I had nothing to do with Jan. 6,” said Parscale, who has not played an active role in the campaign since a month bef</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers promise sensational revelations...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4282550/ghislaine-maxwell-sensational-revelations-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell is unlikely to testify in her sex trafficking trial — but her lawyers are promising sensational revelations in their bid to clear her. The British socialite, 59, is said to be “to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daredevil becomes first to fly in and out of active volcano...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/16/ex-chilean-pilot-becomes-first-person-to-fly-in-active-volcano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thrill-seeker jumped out of the chopper at an altitude of almost 2.2 miles and reached speeds of about 180 mph as he flew into and out of the 656-foot-wide crater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE RETIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2021/12/16/lowenthal-wont-seek-reelection-in-2022-1400288</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Long Beach Democrat said in a statement that he would not seek a sixth term in Congress, choosing instead to “pass the baton” and spend time with family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From blood clots to infected neurons, how virus threatens brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/12/16/1064594686/how-covid-threatens-the-brain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus that causes COVID-19 can cause strokes, inflammation, oxygen deprivation and infection in the brain. And each of these may lead to long-term neurological problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>103 Marines booted for refusing vax...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/103-marines-booted-refusing-covid-vaccine-services-begin/story?id=81793800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marines have discharged more than 100 Marines for refusing to take the COVID vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In profane rant, Nevada Rep. blames fellow liberals for competitive race...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/profane-rant-nevada-congresswoman-blames-fellow-democrats-competitive-race-n1286153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Titus suggested that Democrats could lose the three Nevada congressional seats they currently hold in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SEX AND CITY STAR' denies rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10317761/Sex-Citys-Chris-Noth-accused-sexual-assault-two-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allegations against the 67-year-old American actor were detailed in a new report from The Hollywood Reporter published on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Beware Prophecies of Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/beware-prophecies-of-civil-war/ar-AARS8eg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge grips NYC:  'Never seen this before'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/16/new-york-city-is-seeing-a-covid-surge-ahead-of-the-holidays-weve-never-seen-this-before.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's test positivity rate doubled in just three days, Dr. Jay Varma, a top health advisor to Mayor Bill de Blasio, tweeted Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone' Has Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/technology/2021/12/omicron-spike-nyc-explained.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron is spiking among a very specific group of people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Noth Accused of Sex Assault by 2 Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/chris-noth-accused-of-sexual-assault-1235063596/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Triggered by the recent 'Sex and the City' reboot, the women allege two incidents of misconduct they say took place more than a decade apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROADWAY shows cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.broadwayworld.com/article/Tonights-Performance-of-TINA-THE-TINA-TURNER-MUSICAL-Canceled-Due-to-Positive-Covid-Tests-Results-in-the-Company-20211216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.broadwayworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tonight’s performance of TINA – THE TINA TURNER MUSICAL (Thursday, December 16 at 7pm) is being canceled due to positive Covid-19 test results within the Broadway company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC, California, Hawaii Top List Of 'Safest States To Live' During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/safest-states-to-live-during-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprisingly, researchers find the safest place to avoid the virus isn't even a state -- it's Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER LAUNCHES DRIVERLESS FOOD DELIVERY...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/uber-eats-motional-driverless-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meal-kit deliveries will come via Motional’s all-electric Hyundai robotaxis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Could Be Freed In NY Rape Case, Appeals Court Indicates...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/harvey-weinsteins-rape-appeal-hearing-1234891904/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein’s 2020 rape conviction was under intense scrutiny today before an all-female bench of appeals court judges in New York. With terms including “overkill” and “that argument rubs me t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  Stop Culturally Appropriating Fishing Hats!</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/bassholes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop culturally appropriating, or, a meditation on the importance of fishing hats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK warns hospitalizations could exceed previous peaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/england-s-whitty-calls-for-limited-interactions-in-omicron-swell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Warns Omicron Hospitalizations Could Exceed Previous Peaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'To the Moon' Crash Is Coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kbx9b/the-to-the-moon-crash-is-coming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A longtime venture capitalist sees the religious dedication to Elon Musk, hype, and YOLO investing as almost a dot com-style pyramid scheme in the making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Beware Prophecies of Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2022/01/america-civil-war-prophecies/620850/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea that such a catastrophe is unavoidable in America is inflammatory and corrosive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The magazine story that made Elizabeth Holmes famous could now send her to prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-magazine-story-that-made-Elizabeth-Holmes-16706813.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The story was 5,500 words of pure rapture about a Silicon Valley company few had ever...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France says 110,000 fake health passes in circulation...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211216-france-says-110-000-fake-health-passes-in-circulation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 110,000 fake health passes are in circulation in France, the interior ministry said Thursday, with hundreds of investigations launched against makers and users of the forged documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's New Boom Towns...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/16/americas-new-boom-towns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic’s economic impact was sudden, and the turn toward recovery has been complicated. Now as new Covid-19 variants emerge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copeland is wealthiest pastor in America. So why does he live in tax-free mansion?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10315223/Americas-wealthiest-pastor-Kenneth-Copeland-whos-worth-760M-dodges-150K-annual-property-tax.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Copeland, 85, enjoys the spoils of his six-bed, six-bath house - with a sweeping spiral staircase, crystal chandeliers and a tennis court - on the taxpayers' dime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jail Where Epstein Found Dead Reckons With Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/jail-where-jeffrey-epstein-hanged-himself-reckons-with-future-1.1696789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few hundred feet from Ghislaine Maxwell’s sex-trafficking trial is the dark, shuttered jail where her onetime boyfriend Jeffrey Epstein hanged himself and left her to answer for their alleged crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans flocking to Mar-a-Lago to pay for privilege of hosting events...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/GOP-candidates-are-flocking-to-Mar-a-Lago-to-pay-16706428.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As his guests sampled short ribs and chocolate cake at a Dec. 1 reception held in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen axes pre-Xmas party...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/queen-elizabeth-cancels-pre-christmas-lunch-with-family-palace-source-2021-12-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth has cancelled a pre-Christmas lunch with her family as a precaution while cases of COVID-19 soar in Britain, a Buckingham Palace source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania Joins Crypto Frenzy With Release of First NFT...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/melania-trump-joins-crypto-frenzy-with-release-of-first-nft/ar-AARSqqC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Limping Toward End of Year as Divisions Roil Agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-limping-toward-end-of-year-as-divisions-roil-agenda/ar-AARRFiJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In suit, radio host Ramsey's former employee says he was told to 'pray away' covid before being fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/In-lawsuit-radio-host-Dave-Ramsey-s-former-16706441.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days after Tennessee Republican Gov. Bill Lee declared a state of emergency in March 2020...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoE becomes first major central bank to raise rates since pandemic...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211216124646-kgj0x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-BOE/ (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-BoE becomes first major central bank to raise rates since pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA records most hurricane-force gusts in single day...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211216111939-6jtr4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/STORM (PIX):U.S. records most hurricane-force gusts in a single day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salvadoran drag queen emerges as colorful presidential critic...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211215192616-rm3bl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL SALVADOR-POLITICS/LADY DRAG (PIX, TV):Salvadoran drag queen emerges as a colorful presidential critic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Music Acts Seeing 20% No-Show Rates at Concerts...</title>
      <link>/https://www.wsj.com/articles/major-music-acts-are-seeing-20-no-show-rates-at-concerts-11639663201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawl breaks out on train over masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/uk-news/4283658/face-mask-row-brawl-on-train-furious-passengers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FACE mask row on a train sparked a massive brawl between furious passengers and left kids in tears. The fight broke out after a man wearing a white face mask started shouting at other passengers,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Hell: 1 In 3 Skipping Vital Medical Care Due To Cost...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/skipping-vital-medical-care-cost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even 20 percent of the country's highest earners say the cost of seeing a doctor keeps them from seeking treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline exec says coverings 'don't add much' on flights...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/transportation/586072-airline-executive-says-masks-dont-add-much-on-flights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines CEO Gary Kelly told a U.S. Senate panel on Wednesday that the air in passenger jets' cabins is so clean that face masks "don't add much" additional protection against the spread of COVID-19 on planes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron infects 70 times faster than previous strains...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/586074-omicon-infects-70-times-faster-than-previous-covid-strains-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study says that while the COVID-19 omicron variant infects the human body 70 times faster than previous coronavirus strains, the infections appear to be less severe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK SURGE WARNING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-travel-business-9eb16609e108037b165f71059aa2face</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Spiraling infections in Britain driven in part by the new omicron variant of the coronavirus  sent shockwaves Thursday into the rest of Europe, fueling a familiar dread that tighter restrictions will scuttle holiday plans again this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jittery Ukrainian villagers 'fear big war will start'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-russia-ukraine-57128337f35c21976933463c3b5cdd7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEVELSKE, Ukraine (AP) — Liudmyla Momot wipes away tears as she searches for clothes and household items to salvage from the ruins of her home that was shelled by Russia-backed separatists in eastern Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby discovered inside woman's LIVER ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4280704/rare-ectopic-pregnancy-liver-woman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BABY was discovered growing inside a woman’s liver in an “extremely rare” ectopic pregnancy, a doctor has revealed. Paediatrician Michael Narvey, of Children’s Hospital Research…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court orders Virginia hospital to allow outside physician to provide ivermectin to covid patient...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/coronavirus/coronavirus-in-virginia/judge-rules-hospital-cant-block-treatment-of-covid-19-with-ivermectin/2909936/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Virginia hospital can’t stand in the way of a family’s preference to be treated for COVID-19 with the drug ivermectin, which is not approved for treating the virus, a judge ruled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photojournalist sues to block subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/586062-photographer-sues-to-block-subpoena-from-jan-6-committee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freelance photojournalist filed a lawsuit against the House Jan. 6 committee on Wednesday, seeking to block a subpoena requesting her phone records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports leagues facing crisis...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/586042-us-sports-leagues-facing-covid-19-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professional sports leagues across the U.S. are dealing with a COVID-19 crisis, as a rash of cases is forcing the NHL and NBA to postpone games, and NFL teams to scramble to fill roster spots for absent players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DA's last big decision: Whether to charge Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-manhattan-donald-trump-cyrus-vance-jr-2a8fb1e013858ed5dd1edf4f7096663a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — After a dozen years in office, one piece of unfinished business remains for Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance Jr. before he retires at the end of the month: Will the prosecutor known for his caution go out with a bang by bringing criminal charges against Donald Trump?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Brothers in Arms Plotted Theft, Sale of Army Weaponry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-business-florida-north-carolina-theft-5fe1ad681d89dfc063c1d0d10b95b870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Packed with rifles and explosives, the SUV hurtled down a Florida interstate beneath bright blue autumn skies, passing other motorists with little notice. It was November 2018, and the driver, Tyler Sumlin, was uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland hospitals near capacity...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/As-covid-cases-rise-in-the-region-Maryland-16706012.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sole hospital in one Southern Maryland county is at capacity. The number of covid-19...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingraham defends Jan. 6 reaction, but there's difference between on-air and private comments...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Ingraham-defends-Jan-6-reaction-but-there-s-a-16705402.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, we got evidence that some of the most prominent figures who have tried to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC weighs limits on J&amp;J vax over blood clots...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/cdc-advisers-to-weigh-limits-on-johnson-johnson-vaccine-because-of-continued-blood-clot-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine advisers to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention will weigh possible limits on the use of the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine because of continued blood clot issues, mostly in young and middle-aged women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY appeals court calls Manhattan DA's 'pile on' case against Weinstein 'overkill'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/manhattan/ny-harvey-weinstein-first-department-appeal-overkill-manhattan-da-20211216-rnrzm5odxzbnvovdp6f4g5qiki-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Weinstein’s trial, the judge and a juror sabotaged the Hollywood mogul’s chances of getting a fair shake, Weinstein’s lawyer Barry Kamins told the Appellate Division, First Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In policy shift, Fed projects three interest rate hikes in '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/in-policy-shift-the-fed-projects-three-interest-rate-hikes-in-2022/ar-AARQL2a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMICRON UPENDS PANDEMIC RULES</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/How-omicron-is-changing-the-rules-of-the-covid-19-16706358.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic playbook is, once again, being torn up. In the course of just a few weeks,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAGUARS fire coach Urban Meyer amid season filled with controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32879774/urban-meyer-jacksonville-jaguars-head-coach-rocky-first-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jacksonville Jaguars have fired head coach Urban Meyer, bringing an end to a one-year tenure filled with missteps on and off the field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid huge shortage, new truck drivers train for some of supply chain's toughest jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Amid-huge-shortage-new-truck-drivers-train-for-16706379.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCHNECKSVILLE, Pa. - The tractor-trailer lurches into gear. As the student driver turns...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware That Nocebo Strapped to Your Wrist...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/wrist-size-fitness-gadgets-make-for-great-gifts-but-beware-of-the-nocebo-effect</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beware That Nocebo Strapped to Your Wrist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOSTER MANDATES BEGIN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/americans-split-on-what-it-means-to-be-fully-vaccinated-543a12fe-41ce-4321-bcae-309606e3f5ff.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are completely split on what it means to be fully vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado 'Critical'...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/colorado-hospitals-critical-covid-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients with other ailments are frustrated, and nurses and doctors are stressed and burned out, as unvaccinated covid-19 patients fill ICU and acute care beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen Sells Music Catalog for $500 Million!</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/15/bruce-springsteen-sells-music-catalog-in-massive-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Springsteen has sold his music rights to Sony Music Entertainment in what may well be the biggest transaction ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Role as Trump gatekeeper puts Meadows in legal peril...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/role-as-trumps-gatekeeper-puts-meadows-in-legal-peril-and-at-odds-with-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Meadows' proximity as Donald Trump's former gatekeeper and top aide has thrust Meadows into legal jeopardy — even as revelations in texts from the former president's son and in his new book also threaten his standing with Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail sales disappoint in November; Inflation tamping down spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/retail-sales-disappoint-in-november-raising-concerns-that-inflation-is-tamping-down-on-spending/ar-AARQlEW?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Debt Equals $287,859 Per Household...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/index.php/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-debt-equals-about-287859-income-tax-paying-household</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the debt limit lifted, the federal debt will take a jump upward, then keep steadily climbing, constantly increasing the burden on future taxpayers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGHEST EVER DAILY COVID CASES IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/15/uk-reports-highest-number-of-daily-covid-cases-since-pandemic-began.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.K. reported a record number of new daily Covid cases on Wednesday, with 78,610 in the last 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy fires laser weapon in Mideast amid drone boat threat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-dubai-united-arab-emirates-yemen-15630a25f448cb6100818286bc9c9de5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The U.S. Navy announced Wednesday it tested a laser weapon and destroyed a floating target in the Mideast, a system that could be used to counter bomb-laden drone boats deployed by Yemen's Houthi rebels in the Red Sea.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
