<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA to have 3rd shot ready by fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-vaccine-booster-shots-moderna-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A booster shot could provide extra protection against COVID-19 variants, according to drugmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Ramsey company sued for alleged religious discrimination, 'cult-like' atmosphere...</title>
      <link>https://religionnews.com/2021/04/15/former-employee-sues-dave-ramseys-company-for-alleged-religious-discrimination-cult-like-atmosphere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;religionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — The lawsuit claims employees have to submit to Ramsey as a spiritual leader and agree with his views on COVID-19, with no questions allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potholes, graffiti, broken streetlights: Lebanon's crumbling capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210418-potholes-graffiti-broken-streetlights-lebanon-s-crumbling-capital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Potholes, graffiti, broken streetlights: Lebanon's crumbling capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JITTERS:  NYPD confiscates T-shirt gun mounted to rapper's HUMMER...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/17/nypd-confiscates-t-shirt-gun-mounted-to-rappers-hummer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe he’s humming a different tune now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed patrol group tries to keep peace...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-death-of-daunte-wright-police-minnesota-death-of-george-floyd-49c1cf08ab54f3863c1ba3b0e1557a4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOKLYN CENTER, Minn. (AP) — As protests intensified in the Minneapolis suburb where a police officer fatally shot Daunte Wright, a group of Black men joined the crowd intent on keeping the peace...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest American Dead at 116...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/features/producers-picks/hester-ford-dies-at-116/275-fec0a906-3788-4199-b3d8-11d85f73bd03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hester Ford had 12 children, 48 grandchildren, 108 great-grandchildren, and approximately 120 great-great-grandchildren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers hiring again -- but struggling to find workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/ajcjobs/employers-are-hiring-again-but-struggling-to-find-workers/VU7GFRW4K5F4JINJFNP5DL3534/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia job listings are rising as the economy gains momentum, but employers say they're struggling to fill positions despite hundreds of thousands in the jobless ranks. The reasons are likely many.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India's capital under siege...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210418084050-ki5mf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/INDIA (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-'Dire need of beds, oxygen': India's capital under siege from COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT reporter seeks help in finding missing DEUTSCHE BANK source...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-news/iran-shows-off-dozens-of-drones-in-military-parade-665482&gt;&lt;i&gt;Shows off dozens of drones in military parade...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters tells Minnesota BLM protesters 'to get more confrontational'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9483471/Fury-Maxine-Waters-tells-Minnesota-BLM-protesters-weve-got-confrontational.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday marked the seventh night of protests in Brooklyn Center, Minnesota, where skirmishes broke out between police and protesters on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic good Samaritan faces hefty tax bill for his efforts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/connecticut-philanthropy-holidays-covid-19-pandemic-coronavirus-pandemic-1a54d5ca4736d5dbd9d4810fb394d991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANSFIELD, Conn. (AP) — A Connecticut middle school teacher who raised $41,000 to help hundreds of his struggling neighbors during the COVID-19 pandemic got an unwelcome surprise for his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABBA Bjorn Ulvaeus urges reforms to pay songwriters their due...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/abbas-bjorn-ulvaeus-urges-reforms-061748099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Covid-19 pandemic's rampage through the music world has laid bare the industry's flaws, shining a bright light on "the plight of songwriters," says ABBA's Bjorn Ulvaeus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT reporter seeks help in finding missing DEUTSCHE BANK source...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/new-york-times-journalist-deutsche-bank-source-missing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A journalist issued an urgent plea on Friday seeking help to find Val Broeksmit, the adopted son of the late Deutsche Bank executive William Broeksmit who has cooperated with investigators looking into the bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 400 migrant families to be released PER DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/400-migrant-families-released-per-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration anticipates that it will be releasing 400 migrant families into the country a day by mid-June as the influx of people encountered illegally crossing the border overwhelms its detention capacity, according to a government planning document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran state television names suspect in Natanz nuclear facility attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/17/iran-names-suspect-in-natanz-nuclear-plant-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State television identifies suspect in 11 April sabotage as 43-year-old Reza Karimi and vows to repatriate him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI ethicist: Robots can be our partners...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/apr/17/ai-ethicist-kate-darling-robots-can-be-our-partners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MIT researcher says that for humans to flourish we must move beyond thinking of robots as potential future competitors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two blocks from Federal Reserve, a growing encampment of homeless grips  economy's most powerful person...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Two-blocks-from-the-Federal-Reserve-a-growing-16108882.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As he drove past the intersection of 21st and E streets in Northwest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockdowns allowed resentment to grow, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/fedex-killings-mark-return-mass-workplace-shootings-paused-pandemic-n1264355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shutdowns resulted in fewer incidents but allowed resentment to grow, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIM TOO?  Scott Rudin steps aside amid accusations of abusive behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/broadway-producer-scott-rudin-steps-aside-amid-accusations-of-abusive-behavior-going-back-decades-apologizes-for-pain-he-caused/ar-BB1fL3G2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he cedes control, a string of hits will be left in the hands of others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC chairwoman under pressure to show more independence from Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/rnc-chairwoman-ronna-mcdaniel-comes-under-pressure-to-show-more-independence-from-trump/ar-BB1fKWuB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some party committee members want the GOP to create some distance from the former president — or at least grapple with the fact that Republicans lost the White House, Senate and House during his administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police balk at new edict as Ontario brings in emergency measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/police-balk-at-new-edict-as-ontario-brings-in-emergency-measures/ar-BB1fLetA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ontario Premier Doug Ford said he had no choice but to impose some of North America’s toughest restrictions to curb a sharp rise in Covid-19 cases. Some police forces have pushed back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo, wife made more than 100 personal requests of State Dept employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article250736474.html#cardLink=row1_card1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report details over 100 instances of misconduct that “had no apparent connection to the official business of the Department.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RECORD SMASHED:  AMAZON spending $465 million for just single season of 'LORD OF THE RINGS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/amazons-lord-of-the-rings-cost-465-million-one-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The highly anticipated fantasy series will cost far more than previous record-breaking estimates: "This will be the largest television series ever made."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions with Ukraine soar as diplomats expelled....</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210417-russia-ukraine-expel-diplomats-as-tensions-soar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia, Ukraine expel diplomats as tensions soar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Philip laid to rest as somber queen sits alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9481659/Prince-Philip-funeral-Mourners-arrive-Queen-prepares-bid-farewell-Duke-Edinburgh.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her Majesty looked grief-stricken and bowed her head in reverence as she accompanied her beloved Philip's coffin on its final journey as their eldest son Prince Charles cried as he walked behind the casket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House faces pressure to act after string of mass shootings...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/White-House-faces-pressure-to-act-after-string-of-16108602.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists are seizing on the most recent spate of deadly shootings to try to disrupt the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Space Junk New Tragedy of Commons...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/space-junk-like-overfishing-and-pollution-is-a-global-tragedy-of-the-commons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space Junk Is Our New Tragedy of the Commons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Hill's far right pushes 'Anglo-Saxon' values, European architecture...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/america-first-anglo-saxon-marjorie-taylor-greene-e6dbc363-7352-47a7-8d4a-ae90d9ba7090.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group says it will "follow in President Trump’s footsteps."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Keefe vows revenge on CNN and TWITTER after ban...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/17/james-okeefe-vows-revenge-on-cnn-and-twitter-after-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James O’Keefe of Project Veritas, a day after being permanently banned from Twitter, says he is preparing to launch a legal broadside against Big Tech and the mainstream media. “We&amp;#821…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars producers lift lid on nearly 'impossible' ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oscars-producers-lift-lid-nearly-205219007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "teeny-tiny" red carpet, no invitations for Hollywood's most powerful moguls, and a "central" role for masks -- next weekend's in-person Oscars are taking no risks when it comes to Covid-19, but the event still would have been "impossible" to hold just weeks earlier, producers said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Narcocat' intercepted with drug delivery for prison...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/narcocat-intercepted-drug-delivery-panama-205222179.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Panama on Friday intercepted an unlikely smuggler, a fluffy white cat, bearing an assortment of drugs in a pouch tied to its body as it tried to enter a prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida variant cases explode after springbreak...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-covid-variant-cases-explode-214900295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One month after the peak of Florida’s spring break, the number of residents infected with more infectious mutated strains of COVID-19 has exploded, rising six-fold since mid-March and leaving 122 people hospitalized. The information, disclosed in response to a lawsuit by the Orlando Sentinel against the Florida Department of Health, shows the total as of Thursday reached 5,177 cases involving ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hits golf course for first time in presidency...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-hits-golf-course-first-185657645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden played golf for the first time in his presidency Saturday, hitting the fairways in his home city of Wilmington -- and taking a page from his golf-obsessed predecessor Donald Trump's book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Days Without Donald on TWITTER: Nation Scrolls More Calmly...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/17/100-days-without-trump-on-twitter-a-nation-scrolls-more-calmly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That soothing sound that Gary Cavalli hears emanating from Twitter these days? It is the sound of silence — specifically,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin critic Navalny could 'die any minute'...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/kremlin-critic-navalny-could-suffer-142541946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jailed Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny risks cardiac arrest at "any minute" as his health has rapidly deteriorated, doctors warned Saturday, urging immediate access to Russia's most famous prisoner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulator warns of death by PELOTON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/product-safety-be5516665f9a2c7c4bb9b9441d4aef01</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Safety regulators warned people with kids and pets Saturday to immediately stop using a treadmill made by Peloton after one child died and others were injured. The U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OREGON 'PERMANENT' MASK RULE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-oregon-6f7f919d27644d02c330da5a8648af95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — As states around the country lift COVID-19 restrictions, Oregon is poised to go the opposite direction — and many residents are fuming about it. A top health official...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
