<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Media Turn: Golden Boy Now 'Problematic'...</title>
      <link>https://thebulwark.com/the-beto-woke-wars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O’Rourke has become problematic. O’Rourke was 2018’s progressive golden boy, with record breaking small-dollar fundraising, a viral defense of kneeling NFL players, and the love of Richard Linklater. His merch littered the enclaves of liberal America. From Coachella to Crown Heights, you were more likely to see a Beto tee or yard sign than …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underpaid?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/2019/03/19/mike-trout-baseballs-million-man-is-actually-underpaid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best player in the game — even at a total dollar figure no one else has approached, let alone exceeded — remains vastly underpaid relative to his performance-value within the sport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist Joins Sanders As Senior Aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/03/sanders-promised-civility-hired-twitter-attack-dog/585259/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Sirota had been working unofficially for Sanders while savaging the other Democratic candidates on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigate woman who misgendered trans in tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/19/devout-catholic-interviewed-police-trans-twitter-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A devout Catholic and mother of five has been asked to attend a police interview after being accused of using the wrong pronoun to describe a transgender girl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid bumpiness threatens NASA plan to scoop sample...</title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-00859-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nature.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA mission finds asteroid Bennu littered with big boulders and spraying out particles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAX BITE: If California resident, will pocket LESS THAN HALF!</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2019/03/19/mike-trout-extension-contract-angels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assuming the numbers are accurate, what will he pocket?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Refuses Resignation of Cardinal Convicted of Sex Abuse Cover Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pope-francis-declines-to-accept-french-cardinals-resignation-11553007071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has declined to accept the resignation of a French cardinal convicted of covering up sex abuse, a decision likely to draw fire from sex abuse victims and their advocates in France and abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi dismisses pro-impeachment critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/03/19/nancy-pelosi-impeachment-gift-donald-trump-without-gop-support/3211241002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some progressives have "wanted to impeach the president since the day he got elected," House Speaker Nancy Pelosi told USA TODAY.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds suicide of beloved Obama, Clinton adviser...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6826927/Alan-Krueger-killed-release-sixth-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alan Krueger, 58, had a new book coming out in June and was still a member of faculty at Princeton University in New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paid $500,000 by company linked to Russian oligarch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/michael-cohen-search-warrant-documents-dle/h_9fa9cacd52cc615892712d6513b96a0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cohen materials outline how in October 2016 Essential Consultants was established, and then how in January 2017, money began to flow in monthly from Columbus Nova LLC. The monthly installments were for $83,333 and totaled $583,332 from January, 2017 to August 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii bills push 1st state ban on plastics in restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/hawaii-bills-push-1st-state-ban-on-plastics-in-restaurants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KOMO 4 TV provides news, sports, weather and local event coverage in the Seattle, Washington area including Bellevue, Redmond, Renton, Kent, Tacoma, Bremerton, SeaTac, Auburn, Mercer Island, Bothell, Shoreline, Lynnwood, Mill Creek and Everett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-AOL Boss Gets $60 Million Exiting VERIZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tim-armstrong-former-aol-boss-getting-more-than-60-million-as-he-exits-verizon-11553014033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Armstrong, the former leader of AOL, is walking away with more than $60 million as he leaves Verizon Communications, which recently wrote down half the value of the internet business he led.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cotton swab stuck in ear led to seizures, skull infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/health/cotton-swab-stuck-ear-led-man-suffer-seizures-skull-infection-t150611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors have been warning for years to avoid using cotton swabs to clean ears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump endorses Bolsonaro at White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-brazil/trump-endorses-bolsonaro-at-white-house-mulls-bringing-brazil-into-nato-idUSKCN1R01VV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump gave Brazil's new far-right leader Jair Bolsona...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's AMLO vows not to seek re-election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190319-mexicos-amlo-vows-not-seek-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's AMLO vows not to seek re-election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA-backed forces celebrate 'victory'; ISIS 'caliphate' reduced...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6825363/U-S-backed-SDF-says-captured-157-militants-foreigners.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials from the Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF) were seen singing and dancing and giving 'V for victory' signs as they returned from the frontline in Baghouz in the country's east.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY ENDING: Prosecutors Offer to Drop Charges Against PATRIOTS Owner Bob Kraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/florida-prosecutors-offer-to-drop-charges-against-patriots-owner-robert-kraft-11553014972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida prosecutors have offered to drop charges against New England Patriots owner Robert Kraft and a number of other men charged with soliciting prostitution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt tightens restrictions on media...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1540f1133267485db356db1e58db985b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — Egypt's top media regulator on Tuesday put into effect tighter restrictions that allow the state to block websites and even social media accounts with over 5,000 followers if they are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes uphold no bail ICE detention for serious criminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/19/supreme-court-upholds-ice-detention-without-bail-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigrants with serious criminal records can be held without bail while awaiting deportation even if ICE didn’t immediately pick them up when they were released from prison or jail, the Supreme Court ruled Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visiting NKorea? Publisher offers guidebook...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190319-visiting-north-korea-french-publisher-offers-guidebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visiting North Korea? French publisher offers guidebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Into America's Spiritual Void With Marianne Williamson...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/katherinemiller/marianne-williamson-president-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential campaigns can poll at zero and still have something interesting to say about America. In Iowa on the trail with Marianne Williamson, who helped shape today's conversation about spirituality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runaway cow wreaks traffic havoc on NYC highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Cow-on-Major-Deegan-Causes-Traffic-Jam-507354651.html?fff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once again, a cow has taken over the streets of New York City - this time running wild on the Major Deegan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge scolds man who torched girlfriend to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article228083034.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMERICAN IDOL' Ratings Hit New Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/voice-beats-american-idol-tv-ratings-monday-march-18-2019-1195622</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Idol' hits series lows for either ABC or Fox in its first head-to-head matchup of the season with NBC's singing competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schultz to be featured in FOXNEWS town hall... </title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/434726-howard-schultz-to-be-featured-in-fox-news-town-hall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News announced Tuesday it will host a town hall with former Starbucks CEO and potential 2020 presidential candidate Howard Schultz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities move to shut down 'national puppy laundering ring'...</title>
      <link>https://herald-review.com/news/state-and-regional/authorities-move-to-shut-down-national-puppy-laundering-ring-with/article_f12a0c8d-01a6-5308-a751-53506391a7e5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;herald-review.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — An alleged "national puppy laundering ring" that supplied dogs to Chicago pet shops could be shut down following a Chicago Tribune report last year that exposed how the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JELLY BELLY Already Sold Out Of New CBD-Infused Candy...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/03/19/cbd-jelly-belly-jelly-beans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannabis confections are all the rage now that CBD oil is increasing in popularity. The creator Jelly Belly jelly beans is jumping on the bandwagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK BLOCKS TRUMP DIGITAL CZAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/facebook-blocks-trumps-social-media-chief-no-reason-given</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook abruptly censored the account of President Trump’s chief social media guru, blocking him for simply responding to a question from a reader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best, worst airlines ranked...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2019/03/19/best-airlines-delta-alaska-southwest-united-worst-airlines-frontier-spirit-allegiant-jetblue/3200926002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta led this year's list, edging out Alaska Airlines, the leader the past two years, and Southwest Airlines, the largest domestic carrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers who took on Big Tobacco now going after realtors and 6% commission...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/big-name-lawsuit-could-upend-realtors-and-their-6-fee-2019-03-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new class-action lawsuit takes aim at real estate agents and the tools they use to do business, and housing industry watchers say it could revolutionize...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE:  1 million illegals with final deportation orders --  still remain in country...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/arent-deporting-illegal-aliens-already-deportation-orders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total number of illegal aliens who remain in the country despite final deportation orders is 1,009,550.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos: Swarm of painted lady butterflies fill sky in California during migration...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/photos-swarm-of-painted-lady-butterflies-fill-the-sky-during-migration/70007734</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Pitches More than $100 Trillion in New Spending During CNN Townhall...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-sen-warren-pitches-more-100-trillion-new-spending-during-bri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From universal childcare to slavery reparations to the Green New Deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Star Set to Ink $430 MILLION contract; Largest in sports history...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/26306935/sources-angels-trout-reach-430m-extension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-time AL MVP Mike Trout is close to smashing the record for the largest contract in professional sports history, as he's finalizing a new 12-year deal with the Angels worth more than $430 million, sources told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LORD OF THE AMAZON: BEZOS LAUNCHES ROBOT DRAGONFLY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/19/jeff-bezos-hosts-mars-2019-with-flying-robots-blue-origin-engine.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conference is designed to be a showcase for the latest and quirkiest technology in the fields of machine learning, robotics and space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top antitrust Dem calls on FTC to probe FACEBOOK market dominance...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/434678-top-antitrust-dem-calls-on-ftc-to-probe-facebooks-market-dominance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. David Cicilline (D-N.J.), the chairman of the House antitrust subcommittee, on Tuesday called for the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) to probe whether Facebook has violated U.S. antitrust laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto minivan tour risks being too nice for anti-Trump party...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/article_1d2d8e71-0c5f-5b67-a0e2-8cb8eb57f951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His youthful vigor allows him to hop onto coffee house counters in a single bound and drive himself to campaign events, but Beto O’Rourke may be lacking a qualification some</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kazakhstan's long-ruling president to resign after three decades in power...</title>
      <link>https://eurasianet.org/kazakhstans-leader-resigns-after-almost-30-years-in-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eurasianet.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though he is stepping down as head of state, Nazarbayev will retain a wide-ranging degree of authority under his bespoke title of Leader of the Nation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese-Americans see ghost of communism in leftward turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/damn-socialism-why-are-you-chasing-me-chinese-americans-see-ghost-of-communism-in-democrats-leftward-turn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRVINE, Calif.— When Saga Zhou first moved to the United States from China in 2009, she steered clear of politics. The Communist Party rules supreme in China, so most Chinese immigrants bring a built-in aversion to political involvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat cannibalism: Report discloses 'questionable' gov't animal experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/cat-cannibalism-report-discloses-questionable-gov-t-animal-experiments-n984546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of dead animals were bought from China, Vietnam and elsewhere for use in research on lab cats back home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Opens Fire on Kellyanne Husband: 'Total Loser'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-opens-fire-on-kellyanne-conways-husband-a-total-loser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested at airport with human embryo...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-47621526 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in Mumbai, India, believe they may have uncovered a smuggling ring linked to a clinic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records show FBI was probing Michael Cohen long before raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/63b58a572f844f11889610f04ee4ad1d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The FBI was investigating President Donald Trump's former personal attorney and fixer for nearly a year before agents raided his home and office, documents released Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sees 'North-South axis' of power in budding relationship with Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article228101904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More households subscribe to streaming than traditional TV, according to report...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-deloitte-touche-report-20190318-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The finding underscores the continued popularity of services like Netflix, Hulu and Amazon Prime, which all offer original series and movies as well as content licensed from other studios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theater staging 'Mein Kampf' play...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/OMG/Warsaw-theater-staging-Mein-Kampf-play-583915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The play's director said he wants to show that the language used today "is worse than the language of Hitler."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fascist' perfume, flatulent hippo: War for Israel election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190319-fascist-perfume-flatulent-hippo-social-media-war-israel-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Fascist' perfume, flatulent hippo: social media war for Israel election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as trophy hunter seen killing sleeping lion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6824509/Outpouring-disgust-trophy-hunter-seen-creeping-sleeping-lion-shooting-it.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC CONTENT Video shared on social media shows a trophy hunter shooting and killing a sleeping lion and then being congratulated on the kill. The man's identity is not known.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt offering $1,000 to anyone adopting wild horse...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/434661-federal-government-offering-1000-to-anyone-adopting-a-wild-horse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bureau of Land Management (BLM) said it will offer up to $1,000 to anyone who adopts a wild horse in an effort to “encourage more adopters to give a wild horse or burro a good home.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People want higher taxes on rich, better welfare: 21-country OECD survey...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190319112743-3136f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OECD-RISKS/:People want higher taxes on rich, better welfare - 21-country OECD survey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Hotels Mushroom in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-hotels-mushroom-in-miami-11552993200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotel construction is booming in Miami thanks partly to the growing appeal of the city’s downtown district and the flocking of well-heeled tourists to South Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron sacks police chief; 'Yellow vest' demos face ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20190318/french-government-bans-demos-and-sacks-paris-police-chief-after-weekends-yellow-vest-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French Prime Minister has announced a package of measures aimed at preventing further violence linked to 'yellow vest' protests, including replacing the Paris chief of police and a ban on demos on the Champs-Elysées if radical protesters are present.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS spokesman calls on followers to 'take revenge' for mosque attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-new-zealand-shooting-christchurch-mosque-attack-syria-a8829246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformative Trips New Midlife Crisis Splurge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/transformative-trips-are-the-new-midlife-crisis-splurge#gs.25jcco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transformative Trips Are the New Midlife Crisis Splurge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How old is too old?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-presidential-race-old-too-old-011621237.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a septuagenarian president preparing his re-election bid, and two likely main challengers in their late seventies by 2020, Americans are facing an inevitable question: does age matter in White House politics? Donald Trump, the oldest person ever elected US president, will be 74 on Inauguration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physicist: 'Science does not kill God'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/physicist-marcelo-gleiser-science-does-not-kill-god-090100672.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Templeton Prize, which recognizes outstanding contributions to "affirming life's spiritual dimension," was awarded Tuesday to Brazilian Marcelo Gleiser -- a theoretical physicist dedicated to demonstrating science and religion are not enemies. A physics and astronomy professor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths, jail and cyber spies: Dangers of dissent in Thailand...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deaths-jail-cyber-spies-dangers-dissent-thailand-014110711.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dead dissidents dumped in a river, activists knotted up by the courts, and Big Brother-style internet laws -- critics of Thailand's junta fear this week's election is poised to sharpen the dangers faced by those who disagree. Scores of dissidents, academics and "Red Shirt" activists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROCKETMAN' begins blast off as star reveals first footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2019/03/19/elton-john-rocketman-first-footage-taron-egerton/3203401002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Taron Egerton and producer David Furnish showed off the first footage from the Elton John musical "Rocketman" at the historic Troubadour club Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case for Investigating FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/19/opinion/facebook-antitrust-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why I am calling on the Federal Trade Commission to investigate Facebook for violating antitrust laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado joins effort to elect presidents by popular vote, go around Electoral College...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/colorado-joins-effort-to-elect-presidents-by-popular-vote-skip-electoral-college</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado has become the latest state — and the first swing state — to join a group that would go around the electoral college.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING's liability for 737 MAX hinges on investigations...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/boeing-s-liability-for-max-hinges-on-crash-and-oversight/article_74c24d80-60bf-5d51-a927-a6a5f2272b0d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The fatal crashes of two Boeing Co. 737 Max jets and the fleet’s worldwide grounding have triggered a complicated scramble regarding legal liability involving the manufacturer, airlines and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese's 'THE IRISHMAN' could show in IMAX theaters, if NETFLIX loosens its grip...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/11/the-irishman-could-show-in-imax-theaters-if-netflix-losens-its-grip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Scorsese's "The Irishman" could come to IMAX theaters, if Netflix makes concessions about how long it's willing to let the film play in theaters before bringing it to its streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN SIGNS 'FAKE NEWS' LAW!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/insulting-putin-may-now-land-you-in-jail-under-new-russian-law#gs.240i61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin signed laws punishing online media and individuals for spreading â€˜fake newsâ€™ thatâ€™s insulting to Russian officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG  Barr tries to restore confidence in Justice Dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2187121?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- In his first month in office, Attorney General William Barr has sent a reassuring message to the beleaguered Justice Department -- he wants a return to basics after years of disruptive firings, tweet storms and scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE RACE:  Andrew Yang draws campaign crowd of 3,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/SF-meets-Andrew-Yang-a-presidential-candidate-13693316.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Yang proposes a $1,000-a-month “freedom dividend” to every adult in America — he spoke in SF, drawing some 3,000 supporters who heard him warn about how artificial intelligence and robotics are taking jobs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE FALLS: WARNER BROS. CEO Out Amid Sex-Misconduct Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/warner-bros-kevin-tsujihara-exit-as-studio-chief-1054951</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He has led the Burbank studio since 2013.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promises universal basic income, news czar...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/829377/andrew-yang-ross-perot-millennials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yang's maverick populist wonkery is just what the Democrats need</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Textalayzer': Nevada considers tech to scan phones after crashes...</title>
      <link>https://news3lv.com/news/local/textalayzer-nevada-legislature-considers-technology-to-scan-phones-after-crashes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news3lv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A legislative proposal could make Nevada one of the first states to allow police to use a contentious technology to find out if a person was using a cellphone during a car crash. The measure is igniting privacy concerns and has led lawmakers to question the practicality of the technology, even while acknowledging the threat of distracted driving. It would let police use a device known as the "textalyzer" that connects to a cellphone and looks for user activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkhorse to get spotlight on Dem debate stage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/andrew-yang-pete-buttigieg-democratic-debates-164137300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech entrepreneur Andrew Yang and South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg are primed to use a new rule for qualifying to earn their way onto the presidential debate stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun charge filed against man who  shot himself in the penis...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/below-the-belt-gun-charge-762958</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 18--The Indiana man who accidentally shot himself in the penis and scrotum has been charged with carrying a handgun without a license, according to court records. Mark Anthony Jones, 46, is fac</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 71% SAY ECONOMY IN GOOD SHAPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/18/politics/cnn-poll-trump-economy-tech/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans give the nation's economy glowing reviews in a new CNN Poll conducted by SSRS, and Donald Trump's approval rating may be reaping the benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Angels of sky' offer flights into, out of flooded Nebraska city...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2bef48225ebc40c8906591212d31e4cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nebraska city walled off by massive flooding is getting a big lift from private pilots who are offering free flights to shuttle stranded residents to and from their hometown. Flooding from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Meteor' turns evening 'bright and warm' in Siberia...</title>
      <link>https://siberiantimes.com/other/others/news/a-meteor-turns-evening-bright-and-warm-in-the-north-of-siberia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;siberiantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico town becomes 'sanctuary city for unborn'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/new-mexico-town-becomes-sanctuary-city-for-the-unborn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifesitenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City Council of Roswell, New Mexico passed a resolution in support of 'fetal life.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman Sues TWITTER, Handful of Users...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nunes-files-bombshell-defamation-suit-against-twitter-seeks-250m-for-anti-conservative-shadow-bans-smears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California GOP Rep. Devin Nunes filed a major lawsuit seeking $250 million in compensatory damages and $350,000 in punitive damages against Twitter and a handful of its users on Monday, accusing the social media site of "shadow-banning conservatives" including himself to influence the 2018 elections, explicitly and systematically censoring opposing viewpoints and "ignoring" lawful complaints of repeated abusive behavior.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
