<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Fight Rodgers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/scientists-fight-a-new-source-of-vaccine-misinformation-aaron-rodgers/ar-AAQt5nn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correction: November 8, 2021 An earlier version of this article misstated the length of Aaron Rodgers's career. He is playing in his 17th season, not his 16th. This spring, he was auditioning to be the host of “Jeopardy!” Nearly every day, he pops up on television ads for national brands like State Farm insurance. And on Sundays this fall, he has led the Green Bay Packers to a division-best 7-2 record. Quarterback Aaron Rodgers is not just the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo refutes theories giraffes died from jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/conspiracy-theory-giraffe-deaths-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conspiracy theorists are falsely claiming that three giraffes at the Dallas zoo died after receiving the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY:  'Far be it from me to tell anyone what to put in their body'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/09/tom-brady-uses-aaron-rodgers-covid-vaccine-drama-to-sell-tb12-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never miss an opportunity to sell. Even if that opportunity is being asked about Aaron Rodgers’ decision not to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vermont now 1st state to require condoms in all middle schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vermont-is-now-1st-state-to-require-access-to-condoms-in-all-middle-and-high-schools/ar-AAQvTCP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The law was created in an effort to prevent sexually transmitted diseases and unintended pregnancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon general warns against memes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/surgeon-general-warns-against-memes-misleading-graphs-cherry-picked-stats-health-misinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. surgeon general released a brochure this week warning against misleading memes and graphs online in an effort to stamp out “health misinformation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Informers key in enforcing Biden mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/9/informers-key-in-enforcing-biden-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To enforce President Joe Biden’s forthcoming COVID-19 mandate, the U.S. Labor Department is going to need a lot of help. Its Occupational Safety and Health Administration doesn’t have nearly enough workplace safety inspectors to do the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City OKs GOOGLE data centers amid secrecy, water worries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-the-dalles-oregon-droughts-62b3774442293497ceb2306a606471af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — The council of a small Oregon city has approved a deal with Google that will enable the technology giant to build two more water-guzzling data centers there, though some residents worry about drought and secrecy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland says Putin masterminding border crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59226226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of migrants are at the Belarus-Poland border, camping in cold and dangerous conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media users could disable algorithms in new proposal...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211109202619-ww2p2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TECH/LEGISLATION:Social media users could disable algorithms in new U.S. proposal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public allowed at Tomb of Unknown for first time in 100 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/politics/tomb-of-the-unknown-soldier-centennial-commemoration/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in nearly a century, members of the public will be able to walk on the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier plaza and lay flowers before the sacred memorial site in Arlington National Cemetery on Tuesday and Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metallurgist admits faking steel test results for US Navy subs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-59186655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A metallurgist has pleaded guilty to fraud after faking the results of strength tests on steel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 shots and 1 booster later, this man has little protection against Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/health/immunocompromised-covid-19-booster-wellness-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials are recommending third and even fourth shots to boost Covid resistance for people with certain conditions, but that hasn't eased the fears for some immunocompromised people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz Prepares To Jump Into Pennsylvania Senate Race...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/dr-oz-prepares-to-jump-into-pennsylvania-senate-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Mehmet Oz is preparing to jump into Pennsylvania Senate race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop Who Left Clergy for Erotica Writer Accused of Being 'Possessed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3vgw7/bishop-who-left-clergy-for-erotica-writer-accused-of-being-possessed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Bishop Xavier Novell reportedly began a new job at Semen Cardona, a company which produces and exports high-quality pig semen to over 20 countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans have never been in so much debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/economy/fed-household-debt-inflation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American households are carrying record amounts of debt as home and auto prices surge, Covid infections continue to fall and people get out their credit cards again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faced with soaring Ds and Fs, schools ditch old way of grading...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/faced-soaring-ds-fs-schools-130030318.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pandemic-forced school closures revealed how grade-point systems hurt disadvantaged children, prompting educators to look for ways to bring equity to grading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Evidence' from witness who 'saw Prince Andrew groping Virginia Roberts' to air in new doc...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4031231/prince-andrew-virginia-roberts-witness-evidence-documentary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE witness who says he saw Prince Andrew grope Virginia Roberts is set to make bombshell claims in a new documentary. Jeffrey Epstein’s former telecoms specialist Steve Scully is set to give his e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's taxpayer-funded political machine...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trumps-taxpayer-funded-hatch-act-13-f2cc1a45-163b-4c3d-b967-bff294478534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hatch Act bars the use of taxpayer resources for partisan politicking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of red UK phone boxes to be protected from closure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-technology-business-europe-c729398ca506057a1739a9f3bdc6bac9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thousands of Britain’s iconic red phone boxes will be protected from removal under new rules, the U.K.'s telecommunications regulator said Tuesday. The public payphone boxes may look like obsolete relics in an age of ubiquitous smartphones, but regulator Ofcom said they can still be a “lifeline” for people in need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE: People under 30 should not get MODERNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/covid-19-people-under-30-should-not-get-moderna-vaccine-france-684457</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna Inc applied for European authorization of its COVID-19 vaccine in children aged 6-11 years, weeks after it delayed a similar filing with US regulators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BLOOD SACRIFICE'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4030813/astroworld-travis-scott-satanic-ritual-conspiracy-theories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRACKPOT conspiracy theorists have sensationally claimed that the tragic deaths of eight people at Travis Scott’s “hellish” Astroworld concert last week came as part of a “s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER CEO: People who spread vax misinfo are 'criminals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/covid-vaccines-pfizer-ceo-says-people-who-spread-misinformation-on-shots-are-criminals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They're criminals because they have literally cost millions of lives," Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuser details 'sex assault' allegations against CNN's Don Lemon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/08/accuser-details-sex-assault-allegations-against-cnns-don-lemon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dustin Hice, who accused CNN’s Dom Lemon of assaulting him in a Hamptons bar three years ago, claimed that the alleged behavior could be part of a “pattern.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switched Before Birth: Couple Suing Clinic After IVF Mixup Leads to Wrong Baby...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/08/it-was-truly-my-hell-couple-files-lawsuit-after-ivf-mishap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles couple is suing the California Center for Reproductive Health for in vitro fertilization after they learned the baby they had birthed and raised was not theirs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going To Bed At 10 P.M. May Save Life?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/bedtime-heart-health-10-pm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team finds that even bedtimes earlier than 10 p.m. increased the risk of cardiovascular disease in adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate, angry, destructive: How Americans morphed into mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desperate-angry-destructive-how-americans-morphed-into-a-mob/ar-AAQuRIB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What we know about the people who stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook Pumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/09/apple-ceo-tim-cook-says-he-owns-cryptocurrency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook dismissed suggestions that Apple might take cryptocurrency in exchange for products or buy it with corporate funds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Squid coin to memes, 'Wild West' of crypto...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/squid-coin-memes-wild-west-154732160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a dodgy digital currency inspired by Netflix hit "Squid Game" to highly-volatile dog-themed coins, the cryptocurrency sector has become riskier than ever as it soars in value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID hospitalizations rising in California, a potentially ominous sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/covid-19-hospitalizations-rising-in-parts-of-california-a-potentially-ominous-sign/ar-AAQuNrG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 hospitalizations have risen significantly in the Inland Empire and Central Valley, bringing new concerns about whether the shift represents a precursor to a wider spike in COVID-19 in California as the winter holidays approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin, Ether Hit Records Amid Broad Rally in Cryptocurrencies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-ether-hit-records-amid-broad-rally-in-cryptocurrencies/ar-AAQtaeT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin and Ether hit all-time highs amid a broad rally in financial assets that some analysts attributed partly to the search for a hedge against inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAKE BREAKS SILENCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/drake-astroworld-statement-1235044619/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper featured during Travis Scott's set that later led to a crush and the death of eight people and injuries to many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now scale one of NYC's tallest skyscrapers: No walls, no railings..</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/news/local-news/manhattan/you-can-now-scale-one-of-nycs-tallest-skyscrapers-no-walls-no-glass-windows-no-railings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It gives thrill-seekers a unique perspective on New York that no observation deck could hope to match:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Producer prices rise 8.6%, matching record high...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-producer-prices-prices-inflation-economy-56eee45eace6035280f7d3b0fe932bdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Inflation at the wholesale level rose 8.6% last month from a year earlier, matching September's record annual gain and offering more evidence that inflationary pressures are not yet easing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: The 'F*cking Idiot' Who Ran Final Days of Trump White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/the-fcking-idiot-who-ran-the-final-days-of-trumps-white-house-5-craziest-details-from-jon-karls-new-tell-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic's just-published excerpt of Jon Karl's new behind-the-scenes account of the final days of the Trump White House features no shortage of bonkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWSUITS MULTIPLYING...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/million-dollar-lawsuits-against-travis-232007082.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter @Onacasella via ReutersThe lawsuits against Grammy-nominated rapper Travis Scott and Astroworld organizers and promoters are piling up.The lawsuits collectively point at gross negligence on behalf of Scott, event organizers, and NRG Park venue managers, alleging they failed to keep the Houston festival’s roughly 50,000 attendees under control, resulting in the deaths of eight people and injuries to many more when the packed crowd surged forward within minutes of Scott’s performance begin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules UNITED AIRLINES can mandate shots for employees...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/580671-judge-rules-united-airlines-can-mandate-vaccine-for-employees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas federal judge ruled on Monday that United Airlines can mandate its employees be vaccinated against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Speculation Swirls Over Newsom Disappearance...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/09/wheres-gov-gavin-newsom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks ago, Gov. Gavin Newsom announced he would be leading a delegation to the U.N. climate change summit in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LED ZEPPELIN molested teen with fish, book reveals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/09/led-zeppelin-molested-groupie-with-fish-book-reveals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Spitz’s new book “Led Zeppelin: The Biography” details a disturbing sexual incident involving a 17-year-old groupie and some fish in 1969.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nightmare' IVF mix-up leaves couple giving birth to other family's baby...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nightmare-ivf-mix-leaves-l-231314461.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles husband and wife have sued a fertility clinic and its medical director after lab tests confirmed they and another couple had given birth to each other's babies after their embryos were mixed up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History teacher told students Donald was still president. She's been removed from school...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-history-teacher-told-her-students-trump-was-still-president-she-s-been-removed-from-the-school/ar-AAQuO6p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The teacher has been removed from the California middle school, and leaders say they're taking steps to "ensure that this does not happen again."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest restrictions in New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211109-thousands-protest-covid-restrictions-in-new-zealand</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of demonstrators marched on the New Zealand parliament to protest against Covid-19 restrictions Tuesday, prompting a major police deployment at the Wellington building known as the Beehive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says warned off US drones during war games...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211109-iran-says-warned-off-two-us-drones-during-war-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's military warned off two US drones which overflew waters where it was holding naval war games near the strategic Strait of Hormuz this week, state media reported Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's unvaccinated defiant as rules tighten...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211109-in-a-corner-germany-s-unvaccinated-defiant-as-rules-tighten</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The eastern German state of Saxony may have ordered tough curbs on the unvaccinated to push them to get the Covid-19 jab, but shop assistant Sabine Lonnatzsch, 59, is unmoved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orban Locks In Prosecutor Ally Before Close Hungary Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/orban-to-lock-in-prosecutor-ally-before-close-hungarian-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orban to Lock In Prosecutor Ally Before Close Hungarian Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  TRAVIS SCOTT WARNED BEFORE TOOK STAGE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211109021136-bz6uk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEXAS-SECURITY/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Police chief met with rapper before stampede that killed 8 at Houston concert</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why 310 of ROBINHOOD's 7 Million Cyber-Attack Victims Should Be Worried...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-310-robinhoods-7-million-054515371.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Robinhood Markets Inc. announced on Monday an embarrassing security breach that exposed the personal information of millions of its users, which will be of particular concern to the 300 or so customers who suffered the worst privacy compromise.Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesWhere Did All the Public Bathrooms Go?COP26 Protests: Inflatable Cows, Megaphones and a RainbowThe Rising Pacific Forces a Native Village to Move. Who Wil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA NAVY NOW WORLD'S LARGEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/8/chinas-navy-now-worlds-largest-460-warships-2030-p/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s navy is now the world’s largest maritime military force and will deploy 460 warships by the end of the decade, according to the Pentagon’s latest annual report on Chinese military power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS unmasks supporters terrifying election officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/usa-election-threats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement has taken little action over threats to election officials. Reuters tracked down 9 of the harassers. All admitted sending threats. Most were unrepentant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Wyden Son Trashes Him: Why Does He Hate American Dream So Much?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/democratic-sen-wydens-son-trashes-him-on-twitter-why-does-he-hate-the-american-dream-so-much/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ron Wyden's (D-OR) son took to Twitter on Sunday to take aim at his father's proposed tax policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter challenges coming for White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/580640-winter-challenges-are-coming-for-biden-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is facing a challenging winter.Supply chain bottlenecks spurred by increased demand threaten to hold up Christmas gifts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trucker Shortage Still Biggest Kink in Supply Chain...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/09/the-biggest-kink-in-americas-supply-chain-not-enough-truckers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Facing more than $50,000 in student debt, Michael Gary dropped out of college and took a truck driving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Wallen banned from CMAs. Will voters pick his album?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/arts-entertainment/2021/11/08/cma-awards-morgan-wallen-dangerous-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Morgan Wallen, one of the biggest stars in country music, had his music temporarily pulled from the radio and was briefly suspended from his record label when TMZ published a video of him saying the n-word. But he's still nominated at the CMA Awards, and we asked voters how they plan to handle it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAVE OF SATANIC CONSPIRACY THEORIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/nov/09/astroworld-disaster-fuels-wave-of-satanic-conspiracy-theories-on-tiktok</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claims highlight how ‘digital natives’ are susceptible to viral misinformation despite their savvy reputation, experts say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: 'Abjectly stupid' man who betrays base, lies to them...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/ann-coulter-donald-trump-andrew-sullivan-dishcast-border-wall-abjectly-stupid-1647314</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative commentator accused the ex-president of betraying his base and criticized him for not delivering on his much promised border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Rep. Gosar tweets video showing him killing AOC, attacking Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/rep-paul-gosar-tweets-photoshopped-anime-video-showing-him-killing-rep-ocasio-cortez-and-attacking-president-biden/ar-AAQsHfD </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTIGATIONS WIDEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/us/houston-astroworld-festival-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers for the Day N Music Festival announced late Monday rapper Travis Scott will no longer perform at this weekend's event in Las Vegas following the deadly crowd surge at Houston's Astroworld Festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German infection rate highest since pandemic began!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211108081712-7d8fo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-German coronavirus infection rate hits highest since pandemic began</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Warns of Peril in Run-Up of Risky Asset Prices, Stablecoins...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-warns-risky-asset-prices-210000547.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan 6 investigators subpoena Trump associates...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/08/jan-6-committee-subpoenas-trump-allies-520315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest batch targets a mix of people who worked on Donald Trump’s campaign and others who strategized how to overturn election results from the outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe who? Obama star power still dominates world stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/joe-who-obama-e2-80-99s-star-power-still-dominates-the-world-stage/ar-AAQtHGf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Obama's appearance at COP26 showed, the former president's enduring popularity is both a blessing and a curse for Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot Roast Can Set You Back $100 as Meatflation Hits Shoppers...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/economy/a-pot-roast-can-set-you-back-100-as-meatflation-hits-shoppers-2671892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pot Roast Can Set You Back $100 as Meatflation Hits Shoppers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin sees his power grow...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/580647-manchin-sees-his-power-grow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) may be the most powerful member of the Senate and his leverage in the fight over President Biden's social spending and climate agenda has increased in the past week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brainard Interviewed by Biden for Fed Chair as Search Heats Up...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brainard-interviewed-biden-fed-chair-015628655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard was interviewed for the top job at the U.S. central bank when she visited the White House last week, according to people familiar with the discussions, signaling that Chair Jerome Powell has a serious rival as President Joe Biden considers who will lead the Fed for the next four years.Powell and Brainard are the only people who have publicly surfaced as being in the running for chair. Powell’s current term in that post expires in February and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Gore's Latest Solution To 'Climate Change': Mass Surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/watch-al-gores-latest-solution-climate-change-mass-surveillance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Reporting Requirement Sparks Backlash From Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90694594/irs-6050i-crypto-infrastructure-explained</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry groups are concerned about a ‘digital assets’ provision that may require reporting cryptocurrency transactions to the Internal Revenue Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  50-State List of Top Tax Rates Under Dem Bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/50-state-list-top-tax-rates-under-democrat-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the Democrats' tax-and-spend reconciliation bill is enacted, the average top tax rate on personal income would rise to 57.4 percent, according to the Tax Foundation.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;This would give the U.S. the highest tax rate in the developed world, and stick all 50 states with a combined federal-state tax rate higher than 50 percent.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;The combined federal and state top marginal income tax rates for each state under the Democrat bill are listed below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS-ROYCE to make mini nuclear reactors...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/nov/08/rolls-royce-secures-450m-for-mini-nuclear-reactors-venture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineering firm to proceed with rollout after UK government agrees to match consortium’s investment</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
