<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Math nerds enter mapping process that could sway power in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/math-nerds-enter-mapping-process-that-could-sway-power-in-washington/article_76cb9022-c67a-5d52-9123-794f84f06955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State judges bedeviled by weirdly shaped and obviously partisan congressional district maps can now get expert help from an unusual source: math nerds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Biden Agenda in Limbo, Dems Work to Sell Unfinished Promise...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/with-biden-agenda-in-limbo-democrats-work-to-sell-an-unfinished-promise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALLENTOWN, Pa. — When Representative Susan Wild, Democrat of Pennsylvania, accompanied Jill Biden, the first lady, to the Learning Hub,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Are Americans growing warier of more govt just as Joe tries to pass big agenda?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Are-Americans-growing-warier-of-more-government-16537889.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A year ago, as Americans were casting their votes for president, the effects...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HALLOWEEN KILLS' Heads for $50M Opening Despite Dual Streaming Launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/halloween-kills-box-office-opening-last-duel-1235032467/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The slasher film is having no trouble defeating James Bond pic 'No Time to Die' while Ridley Scott's historical epic 'The Last Duel' is bombing in its debut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK CONFRONTS NEW EPISODE OF TERRORISM...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/with-lawmakers-killing-the-u-k-confronts-a-new-episode-of-terrorism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Prime Minister Boris Johnson and other British leaders paid their respects on Saturday morning at a church east</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman raped on train as bystanders did nothing, police say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-arrests-pennsylvania-philadelphia-1d0c62ae547165eabfc40fc6a20f25be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPPER DARBY, Pa. (AP) — A woman was raped by a stranger on a commuter train in suburban Philadelphia in the presence of other riders who a police official said “should have done something." Superintendent Timothy Bernhardt of the Upper Darby Police Department said officers were called to the 69th Street terminal around 10 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNVAXXED GERMANS BANNED FROM FOOD STORES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20211015/supermarkets-in-german-state-of-hesse-can-now-block-entry-to-the-unvaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supermarkets in Frankfurt and the surrounding region can now implement rules that only allow vaccinated and Covid-recovered people onto their premises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine's court-martial highlights military straining to deal with partisan politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Marine-s-court-martial-highlights-the-military-16537739.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMP LEJEUNE, N.C. - When a Marine officer who repeatedly disrespected senior officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Picks Lag...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-e2-80-99s-picks-lag-cheney-gop-incumbents-in-fundraising/ar-AAPAhri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three House Republicans targeted by former President Donald Trump raised more money in the third quarter than his hand-picked candidates to defeat them, according to Federal Election Commission filings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Quants Could Disrupt Process That Sways Power in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/math-quants-could-disrupt-process-that-sways-power-in-washington-1.1667150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State judges bedeviled by weirdly shaped and obviously partisan congressional district maps can now get expert help from an unusual source: math nerds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov Abbott, DeSantis Compete for National Limelight...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/republican-governor-frenemies-compete-for-national-limelight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Governor ‘Frenemies’ Compete for National Limelight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Parts: Cars Stuck at Garages for WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/car-parts-shortages-are-hitting-u-s-garages-creating-weeks-long-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cars Get Stuck at U.S. Garages for Weeks in Spare-Parts Shortage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax stand-off between Chicago mayor, police hits courts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-vaccine-stand-off-between-073631289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago judge on Friday banned a police union president from making public statements on the city's Covid-19 policy as a stand-off over vaccine mandates sparked dueling lawsuits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After months in lockdown, a weary world is ready to dance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-cuba-4d54c5429b5238d2d1c086290881d4fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in the depths of the pandemic -- even when the world locked down, leaving billions isolated and desolated -- there were those who danced. “I did not stop dancing for a second,” says Federico Carrizo, who competed in the Tango World Championship in Buenos Aires last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unhappy with prices, ranchers look to build own meat plants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-iowa-nebraska-d95ef3d2aee8e80aa5aca6d06ffa50a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Like other ranchers across the country, Rusty Kemp for years grumbled about rock-bottom prices paid for the cattle he raised in central Nebraska, even as the cost of beef at grocery stores kept climbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands demonstrate in Rome against neo-fascists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-rome-italy-49b05744b74f06230af52e7f829e1006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Tens of thousands of union members and other Italians gathered in Rome to stand up against rising fascism Saturday, a week after right-wing extremists forced their way into the headquarters of Italy's most powerful labor confederation while protesting a COVID-19 certification requirement for workplaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furious Manchin slaps Sanders: 'I won't take orders from socialist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10098231/Joe-Manchin-criticizes-stater-Bernie-Sanders-op-ed-West-Virginias-biggest-newspaper.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders, senator for Vermont, took the highly unusual step on Friday of publishing an op ed in the main newspaper in West Virginia, home state of Senator Joe Manchin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem incumbents bolster advantage in key Senate races...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/577034-democratic-incumbents-bolster-fundraising-advantage-in-key-senate-races</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic senators waging tight reelection bids saw a windfall in fundraising in the third quarter of 2021, beefing up their war chests ahead of what are expected to be brutal fights to retain their seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden giving stiff-arm to press interviews...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/577020-biden-giving-stiff-arm-to-press-interviews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has only given 10 one-on-one press interviews since taking office in January, a low number that is drawing more attention toward the White House’s efforts to control and manage the way Biden interacts with reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX can't shake Chappelle controversy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/576998-netflix-cant-shake-chappelle-controversy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix can't seem to close the door on "The Closer," with the streaming giant only further inflaming controversy with its defense of Dave Chappelle's mocking of the transgender community in his latest comedy special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short on Staff, Hospices Ask New Patients To Wait...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/short-on-staff-some-hospices-ask-new-patients-to-wait/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anne Cotton had enjoyed her years at an assisted living facility in Corvallis, Ore. But at 89, her health problems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money Floods Race for Control of Congress, More Than Year Early...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/money-floods-the-race-for-control-of-congress-more-than-a-year-early/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dizzying amount of money is already pouring into the battles for the House and the Senate more than a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Venezuela, Rum Maker Offers Gangsters Life Outside of Crime...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/in-venezuela-a-rum-maker-offers-gangsters-a-life-outside-of-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the process, the family running the company, Ron Santa Teresa, has gone from bankruptcy to exporting an award-winning vintage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finneas, Pop Star's Secret Weapon, Strides Into Spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/15/finneas-a-pop-stars-secret-weapon-strides-into-the-spotlight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — There’s a ghoul hanging around Finneas’s house. A dark shadow spinning past the window of his otherwise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graveyard of Empires: Beijing Spooked by Afghanistan Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-10-14/afghanistan-quagmire-threatens-to-lure-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent attack in Afghanistan carried out by a Uighur Muslim has shaken China’s top national security decisionmakers, who now question the value of promises from the Taliban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio ignores?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/15/radio-nowhere-so-far-adeles-easy-on-me-ignored-by-two-biggest-pop-stations-in-new-york-los-angeles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sulu Calls Kirk 'Unfit Guinea Pig'...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/10/william-shatner-blue-origin-space-ride-draws-celebrity-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Takei called him an “unfit guinea pig” for space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy to Discharge All Sailors Refusing Vax... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/10/14/new-navy-guidance-will-discharge-sailors-refusing-covid-19-vaccination-without-exemption</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This story has been updated with additional information about the Navy vaccine mandate. All active-duty Navy personnel must be vaccinated by Nov. 28 or face separation, according to a Navy administrative message released Wednesday. Any active-duty Navy service members who do not get fully vaccinated or do not have an approved or pending exemption will …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bill Clinton in hospital for infection; ICU for days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-entertainment-business-california-bill-clinton-575328d3d0411d5186465c6712ee3d8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORANGE, Calif. (AP) — Bill Clinton is doing fine and will be released soon from a Southern California hospital where he's being treated for an infection, President Joe Biden said. Biden said Friday during remarks at the University of Connecticut that he had spoken to Clinton and the former president “sends his best.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  76ERS Star Faked Exposure To Evade NBA Playoff Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/bombshell-report-claims-76ers-star-ben-simmons-may-have-faked-covid-19-exposure-to-evade-nba-playoff-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Simmons is back with the Philadelphia 76ers, returning just one week before the regular season tips off, but all does not appear to be resolved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Defends:  'Good Thing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jen-psaki-defends-rising-prices-good-thing-because-it-means-more-people-are-buying-goods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Jen Psaki defended the idea of economic fragility as a "high-class problem," saying it meant "more people" were buying goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to Stage Largest Robot Tank Experiment Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2021/10/us-army-stage-largest-robot-tank-experiment-ever/186110/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its lessons will inform the Army’s next-gen-unmanned-vehicles plan to ask tech firms to deliver the brains and established firms to deliver the wheels.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
