<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Is This Worse Than 1968?</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/10/is-this-worse-than-1968/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday, in Pittsburgh, a Sabbath celebration at the Tree of Life synagogue became the site of the largest mass murder of Jews in U.S. history. Eleven worshipers were killed by a racist gunman. Friday, we learned the identity of the crazed criminal who mailed pipe bombs to a dozen leaders of the Democratic Party, including […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had list of 100 TARGETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/Bomb-Suspect-Set-for-Florida-Court-Appearance-498875761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida man accused of sending packages containing explosive material to prominent Democrats and others who've been criticized by President Donald Trump had a list of more than 100 people to target, a senior...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moose bomb: 100-lbs of explosives incinerate carcass near popular trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.jhnewsandguide.com/jackson_hole_daily/local/article_8b23bd1c-ed9e-52b5-aa70-82355c0836da.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jhnewsandguide.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worried about possible people-carnivore conflict, Bridger-Teton National Forest officials recently exploded a full-grown bull moose whose final resting place was along a popular trail near the Cache Creek trailhead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCAULIFFE: She's Never Going To Be on a Ballot Again...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-mcauliffe-hillary-never-going-be-ballot-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I feel confident saying she’s not going to run for president’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX Owner Expects Team To Accept White House Invitation, But Manager Not So Sure...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/10/29/red-sox-white-house-visit-world-series-alex-cora-president-trump/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will the World Series champion Boston Red Sox visit President Donald Trump at the White House? Manager Alex Cora said that decision has not yet been made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged bomber mouths 'I love you' to someone in court...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6330503/MAGAbomber-Cesar-Sayoc-tearful-court-faces-five-felony-charges-pipe-bombs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cesar Sayoc appeared in court on Monday for the first time in Miami, where he has been held without bond since his arrest on Friday. The suspected MAGAbomber will be tried on five felony counts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saved by Jewish doctors, nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-tended-to-by-jewish-doctors-and-nurses-officials-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jewish doctors and nurses at Allegheny General Hospital in Pittsburgh put their personal feelings aside to help save the life of the man who allegedly claimed he wanted to “kill all the Jews” as he opened fire at a synagogue and murdered 11 worshipers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President, First Lady to Visit...</title>
      <link>http://www.post-gazette.com/news/crime-courts/2018/10/29/Trump-jewish-synagogue-shootings-Pittsburgh-tree-of-life/stories/201810290133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Russia in crosshairs, Canada moves to buy sub hunter...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/naval/2018/10/29/with-russia-in-its-cross-hairs-canada-moves-to-buy-a-sub-hunter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's selection of an as-yet unproven ship that is a purpose-built sub hunter could be a sign that the nation is willing to accept the cost and schedule growth risks because of the strategic threat Russia poses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network chyron error...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/drudge-bashes-fox-news-segment-on-political-violence-check-your-soul-in-the-makeup-chair?source=articles&amp;via=rss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative media titan seemed incensed Monday morning by a Fox News panel discussion that appeared to make light of recent political violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAUGHTER, JOKES ON FOXNEWS SEGMENT ABOUT TERROR FALLOUT?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/matt-drudge-rips-bizarre-fox-news-segment-on-synagogue-shooting-check-your-soul-in-the-makeup-chair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian official says president's cellphone tapped...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75f84b91a7c94fdd94e57707a5d77ccc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iranian officials say President Hassan Rouhani's mobile phone was tapped, without providing details on who was behind it or what information they might have gleaned. The semi-official ISNA news agency on Monday quoted Gen. Gholam Reza Jalali, the head of a military unit charged with combatting sabotage, as saying Rouhani's phone was tapped "recently" and would be replaced with a more secure device. He did not provide further details. Iran moved to boost its cyber capabilities in 2011 after the Stuxnet computer virus destroyed thousands of centrifuges involved in its contested nuclear program. Stuxnet is widely believed to be an American and Israeli creation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump May Answer Mueller Questions Post-Election, Giuliani Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-29/trump-may-answer-mueller-queries-post-election-giuliani-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soccer star found dead'; 'Almost beheaded with genitals severed'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/29/soccer-star-found-dead-almost-beheaded-with-his-genitals-severed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A soccer star was found dead in a bush “almost beheaded and with his genitals severed,” according to reports. Sao Paulo star Daniel Correa Freitas, 24, was discovered in Sao Jose dos Pi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice on 'code red' as city floods... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venice-apos-code-red-apos-172202059.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice was almost completely flooded on Monday, with rain-soaked tourists evacuated from St Mark's Square as fierce storms lashed Italy. Water transport services were halted across Venice as 75 per cent of the city centre flooded to 156cm (61inc) by early afternoon, the highest level since 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUNMAN SHOOTS OUT WINDOWS OF GOP OFFICE IN FL...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/10/29/gunman-gop-office-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange says Ecuador seeking to end asylum, hand him to USA...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/wikileaks-assange-says-ecuador-seeking-end-asylum-173550865.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO (Reuters) - Wikileaks founder Julian Assange said on Monday that Ecuador is seeking to end his asylum in its London embassy and hand him over to the United States. He spoke from the London embassy via teleconference as part of a trial in Quito initiated by his legal team that challenges recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuated after 'health attacks' in Cuba and China, diplomats face new ordeals...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/investigations/evacuated-after-health-attacks-cuba-china-diplomats-face-new-ordeals-n920241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some diplomats and their doctors tell NBC they're concerned the U.S. wants to downplay what happened. Some suspect harassment has continued inside the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Marijuana Heightens Risk of Psychosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/alice-b-lloyd/mind-the-link-marijuana-heightens-the-risk-of-psychosis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As legalization looms, psychiatrists and public health advocates are spreading awareness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARSCALE: Agenda on 2018 Ballot... </title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-not-on-the-ballot-in-2018-his-campaign-manager-parscale-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump 2020 campaign manager Brad Parscale talked with "CBS This Morning" about the campaign's new ad urging voters to back GOP in midterm elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing allows trade of rhino, tiger goods...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-permits-limited-trade-rhino-tiger-goods-161504281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Monday announced it was authorising the trade of rhinoceros and tiger parts for scientific, medical and cultural purposes, a move wildlife conservationists fear could have "devastating consequences" globally. The trade of rhinos, tigers, and their related products will be allowed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students say open border to caravan!</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11457</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think we should let them in."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17.7% SENATE...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2018-midterm-election-forecast/senate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight's predictions for the 2018 Senate elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops thought severed human head brought to police station was Halloween prank...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article220784450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two visitors to an Oakland apartment complex found a decaying human head in the back yard and delivered it to a police station to be investigated, officers say. A headless corpse was recently found nearby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Employee Visits 9,000 Porn Sites, Crashes Gov't Networks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cio-briefing/2018/10/porn-watching-employee-infected-government-networks-russian-malware-ig-says/152307/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government auditors traced a malware infection back to a single porn-watching employee within the U.S. Geological Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY 2020? 'I'd like to be president'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/hillary-teases-2020-run-id-like-to-be-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All signs are pointing to a Hillary Clinton run for president in 2020. While she answered “No,” that she wouldn’t make yet another run for the Oval Office in two years, she admitted, “I’d like to be president.” During a Friday evening Q&amp;A with Recode’s Kara Swisher, the subject of the next presidential election came …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI predicts Warren Buffett's holdings at risk from hedge funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.fnlondon.com/articles/ai-predicts-berkshire-hathaway-holdings-at-risk-from-hedge-funds-20181029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fnlondon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 6% of Warren Buffett's company’s holdings could be vulnerable to short-sellers, study by UK fintech Irithmics estimates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne links Pittsburgh shooting to 'anti-religious' trend...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/413621-conway-links-pittsburgh-shooting-to-anti-religious-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House counsellor Kellyanne Conway on Monday condemned the trend of "anti-religiosity" in America, just days after a mass shooting at a Pittsburgh synagogue left 11 people dead and several wounded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Secret Service impostor is 17-year-old boy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article220784240.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a 17-year-old man spent the weekend impersonating a law enforcement officer across Greenville County, South Carolina, he finally had a run in with the real deal. Thomason Michael Barrett Hand was charged Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China military ordered to 'prepare for war' with  west...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/3414168/chinas-military-ordered-to-concentrate-preparations-for-fighting-a-war-as-tensions-with-west-grow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA’s President Xi Jinping has told his military commanders to “concentrate preparations for fighting a war” as Beijing ramps up fighting talk with the West. The communist ruler’s ins…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign launches ad that doesn't feature president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/413611-trump-campaign-launches-6-million-midterm-ad-that-doesnt-feature-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's campaign is making its closing argument in the final stretch of the midterm elections with a $6 million ad buy, but the 60-second spot doesn't mention the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros-Funded Groups Attempt to Ban 'Hate Speech' on Social Media...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/splc-leads-soros-funded-groups-in-orwellian-attempt-to-ban-hate-speech-on-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demanding "tech companies sacrifice free speech on the altar of political correctness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade? No Thanks. Americans Sticking With Old Phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/upgrade-no-thanks-americans-are-sticking-with-their-old-phones-1540818000 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are holding onto their smartphones for longer than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims of Cuba, China 'Health Attacks' Being Harassed in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latin-america/evacuated-after-health-attacks-cuba-china-diplomats-face-new-ordeals-n920241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some diplomats and their doctors tell NBC they're concerned the U.S. wants to downplay what happened. Some suspect harassment has continued inside the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman poised to take over?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/politics/739334/angela-merkel-quits-new-german-chancellor-Annegret-Kramp-Karrenbauer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military to Deploy 5,000 Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/military-to-deploy-5-000-troops-to-southern-border-u-s-officials-say-1540820650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military is deploying 5,000 troops to the southern border, U.S. officials say, an increase from the initial estimate of 800.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious object on ISS live feed sparks NASA conspiracy frenzy; 'They tried to blur it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/739303/Alien-news-mysterious-object-ISS-sparks-NASA-conspiracy-frenzy-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alkaline water miracle cure - or BS? Science is in...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global/2018/oct/29/alkaline-water-cure-bs-science-beyonce-tom-brady</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beyonce and Tom Brady swear by it – but experts throw cold water on the new beverage fad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montgomery Clift: Untold story of Hollywood's misunderstood star...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/oct/29/montgomery-clift-actor-untold-story-hollywood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new documentary, myths and assumptions about the Oscar-nominated heartthrob who struggled with his sexuality are replaced with the little-known truth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 50%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/current_events/politics/prez_track_oct29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Stadiums Still Showing Thousands of Empty Seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2018/10/28/weak-eight-nfl-stadiums-still-showing-thousands-empty-seats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With half the NFL season behind us, fan attendance still has not ticked upward for the most part. And at least one fan thinks that the empty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Save Less to Sustain Spending as Income Gains Cool...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-save-less-sustain-spending-123001355.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchases, which account for about 70 percent of the economy, rose 0.4 percent from the prior month, matching economists’ estimates, following an upwardly revised 0.5 percent increase, Commerce Department figures showed Monday. Incomes advanced a less-than-projected 0.2 percent, the weakest in more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of era...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/merkel-not-seek-election-cdu-party-chair-source-092518256.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel told leaders of her conservatives on Monday that she will not seek re-election as party chairwoman, senior party sources said, heralding the end of a 13-year era in which she has dominated European politics. Merkel, 64, has been chairwoman of her conservative Christian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Declining Trust May Be Sending Many To Grave Sooner...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/declining-trust-americans-sending-grave-sooner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that people who are more trusting of others tend to have longer lifespans than those mired in suspicion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocers Enlist Robots to Chase E-Commerce...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/grocers-enlist-robots-to-chase-e-commerce-1540814521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grocers are stocking their warehouses with robots and artificial intelligence to increase efficiency as competition for consumer spending on food picks up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors seek death penalty...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/pittsburgh-shooting-synagogue-today-suspect-robert-bowers-squirrel-hill-live-updates-2018-10-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven people were killed and six others wounded Saturday at the Tree of Life synagogue in Pittsburgh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Six people shot' at LA nightclub during 'First Purge' Halloween party...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7608449/la-nightclub-shooting-california-bar-first-purge-halloween-party/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO people were rushed to hospital after a shooting at a Halloween party called “The First Purge”. Local police confirmed an additional five victims were brought to hospital, bringing t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury after China reverses 25-year-old tiger bone and rhino horn ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-fury-after-china-reverses-13499549</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We'll be bringing you the very latest updates, pictures and video on this breaking news story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same-sex couple carries same 'miracle' baby in fertility world first...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/10/29/same-sex-couple-carries-same-baby-ivf-fertility-treatment-first/1804554002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Texas mothers each carried their son using a new fertility process that's similar to traditional IVF.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In highly partisan era, those who dislike both sides could have deciding votes...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-usc-latimes-poll-20181029-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, voters who disliked both Hillary Clinton and Donald Trump broke heavily toward the Republican, handing him the victory. This time around, those who disapprove of both sides appear to be favoring the Democrats, a USC-Los Angeles Times poll shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivor escapes death second time...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-Pittsburgh-a-Holocaust-survivor-was-four-13344286.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twice now, Judah Samet has almost paid with his life for being Jewish. More than 70 years ago, he narrowly escaped death in Germany's Bergen-Belsen concentration camp. Again Saturday, he looked death in the face - not in his native Hungary, where nationalism is resurgent, but in the country where he found sanctuary after the Second World War. Samet, 80, almost died in the parking lot of Pittsburgh's Tree of Life synagogue, his place of worship, when a gunman who "wanted all Jews to die" killed 11 people during morning services. It was the deadliest attack against Jews in U.S. history. "I survived the second time yesterday," he said in an interview on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrowing tales emerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/harrowing-tales-emerge-synagogue-suspect-due-court-095728208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — As Barry Werber walked into the Tree of Life Synagogue, he passed a cart carrying glassware and whiskey meant for the baby-naming ceremony scheduled at Dor Hadash, one of three small congregations that worship there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaccine billboards appear in several states...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/anti-vaccine-billboards-appear-several-states-104234260.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON, W.Va. (AP) — Anti-vaccine billboards claiming that routine childhood shots are deadly have popped up in several West Virginia cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large quake off SAmerica...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6f0a5c9946744c7e98272193f7ead07c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUENOS AIRES, Argentina (AP) — The U.S. Geological Survey says an earthquake with a preliminary magnitude of 6.3 has struck off the southern tip of South America. The quake, which hit at 2:54 a.m. local time Monday, was centered in the ocean, 312.9 kilometers (194 miles) south southeast of Ushuaia, Argentina, and 552 kilometers (342 miles) south southeast of Punta Arenas, Chile. The agency said the quake was at a relatively shallow depth of 10 kilometers (6 miles).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Free speech' platform goes offline...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/gab-goes-offline-hosting/#91jgNg7qgOqY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The site has been under pressure following the Pittsburgh attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sense of Alarm as Rural Hospitals Keep Closing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/29/upshot/a-sense-of-alarm-as-rural-hospitals-keep-closing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are potential health and economic consequences in a trend associated with states that have turned down Medicaid expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts Will Have Hand on Throttle as Supreme Court Veers Right...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/roberts-will-have-hand-on-throttle-as-supreme-court-veers-right</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roberts Will Have Hand on Throttle as Supreme Court Veers Right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant Dies in Clashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/honduran-migrant-dies-in-clashes-at-mexicos-southern-border-1540793695</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Honduran migrant died after violent clashes with Mexican and Guatemalan security forces, the latest incident in an escalating migration crisis as a second group of migrants attempt to get to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credit-Card Spending Limits in Crosshairs as Issuers Grow Cautious...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/credit-card-spending-limits-in-the-crosshairs-as-issuers-grow-cautious-1540805401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the biggest credit-card issuers are tightening lending standards, an unusual move in a strong economy that may signal longer-term concerns about consumers’ financial health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refuse housing, jobs in Mexico: 'We want America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/739010/migrant-caravan-refuse-mexico-housing-jobs-donald-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence casts cloud week before midterms...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/413567-violence-casts-cloud-week-before-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A string of violent incidents has cast a pall over the final weeks of a midterm season already marked by months of bitter partisan fighting, vitriolic rhetoric and angry protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel to Give Up Party Leadership in Dramatic Move...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/merkel-is-said-to-give-up-cdu-party-leadership-in-dramatic-move#gs.uIZBzAw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Merkel will quit as head of Christian Democratic party after nearly two decades, a person familiar with the matter said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST TEAM IN BASEBALL WINS IT ALL!</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/sports/red_sox/2018/10/red_sox_win_world_series</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Down the dugout steps, down a long tunnel that leads to the visitors clubhouse inside Dodger Stadium, the Red Sox began their party.Alex Cora got in the middle of the locker room to thank his players, and it wasn&amp;#39;t long before his speech was overflowed with champagne. They sang in unison again to "New York, New York," an inspiration to this magical run, and Tupac&amp;#39;s "California Love" blared to bookend the journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>178  on board...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/lion-air-flight-crashes-after-taking-off-from-indonesian-capital-jakarta-11538880</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Lion Air flight between Jakarta and an island off Sumatra has crashed, Indonesian search and rescue officials have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican, Democrat Chairs Trade Racism Charges In 'Unity' Segment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/republican-and-democrat-chairs-trade-accusations-of-racism-in-meet-the-press-unity-segment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea eyes Swiss, Singaporean-style success...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c874f3a400eb459daac89b9d46909810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — North Korea is exploring a grand plan to become a regional transportation hub, inspired in part by the successes of Singapore and Switzerland, and would be open to joining world financial institutions such as the International Monetary Fund if current member states give up their "hostile" policies toward it, a senior government economist has told The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger jet crashes mins after take off from Jakarta...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/7605999/indonesian-plane-crash-lion-air-aircraft-crashed-take-off-jakarta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PASSENGER plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Jakarta, Indonesia, according to reports. The Lion Air flight between Jakarta and Pangkal Pinang lost contact with air traffic control earl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk students overload ER, cause mayhem at University hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/education/article220233790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palmetto Health Baptist in Columbia treats many drunk students from the University of South Carolina on game days, and more Richland County EMS ambulances are needed at Williams-Brice Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCarolina Warns About Secret Service Impostor: Gun, badge, siren...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article220769255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Greenville County Sheriff’s Office is warning SC residents and businesses about a man with a gun, badge who is pretending to be a police or Secret Service officer seen driving a Ford Explorer with a siren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Isolated loner'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6326657/Synagogue-shooters-neighbors-knew-forgettable-bland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, police and FBI agents raided the Baldwin, Pennsylvania apartment of Robert Bowers, 46, who is charged with 29 federal crimes and faces the death penalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 Hondurans break cordon, attempt to join...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/1-000-honduran-migrants-break-guatemala-police-cordon-011019246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a thousand Honduran migrants broke through a Guatemalan police cordon on the border with Mexico Sunday as they attempted to join a larger caravan of compatriots heading towards the United States, police and rights groups said. Guatemala's human rights ombudsman, Jordan Rodas, called on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds search for suspect who set fire to Republican HQ...</title>
      <link>https://trib.com/news/state-and-regional/federal-authorities-offer-reward-for-suspect-in-gop-headquarters-fire/article_5df64367-0037-5a63-8449-333299c8e372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LARAMIE — Federal authorities are offering a $5,000 reward for information on the whereabouts of a man charged with vandalizing and setting fire to a local Republican Party headquarters in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India to unveil world's tallest statue; 2x Statue of Liberty height...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/india-unveil-worlds-tallest-statue-13495377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An astonishing £330 million has been spent on the 600ft tribute to Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel in Gujarat, India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple finds hidden camera in cruise ship bedroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2018/10/28/travelers-found-hidden-camera-their-carnival-cruise-bedroom/1800150002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida couple discovered aÂ recording deviceÂ hidden among TV wires in their stateroom last October on a Carnival Fantasy cruise to the Caribbean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat majority could undermine Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/28/mueller-democrats-house-majority-trump-probe-940032</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Democrats retake the House, they want to aggressively open probes into issues the special counsel is also investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-old raped in NYC public bathroom...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/11-year-girl-raped-in-public-bathroom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is looking for a teenager wanted in the rape of an 11-year-old girl in the public bathroom of a Bronx Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals rescued from 'hellish' Albanian zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/animals-rescued-hellish-albanian-zoo-212853415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Albanian police on Sunday broke open cages at a private zoo and removed 11 animals including three lions and a bear being kept in "hellish" conditions, animal welfare workers said. After the owner of the zoo at Fier, around 100 kilometres (60 miles) south of the capital Tirana, allegedly refused</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Concert Threats Continue with Image of Cleaver-Wielding Jihadist...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-concert-threats-continue-with-image-of-cleaver-wielding-jihadist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Third media group picks up month of online depictions of attacks on concert venues; latest calls on Western Muslims to "take an example" from homegrown jihadists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Moore Reveals Footage of Bomb Suspect Cesar Sayoc at Trump Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/michael-moore-reveals-video-bomb-suspect-cesar-sayoc-at-trump-rally-1155772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'Fahrenheit 11/9' director compares Cesar Sayoc to "a lost dog with no direction home."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
