<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CHARGES: Man Turns Backyard Field Into Private Airport!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/10/16/twin-cities-man-accused-of-operating-airstrip-in-field-behind-his-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Twin Cities man is facing charges after allegedly carving a runway into a field behind his home and using it as a private airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems find their anti-Rubio warrior in Val Demings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/dems-find-their-anti-rubio-warrior-in-val-demings/ar-AAPCWN7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida congresswoman is amassing an army of small donors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 5 Nights in Hospital, Bill Clinton May Be Released...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/16/bill-clinton-expected-to-be-released-from-hospital-sunday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Bill Clinton is expected to be released from a California hospital Sunday after five days of treatment for a urological infection, a spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN Fans Throw Trash At Cheerleaders, Coach...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/17/tennessee-fans-throw-trash-ole-miss-lane-kiffin-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennessee fans melted down during a 31-26 loss to Ole Miss late Saturday night. Fans threw trash at Lane Kiffin and Ole Miss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest drawing of ghost discovered on Babylonian tablet...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2021/oct/16/figures-of-babylon-oldest-drawing-of-a-ghost-found-in-british-museum-vault</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 3,500-year-old image tablet of a ‘miserable male ghost’ gives up its secret</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marriage Rates Plummeting. Why Reality Dating Series So Popular?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/10/17/reality-dating-series-conservatism-515581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the dating-and-marriage storyline still appeals so much to audiences who are increasingly opting out of the tradition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lawless city?' Worry after Portland police don't stop chaos...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/lawless-city-worry-portland-police-stop-chaos-80613763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of 100 people wreaked havoc in downtown Portland, Oregon, this week, smashing storefront windows, lighting dumpsters on fire and causing at least $500,000 in damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Tahoe so low, boats marooned...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/renotahoe/article/Lake-Tahoe-drought-water-rim-algae-16533020.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no telling how low Tahoe will get if we don’t see a massive winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia records highest daily new case number...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/russia-records-highest-daily-new-covid-19-case-number-rcna3151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is reporting its largest daily number of new coronavirus infections, more than 70 percent up on the number a month ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives change their tune on big government...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/577021-the-memo-conservatives-change-their-tune-on-big-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Old political orthodoxies are being scrambled by a combination of the COVID-19 pandemic, the influence of former President Trump and the deep current of polarization tearing through the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 American missionaries kidnapped in Haiti...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-caribbean-kidnapping-haiti-puerto-rico-d17832d664f210adb63a05702f6859a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — A group of 17 U.S. missionaries including children was kidnapped by a gang in Haiti on Saturday, according to a voice message sent to various religious missions by an organization with direct knowledge of the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying moment stuntman almost killed during 'AGT' rehearsal...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10100075/Terrifying-footage-moment-Jonathan-Goodwin-America-Got-Talent-stuntman-died-hit-cars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan Goodwin was performing a stunt on America's Got Talent: Extreme filmed in Atlanta. He was being suspended between two elevated cars between which he was supposed to fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor flexes muscle as leverage tips from employers to workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/16/economy/workers-strike-john-deere-iatse-kellogg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers are saying enough is enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lord of the plants: Death metal eco-baron rewilds estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211017-lord-of-the-plants-death-metal-eco-baron-rewilds-irish-estate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lord of the plants: death metal eco-baron rewilds Irish estate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese propaganda film beating Bond, MARVEL at box office...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-58868854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The success of The Battle at Lake Changjin is bad news for Hollywood which wants to grow in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the People Who Won't Have Sex Until They're Sterilized...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/meet-people-won-t-sex-085908351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos GettyWhen Sasha was in college, she did what a lot of young women her age do: she Googled which birth control would work for her. But after some research, the answer seemed to be: none of them. Almost every method had drawbacks: increased risk of irregular bleeding, depression, menstrual cramps, or pelvic infections.When Sasha began her first sexual relationship, she ended up temporarily taking hormonal birth control pills. But she was so nervous ab</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  POLITICS TURNS DEADLY IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-sir-david-amess-death-25227169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man arrested over the killing of MP Sir David Amess, 69, at a constituency surgery in Leigh-on-Sea, Essex, has been named. Detectives are allowed to hold him for questioning until October 22</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's longest lockdown in Melbourne set to end...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10099975/Coronavirus-Australia-Victorias-lockdown-lifted-Dan-Andrews-amends-roadmap-freedom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melbourne will be lifted from lockdown at 11.59pm Thursday under Daniel Andrews' roadmap out of lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realtor poses for full-frontal nude photos to promote LA listing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/15/realtor-stars-in-nsfw-full-frontal-photos-to-promote-la-listing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This real estate agent sure is cocky. Lately, agents are getting more creative in an attempt to promote their listings. One particular agent may have taken it a bit too far when he orchestrate…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free speech or hate speech? NETFLIX at eye of LGBTQ storm...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/free-speech-hate-speech-netflix-012318087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has been plunged into America's culture wars by a Dave Chappelle comedy special that raises concerns about free speech and censorship but has been slammed by its own employees as transphobic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules Jussie Smollett trial is on for Nov. 29...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/judge-rules-jussie-smollett-trial-190800082.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than two and a half years of dramatic developments in the Jussie Smollett case, the former “Empire” actor is officially slated to go to trial in late November. During a hearing Friday, Judge James Linn said jury selection would begin Nov. 29. Attorneys should be prepared for long days, he said, noting that testimony would likely go until 7 or 8 p.m. each day of the trial. Linn also ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVOLT:  Nearly 40% of California state workers unvaccinated despite Newsom order...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nearly-40-25-of-california-state-workers-are-unvaccinated-against-covid-despite-newsom-order/ar-AAPz6w6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oct. 15—The COVID-19 vaccination rate is lower among California state workers than among the state's general population, according to data from the state Human Resources Department. Fewer than two-thirds of state workers — about 62% — were vaccinated as of Oct. 7, according to preliminary figures provided by department spokeswoman Camille Travis. That compares to a rate of about 72% among all ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists got Legionnaires' Disease after staying at Florida Keys resort, lawyers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/two-tourists-got-legionnaires-e2-80-99-disease-after-staying-at-a-florida-keys-resort-lawyers-say/ar-AAPAZdf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Marcia Blanar stayed at Hawks Cay Resort in the Florida Keys during the summer, a decorative fountain surrounded by benches “was raging with active Legionella,” according to a lawsuit filed on her behalf earlier this month in Monroe County Circuit Court. Legionella, a type of bacteria, can cause Legionnaires’ Disease. The disease can cause a severe lung infection and is contracted by ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel 'reaching herd immunity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/coronavirus-israel-is-reaching-herd-immunity-health-official-681746</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head of Public Health Services Dr. Sharon Alroy-Preis also said that avoiding major restrictions through the fourth wave came at the price of 1,400 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk now richer than Bill Gates and Warren Buffett  -- combined!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-wealth-swells-astonishing-25228738</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla and SpaceX's Elon Musk is now worth an obscene $230 billion (£167 billion) following a share sale at SpaceX, making him richer than Bill Gates and Warren Buffett combined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government finding new ways to use drones to invade privacy...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/10/12/government-eyes-in-the-sky/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government and police are finding new ways to use drones to invade privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caught US intelligence by surprise...</title>
      <link>https://nypressnews.com/news/business/china-tests-new-space-capability-with-hypersonic-missile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypressnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China tested a nuclear-capable hypersonic missile in August that circled the globe before speeding towards its target, demonstrating an advanced space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motley Crue singer, 60, falls off stage and breaks ribs...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3870274/motley-crue-singer-vince-neil-fall-off-stage-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOTLEY Crue singer Vince Neil plunged off-stage into a crowd of fans after slipping on set before he was rushed to hospital. The musician, 60, was whisked away in an ambulance after the painful inc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPERMAN REMOVES 'AMERICAN WAY' FROM MOTTO...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/superman-new-motto-dc-fandome-1235090712/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Superman is officially moving on from “the American Way.” Jim Lee, chief creative officer and publisher of DC, announced on Saturday during the virtual fan event DC Fandome that the Man…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adele's comeback single breaks streaming record... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/music/adele-easy-on-me-breaks-spotify-record-most-streams-in-one-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adele's comeback single 'Easy on Me' was streamed 24 million times on Spotify in 24 hours, breaking the platform's record for most streams in a single day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Strike Averted; Crew, Producers Reach Deal... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/hollywood-strike-averted-iatse-amptp-reach-agreement-on-new-film-tv-contract-1234850563/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: With Hollywood on edge and picket signs at the ready, IATSE and the AMPTP have reached an agreement on a new film and TV contract, averting a threatened nationwide strike. The new three-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math nerds enter mapping process that could sway power in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/math-nerds-enter-mapping-process-that-could-sway-power-in-washington/article_76cb9022-c67a-5d52-9123-794f84f06955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State judges bedeviled by weirdly shaped and obviously partisan congressional district maps can now get expert help from an unusual source: math nerds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Biden Agenda in Limbo, Dems Work to Sell Unfinished Promise...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/with-biden-agenda-in-limbo-democrats-work-to-sell-an-unfinished-promise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALLENTOWN, Pa. — When Representative Susan Wild, Democrat of Pennsylvania, accompanied Jill Biden, the first lady, to the Learning Hub,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Are Americans growing warier of more govt just as Joe tries to pass big agenda?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Are-Americans-growing-warier-of-more-government-16537889.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A year ago, as Americans were casting their votes for president, the effects...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HALLOWEEN KILLS' Heads for $50M Opening Despite Dual Streaming Launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/halloween-kills-box-office-opening-last-duel-1235032467/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The slasher film is having no trouble defeating James Bond pic 'No Time to Die' while Ridley Scott's historical epic 'The Last Duel' is bombing in its debut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK CONFRONTS NEW EPISODE OF TERRORISM...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/16/with-lawmakers-killing-the-u-k-confronts-a-new-episode-of-terrorism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Prime Minister Boris Johnson and other British leaders paid their respects on Saturday morning at a church east</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman raped on train as bystanders did nothing, police say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-arrests-pennsylvania-philadelphia-1d0c62ae547165eabfc40fc6a20f25be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPPER DARBY, Pa. (AP) — A woman was raped by a stranger on a commuter train in suburban Philadelphia in the presence of other riders who a police official said “should have done something." Superintendent Timothy Bernhardt of the Upper Darby Police Department said officers were called to the 69th Street terminal around 10 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNVAXXED GERMANS BANNED FROM FOOD STORES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20211015/supermarkets-in-german-state-of-hesse-can-now-block-entry-to-the-unvaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supermarkets in Frankfurt and the surrounding region can now implement rules that only allow vaccinated and Covid-recovered people onto their premises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine's court-martial highlights military straining to deal with partisan politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Marine-s-court-martial-highlights-the-military-16537739.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMP LEJEUNE, N.C. - When a Marine officer who repeatedly disrespected senior officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Picks Lag...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-e2-80-99s-picks-lag-cheney-gop-incumbents-in-fundraising/ar-AAPAhri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three House Republicans targeted by former President Donald Trump raised more money in the third quarter than his hand-picked candidates to defeat them, according to Federal Election Commission filings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Quants Could Disrupt Process That Sways Power in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/math-quants-could-disrupt-process-that-sways-power-in-washington-1.1667150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State judges bedeviled by weirdly shaped and obviously partisan congressional district maps can now get expert help from an unusual source: math nerds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov Abbott, DeSantis Compete for National Limelight...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/republican-governor-frenemies-compete-for-national-limelight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Governor ‘Frenemies’ Compete for National Limelight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Parts: Cars Stuck at Garages for WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/car-parts-shortages-are-hitting-u-s-garages-creating-weeks-long-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cars Get Stuck at U.S. Garages for Weeks in Spare-Parts Shortage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax stand-off between Chicago mayor, police hits courts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-vaccine-stand-off-between-073631289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago judge on Friday banned a police union president from making public statements on the city's Covid-19 policy as a stand-off over vaccine mandates sparked dueling lawsuits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After months in lockdown, a weary world is ready to dance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-cuba-4d54c5429b5238d2d1c086290881d4fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in the depths of the pandemic -- even when the world locked down, leaving billions isolated and desolated -- there were those who danced. “I did not stop dancing for a second,” says Federico Carrizo, who competed in the Tango World Championship in Buenos Aires last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unhappy with prices, ranchers look to build own meat plants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-iowa-nebraska-d95ef3d2aee8e80aa5aca6d06ffa50a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Like other ranchers across the country, Rusty Kemp for years grumbled about rock-bottom prices paid for the cattle he raised in central Nebraska, even as the cost of beef at grocery stores kept climbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands demonstrate in Rome against neo-fascists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-rome-italy-49b05744b74f06230af52e7f829e1006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Tens of thousands of union members and other Italians gathered in Rome to stand up against rising fascism Saturday, a week after right-wing extremists forced their way into the headquarters of Italy's most powerful labor confederation while protesting a COVID-19 certification requirement for workplaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furious Manchin slaps Sanders: 'I won't take orders from socialist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10098231/Joe-Manchin-criticizes-stater-Bernie-Sanders-op-ed-West-Virginias-biggest-newspaper.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders, senator for Vermont, took the highly unusual step on Friday of publishing an op ed in the main newspaper in West Virginia, home state of Senator Joe Manchin.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
