<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mobs in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14400392/anti-lockdown-protesters-clash-police-london/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-lockdown protesters clashed with cops in London today after police warned they could be arrested if they gathered. Hundreds of maskless demonstrators marched through the capital to rally again…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands demonstrate in Switzerland...</title>
      <link>https://www.swissinfo.ch/eng/thousands-demonstrate-against-covid-19-restrictions/46465314</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.swissinfo.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people have protested in the north-western Swiss town of Liestal against restrictions introduced to curb the Covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS FOR FIRST SUSTAINABLE CITY ON MARS UNVEILED...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/living/2021/03/19/plans-for-the-first-sustainable-city-on-mars-unveiled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vertical city has homes, offices and green spaces and construction is due to start in 2054.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany: Police clash with protesters against virus measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/berlin-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-99b7100d7c223654a31c878a6f7375aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Protesters in Germany clashed with police Saturday over coronavirus measures, with officers using water cannons, pepper spray and batons against people trying to break through police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans anxious about return to normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/20/why-some-are-averse-to-return-to-normal-post-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a year into the coronavirus pandemic, some people have fallen in love with their 'Covid caves'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexual Anguish Familiar Thorn for Faith Community...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/20/sexual-anguish-of-atlanta-suspect-is-familiar-thorn-for-evangelicals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Brad Onishi heard that the man accused of a rampage at three Atlanta-area spas told detectives that he had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden on his heels amid migrant surge at Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-immigration-united-states-1efbf1f357a5210d2433b48820b9aa54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Somehow, they didn’t see it coming. Within weeks of Inauguration Day on Jan. 20, the Biden administration had reversed many of the most maligned Trump-era immigration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NATO Scientist With Security Clearance Busted Spying for Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/top-nato-scientist-security-clearance-073352843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaanus Lensment / Ekspress Meedia (Estonia)TALLINN, Estonia—Chinese military intelligence recruited an Estonian national working at a NATO research institution focused on maritime and submarine research, The Daily Beast has learned.The spy, Tarmo Kõuts, renowned in the Estonian scientific community for his research, was convicted last week and sentenced to three years in prison. The Baltic country’s intelligence services had warned for years of the growing Chinese threat, but the conviction was the first of its kind. So far, Estonia’s counterintelligence service, known domestically by its acronym KAPO, has been praised for its success in catching spies recruited and run by Russia.According to Aleksander Toots, the deputy director of KAPO and Tallinn’s top counterintelligence official, Kõuts was recruited in 2018 by China’s Intelligence Bureau of the Joint Staff Department of the Central Military Commission—as Beijing’s military intelligence agency is known—along with an alleged accomplice who is yet to be tried in court. Both were arrested on September 9, 2020, with no publicity or discussion of the case in the Estonian media.Kõuts pleaded guilty to conducting intelligence activities against the Republic of Estonia on behalf of a foreign state. The charges were one stop short of treason. He was sentenced to three years in prison.Kõuts was recruited on Chinese territory, said Toots, who spoke exclusively with The Daily Beast and Estonia’s Delfi newspaper: “He was motivated by traditional human weaknesses, such as money and need of recognition.”Toots added that Kõuts received cash payments from his Chinese handlers as well as paid trips to various Asian countries, with luxury accommodations and dinners at Michelin star restaurants. The intelligence operatives handling him were operating under cover of a think tank. Inna Ombler, the prosecutor handling the case confirmed that Kõuts earned €17,000 -- a little over $20,000 -- for his espionage, which the Estonian government has since seized from him.Kõuts, who earned his doctorate in environmental physics in 1999, had worked for years at Tallinn Technical University’s Maritime Institute where he specialized in geophysics and operational oceanography. His research led to marine scientists successfully predicting a damaging winter storm with rapidly rising sea levels in Estonia in 2005. Kõuts was also part of a scientific research group that was awarded the Estonian National Science Prize in 2002 for finding the best location for a seaport on the island of Saaremaa. Although officially designed to accept cruise ships, the port needed to be able to host NATO vessels.From 2006, Kõuts became directly involved in the national defense sector. He was named a member of the Estonian Ministry of Defense’s Scientific Committee, which oversees the country’s military research and development initiatives. As part of that secondment he also became a member of the Scientific Committee of the NATO Undersea Research Center based in La Spezia, Italy and even served, from 2018 to 2020, as the vice president of that organization, which is now known as the Centre for Maritime Research and Experimentation (CMRE). According to its website, the CMRE “conducts relevant, state-of-the-art scientific research in ocean science, modelling and simulation, acoustics and other disciplines.”Kõuts’s public Facebook account shows he checked-in at Lerici, Italy— from La Spezia—in April 2018, the year of his recruitment by China. His role at the NATO center gave Kõuts direct access to Estonia’s and NATO’s confidential military intelligence. At the time of his arrest, he had a state secret permit as well as NATO security clearance dating back fourteen years. In the three years Kõuts worked for Chinese military intelligence, confined his espionage to observations and anecdotes about his top-level work but did not, according to Toots, yet pass on any confidential military information.“That he had such security clearances was one of the reasons we decided to put a stop to his collaboration [with the Chinese] so early,” Toots said. It might have saved him from a much stricter sentence that would have followed if he’d been charged with treason, which he would have been if Kõuts had passed on state or NATO secrets.Indeed, the biggest espionage breach NATO ever had was an Estonian one, just four years after the Baltic state joined the military alliance. In 2008, KAPO arrested Herman Simm, the head of the Ministry of Defense’s Security Department. Simm’s job was to coordinate the protection of state secrets, issue security clearances and act as a liaison between the Estonian Ministry of Defense and NATO. He’d been working for Russia’s foreign intelligence service, the SVR, for the entirety of his tenure. Simm was sentenced to twelve and a half years imprisonment and he additionally needed to pay €1.3 million—$1.8 million in today’s dollar value—in damages. He was released from prison on Christmas 2019.Since that scandal, Estonia has become one of the foremost Russian spy-catchers. “I'm continually amazed,” Toomas Henrik Ilves, Estonia’s former president, said. “We must be the only country the Kremlin seems to be interested in since we're the only ones catching all their agents. What makes us so special?”Unlike other NATO members, this Baltic country has a tendency to name and shame those it captures. It also rarely trades spies for its own captured assets. A much publicized exception to this rule was the case of Eston Kohver, a KAPO officer who was captured in 2014 by the FSB, Russia’s domestic security service, on the Estonian side of the Estonian-Russian border while conducting an operation to interdict cross-border smuggling. Kohver was traded, Bridge of Spies-style, in 2015 for Aleksei Dressen, a Russian agent the FSB recruited from within KAPO’s own ranks years earlier.Aleksander Toots oversaw both counterintelligence investigations that led to Simm’s and Dressen’s arrests. And despite his pedigree in snaring agents from Estonia’s next-door neighbor and former occupying power, Toots now sees a rising threat from farther east.Over the last three years, KAPO and Välisluureamet, Estonia’s foreign intelligence service, have raised the alarm about the rising threat of Chinese espionage. Last year Välisluureamet warned that Estonians who traveled to China were susceptible to influence operations and recruitment. “To this end, Chinese special services may use various methods and pretexts, such as establishing first contact or job offers over the internet. At home, Chinese special services can operate almost risk-free,” Välisluureamet explained in their annual security environment assessment. Politicians, public servants and scientists who hold political or defense-related clearances were named as possible recruitment targets.KAPO added that it first detected an increase in the interest of Chinese intelligence services after Estonia joined the EU and NATO in 2004 but lately that interest had intensified. The Chinese, Estonian counterintelligence concluded, are particularly interested in “decisions on global issues, be it the Arctic, climate or trade.”Tarmo Kõuts’ recruitment fits that category exactly, as his scientific research concentrated heavily on the maritime impact of climate change and some of his scholarly papers focused squarely on the Arctic region.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say goodbye to $30 plane tickets. Era of dirt-cheap flights ending...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/20/say-goodbye-to-30-plane-tickets-the-era-of-dirt-cheap-flights-is-ending.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airfare and some hotel rates are on the rise as cooped up Americans rush to vacation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Parties Back. Vaccines Optional...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sex-parties-are-back-vaccines-are-optional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As sex parties resume, expect hand sanitizer and temperature checks at the door. As one partygoer says, “No one wants to be the person who ruins the party by causing an outbreak.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Chaotic situation': Puerto Ricans indignant at tourists breaking mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/chaotic-situation-puerto-ricans-indignant-tourists-breaking-covid-mandates-n1261588</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts and residents worry that tourists’ unwillingness to follow Covid-19 measures could reverse the island's successful efforts at containing the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Believe Possible To Become Immortal...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/researchers-believe-its-possible-to-become-immortal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infowars: There's a War on for your Mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot skeleton unveiled in step towards dolls walking 'unaided'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/incredible-ai-sex-robot-skeleton-23763883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RealDoll representative promised that the company is getting ever closer to developing a sex robot that can walk unaided as well as conducting conversations with their owner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods 'did nothing to prevent crash'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9383587/Tiger-Woods-crash-investigation-suggests-golfer-prevent-collision.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New details have emerged in the ongoing Tiger Woods crash investigation revealing the golfer may have done 'nothing to prevent' the collision after he lost control of his car while speeding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury car thieves making killing on streets. In many cases, you're helping...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/luxury-car-thieves-making-killing-111500410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They creep into upscale South Florida neighborhoods on the hunt for Range Rovers, Lamborghinis, and Ferraris. They look for the telltale sign of an unlocked car: unfolded side view mirrors. On a good day — more often than you’d think — they find the car’s key fob inside. And with a simple push of a button, the luxurious car is gone. The scenario has repeated itself over and over recently, as ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Wicked betrayal'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210319165140-h4kd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRIME-GEORGIA/SPAS (PIX, TV):Atlanta shooting suspect's church decries killings as 'wicked betrayal'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summers Says USA Facing Worst Macroeconomic Policy in 40 Years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/summers-says-u-facing-worst-114227209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Former U.S. Treasury Secretary Lawrence Summers warned that the U.S. is suffering from the “least responsible” macroeconomic policy in the last 40 years, pointing the finger at both Democrats and Republicans for creating “enormous” risks.The fiscal-policy outlook has dimmed, the Covid recovery will stoke demand pressure, and the Federal Reserve has “stuck to its guns” for no rate cuts for years while expanding its balance sheet, he said in an interview with David Westin for Bloomberg Television’s “Wall Street Week” “What was kindling, is now igniting.”“I think these are the least responsible fiscal macroeconomic policy we’ve have had for the last 40 years,” he said. “I think it’s fundamentally driven by intransigence on the Democratic left and intransigence and the completely irresponsible behavior in the whole of the Republican Party.”Summers, a top official in the past two Democratic administrations, has emerged as one of the leading critics among Democrat-leaning economists of President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion pandemic plan. Summers warned in the interview the U.S. was facing a “pretty dramatic fiscal-monetary collision.”He said there is a 1/3-chance that inflation will accelerate in the coming years and the U.S. could be face stagflation. He also saw a 1/3-chance of no inflation because the Fed would hit the breaks hard and push the economy near recession. The final possiblity is that there Fed and Treasury will get rapid growth without inflation.“But there are more risks at this moment that macroeconomic policy will cause grave risks than I can remember,” he said.Administration officials have pushed back against the critique, saying the Biden bill aims to provide relief to those in need and won’t overheat an economy still suffering from high unemployment. Fed officials have broadly echoed that view -- flagging the risk of delivering too little fiscal support, and signaling they have no intention of tightening monetary policy anytime soon.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout from riot, virus leaves toxic mood on Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-ap-top-news-coronavirus-pandemic-7153ffc196f746883f57d4d407d38cf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The mood is so bad at the U.S. Capitol that a Democratic congressman recently let an elevator pass him by rather than ride with Republican colleagues who voted against certifying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you should spend more time barefoot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/health/is-it-safe-to-work-out-barefoot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learn about barefoot lifestyle pros and cons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unruly Spring Breakers Force Popular Miami Hotel Restaurant To Temporarily Close...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/19/unruly-spring-breakers-force-popular-clevelander-hotel-restaurant-to-temporarily-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dangerous situation has caused the popular Clevelander Hotel restaurant to shut its doors in Miami Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Was Fast: Blowups With ChinaRussia in Biden's First 60 Days...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/20/that-was-fast-blowups-with-china-and-russia-in-bidens-first-60-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Sixty days into his administration, President Biden got a taste this week of what the next four years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic trauma haunts health workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/why-put-life-line-pandemic-181700979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar. 15—Brittany Bankhead-­Kendall, 34, was a newly minted surgeon when the COVID-19 pandemic began. At first, like thousands of other health care professionals, she worked tirelessly in crisis mode. But by last fall, she was experiencing random and repeated physiological symptoms, including a racing heart and dimmed vision. She diagnosed herself as suffering from post-traumatic stress ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 posing as TINDER dates charged in 'organized attack'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/3-posing-tinder-dates-charged-220000289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Two 18-year-olds “terrorized” two men looking for a Tinder date hook up who instead were attacked from behind, beaten, kidnapped and robbed in Chicago's Kenwood neighborhood earlier this week, prosecutors said Friday. Jahziah McDonald and Jeremiyah Mannie were denied bail Friday by Cook County Judge Arthur Willis during a hearing audio streamed live on YouTube. The suspects, both of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man indicted for using GRINDR to find men for kill and eat...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvertiser.com/story/news/crime/2021/03/19/man-charged-hate-crime-used-grindr-hunting-ground-documents-say/4756378001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chance Seneca is accused of using dating app Grindr used as “hunting grounds,” lured a man to a home where he planned on killing him, according to court documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Atlanta gunman was patient at evangelical treatment center within mile of first targeted spa...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Accused-Atlanta-gunman-was-a-patient-at-16039343.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA - The first spa targeted in the Atlanta-area killings this week was in an area...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could set pattern for sustained partisan war...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/03/19/effort-to-expel-marjorie-taylor-greene-could-set-pattern-for-sustained-partisan-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort to expel Marjorie Taylor Greene from the House could set the stage for extended partisan war in the chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 Cubans in limbo as visa backlog grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/what-is-happening-is-inhumane-100000-cubans-in-limbo-as-us-visa-backlog-grows/ar-BB1eIFHa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — When María Sulay López arrived in the United States in 2014, she assumed her son in Cuba would quickly get a visa to join her. But almost seven years later, the breast cancer patient still doesn’t know when they will be together. As she gasped for breath from an oxygen tank, a result of a permanent tracheotomy, López said she can no longer work and just wants a solution. “I’ve been ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio closes beaches, Bolsonaro frets over vitamin D...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rio-closes-beaches-bid-contain-144643955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio de Janeiro closed its famed beaches Friday in a bid to contain a surge of Covid-19, a move criticized by anti-lockdown President Jair Bolsonaro, who said sun-deprived citizens risked a lack of vitamin D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Gavin Newsom's fateful decision to lockdown California...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-gavin-newsoms-fateful-decision-120012117.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom's March 19, 2020, stay-at-home order was applauded when California was hit less hard by COVID-19 than other parts of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icelandic volcano erupts, lighting up night sky near Reykjavik...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/icelandic-volcano-erupts-lights-night-231325099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A volcano erupted just 40 kilometres (25 miles) from Iceland's capital Reykjavik on Friday, with red lava spewing out of the ground and a crimson glow lighting up the night sky as a no-fly zone was established in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As a 9-year-old, she was saved at sea. Thirty-five years later, she reunited with her rescuers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/9-old-she-saved-sea-130011425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 20 hours in the Pacific Ocean, Desireé Rodriguez was the only one in her family left alive. She had almost given up. Then two fishermen spotted her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setbacks risk another summer travel washout...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210319211628-r8efi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AIRLINES (UPDATE 1, ANALYSIS, PIX):ANALYSIS-Europe's COVID-19 setbacks risk another summer travel washout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANA DEL REY 'MASTERPIECE' WITH 'CHEMTRAILS OVER COUNTRY CLUB'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/03/18/lana-del-rey-delivers-a-pop-masterpiece-with-hit-laden-hypnotic-new-chemtrails-over-the-country-club</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know you’re in for something unusual in 2021 when an album’s title track starts with this couplet: “I’m on the run with you, my sweet love There’s nothing wrong co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE:  Current Cuomo aide makes sex harassment allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Cuomo-faces-new-allegation-of-misbehavior-by-16039850.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another employee of New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, a Democrat, went public Friday with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE BLOB:  MASSIVE JELLYFISH WASHES UP ON MYRTLE BEACH...</title>
      <link>https://www.myrtlebeachonline.com/news/state/south-carolina/article250027144.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.myrtlebeachonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Has no one seen a 50’s horror movie ever? This is how it starts.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany weighs longer lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/germany-weighs-longer-covid-lockdown-amid-exponential-rise/a-56924921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Health Minister Jens Spahn has said that rising infections mean it may be impossible to ease restrictions in the coming weeks. Experts now warn that the rise in cases is "clearly exponential."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most of media totally ignored Biden's Air Force One stumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9381755/Major-media-outlets-shrug-Bidens-stumbles-AF1-steps.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Friday afternoon, the homepages of MSNBC, CBS News, Washington Post, Los Angeles Times and New York Times had no mention of Biden's stumbling incident earlier in the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates says he'll fly a lot less, eat more synthetic meat to fight climate change...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/19/bill-gates-says-hell-fly-less-to-fight-climate-change.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates said Friday in an Ask Me Anything session on Reddit that he aims to cut his carbon consumption by flying less and eating synthetic meat more often.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Current Cuomo aide makes sex harassment allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/19/current-cuomo-aide-accuses-governor-of-sexual-harassment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A current aide to Gov. Andrew Cuomo accused him of trying to cover up the allegation that he groped one of her colleagues — while also sharing her own disturbing interactions with her boss, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asylum' signs welcome those crossing illegally in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/19/asylum-signs-welcome-migrants-who-cross-illegally-in-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Texas — A few hundred feet from the murky, green waters of the Rio Grande River, a handwritten sign tucked inside a plastic Department of Homeland Security property sleeve is duct ta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces New Claims of Sex Harassment From Current Aide...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/19/cuomo-faces-new-claims-of-sexual-harassment-from-current-aide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. — He called her and her co-worker “mingle mamas.” He inquired about her lack of a wedding ring,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mar-a-Lago partially closed due to outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-coronavirus-pandemic-mar-a-lago-32a7a9694c1f738eef6af6d3fc6e5aa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former President Donald Trump's Palm Beach club has been partially closed because of a COVID outbreak. That’s according to several people familiar with the situation,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House considers flying migrants to states for processing...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/biden-administration-considers-flying-migrants-to-states-near-the-canadian-border-for-processing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new spike in the number of families and children crossing the Rio Grande into South Texas over the past several hours is forcing U.S. Customs and Border Protection to request airplanes that will allow the Biden administration to transport...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New bill forces DC think tanks to disclose foreign funding...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/exclusive-new-gop-bill-hits-back-against-chinese-funding-of-u-s-think-tanks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to deterring U.S. collaboration with pro-Beijing entities, naming and shaming the worst perpetrators would be a monumental change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star NFL QB now facing sex assault allegations from 12 women...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/19/tony-buzbee-says-he-has-12-women-filing-deshaun-watson-suits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Buzbee, the high-profile Texas lawyer who has filed seven lawsuits on behalf of Jane Does alleging sexual assault against NFL star Deshaun Watson, said Friday that he’s now representing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan restaurant owner in jail for defying orders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arrests-michigan-coronavirus-pandemic-holland-208f8d19c60910e1943d725ba804e47e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — A western Michigan restaurant owner was arrested before dawn Friday and hauled to jail, a dramatic turn in a monthslong dispute over her persistent refusal to comply with orders and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA approves ethnic studies curriculum for kindergarten...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/after-years-of-debate-california-approves-ethnic-studies-curriculum-for-k-12-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As America reels from its latest spate of deadly hate crimes and racism, the California State Board of Education on Thursday approved the nation’s first statewide ethnic studies curriculum for high…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  When Narrative Replaces News...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/when-the-narrative-replaces-the-news-9ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the media grotesquely distorted the Atlanta massacres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMY Retires 'Chow Halls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/army/warrior-restaurants-how-the-army-hopes-to-boost-dfac-usage-1.666269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an effort to change how and what soldiers eat, the service has begun rebranding its dining facilities, modernizing them and upgrading their offerings to prioritize fresh or frozen ingredients over heavily processed foods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot doctors take over hospital to reduce Covid spread...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/19/mit-robot-doctors-see-patients-fight-spread-of-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The digi-doctor is in. Dr. Spot, a dog-like mobile robot programmed to triage hospital patients, is the newest front-line health-care worker to join the fight against COVID-19.  And while at f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends -- by 'mistake'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/conspiracy-theories-marjorie-taylor-greene-1c3a8e6ac7ab9e5e1a7303aeb9f5784a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Twitter briefly suspended the account of U.S. Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene on Friday, but later said the move was a mistake. The Georgia Republican, who has in the past...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's birthday parade CANCELLED...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14395853/queen-trooping-the-colour-cancelled-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has been forced to cancel her Trooping the Colour birthday parade in London for a second year because of the Covid pandemic. Her Majesty, 94, was planning to hold the annual event in the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Junk Food Crackdown To Speaking Ban, Countries Have Unusual Rules In Place...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-pandemic-mitigation-restrictions-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From 6 p.m. curfews, to "no talking" rules, to men and women being allowed outside only on alternating days, coronavirus​ restrictions around the world are constantly evolving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC judge unleashes epic anti-press rant in libel case...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/19/defamation-law-media-protection-477193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;D.C. Circuit Senior Judge Laurence Silberman’s diatribe amounted to an assault on a landmark Supreme Court decision that set the framework for modern defamation law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Military Drone Washes Ashore On FL Beach...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/19/military-drone-washed-ashore-boynton-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A military drone washed up on the beach at Ocean Ridge Hammock Park in Boynton Beach on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Don't Be Surprised When Vaccinated People Get Infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dont-be-surprised-when-vaccinated-people-get-infected/ar-BB1eKEnL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post-immunization cases, sometimes called “breakthroughs,” are very rare and very expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance fears after CLUBHOUSE app takes Saudi by storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210319-surveillance-fears-after-clubhouse-app-takes-saudi-by-storm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance fears after Clubhouse app takes Saudi by storm</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
