<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UdkiB6dqbH4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;#trump #blacklivesmatter #trumpsupporters Trump Supporters Paint Over Black Lives Matter Mural. A couple attempt to paint out city sanctioned messaging on Co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 People Paint Over Black Lives Matter Mural...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/07/05/california-police-white-people-vandalized-black-lives-matter-mural/5381285002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are looking for two white people who vandalized a Black Lives Matter mural in downtown Martinez, California, on the Fourth of July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Duckworth emerges as serious contender...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Duckworth-emerges-as-contender-for-Biden-running-15387527.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As Joe Biden pushes ahead with his search for a running mate, Sen. Tammy Duckworth, D-Ill., has quietly emerged as a serious contender, according to three people with knowledge of the selection process, one of several developing dynamics as the search enters its final weeks.  Duckworth is a Purple Heart recipient and veteran of the Iraq War, the only finalist with military combat experience - and as a woman of Thai and Chinese descent, one of several candidates of color under consideration. While she has a lower profile than some rivals, she is being taken seriously by Biden's team, according to the people with knowledge of the search, one of whom said she has lately received strong consideration.  Former Senate majority leader Harry Reid, who has been in direct contact with the Biden campaign about its search, said in a recent interview that there was a "lot of attention" lately on Duckworth, whom he called "a highly decorated woman."  Reid suggested Duckworth's qualifications are getting more attention. "You had all the other names there, and it was as if she didn't exist," Reid said. "And suddenly people began to look at her - this highly decorated woman, member of Congress, senator."  Two others with knowledge of the search said Duckworth has been attracting notable interest from the campaign, including one who said Duckworth had left a strong impression on at least part of the Biden team. They spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private deliberations.  The Biden campaign declined to comment.  Duckworth's emergence comes as some Biden allies say former senator Chris Dodd, D-Conn., a close friend of Biden's, is taking a primary role in the search process. It is also unfolding as Republicans prepare to launch fierce attacks on whoever is chosen as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI nearly flubbed... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8492641/FBI-agents-blew-4-9M-covert-operation-storm-Ghislaine-Maxwells-New-Hampshire-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agents preparing to storm the New Hampshire hideout of Ghislaine Maxwell, the former girlfriend of Jeffrey Epstein and alleged madam, nearly blew the $4.9M covert operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  As with all things Trump-related, there can be no middle ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Trump-turned-July-4-into-a-partisan-event-and-15387416.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump, with two speeches in two days, has turned the Fourth of July from a joyful and unifying patriotic celebration of America's founding values into a partisan political event. The damage could outlast his presidency.  From near the base of Mount Rushmore on Friday night and from the South Lawn of the White House on Saturday night, Trump tried to write himself into the history of America as an implacable wartime president. His enemy, however, is not the Nazis of the 20th century or terrorists of the 21st century. Instead, it appears to be those in America who disagree with him - a caricatured blue America.  Trump knows his reelection campaign is in trouble. He sees the fight against this enemy of his creation as his pathway to victory in November. His political weapon of choice is exaggerated and at times racist rhetoric designed to pit Americans against Americans. Never in our lifetimes has the Independence Day holiday been used for such divisive and personal ends.  He put it this way on Friday night: "Our nation is witnessing a merciless campaign to wipe out our history, defame our heroes, erase our values and indoctrinate our children." On Saturday night, he said this: "We will never allow an angry mob to tear down our statues, erase our history, indoctrinate our children or trample on our freedoms. We will safeguard our values, traditions, customs and beliefs."  The president speaks for and to a portion of the country. People can debate how large or small his base is at this point, but the rhetoric of these recent days resonates as much as it divides. Political polarization is real. Identity politics - on both sides - is real.  The culture war, broadly defined, rages across the country, whether the issue is masks or statues. The pandemic seems to have added fuel to that bonfire, and the president...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Trends data shows 'Sleepy Joe' name-calling isn't generating buzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-biden-sleepy-joe-culture-wars-499e1334-4609-4fb6-ad6c-fd33c0054b55.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's quest for a viral attack line against Biden may be driving him to diverge even more politically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans leave large cities for suburban areas and rural towns...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/505944-americans-leave-large-cities-for-suburban-areas-and-rural-towns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several factors have forced residents to move from urban areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 men arrested after allegedly harassing Black family on beach...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/505945-7-men-arrested-after-allegedly-harassing-black-family-on-oregon-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Lincoln City, Ore., said this weekend that they arrested seven men on various charges after a group of white people they were a part of allegedly harassed a Black family on Independence Day by using racial s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring coronavirus cases, hospitalizations overshadow July 4 celebrations...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200705173724-gg24y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 2, GRAPHIC, PIX):UPDATE 2-Soaring U.S. coronavirus cases, hospitalizations overshadow July 4 celebrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Invokes 'Fake News' Law to Defend Migrant Workers' Tests...</title>
      <link>https://crywnews.com/business/singapore-invokes-fake-news-law-to-defend-migrant-workers-tests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;crywnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore’s government defended its stand on the testing of migrant workers, the biggest cluster of its coronavirus outbreak, issuing five corrective directions under its fake-news [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Says Fire at Nuke Site Caused Significant Damage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fire-irans-natanz-nuclear-facility-172709822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire at Iran's underground Natanz nuclear facility has caused significant damage that could slow the development of advanced centrifuges used to enrich uranium, an Iranian nuclear official said on Sunday. Iran's top security body said on Friday that the cause of the fire that broke out on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Deepens..</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6738eb091a5a26500f45c01d019c0fc9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran on Sunday confirmed that a damaged building at the underground Natanz nuclear site was a new centrifuge assembly center, the official IRNA news agency...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 dead, 8 injured in SC nightclub shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.wyff4.com/article/at-least-12-injured-in-shooting-at-upstate-bar-deputies-say/33192716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wyff4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shooting happened at Lavish Lounge on White Horse Rd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Taxes, Birth Control Top Supreme Court's Closing Agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-e2-80-99s-taxes-birth-control-top-supreme-court-e2-80-99s-closing-agenda/ar-BB16lRYj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is intercepted rocket attack on US embassy in Iraq a game changer?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/is-intercepted-rocket-attack-on-us-embassy-a-game-changer-analysis-633915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It adds to 24 hours of tension in Iraq that coincided with American Independence Day. There were claims the US had deployed a C-RAM system to confront threats to its embassy and other facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC turns into no-go zone as murders skyrocket and 500,000 middle-class residents flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8490367/How-coronavirus-BLM-protests-liberal-mayor-doing-Bin-Laden-never-could.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to figures released by the NYPD, for the first six months of this year, there were 176 murders, an increase of 23 per cent on the 143 killed during the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin becomes Russia's president for life...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/505807-vladimir-putin-becomes-russias-president-for-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By 2036, Putin will have outlasted at least three American presidents — four if Trump is not re-elected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed agents, spy planes used to take down Epstein gal pal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/05/ghislaine-maxwell-arrest-spy-planes-armed-agents-used-in-takedown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed agents raced a convoy of 15 vehicles through the New Hampshire woods, with spy planes buzzing overhead, in the moments before they smashed down Ghislaine Maxwell’s door and arrested her…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You started the corona!' Anti-Asian hate incidents explode...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/started-corona-anti-asian-hate-130000846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more Californians report anti-Asian hate incidents, activists push Gov. Gavin Newsom for aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do politicians who pushed for reopening now have regrets?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-politicians-pushed-reopening-now-123018845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How will L.A. County move forward in combating the coronavirus outbreak? Leaders from the Board of Supervisors offer a mixed bag of answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB and NFL hit by setbacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/sports-return-coronavirus-baseball-edd5661f-5fd7-4895-ac94-6e922fc12793.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even the loudest crack of the bat couldn't mask the eery silence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Black protesters march through Confederate memorial park in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.11alive.com/article/news/local/protests/group-of-demonstrators-enter-stone-mountain-park/85-2ea0c153-8a88-46bd-bca7-faf19ec2c8ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.11alive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mountain, known for its massive Confederate memorial carving and hiking trails, was also the location of the rebirth of the KKK in 1915.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/louiskraussnews/status/1279579607637917699</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> MORE RULES IN MIAMI...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/sunday-talk-shows/505906-miami-mayor-says-city-breaking-record-after-record-after-record-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami Mayor Francis Suarez (R) said Sunday he's hopeful measures put in place to curb the spread of coronavirus will prevent city officials from needing to enact even more dramatic restrictions in the coming weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Looks for Answers to the Second Wave...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/israel-looks-answers-second-virus-151255770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Just over a month after turning more upbeat on the economy, the Bank of Israel is still unlikely to tinker with its near-zero interest rates even as it confronts a renewed surge in Covid-19 cases and strengthening shekel.Coronavirus infections plummeted after the government imposed a near-total</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governors stress 'personal responsibility'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/abd3150c6329984133126c805b5131b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Earlier this week, as Tennessee registered what then was its highest single-day coronavirus case increase, Gov. Bill Lee held a news conference and issued a stern...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOENIX SICK...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/sunday-talk-shows/505912-phoenix-mayor-we-opened-way-too-early-in-arizona</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phoenix Mayor Kate Gallego (D) said Sunday that the pace of Arizona's reopening indicated to some residents that the coronavirus crisis was over and, in turn, spurred a record number of new cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body cameras' uses expanding well beyond law enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/as-body-cameras-gain-more-attention-their-uses-are-expanding-well-beyond-law-enforcement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Axon and Motorola Solutions -- both with a significant Seattle presence -- are the nation's two largest manufacturers of body cameras used by police and recently branched out to commercial sales even before Floyd's filmed killing in Minneapolis thrust their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the testing crisis hasn't been solved...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/05/why-us-hasnt-solved-coronavirus-testing-crisis-348394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation has conducted more than 4 million tests in the past week, more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once lauded, Texas now grapples with one of country's worst outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/texas-covid-19-response-greg-abbott-reopen-virus-15384725.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight weeks ago, the White House lauded Texas as a model for containing the COVID-19 pandemic. Now, Gov. Greg Abbott’s plan to reopen the economy has unraveled as the state struggles to contain one of the worst outbreaks in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds flock to beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/05/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parts of the country marked a very different Independence Day this year, with many celebrations going virtual or canceled amid the global coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look to accelerate Southern political shift...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cc5bebbca6534a64d9bac2a70cb80f52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — From Mississippi retiring its state flag to local governments removing Confederate statues from public spaces, a bipartisan push across the South is chipping away at reminders of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Taxes, Birth Control Top Supreme Court's Closing Agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-07-05/trump-s-taxes-birth-control-top-supreme-court-s-closing-agenda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 dead, 8 injured in S.C. nightclub shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-official-says-dead-injured-nightclub-shooting/A0aqRvcRSCj4EPTnPETrXI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting at a South Carolina nightclub left two people dead and eight wounded, a sheriff's official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Susan Rice's stock rises in VP race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/505683-susan-rice-sees-stock-rise-in-biden-vp-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sens. Kamala Harris (D-Calif.) and Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) are getting most of the buzz, but former U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked men and drunks: England assesses reopening of pubs... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67a750c86a62e8ea3223b91260c6df19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — It seems to have been more like a typical Saturday night than a drunken New Year's Eve. The reopening of pubs in England does not seem to have overwhelmed emergency services as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia orders American flag removed from construction site...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/5/virginia-orders-american-flag-removed-construction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials in Virginia ordered the removal of a large American flag from a construction site ahead of the Fourth of July, calling it a potential target for people protesting racial injustice and police brutality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: DNA Linked to Covid-19 Inherited From Neanderthals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/news/other/dna-linked-to-covid-19-was-inherited-from-neanderthals-study/ar-BB16lII5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland declares 'riot' again -- 38th straight day of unrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/portland-police-declare-riot-again-as-city-sees-38th-straight-day-of-unrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Portland, Ore., declared a riot around 11 p.m. local time Saturday as Independence Day marked the 38th consecutive day of civil unrest in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strongmen rush to remake world order...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/05/politics/strongmen-world-order-trump-election-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This past week, on US President Donald Trump's watch Russia and China have effectively re-aligned the coming world order. They didn't do it together, but both took advantage of uncertainty and unpredictability that Trump has helped create.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan debuts new bullet train that can run during earthquake...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/japan-new-shinkansen-model-n700s/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's latest record-breaking bullet train doesn't only run faster and smoother -- it also has a new feature that sends passengers to safety in the event of an earthquake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Biden up big, Dems haunted by fear of letdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/07/05/joe-biden-up-big-and-senate-grasps-dems-haunted-fear-letdown/3284392001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has a larger lead over Donald Trump than Hillary Clinton did at this point in 2016. But Democrats have seen a lead slip away before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY facing lot more than lost summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Disney-could-be-facing-a-lot-more-than-a-lost-15385894.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney, the quintessentially American entertainment company, has long owned July 4.  As the nation celebrated its independence last year, the firm was behind three of the country's top five movies, including new installments of Spider-Man and Toy Story; dominated cable ratings with tennis and a hot dog-eating contest; and drew large crowds to its new Star Wars: Galaxy's Edge theme areas in Orlando and Anaheim. The day after the weekend, it attracted nearly 6 million Americans to watch a baseball home-run derby.  This year, none of that will happen except for a scaled-back hot dog contest.  The debut of "Hamilton" on Disney Plus this weekend is bringing the company a much-needed win, as many existing and new subscribersare tuning in for the Broadway musical about the roiling early days of the republic then jumping on social media to talk about it. Several of the show's stars were trending as of Friday afternoon, and the telecast of the Lin-Manuel Miranda musical has earned strong reviews.  Yet the fervor over the show, which Disney acquired in February, conceals a much deeper and more complex set of challenges. With every passing day of coronavirus uncertainty and social upheaval, Disney finds itself scrambling not only for revenue but for relevance.  The results for Disney's fiscal third quarter, which ended Tuesday, are expected to be dismal, with revenue massively down compared to 2019′s $20.3 billion. But a growing number of voices are starting to ask whether a more fundamental change is brewing, a change that will affect them beyond one bad quarter. They're wondering whether a company built heavily on a foundation of in-person gatherings, and on the peddling of an inoffensive utopia that largely exists outside racial identity, can be effective in a prolonged period of isolation and fulmination.  "What Disney has to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black armed protesters march through Confederate memorial park in GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-race-usa-stone-mountain-idUSKBN24605G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A predominantly Black group of heavily armed protesters marched through Stone Mountain Park near Atlanta on Saturday, calling for removal of the giant Confederate rock carving at the site that civil rights activists consider a monument to racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prostitution in post-lockdown Greece is 'Russian roulette'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/prostitution-post-lockdown-greece-russian-roulette-033509038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A central Athens brothel was buzzing with clients on a recent hot July afternoon, and its Venezuelan workers were relieved to have the business. A list of strict hygiene and safety rules were announced by the Greek authorities to protect clients and the workers, who are more exposed to the risk of infection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 wounded in shooting at South Carolina nightclub... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/faf507c074e0df2ae1f24f54fb12c49f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENVILLE, S.C. (AP) — A shooting at a South Carolina nightclub left at least 12 people in “various conditions” early Sunday, a sheriff's official said. A Greenville County sheriff's deputy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISUNITED STATES</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8490715/Thousands-Americans-gather-Fourth-July-protests-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters in New York City burned an American flag near Trump tower and thousands gathered outside the White House as protests fighting racial inequality and police brutality spark on July 4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep fear and anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/independence-day-marked-division-streets-washington-022034790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators chanting "Black Lives Matter" exchange words with activists waving pro-Trump signs outside a fortified White House: America's Independence Day was marked in Washington on Saturday by confrontation and disunity. As it struggles to contain the coronavirus and reckons with waves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivers speeches in grim monotone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/at-mt-rushmore-and-the-white-house-trump-updates-american-carnage-message-for-2020/ar-BB16kXtQ?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militias flock to Gettysburg...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Militias-flock-to-Gettysburg-to-foil-supposed-15386643.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GETTYSBURG NATIONAL MILITARY PARK, PA. - For weeks, a mysterious figure on social media talked up plans for antifa protesters to converge on this historical site on Independence Day to burn American flags, an event that seemed at times to border on the farcical. "Let's get together and burn flags in protest of thugs and animals in blue," the anonymous person behind a Facebook page called Left Behind USA wrote in mid-June. There would be antifa face paint, the person wrote, and organizers would "be giving away free small flags to children to safely throw into the fire." As word spread, self-proclaimed militias, bikers, skinheads and far-right groups from outside the state issued a call to action, pledging in online videos and posts to come to Gettysburg to protect the Civil War monuments and the nation's flag from desecration. Some said they would bring firearms and use force if necessary. On Saturday afternoon, in the hours before the flag burning was to start, they flooded in by the hundreds - heavily armed and unaware, it seemed, that the mysterious Internet poster was not who the person claimed to be. Biographical details - some from the person's Facebook page and others provided to The Washington Post in a series of messages - did not match official records. An image the person once posted on a profile page was a picture of a man taken by a German photographer for a stock photo service. The episode at Gettysburg is a stark illustration of how shadowy figures on social media have stoked fears about the protests against racial injustice and excessive police force that have swept across the nation since the death of George Floyd in police custody on May 25. Armed vigilantes lined the streets of small Idaho towns last month after false claims circulated online about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals in at least two Texas counties reach full capacity...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/505889-texas-hits-new-record-of-coronavirus-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas reported 8,258 new coronavirus cases on Saturday, setting a record for the second time this week and bringing its total number</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE 2020</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/kanye-west-presidential-bid-july-4th-donald-trump-elon-musk-joe-biden-kim-kardashian-1202977608/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian West has spent a fair amount of time at the White House the past few years, but now it looks likes she is seriously thinking about moving into the ultimate reality show as First Lady…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: Protesters Pull Down City's Columbus Statue, Toss It Into Harbor...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/07/04/video-shows-baltimore-protesters-tear-down-columbus-statue-throw-it-into-harbor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video posted on social media Saturday shows protesters pulling down Baltimore's statue of Christopher Columbus and throwing it into the Inner Harbor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enemy within...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95698f178a15e56a0f4e286708d06668</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On a day meant for unity and celebration, President Donald Trump vowed to “safeguard our values” from enemies within — leftists, looters, agitators, he said — in a Fourth of July...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHE'S GOING TO TALK'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1077230/ghislaine-maxwell-knows-things-that-implicate-prince-andrew/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell knows things that implicate Prince Andrew and will be willing to name names as she is “fighting for her freedom”, two Jeffrey Epstein experts have claimed. John Connol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK VOWS SUPPORT</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1087067/kanye-west-running-president-elon-musk-full-support/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West announced to his fans on the Fourth of July that he plans on “running for president of the United States.” Tesla CEO and Kanye’s friend, Elon Musk, quickly offered up his “full support” …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.spin.com/2015/09/donald-trump-kanye-west-presidency-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
