<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half of Americans want THE ROCK to run for president!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/poll-nearly-50-of-americans-want-dwayne-the-rock-johnson-to-run-for-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll suggests that many Americans would like to see both Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson and Matthew McConaughey run for public office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin puts 100,000 troops on Ukraine border...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/russia-ukraine-days-war-vladimir-23880564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russia-Ukraine crisis could be days from exploding into war with a source saying UK commanders are on "high alert" and monitoring the situation "with growing concern"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthiest look for exits...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/08/new-yorks-wealthiest-look-for-exits-as-state-readies-hefty-tax-increase-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's business leaders are looking for exits as their taxes are set to be raised in the states upcoming budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE BUILDS TO END REMOTE LEARNING...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/stop-abusing-our-children-and-open-the-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open. The. Schools. It’s been more than a year since schools closed for the COVID-19 virus. Across the country and across the world, schools have opened up, full-time, for students. But those of us…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain herd on Monday?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-britain-pass-covid-herd-184428044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain will pass the threshold for herd immunity on Monday, according to dynamic modelling by University College London (UCL), placing more pressure on the Government to move faster in releasing restrictions. According to the UCL results, published this week, the number of people who have protection against the virus either through vaccination or previous infection will hit 73.4 per cent on April 12 – enough to tip the country into herd immunity. The number is in stark contrast to the modelling released by Imperial College this week, which suggested there was just 34 per cent protection by the end of March. Last week, antibody testing by the Office for National Statistics (ONS) suggested that, in the week ending March 14, around 54 per cent of people in England already had antibodies to the virus, and slightly less in the devolved nations. Since then, a further 7.1 million people have received a first dose of vaccine and nearly 100,000 have tested positive for the virus, with many more acquiring a silent, asymptomatic infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lost golden city of Luxor' discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/history/article/lost-golden-city-luxor-discovered-archaeologists-egypt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 3,400-year-old royal city was built by Amenhotep III, abandoned by his heretic son, Akhenaten, and contains stunningly preserved remains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Radio Blasts From Space Just Got Whole Lot Weirder...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7bjb8/mysterious-radio-blasts-from-space-just-got-a-whole-lot-weirder-somehow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists discovered that so-called "giant radio pulses" coincide with X-rays, suggesting they are hundreds of times more energetic than previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC director says racism 'serious public health threat'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/547251-cdc-director-says-racism-is-serious-public-health-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Thursday declared racism a "serious public health threat," becoming the largest federal agency to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FATHER:  'Football messed him up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/e2-80-98i-think-the-football-messed-him-up-e2-80-99-phillip-adams-e2-80-99-dad-blames-nfl-for-mass-shooting-suicide/ar-BB1frDGN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after former Jets cornerback Phillip Adams allegedly killed five people, then himself, his dad said his years in the NFL changed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner moves closer to California recall run...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/08/caitlyn-jenner-california-governor-run-480232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reality TV star and transgender rights activist has brought aboard a team of seasoned GOP strategists for a possible campaign for governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$60 million per week to shelter!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-administration-spending-60-million-per-week-to-shelter-unaccompanied-minors/ar-BB1frIhG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services has announced at least 10 temporary sites to shelter thousands of teens and children at convention centers, oil worker camps and military bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida sues CDC to allow cruises to resume...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/08/florida-sues-cdc-to-allow-cruises-to-resume-us-sailings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's governor said the state will sue the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, demanding cruise ships be allowed to resume sailing immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independence Day Parade on National Mall Canceled...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/fourth-of-july/2021/04/national-park-service-no-independence-day-parade-on-national-mall-in-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Park Service has announced that it will skip this year’s Independence Day Parade on the National Mall, citing logistics and planning limitations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left-wing prosecutors face reckoning as murders spike nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/08/homicide-surge-progressives-district-attorneys-479966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An uptick in murders across the country is testing their resolve — and their electability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Reporter Robbed Of Camera In San Fran For 2nd Time In 2 Months!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/04/07/kpix-5-reporter-guard-pepper-sprayed-attempted-robbery-san-francisco-golden-gate-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second time in two months, a KPIX 5 journalist was the victim of a crime while on the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturers embrace robots, perfect pandemic worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/manufacturers-embrace-robots-perfect-pandemic-worker-n1263434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After social distancing measures forced layoffs in labor-intensive factories, manufacturers turned to automation, despite the high cost. Now, they aren't going back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA considering sending warships to Black Sea amid Russia-Ukraine tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/08/politics/ukraine-us-black-sea/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is considering sending warships into the Black Sea in the next few weeks in a show of support for Ukraine amid Russia's increased military presence on Ukraine's eastern border, a US defense official told CNN Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Researchers Testing Nuke Blast Defense Against Earth-Threatening Asteroids...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/04/08/lawrence-livermore-earth-threatening-asteroids-nuclear-defense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It sounds like a scene from a Hollywood sci-fi thriller, but researchers from Lawrence Livermore National lab have joined with an Air Force team of technologists to test if a nuclear blast could be used to deflect a earth-threatening asteroid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key figure likely cooperating with feds...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/08/key-figure-in-matt-gaetz-probe-likely-cooperating-with-federal-prosecutors-480289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We believe this case is going to be a plea," federal prosecutor Roger Handberg said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage Cans Set On Fire At Transit Stations Across NYC...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/04/08/sources-garbage-cans-set-on-fire-at-transit-stations-across-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources tell CBS2 the fires appear to have been intentionally set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reigning Mrs. World arrested over onstage melee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/reigning-mrs-world-caroline-jurie-arrested-sri-lanka-e686337f8ce16add45937eb0035ff8d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLOMBO, Sri Lanka (AP) — Police in Sri Lanka on Thursday arrested the reigning Mrs. World for pulling the crown off the head of the winner of a Mrs. Sri Lanka beauty pageant and allegedly causing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Executive Actions Could Turn Millions Into Felons...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/guns/biden-gun-exec-orders-could-turn-millions-into-felons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden issued sweeping executive actions to restrict access to popular firearms on Thursday, measures that could turn millions of Americans into felons overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Party of 5,000 Off-Roaders Leads to Absolute Chaos in AZ National Forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/news/40104/illegal-party-of-5000-off-roaders-leads-to-absolute-chaos-in-arizona-national-forest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven vehicular accidents were reported by authorities with violations including DUIs and illegal use of fireworks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden targets 'ghost guns', 'red flag' laws in new gun control measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-target-ghost-guns-red-flag-laws-new-gun-control-n1263438</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president wants to curb the spread of homemade firearms that lack traceable serial numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Britain's richest men stabbed to death inside mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-one-britains-richest-men-23878440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sir Richard Lexington Sutton, an 83-year-old Baronet, was attacked inside his £2m home in north Dorset, on Wednesday night with a woman in her 60s also suffering knife injuries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant encounters up 71% as Biden grapples with border...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/04/08/migrants-border-were-up-march-biden-grapples-immigration/7130399002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection encountered 18,890 unaccompanied children at the southern border in March, a 100% increase from February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will give undocumenteds $15,600 stimulus cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2661358/new-york-illegal-immigrants-15600-stimulus-payments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York state has approved a fund that will award a one-time $15,600 stimulus payment to illegal workers. The $2.2billion program for “excluded workers” will provide payments for hundr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Villagers gather to 'wake the dead' in bizarre ritual; Dousing corpse in water...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/villagers-gather-wake-dead-bizarre-23877289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING, DISTRESSING CONTENT: The bizarre footage shows dozens of villagers surrounding the corpse of a recently deceased man before chanting, pounding on his chest and covering him in water</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic cold blast takes Alaska back to winter; -30&amp;#8457 in Fairbanks!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/all-time-april-low-could-fall-in-alaskan-city/929260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shift in the jet stream will send Arctic air pouring into Alaska, threatening to send temperatures as low as 30 below zero F, which could rival a record last set in 1911.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  America's bipolar summer...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/976080/americas-bipolar-summer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'A time to mourn and a time to dance'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Population Growth Slowest Since 1918...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/us-population-growth-lowest-since-1918-negative-economic-impact-demographics-2020-1-1028810617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J SHOT FACES MORE SCRUTINY</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/07/covid-vaccine-clinic-johnson-dicks-sporting-goods-park-adverse-side-effects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID vaccination clinic at Dick's Sporting Goods Park was put on hold after 11 patients experienced adverse side effects after receiving the shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS puts Pompeo on payroll...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-fox-news-hires-trump-secretary-of-state-mike-pompeo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The frequency of appearances on Fox News by Mike Pompeo is about to increase, and the former Secretary of State under the Trump Administration will now get paid. Fox News Media just announced via press release that Pompeo will enjoy a new contributor role, that will likely serve him well if he still has any […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health officials split on rapid tests as admission tickets...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/health-officials-split-on-rapid-covid-19-tests-as-admission-tickets/article_5b164695-485f-50ee-978a-806ad1a31bce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epidemiologists and other public health experts are debating whether to use rapid COVID-19 tests as admission tickets to schools, businesses and entertainment and sports venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deepfake' of vaping teen at center of harassment case.  But what if not fake?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/deepfake-vaping-video-cheerleaders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts doubt that artificial intelligence was used to create a video police are calling a 'deepfake' at the center of a harassment case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimon says fintech enormous threats to banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/07/jpmorgan-chase-ceo-jamie-dimon-why-fintech-is-a-big-threat-to-banks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his annual shareholder letter, JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon listed fintech as one of the "enormous competitive threats" to banks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffered Multiple Concussions During Career...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/04/08/phillip-adams-nfl-rock-hill-south-carolina-shooting-dr-robert-lesslie-nfl-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman who killed five people including a prominent doctor in South Carolina was former NFL player Phillip Adams, who killed himself early Thursday, according to a source who was briefed on the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who are 'White Lies Matter'? Mysterious group behind theft of Jefferson Davis chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Who-are-White-Lies-Matter-Meet-the-mysterious-16086042.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The email arrived Wednesday evening with the subject line,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should California decriminalize psychedelic drugs? Army vet makes case to lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/should-california-decriminalize-psychedelic-drugs-army-veteran-makes-his-case-to-lawmakers/article_4f4d7eba-3a99-5521-882a-c845daaa5d34.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Jose Martinez believes psychedelic drugs saved his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of variants will define next phase...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Rise-of-coronavirus-variants-will-define-the-next-16086019.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Variants of the coronavirus are increasingly defining the next phase of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why wasn't Tiger Woods cited for speeding after he crashed his SUV going 87 mph?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-wasnt-tiger-woods-cited-205423287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators say the SUV's data systems determined Tiger Woods reached speeds of up to 87 mph around the time of his crash in Rolling Hills Estates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo Joins FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/mike-pompeo-joins-fox-news-as-contributor-donald-trump-1234730120/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has joined Fox News as a contributor, the latest former Trump administration official to join the network. Pompeo will make his first appearance on Fox &amp; F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PRINCE Album To Be Released 5 Years After Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/prince-60-minutes-welcome-2-america-2021-04-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Songs from Prince's "Welcome 2 America," an album written and recorded before a 2010 tour, but never made public, will be heard for the first time Sunday night on 60 Minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Music As Addictive As Alcohol, Money, Fast Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/music-addictive-fast-food-alcohol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds the reason for this lies in the reward center of the brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NFL player kills 5, then self... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/rock-hill-shootings-south-carolina-aaf71f2618f139ab3781592634c8e37c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — The gunman who killed five people including a prominent doctor in South Carolina was former NFL pro Phillip Adams, who killed himself early Thursday, according to a source...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro doubling down despite Brazil's soaring death toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20210408-why-is-bolsonaro-doubling-down-despite-brazil-s-soaring-death-toll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases steady at 65,000 per day...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-coronavirus-cases-fourth-wave-4b6f697d-f560-4ec8-9470-c26a9982c939.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A significant fourth wave is still on the table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insane Bezos-ENQUIRER Drama Takes Bizarre New Turn...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/insane-jeff-bezos-national-enquirer-005815611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GettyThe bizarre years-long drama behind the story of Jeff Bezos’ secret extramarital relationship is about to get even weirder. A shady figure affiliated with the National Enquirer claims in court that one of Hollywood’s most powerful players provided the supermarket tabloid with the sordid details of the affair.After Bezos announced in 2018 he was separating from Mackenzie Bezos, his wife of 25 years, the National Enquirer revealed the world’s richest man was having an affair with Lauren Sanchez, a southern California-based television host and pilot. The sleazy supermarket tabloid’s series on the affair—which included racy text messages and suggestive photos between Bezos and Sanchez—set off a bizarre and sprawling public hunt for the source or sources of the information, roping in Sanchez’s now-estranged brother Michael Sanchez, top executives at Enquirer parent company American Media Inc., and even the Saudi government. 1155581071 "LONDON, ENGLAND - JULY 14: Jeff Bezos and his partner, Lauren Sanchez, look on from the Royal Box on Centre Court on Day 13 of The Championships - Wimbledon 2019 at the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club on July 14, 2019 in London, England. (Photo by Simon Stacpoole/Offside/Getty Images)" Simon Stacpoole/Offside/Getty Now, Nikolaos Tzima Hatziefstathiou, a journalist with a strange and disturbing criminal history who reported the story with the National Enquirer and AMI (since rebranded as “A360 Media”), is claiming one major source of the information was Lauren Sanchez’s then-husband, William Morris Endeavor executive Patrick Whitesell.Hatziefstathiou’s allegations are part of a defamation lawsuit Michael Sanchez brought this year against AMI, claiming that the tabloid media company lied when it outed him as the sole source of information about the Bezos affair.In an affidavit filed by Michael Sanchez’s legal team, Hatziefstathiou claimed then-AMI-senior vice president Dylan Howard assigned him to look into Bezos’ affair after he was told about the relationship by Whitesell, the executive chairman of Endeavor, one of the most prominent talent agencies in the world.Hatziefstathiou asserted that the affair was a convenient excuse for the Endeavor executive to break off his marriage, but AMI was intent on protecting him as a source.“Mr. Whitesell discovered the Affair and, by serving as AMI’s secret, undisclosed source, literally turned the Affair into a ‘get out of divorce free card,’ allowing him to leave his wife… through a pre-planned divorce in which he appeared blameless and scandal-free, just months prior to WME’s planned initial public offering,” Hatziefstathiou wrote in the filing.Representatives for Howard and AMI/A360 did not immediately return requests for comment. “This is categorically untrue, and unfortunately not the first time we have seen this desperate attempt from Michael Sanchez to perpetuate this odd and tiresome circus,” Patrick Whitesell’s spokesman told The Daily Beast. “The fact that Patrick has been implicated in this bizarre series of lawsuits and incriminations is a direct result of the character of those involved and is completely disconnected from reality. Any suggestion to the contrary is malicious and libelous.”In Hatziefstathiou’s 2020 resignation letter from AMI, which is included in this week’s filing, he wrote that the company included “blatant lies” in its court filings related to the Bezos affair, saying AMI was misleading the courts about the source of information.But the former AMI journalist himself has a dubious history of legal troubles which could color the court’s view of his reliability and veracity. In 2019, he was charged with 20 criminal counts for a bizarre scam in which he posed as journalists from the New York Times and Good Morning America and created a fake racist email that purported to be from a Delaware County Adult Probation and Parole officer.As the Philly Voice noted, he previously pleaded guilty to calling law enforcement to report a disturbance at his neighbor’s home after sending dozens of prostitutes there, and was told by a judge to stop watching cop movies after trying to set up a drug dealer for the police.Much of Hatziefstathiou’s testimony this week is a somewhat rambling of his defense of his own personal conduct and details of his reporting on the Bezos affair. Additionally, while Hatziefstathiou claims Whitesell was involved, the filing did not include any exhibits beyond his own testimony clearly linking the WME executive to AMI.Still, Hatziefstathiou said in the filing he additionally has “ten terabytes” of data consisting of a million documents about AMI and his coverage of the Bezos affair to support his claims.The question of who leaked information on the Bezos affair to AMI and the Enquirer has sparked a sprawling years-long hunt involving some of the shadiest players in the world of tabloid journalism, entertainment, and corporate espionage. In 2019, The Daily Beast first reported that Michael Sanchez was AMI’s source for the steamy text messages between his sister and Bezos, a revelation the Enquirer later confirmed.In a court filing last July—AMI’s motion to dismiss Michael Sanchez’s lawsuit and sanction him for allegedly abusing the judicial system—the Enquirer’s parent company included a cache of emails, text messages and sworn statements from AMI employees that tended to finger Sanchez as the source of the salacious stories. The court documents painted a picture of Sanchez as a disloyal brother eager to sell out his married sister and her secret billionaire-lover. 1200028606 "MUMBAI, INDIA - JANUARY 16: Lauren Sanchez and Jeff Bezos attend the Amazon Prime Video celebration on January 16, 2020 in Mumbai, India. (Photo by Prodip Guha/Getty Images)" Prodip Guha/Getty AMI ultimately agreed to pay Sanchez $200,000, according to the July 2020 court filing, for “information, photographs, and text messages documenting an affair between Bezos and L. Sanchez.” It was, as it turned out, a losing proposition. Last month, after Los Angeles County Superior Court judge dismissed Michael Sanchez’s separate defamation lawsuit against Bezos and his security consultant Gavin de Becker, Sanchez was ordered to pay the billionaire $218,385 for Bezos’ legal costs.AMI’s court filing, meanwhile, contained chronological inconsistencies, raising questions about the Enquirer’s initial source, that are outlined in detail in Hatziefstathiou’s affidavit alleging that it was Hollywood powerbroker Whitesell who first alerted the tabloid to the Bezos-Sanchez relationship.The text messages, supplied by Michael Sanchez, weren’t the only salacious evidence of the affair in the Enquirer’s possession. And Sanchez maintained he was not the only AMI source, a theory Bezos’ camp seemed to share.In a lengthy 2019 column for The Daily Beast, Bezos’ top security consultant Gavin de Becker wrote that his investigation concluded with “high confidence” that the “Saudis had access to Bezos’ phone, and gained private information. As of today, it is unclear to what degree, if any, AMI was aware of the details.” United Nations experts later lent credence to those claims.While he suggested that the Saudis had access to Bezos’ phone, de Becker publicly wondered why AMI itself almost seemed intent on outing Michael Sanchez as the Enquirer’s source. “What was unusual, very unusual, was how hard AMI people worked to publicly reveal their source’s identity,” he wrote. “First through strong hints they gave to me, and later through direct statements, AMI practically pinned a kick me’ sign on Michael Sanchez.”Bezos wrote in a 2019 Medium post that AMI was trying to “blackmail” him, saying the media company was threatening to publish a “below the belt selfie — otherwise colloquially known as a ‘d*ck pick [sic]’” unless the Washington Post stopped investigating the leak.“Any personal embarrassment AMI could cause me takes a back seat because there’s a much more important matter involved here,” wrote Bezos. “If in my position I can’t stand up to this kind of extortion, how many people can?”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack on Iran ship off Yemen escalates shadow war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-israel-iran-iran-nuclear-united-arab-emirates-9835ba4644959e9cb4584ca999f49002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — An attack this week on an Iranian cargo ship that is said to serve as a floating base for Iran's paramilitary Revolutionary Guard forces off the coast of Yemen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Home Inspector Pleasured Self With ELMO Doll In Nursery...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/elmo/elmo-assaulted-798513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While unaware that he was being recorded by a nursery camera, a Michigan home inspector pleasured himself with an Elmo doll, according to police. Kevin Wayne VanLuven, 59, was arraigned yesterday on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businessman plans to go 35,000 feet underwater on historic dive to ocean's deepest point...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/04/08/ohio-larry-connor-dive-mariana-trench-date-set-april-2021/7122098002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A businessman and entrepreneur is scheduled to make two dives to the deepest part of the ocean – each one to depths of more than 35,000 feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol riot defendant flips to help prosecutors against Proud Boys...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/07/politics/capitol-riot-flip-proud-boys/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one of the Capitol riot defendants has flipped against the Proud Boys, agreeing to provide information that could allow the Justice Department to bring a more severe charge against the group's leadership, according to an attorney involved in the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Population Growth Slowest Since 1918...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/america-s-population-growth-looks-to-be-the-slowest-since-1918</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s Population Growth Looks to Be the Slowest Since 1918</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Costs Keep Climbing in Threat to Consumer Wallets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/global-food-costs-keep-climbing-080444402.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The global food-price rally that’s stoking inflation worries and hitting consumers around the world shows little sign of slowing.Even with grain prices taking a breather on good crop prospects, a United Nations gauge of global food costs rose for a 10th month in March to the highest since 2014. Last month’s advance was driven by a surge in vegetable oils amid stronger demand and tight inventories, according to Abdolreza Abbassian, a senior economist at the UN’s Food and Agriculture Organization.Food prices are in the longest rally in more than a decade amid China’s crop-buying spree and tightening supplies of many staple products, threatening faster inflation. That’s particularly pronounced in some of the poorest countries dependent on imports, which have limited social safety nets and purchasing power and are struggling with the Covid-19 pandemic.Breakdown of last month’s food costs:The FAO’s food price index rose 2.1% from February.Vegetable oil prices jumped 8% to the highest since June 2011.Meat and dairy costs rose, boosted by Asian demand.Grains and sugar prices fell.Grains prices recently climbed to multiyear highs as China imports massive amounts to feed its hog herds that are recovering from a deadly virus. Still, there are signs that tight supplies may get some relief from upcoming wheat harvests in the Northern Hemisphere.“Generally speaking, supplies for now are adequate,” Abbassian said. “We might have reached a level whereby from now on even if we see price increases, they may be a bit more subtle” than advances seen in previous months, he said.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Fauci says surge on way?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/08/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of new Covid-19 cases has plateaued at a "disturbingly high level," and the US is at risk from a new surge, Dr. Anthony Fauci warned on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ARCHEGOS MELTDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-04-08/how-bill-hwang-of-archegos-capital-lost-20-billion-in-two-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast rise and even faster fall of a trader who bet big with borrowed money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers Have New Offer: Vax Cards...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/08/online-scammers-have-a-new-offer-for-you-vaccine-cards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — On Etsy, eBay, Facebook and Twitter, little rectangular slips of paper started showing up for sale in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauvin used body weight to pin Floyd's neck and never moved, expert says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/derek-chauvin-used-his-body-weight-to-pin-george-floyd-s-neck-and-never-moved-use-of-force-expert-says/ar-BB1fpqeX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pressure of Chauvin’s body weight — estimated by another witness to be about 140 pounds along with 40 pounds of police equipment including body armor — would have put Floyd at risk of “positional asphyxia,” a known danger that is mentioned in most police training, expert Jody Stiger said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Property Taxes Jump Most in Four Years With Sun Belt Catching Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/us-property-taxes-jump-most-in-four-years-with-sun-belt-catching-up/ar-BB1fp1u1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uber-Producer Rudin Ex-Staffers Speak Out on Abusive Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/everyone-just-knows-hes-an-absolute-monster-scott-rudins-ex-staffers-speak-out-on-abusive-behavior</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as other Hollywood bullies are being sidelined, the uber-producer behind 'The Social Network' and Broadway’s 'To  Kill a Mockingbird' has been given a pass for his volcanic temper. Now, former employees open up about a boss who left many traumatized: "It was a new level of unhinged."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before becoming terrorist leader, ISIS chief was prison informer for USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Before-becoming-a-terrorist-leader-ISIS-chief-16084735.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In confidential interrogation reports, Iraqi detainee M060108-01 is depicted as a model...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'KARDASHIANS' is ending. The Kardashians will never go away...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/The-Kardashians-is-ending-The-Kardashians-will-16085545.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian is one of the most recognizable celebrities on the planet, someone who can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadband use surges 30% during pandemic!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/broadband-use-surged-more-than-30-during-pandemic-industry-group-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe it's time to buy a mesh router or pay for better upload speeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline apologizes to cancer survivor who was told to remove hoodie with vulgar word...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article250491574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘American Airlines did a very disrespectful and embarrassing thing to me,’ woman says on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas's conservative gov quietly bucking GOP's dive into culture wars...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/547019-arkansass-conservative-governor-is-quietly-bucking-the-gops-dive-into</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arkansas Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singles ready for casual sex...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/nyc-singles-ready-for-2021s-slutty-summer-of-casual-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few weeks ago, Ashwin Deshmukh saw something he hadn’t in over a year:  “Uhhhh it’s happening. Host is escorting a couple out of a soho restaurant for bathroom shenanigans. They met outside …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan mayor marks homes of patients with red symbol...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210407174659-g0bx8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VENEZUELA-POLITICS:Venezuelan mayor marks homes of COVID patients with red symbol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel Calls Bitcoin 'Chinese Financial Weapon'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/peter-thiel-china-using-bitcoin-093000576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thiel made these comments after he expressing worry the Chinese are using bitcoin to corrode the U.S. financial system. Bitcoin boogeyman Thiel gave his more-than-skeptical sounding comments at a virtual roundtable for members of the Richard Nixon Foundation on April 7. “Even though I’m a pro-crypto, pro-bitcoin maximalist person, I do wonder whether at this … Continued</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military cites rising risk of Chinese move against Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-beijing-taiwan-china-788c254952dc47de78745b8e2a5c3000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The American military is warning that China is probably accelerating its timetable for capturing control of Taiwan, the island democracy that has been the chief source of tension...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Israeli forces' strike Iranian ship in Red Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/iranian-ship-attacked-in-the-red-sea-unconfirmed-report-664311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While officially listed as a merchant ship, the Saviz was likely a covert IRGC forward base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz trip to Bahamas part of federal probe into sex trafficking, sources say...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/matt-gaetz-trip-to-bahamas-is-part-of-federal-probe-into-sex-trafficking-sources-say/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe rights court: Obligatory jabs 'necessary in democratic society'...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/obligatory-jabs-necessary-in-democratic-society-europe-rights-court-01617875705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) on Thursday ruled that obligatory vaccinations can be seen as necessary in democratic societies, in a landmark judgement after a complaint brought by Czech families over compulsory jabs for children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army vax begins trials...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/04/07/armys-own-vaccine-that-could-fight-covid-variants-begins-clinical-trials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX SITE SHUTS AFTER ADVERSE REACTIONS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/07/covid-vaccine-site-closes-early-after-adverse-reactions-to-jj-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen people at a COVID-19 vaccination site in Colorado had adverse reactions to the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine on Wednesday — shutting down operations for the day, a report said. Peopl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to unveil actions on guns, including new ATF boss... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-violence-merrick-garland-gun-politics-gun-violence-7ddb30681ca3abbf1a0faa286e3df7b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is preparing to unveil a series of executive actions aimed at addressing gun violence, delivering his first major action on gun control since taking office....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
