<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FOX name dropped...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/entertainment/ct-ent-disney-fox-rename-20200117-ytbvfutodrdd3jc3ww5uk7ax2q-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20th Century Fox film studio will become 20th Century Studios, and Fox Searchlight Pictures will become simply Searchlight Pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers at U.S. airports to be screened for new, potentially deadly Chinese virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/new-virus-prompts-u-s-health-officials-begin-airport-screenings-n1117911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screening will only take place at the airports with direct or indirect flights from Wuhan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avalanche Reported Near Lake Tahoe; Several Missing...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/17/alpine-meadows-placer-county-avalanche-people-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several people are unaccounted for after an avalanche at Alpine Meadows on Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why SKoreans flipping out over US ambassador's mustache...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/17/asia/harry-harris-mustache-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might just be the most bizarre criticism of a US ambassador in recent memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Census kicks off in remote Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be84b23d6c8fd94e6fb935bd4fecb257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — The 2020 Census kicks off Tuesday in remote Alaska. U.S. Census Bureau Director Steven Dillingham will be there to conduct the first count in the Bering Sea community of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers at U.S. airports to be screened for new, potentially deadly Chinese virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2020/01/17/coronavirus-us-airports-screening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new virus has sickened dozens in China, and two people have died. Cases have spread to Thailand and Japan. There are no known cases in the U.S., but health experts are concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure building on vulnerable senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/politics/impeachment-trial-resolution-mcconnell-susan-collins/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It had been weeks since the House of Representatives passed articles of impeachment, and back home senators were getting pushed on what they believed a fair impeachment trial would look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Considers Changes to Law Banning Overseas Bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-17/white-house-considers-changes-to-law-banning-overseas-bribes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China birthrate hits lowest level since country was founded...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/17/asia/china-birthrate-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's birthrate in 2019 hit its lowest level since the founding of the People's Republic in 1949, according to official statistics released by Beijing Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorite or Volcano? New Clues to Dinosaurs' Demise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/meteorite-or-volcano-new-clues-to-the-dinosaurs-demise/ar-BBZ1Q3o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Starr Bashed Trump During Hearings, Praised Witnesses Against Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trumps-new-lawyer-panned-presidents-poor-judgement-on-impeachment-said-testimony-against-him-doesnt-look-good/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's new lawyer, former independent counsel Ken Starr, served as an analyst for Fox News during the House impeachment proceedings against the president. And in that role, he h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEWINKSY:  Are you f---ing kidding me?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/politics/monica-lewinsky-ken-starr-senate/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement that former independent counsel Ken Starr is joining President Donald Trump's impeachment defense team surprised many on Friday, but one person, apparently, had an especially notable reaction to the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem compares self to Manchester Arena bomber on new track...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2020/jan/17/eminem-manchester-arena-bomb-attack-salman-ramadan-abedi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relatives hit back at ‘disrespectful’ rapper over lyrics referring to terror attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>560-POUND ISIS fanatic dubbed 'Jabba the Jihadi ' is arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/268806/monstrous-40-stone-isis-jihadi-dubbed-jabba-the-hutt-is-arrested-sparking-stream-of-internet-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MASSIVE 40-stone jihadi dubbed “Jabba the Jihadi” has been nicked by Iraqi forces— sparking a stream of hilarious internet memes. Hate preacher Abu Abdul Bari had to be loaded onto a flatbed truc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Woman burned in random bleach attack in NYC subway station...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/woman-becomes-target-of-unprovoked-bleach-attack-in-nyc-subway-station-police/2261025/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 37-year-old woman was the victim of an unprovoked attack when another woman threw bleach at her face in a Manhattan subway station Thursday afternoon, police said. The woman was standing near the subway booth at 7th Avenue and West 14th Street when a 30-year-old woman threw liquid at her, police said. The victim suffered minor burns, according to the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can cast tie-breaking vote?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/history-shows-chief-justice-john-roberts-could-cast-tie-breaking-n1117506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief justice has offered no clues about how he would approach the question of witnesses, but judges typically rule in favor of allowing relevant testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline forces woman to take pregnancy test to stop 'birth tourism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article239389563.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaf man sues porn site over lack of closed captioning...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/report-deaf-man-sues-pornhub-over-lack-of-closed-captioning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An adult video website is reportedly the target of a lawsuit over an alleged lack of closed captioning for its videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic City struggles to keep street lights on...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/atlantic-city-going-in-wrong-direction-hard-rock-ceo-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hard Rock CEO Jim Allen said the company is willing to be part of the solution in Atlantic City but is not encouraged by recent developments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe Might Ban Face Recognition From ALL Public Places...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90453208/the-eu-might-ban-facial-recognition-tech-for-five-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasoning is that facial recognition tech is so new, yet rolling out so quickly, we simply can’t know all the risks and drawbacks associated with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Heiress Backs Bill That Would Tax DISNEY Over CEO Pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90453156/abigail-disneys-new-crusade-fixing-the-ceo-to-worker-pay-gap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under California’s proposed tax rules, companies that make over $10 million in taxable income in the state would be liable for higher tax rates based on the pay disparity between the company’s regular employees and its CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Drone Swarms Over Colorado: Mysterious Objects Secret Military Craft?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/usaf-intelligence-expert-claims-drones-21287021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Mike Turber has suggested the mysterious drone swarms seen over Colorado and Nebraska may not be drones at all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW RATINGS SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2020/01/16/rachel-maddow-ratings-largest-audience-ever-lev-parnas-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Maddow’s exclusive sit-down with the controversial Lev Parnas delivered her eponymous MSNBC program’s largest audience ever on Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's culture minister sparks outrage by echoing Goebbels...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-51149224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The minister uses parts of a speech by Nazi Germany's propaganda boss but calls it a coincidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders supporters threaten to stay home if nominate centrist...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/people-will-sit-at-home-sanders-supporters-threaten-to-stay-home-if-democrats-nominate-a-bland-centrist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa — Bernie Sanders supporters in Iowa are warning that a lack of enthusiasm for Joe Biden could bring the same result the nomination of another milquetoast Democrat did four years ago: electing Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drivers say sniper shooting at cars on highway in eastern NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article239345368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors scrutinizing whether Comey illegally disclosed classified secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/justice-dept-investigating-years-old-leaks-and-appears-focused-on-comey/ar-BBZ23bs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge military exercise could jam GPS for planes flying in Southeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article239372348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi slam reflects rising tensions between social media giant and Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Pelosi-s-Facebook-slam-reflects-rising-tensions-14983267.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Nancy Pelosi's attacks on Facebook highlight how furious Democrats have become with the social network.  The most powerful Democrat in the House accused the company with an office in her home district of cozying up to President Donald Trump during a Thursday news conference.  "All they want are their tax cuts and no antitrust action against them," Pelosi said when asked whether Facebook was too powerful. "And they schmooze this administration in that regard because so far that's what they have received."  The House speaker's words highlight how tensions between the tech titan and Democrats have escalated in the week since Facebook defied Democrats' calls andannounced it wouldn't police the accuracy of ads run by politicians on their site.  Democrats warned the policy will benefit Trump in 2020, especially because his campaign has already been able to run unchecked ads making misleading claims about former vice president Joe Biden.  For years, Facebook and other large Silicon Valley companies were widely viewed as Democratic darlings. But concerns that Facebook didn't do enough to prevent Russian interference during the 2016 election marked a key turning point, and the company's positions on fighting falsehoods have only strained it further.  Pelosi also ripped Facebook as "shameful," "abusive," "irresponsible" and intent on being "accomplices for misleading the American people with money from God knows where."  Pelosi's vitriol is in line with recent attacks on Facebook from leading Democratic presidential candidates. Her remarks were prompted by recent comments that Pete Buttigieg, the former mayor of South Bend, Indiana, made to The New York Times editorial board about Facebook's unbridled power. "No one company and no one person should have the kind of power...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR, DERSHOWITZ JOIN TEAM TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/17/trump-impeachment-defense-to-include-ken-starr-alan-dershowitz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's lawyers Ken Starr and Alan Dershowitz will defend him of against an impeachment charge of abusing power by pressuring Ukraine to investigate former Vice President Joe Biden, a leading contender for the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Coup'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/grammy-deborah-dugan-recording-academy-ouster-coup-1203470424/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED: As the music industry reeled in the wake of Deborah Dugan’s sudden removal from her post as president/CEO of the Recording Academy on Thursday — a mere five months after she’d taken charge…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Drone Swarms Over Colorado: Mysterious Objects Secret Military Craft?</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/202001171078055130-drones-colorado-mysterious-objects-be-secret-military-craft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past several months, people in Colorado have reportedly flooded authorities with information about large drones, raging through night sky there. Although local officials have said there is nothing unusual or criminal about them, commentators are not ready to leave it at that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT HAPPENS WHEN FED STOPS PUMPING?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/debate-over-whether-call-qe-110000007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In the court of investor opinion, the verdict is in. The Federal Reserve is guilty of quantitative easing.Never mind that Chairman Jerome Powell tells everyone his efforts to shore up funding markets are “in no sense” QE. Try as policy makers may, they’ve lost the ability to convince people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You're bunch of dopes and babies': Inside Trump stunning tirade against generals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-called-his-generals-a-bunch-of-dopes-and-babies-in-a-fit-of-rage-book-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new book by Washington Post reporters sheds new light on Trump’s incredible temper tantrum at his top military brass, who he also called “losers.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T under pressure to defy Maduro censors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5247995bc15a8b6bf479bf5af42f411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Last April, as a military uprising roiled Venezuela, Nicolás Maduro’s socialist government ordered pay TV providers to immediately cease transmission of CNN and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Break up big tech's monopoly': Smaller rivals join growing chorus...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tech-antitrust/break-up-big-techs-monopoly-smaller-rivals-join-growing-chorus-ahead-of-congress-hearing-idUSKBN1ZG17J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In April 2019, Tile.com, which helps users find lost or misplaced items, suddenl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Satanic' sect kills pregnant woman and six children in violent 'exorcism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/satanic-sect-kills-pregnant-woman-21298394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bodies of seven people, including a child as young as one, were found in a mass grave after families were held against their will in a church in Panama</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH GETS BIGGER: VALUE TOPS $5 TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/big-tech-worth-over-5-trillion-with-alphabet-joining-four-comma-club.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet became the fourth U.S. technology company to reach $1 trillion in market value, as Big Tech becomes an ever bigger part of the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 BILLIONAIRES HEADED TO DAVOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/davos-world-economic-forum-2020/dalio-dimon-and-117-other-billionaires-set-to-descend-on-davos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richest 119 attendees have $500 billion of combined net worth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicted To Bomb Terribly At Box Office...</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/dolittle-movie-2020-box-office-predictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This certainly isn't Marvel!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers ferry Chinese migrants to Florida in yachts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/feds-smugglers-ferry-chinese-migrants-204941696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities have thwarted two separate attempts by smugglers to bring Chinese migrants illegally into the U.S. through Florida aboard yachts. Three men are facing human smuggling charges in federal courts in Miami and Fort Lauderdale. The Miami Herald first reported they are accused of ferrying a total</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foes Sue to Force Zuckerberg to Sell Majority Stake...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-foes-sue-force-zuckerberg-024127971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc. was sued by four potential competitors who accuse it of anticompetitive behavior and who asked a judge to order Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg to give up control of the social media behemoth.The companies also said if Facebook isn’t forced to sell its WhatsApp and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa Group To March Alongside Pro-Gun Protesters In Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/16/antifa-group-march-pro-gun-protesters-virginia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A diverse gathering of pro-gun protestors set to descend upon Virginia's capital on Monday could include an unlikely ally, a local antifa group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Who's going to Super Bowl LIV?</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001097083/article/qb-index-championship-sunday-who-needs-sb-liv-the-most</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers is hunting for a second ring. A Lombardi Trophy would do wonders for Ryan Tannehill's career. Which of the four Championship Sunday QBs needs to win Super Bowl LIV the most? See how they rank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nations dawdle on agreeing rules to control 'killer robots' in future wars...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200117101055-stqv4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nations are investing in developing lethal autonomous weapons systems which can identify, target, and kill a person all on their own - but there are no international laws governing their use</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: BERNIE, BIDEN TIED...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200116232846-rwbm2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/DEMOCRATS-POLL (PIX):POLL-Sanders climbs, now tied with Biden among registered voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMBSHELLS JOLT IMPEACHMENT TRIAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/16/lev-parnas-trump-impeachment-trial-099781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of revelations are giving Democrats new ammunition to prosecute their case against Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNTDOWN TO CAUCUS: Iowa Dems undecided and under pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-01-16/iowa-caucus-nears-undecided-voters-feel-the-pressure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 2½ weeks before they caucus, a majority of Iowa Democrats are still undecided on which candidate should face Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toughest test yet for Justice Roberts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/478689-trump-trial-poses-toughest-test-yet-for-roberts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts will soon discover firsthand that while the Supreme Court and the Senate sit on adjacent Washington city blocks, the two institutions occupy separate worlds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER WITNESSES...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478704-gop-threatens-to-weaponize-impeachment-witnesses-amid-standoff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are threatening to weaponize a fight on Senate impeachment witnesses amid growing concerns that moderates within their caucus could help Democrats call former national security adviser John Bolton to testify.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden winner in Warren-Sanders fight?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/478687-biden-could-be-winner-in-warren-sanders-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden is an interested observer of the squabble between Sens. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) and Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Mystery Deepens Over Brady Move To CT...</title>
      <link>https://patch.com/connecticut/greenwich/mystery-deepens-over-tom-brady-gisele-bndchens-move-ct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;patch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conflicting reports have surfaced regarding the six-time Super Bowl-winning quarterback and his supermodel wife having moved to Greenwich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honduran migrant caravan rumbles on through Guatemala...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/honduran-migrant-caravan-rumbles-guatemala-202145836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 Honduran migrants broke through a police barrier on the border with Guatemala on Thursday in a bid to join hundreds of others heading for the United States. The latest Central American migrant caravan formed despite increased attempts by President Donald Trump to keep them out of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA grounds drones over espionage fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51100759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US officials are reviewing a civilian drone programme because of concerns about Chinese infiltration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARIANA GRANDE SUED OVER '7 RINGS'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/ariana-grande-7-rings-copyright-suit-1203469915/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ariana Grande was sued on Thursday by a hip-hop artist who claims she ripped off the chorus of his song for her hit “7 Rings.” Josh Stone, who performs as DOT, wrote and recorded &amp;#8220…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly Homicide Rate On Track to Triple...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/01/15/philadelphia-leaders-call-for-end-of-violence-as-homicide-rate-already-triple-what-it-was-at-this-time-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philly is already at triple the number of homicides in 2020 than where it was at this point last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporters getting 1st taste of restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd945e7c4c820637272a087d6b99043b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The impeachment trial of President Donald Trump has barely started and already journalists are getting a glimpse of how hard it will be cover the event under harsh new media...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee calls out perks for CEO, fired days later
...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/01/16/great-lakes-water-authority-manager-fired-questioning-retirement-ceo-whistleblower/4421510002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She told a GLWA board member that a new benefit program and changed-on-the-fly policies meant a retirement windfall for the CEO. Then she was fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Wars: NBC's 'PEACOCK' nears launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/nbc-peacock-price-launch-date-and-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peacock Free will consist of 7,500 hours of programming, including next-day access to current seasons of first-year NBC shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS moving into poor areas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c6133a81c3be90025e9142bb756f5117</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Starbucks has a point to prove: There's more to the company than selling $4 lattes to rich people. The Seattle-based coffee giant that has cultivated a reputation for being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay inmates tie the knot inside prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/gay-inmates-tie-knot-inside-cyprus-prison-n1117226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two men, one a Cypriot and the other a Brazilian national, are only the second same-sex couple to marry in a prison within the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  ALPHABET worth $1,000,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/alphabet-stock-hits-1-trillion-market-cap-for-first-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet's milestone follows Apple, Microsoft and Amazon. Analysts are bullish on the company's new CEO, Sundar Pichai, who previously ran Google, the business that accounts for substantially all of Alphabet's revenue and profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs testing male birth control -- gel rubbed on shoulders...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2020/01/16/i-think-its-great-doctors-looking-for-couples-to-test-male-birth-control-gel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Kansas conducting a clinical trial for a form of male birth control are looking for couples to test it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein lawyers want 'circus' trial moved...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e9d8114b704466ba6e5454fb09683466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Harvey Weinstein’s lawyers went to court Thursday with a last-minute demand to halt jury selection and move his rape trial out of New York City, where they say intense publicity,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB sign stealing scandal explodes: Stars wore 'devices that buzzed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/yankees/2020/01/mlb-rumors-carlos-beltrans-niece-says-astros-jose-altuve-alex-bregman-wore-devices-that-buzzed-as-part-of-sign-stealing-scandal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlos Beltran, the only player named in commissioner Rob Manfred's report on illegal sign stealing by the Houston Astros in 2017, stepped down Thursday as New York Mets manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas nuclear missile silo converted into castle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/a-couple-converted-a-kansas-nuclear-missile-silo-into-a-bizarre-18000-square-foot-castle-and-now-its-on-the-market-for-dollar32-million-%e2%80%94-see-inside/ss-BBZ1Cve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloodthirsty Squirrel Leaves 2 Hospitalized, Residents In Hiding...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/01/16/bloodthirsty-squirrel-leaves-2-hospitalized-neighbors-hiding-out-during-daytime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unruly squirrel is defying Disney stereotypes by terrorizing one Houston neighborhood, according to KPRC-TV.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
