<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Financial Stress Making 2 In 5 Young Americans Sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/money-matters-financial-stress-literally-making-2-in-5-americans-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a survey of 1,000 Americans aged 25-45, financial worries and stress due to health care concerns are quite literally making people sick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino Shows Art Cinemas Can Live Happily Ever After...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/quentin-tarantino-shows-art-cinemas-can-live-happily-ever-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino Shows Art Cinemas Can Live Happily Ever After</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITISH AIRWAYS grounds nearly all flights as pilots strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/baaba9bbb7934b6f9da725c1b79825cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Airways said Monday it has canceled almost all its flights for 48 hours, affecting as many as 195,000 travelers, due to a strike by pilots over pay. The U.K.'s flagship...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Dressed As Elmo Accused Of Groping Girl In Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/09/09/times-square-elmo-charged-with-forcible-touching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 54-year-old man from New Jersey was arrested Saturday and charged with forcible touching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi fights for political life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-fights-political-life-week-israel-votes-105832717.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the September 17 vote looming, Netanyahu and his right-wing Likud have drawn outrage from opposition parties with a push for last-minute legislation that would allow party officials to bring cameras to polling stations. The bill would allow election supervisors from political parties to bring cameras</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Booming Texas May Usher in Dem Win in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/booming-texas-economy-may-usher-080000440.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. For Republicans, the Texas Miracle may become a victim of its own success.The booming economy that helped the Lone Star State weather the 2008 recession has also sparked a migration there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Another TESLA Driver Caught Asleep At Wheel On Highway...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/08/video-driver-apparently-asleep-auto-pilot-mass-pike-self-driving-tesla/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver is hunched over and seemingly fast asleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's giant telescope picks up mysterious signals from deep space...</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-09/09/c_138377523.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next target in 'climate-change' debate: Gas stove...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190909111047-te8j6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of cities are considering legislation to limit the use of natural gas, amid evidence that it leaks of unburned gas may harm the climate more than carbon dioxide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin party loses third of seats in election bloodbath...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9891426/vladimir-putin-party-loses-third-of-seats-moscow-election/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s United Russia party has sensationally lost a THIRD of its seats in Moscow in a local election bloodbath. Sunday’s poll was one of the most closely watched regional elections in yea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Stadium Seats Empty as 100th Season Kicks Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/09/08/weak-1-seats-still-empty-for-several-teams-as-nfls-100th-season-kicks-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week starts the NFL's 100th season, but some teams seem to still be finding a awful lot of empty seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession Already Grips Corners of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/a-manufacturing-recession-could-cost-trump-a-second-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Manufacturing Recession Could Cost Trump a Second Term</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli PM former protege could now bring his downfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/937e390293d24c4e80cd5fa535a8f543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Avigdor Lieberman entered Israeli politics as a loyal protégé of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. Now, the maverick politician could be the one to topple his former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans face must-win race in NCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/460449-gop-faces-must-win-race-in-north-carolina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are scrambling to avoid what would be a devastating loss in the special House election in North Carolina’s 9th District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein accuser sent affectionate e-mails after alleged sex attack...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/09/08/weinstein-accuser-sent-affectionate-e-mails-after-alleged-sex-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandra Canosa, who is suing Weinstein in Manhattan federal court, wrote him the 2010 missive along with, “Miss you too. Love to you and the girls” in early 2011 — less than two weeks after she c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 STATES CANCEL PRIMARIES</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/republicans-in-three-states-cancel-primaries-and-caucuses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP delegates in Nevada, Kansas and South Carolina will be committed to President Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fur clothing bans advance in more cities and states...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/09/05/fur-clothing-bans-advance-in-more-cities-and-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Mexican border town, Central Americans returned by USA targeted by kidnappers seeking ransom...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-a-mexican-border-town-central-americans-returned-by-the-us-are-systematically-targeted-by-kidnappers-seeking-ransom/ar-AAGXzU9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bahamas not lying about deaths, health minister says...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/article234857817.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force acknowledges crew stayed at Trump resort during refueling; 'Not unusual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/08/politics/air-force-donald-trump-turnberry/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crew of a US Air Force C-17 stayed at President Donald Trump's golf resort in Turnberry, Scotland, during a March refueling stop en route to Kuwait, the Air Force acknowledged, again raising ethics questions about government use of the President's private entities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN STAYS ON TOP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cbs-news-battleground-tracker-2020-poll-elizabeth-warren-rises-as-joe-biden-clings-to-delegate-edge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the early voting states, Warren leads in New Hampshire, while Sanders leads in Nevada</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leprosy Next Public Health Crisis To Hit Los Angeles?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/460442-is-a-dark-ages-disease-the-new-american-plague-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It seems only a matter of time before leprosy could take hold among the homeless population in an area like Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNT:  Gaffes could derail him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/460422-biden-makes-supporters-nervous-his-gaffes-could-derail-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tenuous front-runner has delicate lines to walk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than a biopic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/08/a-beautiful-day-in-the-neighborhood-is-more-than-a-biopic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were raised on Mister Rogers, you may find your tear ducts a little wobbly at the first plinking piano notes that play during the opening credits of “A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhoo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Warren smartly sneaking up...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/07/elizabeth-warren-smartly-sneaking-up-on-weak-bloodshot-biden-from-the-left/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his “Confessions,” Saint ­Augustine admitted he had prayed, “Lord, make me chaste, but not yet.” Sen. Elizabeth Warren would understand. She wants to be the Democrats’ 2020 nominee, but doesn’t …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP GETS ANOTHER REPUBLICAN CHALLENGER</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-another-republican-challenger-mark-sanford-152428985.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Republican governor Mark Sanford announced Sunday he is entering the race for his party's presidential nomination, in a long-shot challenge to President Donald Trump. Sanford, who would be the third Republican to mount a primary bid against Trump, said he had decided to run because of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as neo-Nazi elected town council leader in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/outrage-neo-nazi-elected-town-council-leader-germany-174512591.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unanimous election of a neo-Nazi politician in Germany as the head of a town council has sparked outrage among senior political figures and calls to have the decision reversed. A political storm is brewing after Stefan Jagsch of the far right-wing extremist National Democratic Party (NDP) became</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFP joins BBC initiative to fight misinformation; Warning system...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/afp-joins-bbc-initiative-fight-misinformation-055302602.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dozen international media organisations, including AFP, have signed up to a new initiative launched by the BBC to fight misinformation. AFP said in a statement on Saturday it has joined the BBC initiative, alongside organisations such as the European Broadcasting Union, the Financial Times, First</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steyer clears hurdle to join debate in October...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190908165856-1jc0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/STEYER (PIX):Billionaire Tom Steyer clears hurdle to join U.S. Democratic debate in October</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosnians march in first Gay Pride under tight police protection...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190908144717-i930v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bosnia is the last Balkan country to hold a Pride parade, seen as a test of tolerance of minority rights as it seeks to join the European Union</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alive but lost in Bahamas, survivors wonder what next...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190908124204-8dz1l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-DORIAN/ (PIX, TV):Alive but lost: In Bahamas, Hurricane Dorian survivors wonder what next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coughing fit, jumbled words...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/biden-has-near-coughing-fit-and-calls-trump-president-hump-at-new-hampshire-democratic-party-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, New Hampshire — Former Vice President Joe Biden fell into a near-coughing fit and called President Trump “President Hump” during his address to the New Hampshire Democratic Party Convention Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California opens alternative pathway for 2020 delegates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ee5adc940b0f48c498751d8df9642478</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIAN WELLS, Calif. (AP) — California Republicans have approved a rule change intended to ensure the party can send delegates to the GOP's national convention next summer, even if President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-SC Gov. Sanford adds name to Republican long shots against Trumpg...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8e5b9b9b36ee4151ad63bf288677d089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — Mark Sanford, the former South Carolina governor and congressman, joined the Republican race against President Donald Trump on Sunday, aiming to put his Appalachian trail...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hanks unveils his Mr. Rogers at festival...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5af277479f6b469e8f3e8f22c6978d84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ever since it was first announced, the idea of Tom Hanks playing Mr. Rogers has seemed like dream casting, a match as snug as a warm zip-up sweater. "A Beautiful Day in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanford running...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/sep/8/mark-sanford-announces-trump-primary-challenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Mark Sanford on Sunday said he is mounting a primary challenge to President Trump in 2020, officially jumping into the race after publicly toying with the idea for several months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Hanks' Mr. Rogers Brings Audience to Tears...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-beautiful-day-in-the-neighborhood-tom-hanks-mr-rogers-film-brings-audience-to-tears-at-toronto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar-bait drama “A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood” received a glowing reception from fans of the TV host at its Toronto International Film Festival premiere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>82-year-old spent years going on burglary sprees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/08/us/nyc-burglar-82-years-old-upper-east-side/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samuel Sabatino spent his holiday weekends driving from Florida to Manhattan -- and possibly other states. But when he got there, instead of relaxing and sightseeing, he went on burglary sprees in vacant apartments, prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI as good as Mahler? Austrian orchestra performs symphony with twist...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ai-good-mahler-austrian-orchestra-performs-symphony-twist-102216114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can artificial intelligence turn out symphonies to match one of the greats of classical music? "I couldn't really feel the difference... I believe it was really well done," Maria Jose Sanchez Varela, 34, a science and philosophy researcher from Mexico, told AFP. The performance was part</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Previously Unknown Sources Come Forward in a New Book About Harvey Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/09/08/previously-unknown-sources-come-forward-in-a-new-book-about-harvey-weinstein/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years before the allegations of sexual harassment and abuse against Harvey Weinstein became public, his own brother and business</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,250 lightning strikes recorded in Washington in 3 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/08/us/washington-state-lightning-strikes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 1,250 lightning strikes were recorded in western Washington state during a storm that caused widespread power outages Saturday night, the National Weather Service said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Walsh says George Conway advising him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/07/politics/joe-walsh-george-conway-2020-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former US Rep. Joe Walsh of Illinois said conservative lawyer George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, is informally advising Walsh's 2020 campaign for the Republican presidential nominee, challenging Donald Trump for the presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France pushes risky bet on detente with Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-pushes-risky-bet-detente-moscow-093142003.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron senses an opportunity to bring Russia's Vladimir Putin back in from the cold and potentially help usher in peace in Ukraine, an ambitious -- and risky -- undertaking that Western allies might not welcome. In the latest sign of Macron's diplomatic drive, France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Door blows off BOEING 777X during stress test...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/door-blows-off-boeing-777x-during-stress-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A door blew off a Boeing 777X as the new plane was undergoing what was supposed to be its final structural inspection by federal regulators. The test is meant to push the plane beyond its limits. Engineers had the plane pressurized and on the ground. They loaded it up well beyond capacity and bent its wings in an extreme manner, in a way almost certain to never happen in the real world. As the ground test was underway and as engineers and FAA inspectors watched, a door blew off the plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manager: Trump family building 'dynasty' for decades to come...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb8c30ee6b0b4d579f1a915871b1fa80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIAN WELLS, Calif. (AP) — President Donald Trump's campaign manager predicted Saturday that the president and his family will become "a dynasty that will last for decades," transforming the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorian still slamming Canada at hurricane force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a93afda65a914acc85a60752459ed015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — The storm that has already walloped the Virgin Islands, Bahamas and North Carolina is now bringing hurricane-force winds to far-eastern Canada. Dorian has knocked out power to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Eating chicken linked to cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9886155/chicken-linked-cancer-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICKEN has been linked to a higher risk of getting cancer for the first time, it has been reported. Britons consume around 1.3bn chickens every year and poultry has widely been regarded as a healt…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyborg magician: Why I implanted 26 microchips, magnets...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/09/06/a-cyborg-magician-explains-why-she-implanted-26-microchips-and-magnets-in-her-body/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biohacker Anastasia Synn discusses her bodily implants, her medical precautions, and what it’s like to go through airport security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran starts up advanced uranium enrichment centrifuges...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7e896f8a1b0c40769b54ed4f98a0f5e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran on Saturday said it now uses arrays of advanced centrifuges prohibited by its 2015 nuclear deal and can enrich uranium "much more beyond" current levels to weapons-grade...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes erupt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3e1249a0f7724747a8d3cea27728811c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Thousands of demonstrators in Hong Kong urged President Donald Trump to "liberate" the semiautonomous Chinese territory during a peaceful march to the U.S. Consulate on Sunday,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
