<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>May Day rallies in Europe protest govts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-macron-europe-slovakia-0af9d56da54d0f22925af240ed253368</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Citizens and trade unions in cities around Europe were taking to the streets on Sunday for May Day marches, and to put out protest messages to their governments, notably in France where the holiday to honor workers was being used as a rallying cry against newly reelected President Emmanuel Macron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right to be forgotten: Tech firm deletes digital footprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/right-to-be-forgotten-israeli-tech-firm-says-it-can-delete-your-digital-footprint/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tel Aviv firm Mine says over 10 million requests have been sent to firms by users of platform; expert says Israeli public relatively indifferent on matter, legislation inadequate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Omicron sub-lineages dodge immunity from past infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/article-705573</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Based on neutralization escape, BA.4 and BA.5 have the potential to result in a new infection wave," the study said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>En plein air: NYC aims to keep outdoor lifestyle post-virus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/open-streets-new-york-city-05995f41ef24a97cace900850d1b1090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — As COVID-19 ravaged New York City, virus-wary denizens locked out of indoor public places poured into the streets, sidewalks and parks. They dined with friends in outdoor sheds hastily erected by restaurants, and went to health classes, concerts and even therapy sessions on streets closed to traffic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How billionaires boys' club came to dominate public square...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-a-billionaires-boys-e2-80-99-club-came-to-dominate-the-public-square/ar-AAWNFQV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBS RETURN TO DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10771401/Stars-arrive-White-House-Correspondents-Association-Dinner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrities, journalists and politicians have arrived at the 2022 White House Correspondents Dinner at the Washington Hilton for the first time since the event was called off two years in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Canada euthanising poor?</title>
      <link>https://www.spectator.co.uk/article/why-is-canada-euthanising-the-poor-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spectator.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is an endlessly repeated witticism by the poet Anatole France that, ‘the law, in its majestic equality, forbids the rich as well as the poor to sleep under bridges, to beg in the streets, and to steal bread.’ What France certainly did not foresee is that an entire country—and an ostentatiously...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Case of Marina O...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/05/01/the-mysterious-case-of-marina-o-00029150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her anti-war protest on live Russian TV was seen by millions. But is she a Kremlin stooge?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avalanche of leaks risks Jan. 6 committee delivering on blockbuster hearings...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/avalanche-leaks-risks-jan-6-committee-delivering-blockbuster-hearings-rcna26549</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The source of the leaks has become the subject of Washington speculation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China's Fortress, Xi Admits No Doubts...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/05/01/inside-chinas-zero-covid-fortress-xi-admits-no-doubts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s leader, Xi Jinping, waved at crowds of giddily cheering students. He held meetings with Olympic Games officials, economic policymakers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA tech titan's Senate run has 1 target: TESLA self-driving software...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/may/01/dan-odowd-us-senate-tesla-self-driving-elon-musk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan O’Dowd has bankrolled his own campaign to take a swing at what he calls Elon Musk’s ‘amazingly terrible’ technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL GATES:  'Not seen the WORST of Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10772223/Weve-not-seen-WORST-Covid-warns-Microsoft-billionaire-Bill-Gates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech mogul and philanthropist said he did not want to sound 'doom and gloom' but warned there was a risk an 'even more transmissive and even more fatal' variant could be generated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer shoots OWN troops as army morale on brink of collapse: 'F*****g cowards'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1603837/russia-news-commander-shots-troops-ukraine-war-vladimir-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN army officer admitted he has been forced to shoot at his troops to try and force them to fight, as morale among frontline troops appears to be on the brink of collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENTH Russian General 'killed' -- Kremlin losing '1 a week'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1603798/putin-ukraine-tenth-russian-general-killed-invasion-Izyum-kharkiv-andrei-simonov</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TENTH Russian General has been killed during fighting near the city of Izyum in the northeastern region of Kharkiv, according to the Ukrainian military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State TV shows simulation of 3-minute nuke strike on UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1603743/ukraine-live-russia-vladimir-putin-sarmat-missiles-uk-nuclear-war-volodymyr-zelensky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN TV programme showed a simulation of a nuclear strike on the UK, as tensions over an atomic war grew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury ending in NY with no charges against ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-grand-jury-ending-in-n-y-with-no-charges-against-ex-president/ar-AAWL0Cu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wouldn't buy all Bitcoin for $25...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/30/warren-buffett-gives-his-most-expansive-explanation-for-why-he-doesnt-believe-in-bitcoin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a shift in public perception about the cryptocurrency, Buffett still wouldn't buy bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing shuts UNIVERSAL, bans restaurants in major escalation of Covid restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2022/05/01/china/beijing-covid-labor-day-holiday-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing has banned all restaurant dining, shut down Universal Studios and ordered residents to provide proof of a negative Covid test to enter public venues in a major escalation of restrictions as a five-day holiday gets underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British lawmaker resigning after watching porn in House of Commons...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/04/30/1095759573/british-mp-porn-house-of-commons-neil-parish-resigns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The member of Parliament says he watched pornography twice in the House of Commons in a "moment of madness." The Conservative Party suspended him Friday over the allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt-ridden de Blasio spending thousands to live large at hotel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/30/debt-ridden-bill-de-blasio-living-large-at-brooklyn-hotel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After leaving office four months ago, Bill de Blasio and Chirlane McCray made a beeline from Gracie Mansion to the swanky New York Marriott at the Brooklyn Bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Secret Vist to Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/pelosi-congressional-delegation-meet-zelenskyy-kyiv-rcna26806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi is now the highest-ranking U.S. politician to visit Ukraine during the war, with the surprise visit adding to momentum for the West’s support for the fight against Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naomi Judd dead by suicide at 76...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/pittsburgh/news/country-music-star-naomi-judd-dies-at-age-76/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her daughters said they lost their mom to "the disease of mental illness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden jokes about low approval at White House Correspondents' Dinner...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/30/biden-to-headline-renewed-white-house-correspondents-dinner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will crack jokes before more than 2,000 guests on Saturday at the revived White House Correspondents’ Dinner as DC’s biggest annual party returns after two years of COVI…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Phoenix Ghost, secretive 'suicide drone' developed in CA, headed into battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/the-phoenix-ghost-a-secretive-suicide-drone-developed-in-california-is-headed-to-ukraine/article_736436c6-ba47-5ced-a14d-8432363e5f8f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — The Ukrainian military will soon begin tracking and attacking Russian forces with a secret new "suicide drone" produced by Aevex Aerospace, a little-known Solana Beach, California, company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas warns of synagogue attacks in case of new Al-Aqsa raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220430-hamas-warns-of-synagogue-attacks-in-case-of-new-al-aqsa-raid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Palestinian Islamist movement Hamas warned Saturday of attacks on synagogues if Israeli forces carry out another raid on the flashpoint Al-Aqsa mosque in annexed east Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Murray reflects on inappropriate behavior that led to shutdown of film...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/30/bill-murray-reflects-on-inappropriate-behavior-that-led-to-the-shutdown-of-his-latest-film.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Murray is still reflecting on his inappropriate behavior, which led to a production shutdown on the Searchlight Pictures' film "Being Mortal" last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutal Sect of Vlad's Army Accused of Murdering Own Comrades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brutal-sect-putin-army-accused-020124672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo by Narciso Contreras/Anadolu Agency via Getty ImagesBUCHA, Ukraine—Ihor Yuschenko, 61, a former colonel in the Ukrainian Armed Forces who once served as the deputy chief of staff of ground forces in the Donbas in eastern Ukraine, watched in horror as a war crime took place right outside his window in broad daylight.According to Yuschenko, a column of Russian troops advancing through the town stopped and opened fire on his street in central Bucha on Feb. 27, killing two pedestrians. This co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Man Behind the Account that Blew Up Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/04/29/the-person-behind-the-account-that-blew-up-capitol-hill-00028270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Dear White Staffers’ has chronicled the rotten bosses in Congress for two years. It’s not running out of material.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efforts to Find Aliens Have Gone Nowhere. New Strategy Could Change That...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/efforts-alien-life-gone-nowhere-032719124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastFor more than 60 years, scientists have been pointing radio antennas at the sky, hoping to overhear a broadcast from an alien civilization—proof that we’re not alone in the universe.But the search for extraterrestrial intelligence, or SETI, is like listening for a whisper in a hurricane. Space is incomprehensibly big. There’s noise sputtering from every direction, especially from the countless number of stars dying and being born. A signal from E</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffett rips Wall St for turning market into 'gambling parlor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/30/warren-buffett-rips-wall-street-for-turning-the-stock-market-into-a-gambling-parlor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren Buffett has a long history of deriding investment bankers and their institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Trevor Noah headline White House journalists' gala dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220430-biden-trevor-noah-headline-white-house-journalists-gala-dinner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president and jokes are back, the Covid masks are off and the White House Correspondents' Dinner -- Saturday's glitzy party mixing Washington politics, media and Hollywood -- is on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shameless politicians reflect shameless society...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/3472449-shameless-politicians-reflect-a-shameless-society/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our politicians are a reflection, a mirror held up to American society. What we see should terrify us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Deep Dive Into Tucker Rise...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/30/what-to-know-about-tucker-carlsons-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Night after night on Fox, Tucker Carlson weaponizes his viewers’ fears and grievances to create what may be the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depp vs Heard: Supporting cast steals limelight...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220430-johnny-depp-vs-amber-heard-supporting-cast-steals-the-limelight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veering between drama and farce, the courtroom showdown pitting Johnny Depp against ex-wife Amber Heard focused this week on the host of professionals and hangers-on who surround the stars, painting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geopolitics and glitz as Ukraine tipped to win Eurovision...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220430-geopolitics-and-glitz-as-ukraine-tipped-to-win-eurovision</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kitsch, glitz and geopolitics -- the Eurovision Song Contest is back in two weeks' time, with Russia excluded and conflict-ravaged Ukraine the hot favourite to take the crown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un warns of 'preemptive' use of nuclear force...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20220430-north-korea-s-leader-warns-of-preemptive-use-of-nuclear-force-to-counter-hostile-forces</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un has repeated his warning that Pyongyang could "preemptively" use its nuclear weaponry to counter hostile forces, state media reported Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiCaprio In Bolsonaro Beef Over Rainforest Ahead Of Brazil Elections...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/leonardo-dicaprio-jair-bolsonaro-beef-twitter-amazon-rainforest-brazil-elections-1235013649/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leonardo DiCaprio and Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro have engaged in a war of words on social media, after the Oscar winner used the platform to urge the South American country’s young people t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serbia displays Chinese missiles amid concerns in Balkans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-belgrade-serbia-european-union-939c32c64c9d5be5becd6aa3e2b67ab4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELGRADE, Serbia (AP) — Serbia on Saturday publicly displayed a recently delivered Chinese anti-aircraft missile system, raising concerns in the West and among some of Serbia’s neighbors that an arms buildup in the Balkans could threaten fragile peace in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems hone populist appeal with proposed stock trading ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-elections-jeff-merkley-congress-79c2449c353a55242c3003afa029e464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When Rep. Abigail Spanberger first introduced a bill banning stock trading by members of Congress and their families, the Virginia Democrat managed to get only eight co-sponsors. So far this session, 62 — or about one out of every seven House members — have signed on.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
