<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Biden Agenda in Limbo...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-infrastructure-plan-stalls-leaving-his-agenda-in-limbo/ar-AAP4aiR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden’s sweeping economic agenda faces an uncertain future in Congress after he failed this week to unify his own party around a strategy to pass a bitterly contested infrastructure plan that’s one of his top priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J jab linked to another clotting condition?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/574992-jj-vaccine-could-be-linked-to-another-clotting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Medicines Agency (EMA), the European Union's drug regulator, on Friday found a possible link between Johnson &amp; Johnson's COVID-19 vaccine and rare cases of blood clotting in deep veins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letitia James Running for Gov? Decision Coming Soon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/02/is-letitia-james-running-for-governor-her-decision-is-coming-soon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Pole posts most severe cold season on record...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/south-pole-posts-most-severe-cold-season-on-record-an-anomaly-in-a-warming-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extreme cold over Antarctica helped push sea ice levels surrounding the continent to their fifth-highest level on record in August. Scientists credited a very strong polar vortex, strong winds in the stratosphere, for the intensity of the cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems dial down Manchin tension...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/574988-senate-democrats-dial-down-the-manchin-tension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats are trying to turn down the temperature after days of high-profile drama and a delay of the bipartisan infrastructure bill in the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Struggles to Quell Uproar Over INSTAGRAM Effect on Teens...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/facebook-struggles-to-quell-uproar-over-instagrams-effect-on-teens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — Over the past few weeks, top Facebook executives assembled virtually for a series of emergency meetings. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortion, guns, religion top big Supreme Court term...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-college-admissions-donald-trump-amy-coney-barrett-courts-e245e6b581143bc2f87c402f7c667535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The future of abortion rights is in the hands of a conservative Supreme Court that is beginning a new term Monday that also includes major cases on gun rights and religion. The court's credibility with the public also could be on the line, especially if a divided court were to overrule the landmark Roe v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party crowds spark effort to turn down volume in South Beach...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-miami-14f942c443de2bbfd3e996d2e346ec7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Miami Beach wants to turn down the volume in the city's South Beach party neighborhood, citing increasingly raucous crowds, public drinking and growing violence, but efforts to curb the carousing have raised complaints about racism, classism and business practices along one of the nation's most glamorous waterfronts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady-Belichick bout bringing fans from all over...</title>
      <link>https://www.wpri.com/sports/patriots-new-england-nation/brady-belichick-bout-bringing-fans-from-all-over-to-foxboro/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wpri.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not only will it be the first time Tom Brady squares off against his former team in Foxboro — it may also be the last, making tickets a hot commodity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk-food lovers 'more likely' to crash car...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3777863/junk-food-lovers-more-likely-to-crash-their-car-and-get-driving-convictions-study-finds/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen 'spending millions funding Prince Andrew sex abuse fight'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3777355/queen-prince-andrew-defence-sex-abuse/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen is reportedly spending millions of pounds to privately fund Prince Andrew’s fight against allegations of sex abuse. The Duke of York, 61, is battling a lawsuit filed by Virginia Rob…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special ops troops 'hunkered down' in CA airport hangar after ninja attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2021-09-30/ninja-attack-special-operations-california-airport-3076663.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After confirming that the incident described in the document leaked on social media did occur, U.S. Army Special Operations Aviation Command spokesman Maj. Jeff Slinker said officials did not have any further information to add.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sotomayor lets NY order remain...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-supreme-courts-sotomayor-lets-new-york-school-vaccine-mandate-remain/ar-AAP351d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/VACCINE (URGENT):U.S. Supreme Court's Sotomayor lets New York school vaccine mandate remain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh positive for Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/01/politics/brett-kavanaugh-covid-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Brett Kavanaugh has tested positive for Covid-19, the Supreme Court said Friday, the first publicly known case of coronavirus among the high court's justices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CUTS HOSPITALIZATION, DEATH IN HALF'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/merck-to-seek-emergency-authorization-for-oral-covid-19-treatment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merck and Ridgeback Biotherapeutics will seek emergency authorization for their drug, which they say could have “a profound impact in controlling the pandemic.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California first state to mandate vax for public and private schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/state/california-first-to-require-students-be-covid-19-vaccinated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom on Friday announced a COVID-19 vaccine mandate for all students – the first requirement of its kind in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants' Fragile Recovery Fizzling...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/restaurants-fragile-recovery-is-fizzling-in-the-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's most restrictive abortion law back in Texas court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-austin-texas-courts-lawsuits-a7961b629e913e1008f8e929c99fb310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — The Biden administration on Friday urged a federal judge to block the nation's most restrictive abortion law, which has banned most abortions in Texas since early September and sent women racing to get care beyond the borders of the second-most populous state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE COVID PILL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-health-pandemics-a9a2245fdcee324f6bbd776a0fffcc60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a potential leap forward in the global fight against the pandemic , drugmaker Merck said Friday that its experimental pill for people sick with COVID-19 reduced hospitalizations and deaths by half.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers arrested in Hawaii for fake test results...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-arrests-california-los-angeles-united-states-946e3983622e19d5617222f763964707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hawaii authorities arrested two people from California for submitting fake COVID-19 test results to avoid a mandatory traveler quarantine meant to curb the virus' spread in the islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  OZY shutting down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/ozy-media-is-shutting-down-after-reports-about-misconduct-and-lies-at-the-company.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ozy Media's board on Friday announced that the company is shutting down, according to The New York Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With gas pumps still dry, Britain brings in army...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001205906-6xhb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-TRUCKERS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-With gas pumps still dry, Britain brings in the army</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vaxxer Goes to Homeless Shelter to Pay Someone For Fake Status...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyvn3w/anti-vaxxer-went-to-homeless-shelter-to-try-to-pay-someone-for-fake-vaccine-status</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating the incident at a homeless shelter in northern Alberta. The incident occurred two days after the province announced vaccine passports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going to Make Rich Pay,' Manchin Tells Protesters From His Yacht...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kvgxe/were-going-to-make-the-rich-pay-joe-manchin-tells-protesters-from-his-yacht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists kayaked to Senator Joe Manchin's $700,000 yacht to ask why he wouldn't support the infrastructure bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces fractious Dems with agenda on line...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/01/house-democrats-biden-infrastructure-deal-514878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi repeated her mantra that Democrats are “on a path” to pass the infrastructure bill Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Skips Town for 'Medical Appointment', Fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/574941-sinema-in-arizona-as-democrats-try-to-get-spending-infrastructure-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Bezos Being Knocked Back Down to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/jeff-bezos-is-being-knocked-back-down-to-earth/ar-AAP328N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a summer of flying high, the space billionaire is facing a chaotic moment at his rocket company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER antibodies gone by 7 months for many...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001194329-xkwip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SCIENCE (GRAPHIC):COVID SCIENCE-Delta increases COVID-19 risks for pregnant women; Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine antibodies gone by 7 months for many</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV station has 'No News Monday' so staff can attend trauma, stress management seminar...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/entertainment/2021/09/portlands-katu-has-no-news-monday-so-staff-can-attend-trauma-and-stress-management-seminar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an unusual move, Portland's KATU-TV preempted morning and afternoon news shows so the staff could attend a seminar designed to help deal with job-related trauma and stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why this woman becoming world's most dangerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/leaders/kim-yojong-the-powerful-sister-of-north-korean-dictator-kim-jongun-on-track-to-become-worlds-most-dangerous-woman/news-story/70bf32c7f581b2ab577227ea84911e4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not too long ago, even the most devoted watchers of North Korean politics knew little to nothing about Kim Yo-jong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN WAR GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001155142-62r2v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-AZERBAIJAN/WARGAMES:Iran holds border war games amid tense relations with Azerbaijan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Union Boss Says 60K Members 'Deserve Respect' As Strike Ballot Voting Begins...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/iatse-srike-authorization-ballots-sent-out-network-studios-labor-1234848042/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The countdown has officially started this morning in what could be one of the largest labor actions in Hollywood history. Tens of thousands of IATSE members woke up early Friday or were …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers stole crypto from 6,000 COINBASE customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/coinbase-says-hackers-stole-cryptocurrency-least-6000-customers-2021-10-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers stole from the accounts of at least 6,000 customers of Coinbase Global Inc , according to a breach notification letter sent by the cryptocurrency exchange to affected customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Steps Up Taiwan Flybys as 38 Warplanes Enter Defense Zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-steps-up-taiwan-flybys-as-38-warplanes-enter-defense-zone/ar-AAP2QT7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese warplanes made multiple incursions close to Taiwan Friday in the second major display of military might in two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly Priest Shot With Paintball Gun In Church Parking Lot Over Funeral Parking Spat...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/09/30/priest-paintball-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baffert's Last Stand:  Horse racing's most successful, embattled trainer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/the-last-stand-of-bob-baffert-horse-racings-most-successful-and-embattled-trainer/ar-AAP28HQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Baffert has cultivated the story of a horse racing dynasty built from humble roots. He now faces scrutiny about short cuts he's alleged to have taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissension among Supremes as justices take anger public...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/01/politics/supreme-court-unhappy-justices/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court justices have revealed a new level of defensiveness and anger in recent weeks, showing irritation with public expectations, the news media and one another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Hosts First Royal Wedding Since Bolshevik Revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-romanov-royal-wedding/31488187.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rferl.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has held its first royal wedding since the 1917 Bolshevik Revolution toppled the Romanov monarchy, with royals from across Europe attending the lavish ceremony in the city of St. Petersburg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private jet rage grows; Record fliers strain system...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/private-jet-rage-grows-as-a-record-number-of-fliers-strain-the-system.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private jet fliers are facing increasing delays and cancellations as the industry struggles to serve a record number of new fliers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Robertson steps down as '700 Club' host after 60 years...</title>
      <link>https://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/2021/september/pat-robertson-steps-down-as-daily-host-of-the-700-club-after-60-years-of-history-making-tv-ministry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBN Founder Pat Robertson, America's longest-running TV host, is stepping down from his role as daily host of The 700 Club. "'Good and faithful' doesn't even begin to describe my father's service to CBN for 60 years," says CBN CEO Gordon Robertson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bible archaeologists find Mount Sinai where 'God handed Moses the Ten Commandments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3774807/bible-archaeologists-mount-sinai-god-moses-commandments-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIBLICAL archaeologists have claimed to have located the holy mountain where the Bible says God gave Moses two stone tablets inscribed with the Ten Commandments. They believe features and archaeolo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's death pinned on cougar attack; Wildlife experts say no way...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/agriculture/nobody-will-tell-me-the-truth-man-s-death-pinned-on-cougar-attack-wildlife-experts/article_6f30de57-9c05-5bde-99ca-fb2e20582471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS — With a mountain lion skull tucked safely under his arm, Mike Bodenchuk walked more than a mile across downtown Fort Worth to the medical examiner’s office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to Build Specialized Quarantine Hubs for Travelers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-is-building-a-chain-of-giant-covid-quarantine-centers/ar-AAP2sWd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is asking city governments to create specialized quarantine facilities that can house thousands of overseas arrivals, as the country continues to take a zero-tolerance approach to keeping out Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of NEIMAN MARCUS Customers Exposed In Cyber Breach...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/01/neiman-marcus-cybersecurity-4-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Neiman Marcus Group customers are being alerted that their online accounts -- including very sensitive information -- may have been breached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican cartel thugs line up and execute 20 rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3772973/mexico-cartel-line-up-execute-20-rivals-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISTURBING video shows Mexican cartel hitmen lining up 20 rival gangsters in a forest before executing them one by one. It was released as a warning on social media by Los Tlacos, who claimed they …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER MOB TURNS ON ROBINHOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/newsletters/protocol-fintech/robinhood-florida-lawsuits </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Bonkers Revelations in Stephanie Grisham's Tell All...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/7-most-bonkers-revelations-about-the-trump-white-house-in-stephanie-grishams-book-clown-car-on-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Grisham's new book details the behind-the-scenes disarray in the Trump White House, which she reveals in an excerpt published in Politico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For first time ever, ocean drone sent into eye of Cat 4 hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/drone-mission-to-the-eye-of-hurricane-sam/1026104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sea drone traveled "where no research vessel has ever ventured" when it entered the eye of Hurricane Sam, and the groundbreaking mission has the potential to alter scientists' understanding of hurricanes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Stagehands Begin Strike Vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-pressure-hollywood-producers-negotiate-021501920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Adam B. Schiff and Sens. Charles E. Schumer and Bernie Sanders wade into Hollywood's biggest labor fight, telling AMPTP to negotiate with IATSE crews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Backs Down! House Of Mouse Settles Streaming Lawsuit With Johansson...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/disney-black-widow-lawsuit-scarlett-johansson-rsettlement-1234847437/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with more details: Just days after the first court hearing in Scarlett Johansson’s Black Widow profits mega-bite lawsuit on Disney was pushed back to March 2022, the Oscar nominee and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion mogul Nygard consents to extradition to USA on sex trafficking charges...</title>
      <link>https://winnipeg.ctvnews.ca/peter-nygard-consents-to-extradition-to-united-states-1.5607086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;winnipeg.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former fashion mogul Peter Nygard has consented to being extradited to the United States to face charges including sex trafficking and racketeering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing historic challenge, Florida Dems stumble against DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facing-a-historic-challenge-Florida-Democrats-16501880.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. - To Kelly Smith, the case against Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Market Grapples With Surge in Get-Me-Away Demand...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/private-jet-market-grapples-with-surge-in-get-me-away-demand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even people who can normally afford to charter a private jet at a moment’s notice are being forced to be</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
