<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>11 Tons Of Water And 'Special Container' Used To Extinguish Burning TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/energy/11-tons-water-and-special-container-used-extinguish-burning-tesla-austria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE:  IT WAS HEART ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/bernie-sanders-had-heart-attack-week-campaign-says-n1062736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors diagnosed Sanders, 78, with a myocardial infarction, a medical term for heart attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mounting evidence buttresses facts...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Mounting-evidence-buttresses-the-facts-laid-out-14495008.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the revelation of an explosive whistleblower complaint that sparked an impeachment crisis for President Donald Trump, he and his Republican allies have coalesced around a central defense: The document was based on secondhand information, mere hearsay riddled with inaccuracies.  But over the past two weeks, documents, firsthand witness accounts and even statements by Trump himself have emerged that bolster the facts outlined in the extraordinary abuse-of-power complaint.  The descriptionof a July 25 phone call between Trump and the president of Ukraine, which formed the heart of the complaint and was still secret at the time the claim was filed in mid-August, matches a rough transcript of the call that the White House released a day before the complaint was made public.  The whistleblower's assertion that records related to the phone call were transferred to a separate electronic system intended for highly classified material has since been confirmed by White House officials.  And the whistleblower's narrative of the events that led up to the call - including a shadow campaign undertaken by Trump's personal attorney Rudy Giuliani and the attempts of U.S. State Department officials to navigate his activities- have been largely confirmed by the text messages of three diplomats released Friday, as well as Giuliani himself in media interviews.  Independent evidence now supports the central elements laid out in the seven-page document. Even if they disregarded the complaint, legal experts said lawmakers have obtained dramatic testimony and documents that provide ammunition for the whistleblower's core assertion: that the president of the United States used "the power of his office to solicit interference from a foreign country in the 2020 U.S. election."  "Everything we've found to date validates the information. . . ....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Faced His Biggest Challenge, and Struggled to Form Response...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/05/biden-faced-his-biggest-challenge-and-struggled-to-form-a-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — Joseph R. Biden Jr.’s presidential campaign was under attack, and he and his advisers were torn over what to do.For more than a week,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pompeo go home': Ugly scenes in Greece as rioters burn American flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7540881/Pompeo-blasts-harassment-Congress-impeachment-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo on Saturday accused members of Congress of harassing his department to obtain documents linked to the impeachment probe of Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snaps at press...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7540805/Joe-Biden-berates-reporter-question-Ukraine-conflicts-interest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a union forum in Los Angeles on Friday, Biden was asked about his work overseeing foreign policy for Ukraine as vice president while his son served on the board of a Ukrainian company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA NUKE TALKS BREAK DOWN IN LESS THAN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49947836 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nuclear talks restarted in Sweden earlier on Saturday after months of stalemate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' WILD AT BOX OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a2a8dd107ea74e9da8d2115ab3a0f359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extra layers of security, intense on-screen action and a frightening incident inside a New York theater combined to create an unsettling experience for some moviegoers who went to see "Joker" on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans search for boogeyman...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/464460-gop-searches-for-impeachment-boogeyman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are hunting for a boogeyman in the burgeoning impeachment fight as the party struggles to unify behind a single strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The secret love nest of Frank Lloyd Wright haunted by fire and unspeakable ax murders...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/05/the-tragic-story-of-guggenheim-architect-frank-llyod-wrights-secret-love-nest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire at Taliesin had been deliberately set, and the arsonist had slaughtered his lover and the children with an ax before turning to six workers who were also at the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising Setback Stirs Questions About His Durability...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-fundraising-setback-stirs-questions-163549377.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joe Biden’s campaign was keeping its latest fund-raising numbers close to the vest. Then, on Thursday, the former vice president broke the news himself, putting the campaign on the defensive.At a private fundraiser in Palo Alto, California, Biden said his campaign had raised just over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMALL QUAKE JOLTS SAN FRAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-05/3-5-earthquake-near-daly-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 3.5 earthquake occurred one mile from Daly City, two miles from South San Francisco and three miles from San Francisco on Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUN SALES SPIKE...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/monthly-gun-sales-up-10-percent-since-last-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;September 2019 saw 10 percent more gun sales than September 2018, according to two analyses of background check data released this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney ramps up rhetoric on Trump, but what's his next move?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/76ab7ccee90441af97d0febc918c22b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — In the hours after President Donald Trump called on China to investigate his political foe — plowing through another political guardrail — Democrats and Trump critics looked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spits at audience, claps during violent scenes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/05/hero-confronts-unruly-man-who-terrified-patrons-at-joker-screening-witnesses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s the hero “Joker” fans deserved. A mystery man known only as “V for Vegas” confronted an unruly patron during a screening of the new Joaquin Phoenix flick Friday night in Time…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Smugglers Rescue Cops Pursuing Them in Atlantic Ocean...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/05/spanish-police-plucked-from-ocean-by-drugs-smugglers-they-were-chasing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three officers were hauled to safety after their boat crashed with vessel they were pursuing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Cuts Loose on Romney: 'Pompous Ass' Who 'Choked'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/trump-cuts-loose-on-mitt-romney-he-is-a-pompous-ass-who-choked-and-so-bad-for-rs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump began this week's Saturday morning rants in the usual fashion, bashing the media for being "fixed" and "corrupt", but after those few tweets were out of the wa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Fukushima plant, a million-ton headache: Radioactive water...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/fukushima-plant-million-tonne-headache-radioactive-water-035703047.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the grounds of the ravaged Fukushima Daiichi nuclear plant sits a million-tonne headache for the plant's operators and Japan's government: tank after tank of water contaminated with radioactive elements. All those entering must wear elaborate protection: a full body suit, three layers of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most illegal crossings in 12 years: Border Patrol took 851,000 into custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/most-illegal-crossings-in-12-years-border-patrol-took-851-000-into-custody-during-fiscal-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents working along the U.S.-Mexico border took into custody approximately 851,000 people in the U.S. government’s fiscal 2019, marking the highest number of arrests since 2007, according to federal data exclusively obtained by the Washington Examiner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested and taken to court for going topless in own home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/woman-arrested-after-going-topless-20465728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law says she could be on sex offenders' register for 10 years if convicted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance video shows man struck by lightning; Saved by good Samaritans...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/surveillance-video-shows-man-struck-lightning-saved-good/story?id=66077499</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video obtained by Houston ABC station KTRK shows the moment a man was struck by lightning Thursday, seconds before three good Samaritans rushed to his aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind Texas firewall, suburban shifts leave Trump vulnerable...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/09/28/behind-the-texas-firewall-suburban-shifts-leave-trump-vulnerable-can-strongholds-save-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONROE, Texas - It’s a steamy Friday night and, this being Texas, that means high school football - the glaring lights, the band and cheerleaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WW3 over 'deepfake'?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ww3-break-out-over-deepfake-20401173</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Verification expert Shamir Allibhai warns war could break out over manufactured evidence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rampaging gangs of violent monkeys launching attacks on monastery visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/rampaging-gangs-violent-monkeys-launching-20442612</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desperate measures as the Indian street gangsters as they take over the living quarters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Orders Big Cut to National Security Staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/trump-orders-cut-to-national-security-staff-after-whistle-blower-1.1326901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has ordered a substantial reduction in the staff of the National Security Council, according to five people familiar with the plans, as the White House confronts an impeachment inquiry touched off by a whistle-blower complaint related to the agency’s work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even High-Income Millennials Fear They'll Need to Work Forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/even-high-income-millennials-fear-they-ll-need-to-work-forever-1.1326941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of high-income millennials ages 30 to 34 fear they’ll have to work forever because they won’t be able to save enough to retire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court abortion case poses major test for Trump picks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/464475-supreme-court-abortion-case-poses-major-test-for-trump-picks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court's decision to take up a Louisiana abortion case this term will pose a major test for President Trump's nominees on the politically divisive issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloodbath in Chinatown...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/05/4-homeless-men-found-murdered-in-chinatown-suspect-in-custody/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four homeless men were found beaten to death in Chinatown early Saturday and a fifth was critically injured in a terrifying Lower Manhattan rampage, police said. Police responding to reports of an …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hundreds' of young trans seeking to return to original sex...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/hundreds-of-young-trans-people-seeking-help-to-return-to-original-sex-11827740 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who detransitioned in 2018 says there are many people who have had gender reassignment surgery who wish they hadn't.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD: Impeachment almost certain...</title>
      <link>https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2019/oct/03/legendary-reporter-bob-woodward-talks-trump-impeac/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Woodward told a large crowd that journalists need to work harder to verify information before reporting it and that Trump’s actions have not yet reached the lengths of Watergate, though they are inching closer every day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAFFIC HELL:  LAX ban on taxi, UBER and LYFT curbside pickups irks passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/lax-ban-on-taxi-uber-and-lyft-curbside-pickups-irks-passengers-its-inconvenient/ar-AAIiNpM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC:  We may be closing in on discovery of alien life...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/we-may-be-closing-discovery-alien-life-are-we-prepared-ncna1062176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New robotic craft bound for Mars should give us our best shot at finding life on the Red Planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry sues UK tabloids over 'phone hacking'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/prince-harry-sues-uk-tabloids-over-phone-hacking-195301317.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry has launched legal action against two British tabloid newspaper publishers, they confirmed Friday, over alleged phone hacking -- just days after he condemned the press for critical coverage of his wife. Harry, 35, extended his campaign against the tabloids with fresh action after suing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGA POLL:  Do Americans Support Impeaching Trump?</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/do-americans-support-impeaching-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking polls that ask whether respondents support impeaching President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR ON PIERS MORGAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/prince-harry-launches-all-out-war-on-the-sun-and-mirror-and-piers-morgan-in-phone-hacking-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry’s lawsuits against the Sun and Mirror add to Meghan Markle’s against the Mail on Sunday. War on the tabloids has been declared—and Piers Morgan’s in the line of fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport Facial Recognition Programs Under Scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/10/federal-privacy-board-reviewing-dhs-airport-facial-recognition-programs/160341/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An agency shared new details around its recent observations of one TSA biometrics pilot—and what it aims to assess in a comprehensive report it’s generating over the course of the next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top CIA lawyer made criminal referral on whistleblower complaint...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/cia-s-top-lawyer-made-criminal-referral-whistleblower-s-complaint-n1062481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts are raising questions about why the Justice Department did not open an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRANDUS:  Real reason for his meltdowns...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-real-reason-for-trumps-meltdowns-2019-10-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump still has not learned — much less respected — the essential fact that he has been, for three years now, a public servant. A lack of accountability may...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Trump cursed out staff over DRUDGE headline about billions in aid to Mexico... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7537749/Trump-flew-rage-shouted-f-k-Mexico-wall-money-fell-apart.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I'm not getting $5 billion for the wall, and instead I'm paying Mexico $5 billion? What the f**k am I getting out of this?' Trump boomed after he saw a DRUDGE REPORT headline about him caving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUBPOENAS  FLY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2e7caf3c8fd41d7aec36acd9d1ea5f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and the Democrats' impeachment inquiry (all times local): 6:25 p.m. A House committee has sent a subpoena to the White House...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump formally objecting to probe, won't say he'll cooperate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1fe55157bfcb4f1c96cf128c2c5f2d99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The impeachment investigation into President Donald Trump widened on Friday into a constitutional battle between the executive branch and Congress, as Democrats subpoenaed White...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested after asking cops to test purity of her meth...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/alabama/meth-test-arrest-215760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Alabama woman concerned that her methamphetamine may have been tainted with another drug asked police to test her stash, a service request that resulted in her arrest for possession of a controll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Inspector General to Review Handling of President's Tax Returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/treasury-inspector-general-to-review-handling-of-trumps-tax-returns/ar-AAIiDAo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie keeping health condition 'mystery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/04/bernie-sanders-had-a-common-procedure-so-why-the-mystery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — “None of us know when a medical emergency will affect us,” Senator Bernie Sanders wrote in a tweet from Desert Springs Hospital Medical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planes Landing At JFK Airport Targeted By Laser Pointers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/10/03/planes-jfk-laser-pointers-fbi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators are now looking for the person or people who have been doing this and say they believe the suspects are somewhere around Roslyn, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA bans 'deep fakes' video, audio close to elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/california-bans-deep-fakes-video-203227787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is trying to stop people from deceptively editing videos and audio in ways that are aimed at influencing elections. Legislation signed by Gov. Gavin Newsom on Thursday bans the distribution of manipulated videos and pictures that maliciously aim to give someone a false impression about a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman's 'box of sex toys' contained lover's decapitated head...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/world/ny-missing-man-decapitated-head-sex-toys-partner-neighbor-20191004-7wyawtl4pja2dg7owt4uprjsly-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decapitated head of a missing man was found in a box his partner told neighbors contained sex toys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kudlow Refuses to Promise Biden Investigation Won't Be Part of China Trade Talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/larry-kudlow-refuses-to-promise-biden-investigation-wont-be-part-of-china-trade-talks-not-going-to-be-front-and-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United States National Economic Council Director Larry Kudlow refused to promise that President Donald Trump's call for China to investigate a political rival won't be part of ongoing trade talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic license plate readers making getaway cars extinct...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1722215/technology-is-making-getaway-cars-extinct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology has made it easier than ever to track suspects, but privacy advocates have questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Millennials' Brains Shrink After Income Drops...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/young-adults-who-experience-drops-in-income-have-poorer-brain-health-in-middle-age/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young adults who face annual income drops of 25% or more may be at a greater risk of developing thinking problems and diminished brain health later on in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren fires senior staffer for 'inappropriate behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/04/warren-staffer-inappropriate-behavior-campaign-2020-028583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Target Pence...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/04/intel-watchdog-trump-ukraine-027432</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier hero from El Paso shooting arrested for going AWOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/2019/10/04/soldier-praised-as-hero-during-el-paso-shooting-arrested-after-going-awol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The soldier was picked up hundreds of miles from Fort Bliss, near Fort Hood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRECTV Charges Early Termination Fee After Woman Dies at 102...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/directv-charges-woman-early-termination-fee-after-she-dies-at-102/ar-AAIaALW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, Russia Deepen Tech Ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2019/10/china-russia-are-turning-each-other-tech-help-west-limits-access/160364/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With joint dialogues, incubators, and technology parks, Beijing and Moscow are seeking to overcome deficiencies and compete with the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text messages boost pressure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-openly-calls-ukraine-china-investigate-biden-163424837.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Text messages sent by US diplomats revealing an apparent effort by Donald Trump's government to push Ukraine to investigate his political rival Joe Biden bolstered the Democrats' impeachment inquiry Friday, as the president suggested he might not cooperate with the probe. The investigation picked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Fed to extend operations to pump money into markets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-fed-extend-operations-pump-money-markets-nov-181502121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Federal Reserve Bank said Friday it will continue to inject billions into the US financial plumbing on a daily basis through November 4, extending the operations by three weeks. The effort, begun in mid-September, is aimed at preventing a spike in short-term interest rates, the New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Denies Quid Pro Quo, but Envoys Had Doubts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-denies-quid-pro-quo-for-ukraine-but-envoys-had-their-doubts/ar-AAIhh4K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customs Officer Harasses Journalist at Dulles...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2019/10/us-customs-officer-harasses-defense-one-journalist-dulles/160380/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Repeating â€œYou write propaganda, right?â€�, officer held passport until he received an affirmative answer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry claims 'illegal interception of voicemails'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/prince-harry-files-high-court-claims-over-illegal-interception-of-voicemail-messages-11827492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The claim comes just days after Harry and Meghan announced they were suing the Mail on Sunday newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian hackers said to target presidential campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b41730128be847b9924c421716ddc024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Microsoft said Friday that hackers linked to the Iranian government targeted a U.S. presidential campaign, as well as government officials, media targets and prominent expatriate...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
