<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>X:  Madonna suffering 'indescribable' pain; Delays rest of Tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/12/25/madonna-says-shes-in-indescribable-pain-cancels-last-miami-show-delays-european-dates-to-avoid-irreversible-damage-to-my-body</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna is still on her theater tour, and it’s not going so well. On Sunday she cancelled her final show in Miami because she’s in “indescribable” pain, she says on Instagra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Merry Christmas' bank robber throws cash at passers-by...</title>
      <link>https://www.kktv.com/content/news/Bank-robbed-in-downtown-Springs-566439071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kktv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Witnesses say a robber was doing everything he could to get caught after holding up a downtown Springs bank in the middle of lunchtime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison cameras hacked, live-streamed on YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/prison-camera-hacked-streamed-live-on-youtube</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Thailand say they are investigating an apparent online break-in by a computer hacker that allowed him to broadcast surveillance video from inside a prison in the country's south.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell flexes reelection muscle with $1B gift for Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/475831-mcconnell-flexes-reelection-muscle-with-1b-gift-for-kentucky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is delivering more than $1 billion worth of federal spending and tax breaks to his Kentucky constituents, just in time for Christmas and ahead of a potentially tough reelection campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veiled women make Santa dolls in Gaza Strip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/veiled-women-santa-dolls-gaza-strip-171252475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beit Lahia (Palestinian Territories) (AFP) - The scene on Tuesday morning in the northern Gaza Strip could at first look incongruous -- a group of women in black niqab veils sewing Santa Claus dolls for Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Chinese woman sues over egg freezing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/single-chinese-woman-sues-over-egg-freezing-100529352.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A single woman in China has gone to court challenging rules that forbid unmarried women from freezing their eggs in the first case of its kind in the country. Teresa Xu said she was prompted to take legal action after a top hospital in Beijing declined to freeze her eggs last year, and instead told</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French transport strike enters fourth week...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gloomy-christmas-eve-20th-day-french-strike-172857134.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas Day brought no respite for travellers in France as a transport strike entered its fourth week, ruining the plans of thousands to share a traditional meal and quality time with loved ones. Many scrambled at the last minute to make alternative arrangements as the protest against pension reform</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of UK royals back in spotlight after Queen's year to forget...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cost-uk-royals-back-spotlight-queens-forget-060154217.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a torrid 2019 in which the queen's son Prince Andrew was implicated in an underage sex abuse scandal, many in Britain are again asking if the monarchy has gotten too big -- and rich -- for its own good. The family's year to forget may encourage Prince Charles, set to eventually take over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro says 'fine' now but lost memory after fall...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-says-fine-now-lost-memory-fall-003907068.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro temporarily lost his memory after hitting his head in a fall at his official residence, he said in an interview on Tuesday. "The following day, this morning, I managed to get back a lot of things and now I am fine," Bolsonaro said in a telephone interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON'S END:  Ravens, Saints, 49ers top 3 teams in AP poll...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/66107090272c0ef09254e4029da3b9ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Lamar Jackson and the Baltimore Ravens have already made plenty of history this season. They have won 11 consecutive games, have the NFL’s best record at 13-2 and have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonstop violence as Baltimore nears record homicide rate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/521b92265e24a213b2a3d9218fc5774b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — Baltimore could wrap up 2019 with its highest per-capita homicide rate on record as killings of adults and minors alike for drugs, retribution, money or no clear reason continue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We only learned about this when reporter called us'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/451e897954d3202a19996e367ead9299</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic presidential contender Michael Bloomberg cut ties with a contractor that used prisoners to make calls for his presidential campaign, he said in a statement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope offers hope against darkness in Christmas Day message...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00585ce6767d6bde058dcac77facab3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis offered a Christmas message of hope Wednesday against darkness that cloaks conflicts and relationships in large parts of the world from the Middle East to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA's Ratings Crash Ahead of Christmas Showcase...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/12/24/nbas-ratings-crash-ahead-christmas-showcase/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV ratings for the National Basketball Association are taking a tumble as we approach Christmas week, even as the sports media tries to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged bank robber throws money into air, yells, 'Merry Christmas!'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/24/alleged-bank-robber-throws-money-into-air-yells-merry-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s one way to spread some holiday cheer. A Colorado bank robber tossed fistfuls of cash into the air and exclaimed, “Merry Christmas!” following a stick-up, according to a rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Method to Silence Dissent: Military Service in Arctic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-russian-method-to-silence-dissent-military-service-in-the-arctic/ar-BBYji5j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING document dump shows 'disturbing' picture...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boeing-document-dump-shows-disturbing-picture-737-max-205910958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing provided a fresh batch of incriminating documents on the 737 MAX to regulators and congressional investigators, only hours after announcing a leadership shakeup, officials confirmed Tuesday. The document dump came just before Christmas, when many officials already are on holiday, and "appear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope marks joyful Christmas Eve after less-than-joyful year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/adad91b6d695089d744116b87a7baa58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis assured the faithful on Christmas Eve that God loves everyone — “even the worst of us” — as he celebrated the joyous birth of Christ after a less-than-joyful year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alive Inside: How to reach 'vegetative' patients -- aware of everything...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/alive-inside-how-do-we-reach-vegetative-patients-when-tests-show-theyre-aware-of-everything</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not clear how much Jeff Tremblay knows about the role he’s playing in a revolution in the treatment of the catastrophically brain injured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs process numbers, count their treats...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/a-new-study-shows-dogs-can-process-numbers-and-theyre-counting-their-treats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Our work not only shows that dogs use a similar part of their brain to process numbers of objects as humans do — it shows that they don’t need to be trained to do it’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New BOEING docs show 'very disturbing' concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-boeing-737max/new-boeing-737-max-documents-show-very-disturbing-employee-concerns-u-s-house-aide-idUSKBN1YS1BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Co documents under review by a U.S. congressional panel appear to point t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake, Dangerous Kids Products For Sale On AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/12/24/warning-fake-dangerous-kids-products-are-turning-up-for-sale-on-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was advertised to look like a high end brand, but this car seat is a copycat. Legitimate sellers say it's one of many potentially dangerous kids products sold on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crop duster spreads 100 gallons of holy water on Louisiana town...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/crop-duster-spreads-100-gallons-holy-water-louisiana/story?id=67914735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crop duster spread holy water on a Louisiana town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the REDSKINS Plummeted to Rock Bottom...</title>
      <link>https://www.theringer.com/nfl/2019/12/24/21035742/washington-redskins-rock-bottom-dan-snyder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theringer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The professional football team in the nation’s capital was the hottest ticket in town for decades. But under Dan Snyder’s ownership, the franchise has lost a lot of games and managed to alienate even some of its most dedicated fans. What made one of most unshakable fandoms in America give up on its team?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA plans to dramatically shrink Navy destroyer fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/naval/2019/12/24/pentagon-proposes-big-cuts-to-us-navy-destroyer-construction-retiring-13-cruisers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pentagon proposal sent to the white house would cut five destroyers out of the budget over the next five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI iooking into former KY gov's pardons...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/politics/2019/12/23/matt-bevin-pardons-fbi-asking-questions-situation/2737842001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators are looking into former Kentucky Gov. Matt Bevin's last-minute pardons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW WEINSTEIN CASES BEING REVIEWED BY LA DA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/harvey-weinstein-cases-review-1203451578/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein is set to go on trial next month in New York on charges of rape and sexual assault. But no matter how that case turns out, he will still face criminal jeopardy in Los Angeles. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'God Has Me Right Where He Wants Me': Bieber Announces New Single 'Yummy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/12/24/god-has-me-right-where-he-wants-me-justin-bieber-announces-new-single-called-yummy-for-january-3rd-2020-tour-dates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber released a video announcement today for new music and tour dates. His single, “Yummy,” comes January 3rd. He says, “As humans we are imperfect. My past, my mistakes,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Exploited Prison Labor to Make 2020 Campaign Phone Calls...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/12/24/mike-bloomberg-2020-prison-labor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bloomberg campaign said it ended the arrangement after learning of the prison call centers from an The Intercept inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan could release Fukushima radioactive water into environment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/japan-could-release-fukushima-radioactive-water-environment-072000457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Japanese government agency has proposed releasing radioactive water from the stricken Fukushima nuclear plant into the environment, as storage space runs out. About a million tonnes of contaminated water has built up since then and the tanks that hold it are almost full. An extensive pumping and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloomy Christmas Eve on the 20th day of French strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gloomy-christmas-eve-20th-day-french-strike-131303722.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas Eve 2019 was an unusually gloomy one for France, as the 20th day of a transport strike left many scrambling Tuesday to reach their loved ones for the traditional family feast, while others simply gave up. The protest against pension reform has led to thousands of trains being cancelled or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAUGHTY OR NICE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0c322ada689cc214d75e6b9a2f91720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — President Donald Trump said Tuesday that North Korean leader Kim Jong Un may be planning to give him “a nice present" such as a “beautiful vase” for Christmas rather than a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser-Linked Satellites Could Deliver Worldwide 'Internet from Space'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/12/laser-linked-satellites-could-deliver-internet-space/162009/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such a network could potentially reach remote and underserved areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Accused of Humiliating Needy For Throwing Cash at Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/rapper-blueface-accused-humiliating-needy-after-throwing-large-amounts-cash-homeless-people-1478965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable News Moments That Defined the 2010s...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/best-decade-ever-the-cable-news-moments-that-defined-the-2010s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the 2010s come to a close, it's an interesting exercise to consider how future historians will help explain just what the hell happened over the past decade, which so happens to coincide neatl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren embraced high-dollar fundraiser circuit for years -- until just before her presidential campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Warren-embraced-the-high-dollar-fundraiser-14929335.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chase Williams grinned broadly as he stood for a photo next to Sen. Elizabeth Warren, chatting briefly with the Massachusetts Democrat before moving on so someone else could have their turn.  It was the kind of moment that has become a ubiquitous part of Warren's presidential campaign and its long "selfie lines," where supporters wait for hours to pose with her at no charge.  But this shot, taken in October 2017, was at an entirely different kind of event: an exclusive "backstage" reception that took place in the vault of a former Cleveland bank. And that was the day's low-rent affair - donors who agreed to pay more attended an even more exclusive shindig with Warren that day, according to two people familiar with her schedule.  The events were part of a high-dollar fundraising program that Warren had embraced her entire political career, from her first Senate run in 2011 through her reelection last year. Warren was so successful at it that she was able to transfer $10 million of her Senate cash to help launch her presidential bid.  But in the past year Warren has undergone a transformation, moving from one of the Democratic Party's biggest draws at high-dollar fundraisers to a presidential candidate who has sworn them off as sinister attempts to sell access.  In a debate last week, Warren criticized rival Pete Buttigieg for having an exclusive fundraiser in a crystal-filled wine cave in Napa Valley, prompting the South Bend, Indiana, mayor to respond that she shouldn't issue "purity tests you cannot yourself pass."  Williams, who supports Buttigieg in the presidential race, said Warren's position was "disingenuous."  "I am frustrated because she said, 'I don't do this. This isn't something I do.' And two years ago she very much did do that, and I was in the room," said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia unveils new 'unstoppable' 7,000mph hypersonic missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-unveils-new-unstoppable-7000mph-21158649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The undetectable high speed Russian missile can now be launched from land, sea or air and travel at a quite extraordinary 7,000mph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1917' Star on Filming Best War Movie in 20 Years -- in One Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/1917-star-george-mackay-on-filming-the-best-war-movie-in-over-20-yearsin-one-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Mendes’ new war epic is being hailed as “the best war film since ‘Saving Private Ryan.’” Star George MacKay talks the arduous task of filming the whole thing as just one take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The surge is real': Klobuchar makes late push in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/24/amy-klobuchar-iowa-089646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her strong debate performance and Midwestern sensibility raises hopes of a surprise showing in Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON'S BEATINGS: Brawls break out in malls across country...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7823773/Brawls-break-malls-minute-shoppers-try-score-deal-Super-Saturday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American shoppers spent a record $34.4billion on Super Saturday, the biggest single day in American retail history, but the weekend was marred by violent incidents at several locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite image heightens concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/satellite-image-of-construction-at-north-korea-factory-hikes-concerns-about-possible-icbm-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new satellite image shows construction at a factory where Pyongyang makes military equipment for such long-range missiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Kaepernick shoe sells out in day...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/475821-new-kaepernick-shoe-sells-out-in-a-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nike’s new sneaker featuring former NFL quarterback Colin Kaepernick was sold out by Tuesday, a day after its release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania silently forges path through ordeal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/887f8e64ba46b92c9c4daf5cc74ea604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Hillary Clinton spent the morning of her husband's impeachment visiting Capitol Hill to rally Democrats to his side. Pat Nixon kept assuring reporters her husband wouldn't quit —...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
