<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez compares 'global warming' to Nazism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/37382/ocasio-cortez-defeating-nazis-blueprint-defeating-ryan-saavedra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Socialist Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez said on Friday at a campaign event that the United States' blueprint for beating global warming needs to be the same as the blueprint the U.S. used for defeating Nazi Germany in the 1940s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man killed by group of aggressive monkeys throwing bricks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/monkeys-kill-man-tree-bricks-13448752</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dharampal Singh was rushed to hospital with head and chest injuries but doctors were unable to save him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio Has Largest Job Gain in 21 Years!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/florida-and-texas-post-record-sept-sept-job-gains</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump and First Lady Melania Trump in Texas (Screen Capture)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez compares 'global warming' to Nazism...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/single-clap-rings-out-as-ocasio-cortez-compares-global-warming-existential-threat-to-nazism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The word vomit out of the socialist Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez continues. Speaking in a small venue, the Democrat darling said the blueprint for defeating the progressive boogeyman “global warming” should be the same as the one used to fight Hitler. ﻿ “The last time we had a really major existential threat in this country was around …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandal Jolts Heir to Throne...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/scandal-over-dead-journalist-jolts-heir-to-saudi-throne-1540076164</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, secure for now, is scrambling to contain global backlash over the killing of government critic Jamal Khashoggi in Saudi Arabia’s Istanbul consulate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY HAS '3 DAYS TO SAVE HER JOB'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/theresa-may-enters-killing-zone-lbv0rrxb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tory rising star today issues a call to arms for MPs to oust Theresa May, saying Britain cannot be led by someone guilty of an “abject failure to govern” at such a defining moment in our history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass rally in London for new Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-final-say-demonstration-london-peoples-vote-numbers-theresa-may-a8594011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We were the few, and now we are the many,’ activists told as huge crowds urge Theresa May to change course</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES REVOLT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6298561/Theresa-faces-trial-Tory-MPs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Prime Minister (pictured) has been urged to confront disgruntled backbenchers at a crisis meeting as her rivals step up their campaigns to succeed her in No 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adelsons Bet Another $25 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-20/adelsons-add-25-million-to-their-midterm-campaign-spending</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Rips Trump in 2020 Preview...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/412409-sanders-trump-setting-terrible-example-for-our-children</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vermont) accused President Trump of setting a "terrible example" for children at a rally in South Carolina on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will lead rally for Cruz, keeping hatchet buried...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-will-lead-rally-cruz-keeping-hatchet-buried-193203212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s visit is also likely to invoke memories of the bitter 2016 primary fight between Cruz and Trump, one of the ugliest campaigns in recent memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THOUSANDS STRANDED</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexico-allows-caravan-women-children-thousands-still-stranded-222024004.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican authorities allowed dozens of women and children from a US-bound Honduran migrant caravan to enter the country Saturday but thousands remain stranded on a border bridge between Guatemala and Mexico where riot police barred their progress. Mexico's ambassador to Guatemala Luis Manuel Lopez</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khashoggi criticizes Saudi prince in newly released interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/khashoggi-criticizes-saudi-prince-newly-released-interview-085522901.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi critic Jamal Khashoggi criticized Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's "authoritarian rule" shortly before his death, in an interview published following confirmation he died at the kingdom's Istanbul consulate. Speaking off the record to a Newsweek journalist working on a story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany urges global tax for digital giants...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/germany-urges-global-minimum-tax-digital-giants-220405598.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Finance Minister Olaf Scholz said in an interview for publication Sunday he backed a global minimum fiscal regime for multinationals as Europe looks to levy tax notably on US tech giants. "We need a minumum tax rate valid globally which no state can get out of (applying)," Scholz,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil election battle rages over FACEBOOK's WhatsApp...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/facebooks-whatsapp-flooded-fake-news-brazil-election-193256823--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has touted efforts to crack down on misinformation on its main platform ahead of the Oct. 28 presidential run-off between right-winger Jair Bolsonaro and leftist Fernando Haddad. Haddad now alleges that businessmen supporting Bolsonaro have been paying to bombard voters with misleading propaganda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudis Shocked by Official Flip-Flop on Khashoggi...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/official-flip-flop-on-khashoggi-murder-shocks-loyal-saudis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudis Shocked by Official Flip-Flop on Khashoggi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Trump Duel in Nevada...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/biden-and-trump-duel-in-the-desert-for-critical-nevada-senate-race </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two men spoke almost concurrently to boost their favored candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Candidates Struggling in Key Battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/gop-candidates-struggling-in-key-battlegrounds-with-house-at-stake/ar-BBODYad?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXICO SLOWS CARAVAN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f817576eef064523b55101d02c0a11f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — Mexican authorities for a second straight day Saturday refused mass entry to a caravan of Central American migrants held up at the border with Guatemala, but began accepting small groups for asylum processing and gave out some 45-day visitor permits that would theoretically allow recipients time to reach the United States. Seeking to maintain order after a chaotic Friday in which thousands rushed across the border bridge only to be halted by a phalanx of officers in riot gear, authorities began handing out numbers for people to be processed in a strategy seen before at U.S. border posts when large numbers of migrants show up there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White SAfrican farmers could flee to Russia after land expropriations...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/737666/south-africa-land-expropriations-white-farmers-russia-cyril-ramaphosa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TESTED</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6297959/Trump-blames-obstructive-Democrats-immigration-laws-tired-migrants-bathe-Mexican-border.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president took to his Twitter on Saturday morning to blast Democrats for not working to get proper immigration laws, as thousands of migrants struggled to find proper baths at the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is case against Weinstein unraveling?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/20/entertainment/weinstein-case-unraveling-questions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein, the disgraced movie mogul whose alleged sexual assaults sparked the international #MeToo movement, may be sentenced to a lifetime of shame and ridicule. Legal experts, however, now indicate he may never see the inside of a jail, let alone go to trial to face his accusers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOUBTS ON EXPLANATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Circumstances-of-Jamal-Khashoggi-s-death-will-not-13322985.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL - A spokesman for President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's ruling party vowed Saturday that Turkey would "uncover what has happened" to Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi, hours after Saudi authorities said that the Washington Post contributing columnist had been killed earlier this month during a fistfight inside the Saudi Consulate in Istanbul. The Saudi explanation - that an argument in the consulate led to a fatal brawl - is at odds with the conclusions of Turkish investigators, who believe that Khashoggi was deliberately killed by a team of Saudi agents who were dispatched to Istanbul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Half million' rally in London for new Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tens-thousands-rally-london-brexit-vote-004938246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU flag waving Britons rejecting a future outside Europe packed the heart of London on Saturday for an anti-Brexit protest organisers said drew more than half a million people. The police gave no figures for how many showed up for the massive march and rally outside parliament aimed at pressing the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Reno, boomtown resurgence leads to housing crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/reno-boomtown-resurgence-leads-housing-154217675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. (AP) — They were the toast of Reno in the 1950s, when the growing casino industry sparked a boom that for a time turned northern Nevada into the West's top gambling destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Indicts Woman Who Tried to Block Afghan Man's Deportation on Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/20/world/europe/sweden-elin-ersson-deportation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors said Elin Ersson had violated the Swedish aviation act by remaining standing on takeoff. But she vowed to continue her campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Candidates Struggling in Key Battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/20/us/politics/republican-governors-congress-midterms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Party leaders worry that candidates for governor and Senate are in trouble in Michigan, Illinois, Minnesota, Pennsylvania and possibly Wisconsin, and that difficulties could spill into House races.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnitude 4.0 earthquake shakes Texas, Oklahoma panhandles...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/texas/article/Magnitude-4-0-earthquake-shakes-Texas-Oklahoma-13323017.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMARILLO, Texas (AP) - An earthquake has shaken parts of the Texas and Oklahoma panhandles. The U.S. Geological Survey says the 4.0 magnitude earthquake was recorded at 8:04 a.m. Saturday about 9 miles (15 kilometers) north-northeast of Amarillo. The temblor was recorded at a depth of 3 miles (5 kilometers). There were no immediate reports of damage or injuries. Geologists say damage isn't likely in quakes of magnitude 4.0. Thousands of earthquakes have been recorded in Oklahoma in recent years, with many linked to the underground injection of wastewater from oil and natural gas production. Scientists have also linked earthquakes in Kansas, Texas and other states to wastewater injection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL THEY TURN BACK?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181020165252-ccbx7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CARAVAN (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-U.S.-bound migrant caravan stuck on Guatemalan border with Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big numbers of illegals arriving at AZ border...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/arizona-news/big-numbers-of-central-americans-arriving-at-arizona-border-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large groups of Central American migrants continue to surrender to Border Patrol agents in Arizona with the arrival of one recent group numbering 108 captured in dramatic video images, authorities said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside notorious 'serpent church' where devotees die from grabbing rattlesnakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7512634/inside-snake-church-kentucky/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the nail-biting moment a pastor drinks fatal poison while holding up a deadly rattlesnake with his bare hands – and miraculously survives.  As the deadly strychnine, which can cause m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob Assaults Gay Journalist at Gillum Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/10/angry-democrat-mob-assaults-gay-journalist-at-andrew-gillum-rally-jobsnotmobs-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot gets 92 TINDER matches in 2 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/usa/441792-sex-robot-tinder-harmony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people go on dating apps for some human warmth now and then – for some, though, 'human' isn’t necessarily part of the equation. A realistic sex robot has garnered almost a hundred matches on Tinder in just two hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California growing shadow looms over Nevada races...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/californias-growing-shadow-looms-over-nevadas-midterms-152851133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — The Republicans running in Nevada's hotly contested races for governor and U.S. Senate are taking aim at a common target as they try to maintain GOP control of the seats: California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lioness kills father of her 3 cubs at Indianapolis Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/20/us/indianapolis-zoo-lion-dead/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lioness killed the father of her three cubs at the Indianapolis Zoo this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN host invites congressman to body slam him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/412377-cnns-chris-cuomo-invites-gianforte-to-bodyslam-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN host Chris Cuomo on Friday invited Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto campaign sued for spam texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/election/article220344070.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politics: Campaign of Beto O’Rourke, who is running for Senate against Ted Cruz, is facing a class action lawsuit by a Collin County resident who says the organization sent him text messages without permission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign mode revives fiery immigration talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/138443b2ba4646ad8f2b3abf4837bf00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. (AP) — Donald Trump fueled his 2016 campaign with fiery immigration rhetoric, visions of hordes flowing across the border to assault Americans and steal their jobs. Now, in the final weeks before midterm elections, he's back at it as he looks to stave off Democratic gains in Congress. It's an approach that offers both risks and rewards. He could energize Democratic foes as well as the Republicans he wants to rouse to the polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/19/tulsi-gabbard-2020-presidential-bid-917418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gabbard became a darling of the left in 2016 when she resigned as a DNC vice chair after fighting against the primary debate schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie, Kamala set to criss-cross Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412334-sanders-harris-set-to-criss-cross-iowa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego No. 1 booziest city...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/business/tourism/sd-fi-sandiego-booziest-cities-20181020-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on an analysis of average annual expenditures on booze, San Diego tops the list of metro areas of tipsiest cities in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing broadens propaganda drive to heartland America...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinese-broadens-propaganda-drive-heartland-132238597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — China's propaganda machine has taken aim at American soybean farmers as part of its high-stakes trade war with the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks on public figures growing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/412273-attacks-on-public-figures-are-growing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of protection, there is no room for error and in today’s threat matrix. There is little lack of imagination concerning what a threat could be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasive 'Spotted Lanternfly' Threatening Christmas Tree Crop...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/10/19/spotted-lanternfly-christmas-trees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With wings coated in black and red spots and a body of bold yellow, the spotted lanternfly could soon be hitching a ride home with you from the farm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Confronted at Restaurant by Angry Customers...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/10/20/senator-mitch-mcconnell-confronted-restaurant-protesters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Mitch McConnell was confronted at restaurant by protesters who threw his doggie bag out the door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi cursed out by protesters in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/20/nancy-pelosi-cursed-out-by-protesters-in-florida/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi was hounded by a group of protesters in Florida — with some cursing and calling her a “communist.” Video of the confrontation shows the small gr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 DAYS LATER: Candles, flashlights, no AC in Florida's hurricane zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/candles-flashlights-no-ac-floridas-hurricane-zone-123055049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PANAMA CITY, Fla. (AP) — More than 100,000 Florida customers are still without power due to Hurricane Michael, which tore into the Florida Panhandle more than a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors blast CDC...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/as-afm-illness-strikes-dozens-of-children-doctors-say-cdc/article_4debc074-5f93-5d4b-9d61-1750bf88729d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — LaMay Axton watched in horror as her granddaughter Cambria stumbled and toppled over as she ran into the kitchen of their house. The 2-year-old tried to stand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey won't allow 'cover-up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/086a03cd1b4d44b0a1d06263e353c092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey will "never allow a cover-up" of the killing of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi in Saudi Arabia's consulate in Istanbul, a senior official in Turkey's ruling party said Saturday after Saudi Arabia announced hours earlier that the writer died during a "fistfight" in its consulate. The critical reaction by Numan Kurtulmus, deputy head of the Justice and Development Party, suggested that Turkey, which started its own investigation amid pro-government media reports that a Saudi hit squad killed Khashoggi, was not prepared to go along with the Saudi version of what happened to the writer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudist beach surfer punches shark to escape attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nudist-beach-surfer-punches-shark-escape-attack-070339086.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surfer who got bitten by a shark at an Australian nudist beach managed to make his break for freedom after punching the creature until it let him go, he said Saturday. Paul Kenny was riding the waves off Samurai Beach, a naturist spot 200 kilometres (125 miles) north of Sydney, when he accidentally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: 63 Remains of Fetuses Found at Second Detroit Funeral Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2018/10/19/fetuses-perry-funeral-home-detroit/1702594002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the grisly total, there were 36 fetuses stored in boxes and another 27 found in freezers, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Drowning in Chinese Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/vancouver-is-drowning-in-chinese-money#gs.72Padkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vancouver was the first place to experience the tidal wave of Chinese cash. Now the city is leading efforts to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands turn out for anti-Brexit protest in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8ce2135b264e49e59614ff87d1ea0014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thousands of protesters were gathering in central London on Saturday to call for a second referendum on Britain's exit from the European Union. London Mayor Sadiq Khan was among those set to address the People's Vote March, which culminates at a rally in Parliament Square. Organizers expect the protest to be the biggest of its kind, with about 150 buses ferrying thousands of activists from across the country to the capital. Britons voted to leave the trade bloc by a narrow margin in the 2016 EU membership referendum. Prime Minister Theresa May has ruled out another public vote on the subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b913157e71ec4730b414b357758a450c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MESA, Ariz. (AP) — President Donald Trump, seeking to frame the choices for voters in the midterm elections, said Friday that Democrats are "too extreme and too dangerous" to take control of Congress. On a three-day swing out West to make his closing arguments for Republican candidates, Trump sought to hone in on immigration as one of the defining election issues this fall by falsely accusing Democrats of wanting "open borders" and encouraging illegal immigration. "Anybody who votes for a Democrat now is crazy," Trump said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL THEY TURN BACK?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181020015542-5zzjs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CARAVAN (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Migrant caravan halted on Mexico-Guatemala border, pressure to turn back mounts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil election battle rages over FACEBOOK's WhatsApp...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181019225559-3eodi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Brazil election battle rages over Facebook's WhatsApp</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
