<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Huma Abedin's 'No Apology' Tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/11/15/huma-abedin-hillary-clinton-aide-no-apology-tour-521199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-silent Clinton aide struggles to tell her life story when the media just wants to know one thing: Why did you stay with Anthony Weiner?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon surrenders on contempt charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/15/trump-ally-steve-bannon-surrenders-on-charges-stemming-from-jan-6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bannon faces two counts of contempt of Congress after refusing to comply with demands to produce documents and sit for a deposition as part of the Jan. 6 probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Teens and tweens sharing more nude pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/teens-tweens-share-nude-pictures-study-b329a0a7-c0ad-4984-84b6-e0317d27df37.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twice as many kids aged 9-12 reported sending nudes or other suggestive pictures of themselves in 2020, compared to 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Chris Christie's breakup with The Don...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/chris-christie-trump-january-6-feefb7e3-a3af-41ad-b442-93accdb02bd8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christie frantically tried to reach Trump on Jan. 6, but he never picked up the phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BOILING POINT'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4069307/russia-tensions-west-boiling-point-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has warned relations with the West “almost at boiling point” as tensions mount of over migrants at the Poland-Belarus border. With Nato and Russian forces playing cat and mouse games, Vladim…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN URGED TO QUIT AMID GROWING HEALTH FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/4022057/queen-elizabeth-news-how-is-health-old-ill-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEARS for the Queen are growing after the monarch suffered another setback and missed the Remembrance Sunday service over the weekend. Buckingham Palace announced Her Majesty has sprained her back …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YEAR OF MEDICAL ISSUES...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/celebrity-life/royals/queen-elizabeths-sprained-hip-is-just-the-latest-health-concern-thats-plagued-the-royal-in-2021/news-story/b47cd01427b47f55193b98af89636bb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a month of health concerns and cancelled events, Queen Elizabeth II is alarming fans after a sprained back forced her to cancel her appearance at the Remembrance Sunday Service, two hours before the event was slated to start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Oprah interview, Adele talks divorce, weight loss, album, more...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-four-most-personal-revelations-from-oprah-e2-80-99s-interview-with-adele-from-her-divorce-to-weight-loss-to-new-boyfriend/ar-AAQIhd1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: McConnell sought to disinvite Trump from Biden inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/mcconnell-sought-disinvite-trump-biden-inauguration-triggering-final/story?id=80980103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News correspondent Jonathan Karl shares the little-known story behind Donald Trump's final tweet in his new book, "Betrayal: The Final Act of the Trump Show."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once more unto the breach: Pelosi strives to deliver agenda that has divided caucus, testing her power...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/pelosi-biden-reconciliation-infrastructure/2021/11/14/f9e59026-3e42-11ec-bfad-8283439871ec_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the Democratic House speaker succeeds, it would likely serve as a capstone to a career that is already one of the most significant in modern congressional history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Craze Cools? 2 In 5 Canceling Subs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-canceling-streaming-tv-cut-cord-rising-costs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three in four say they've had too many technical problems with their streaming TV devices, while two-thirds feel the product is too difficult to use or navigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO ALARM OVER RUSSIAN TROOP BUILD-UP</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/nato-chief-calls-on-russia-to-avoid-escalation-near-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of NATO urges Russia to prevent any escalation in the wake of its build-up of forces near the border with Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala sidelined amid growing tensions with president...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/15/kamala-harris-sidelined-amid-tensions-with-president-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris is being increasingly alienated in the White House as her approval ratings plummet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Overtakes USA in Wealth...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-wealth-surges-china-overtakes-030000699.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global wealth tripled over the last two decades, with China leading the way and overtaking the U.S. for the top spot worldwide.Most Read from BloombergAmazon Sued Over Crashes by Drivers Rushing to Make DeliveriesWhat Designers of Video Game Cities Understand About Real CitiesBiden Plan Funds New Bridges That Locals May Not WantHong Kong's New Museum Tries to Please Art World — and BeijingFarmers Take on ‘Post-Apocalyptic’ Food CrisisThat’s one of the takeaways from a new report b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital revokes Houston doctor's privileges for 'spreading misinformation' about covid on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/news/local/2021/11/14/houston-methodist-suspends-privileges-of-houston-doctor-hospital-following-controversial-tweets-about-covid-19-treatments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houston Methodist has suspended the privileges of a local doctor the hospital said was spreading dangerous misinformation about COVID-19 treatments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is AI more formidable than nukes?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/581460-is-artificial-intelligence-more-formidable-than-nuclear-weapons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could AI’s super-intelligence cure cancer, enhance wellbeing, redress climate change and deal with many of the planet’s worst evils?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban opposition to protest despite ban...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/cuban-opposition-protest-despite-ban-121756445.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cuban opposition has said it will take to the streets as planned on Monday to demand the release of political prisoners, despite authorities banning the demonstration and preventing its organizers leaving their homes the day before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU says FBI raid of O'Keefe home could threaten 'press freedom'...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/courts-law/aclu-says-fbi-raid-project-veritas-founder-okeefes-home-could-threaten-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barring significant evidence of criminal theft, the government 'should not have subjected them to invasive searches and seizures,' wrote the ACLU</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His Reasons for Opposing Trump Were Biblical. Now Top Christian Editor Is Out....</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/14/his-reasons-for-opposing-trump-were-biblical-now-a-top-christian-editor-is-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Marvin Olasky gets angry emails from readers — more often than not about an exposé of wrongdoing at an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Great Sex Recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4064829/sex-recession-americans-not-having-sex-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICANS are having less and less sex, especially casual sex, with almost 30 percent of single people surveyed reporting they haven’t had sex for at least one year. In a report issued by the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation braced for verdicts in Rittenhouse, Arbery trials...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/news/other/us-braced-for-verdicts-from-two-high-profile-trials/ar-AAQHvcT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is bracing for the outcome of two high-profile trials featuring a volatile mix of guns, self-defense claims and racial tensions. One of the cases is being tried in the town of Brunswick in Georgia, a southern state with a segregationist past. Three white men are on trial for shooting and killing Ahmaud Arbery, a Black jogger, on February 23, 2020 after chasing him through their neighborhood in pickup trucks. Gregory McMichael,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump aide told not to play Taylor Swift at White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Former-Trump-aide-said-she-was-told-not-to-play-16621353.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olivia Troye lost an argument, and she was angry. The former homeland security,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper defends China satire 'FRAGILE' as views hit 30 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211115-rapper-defends-china-satire-fragile-as-views-hit-30m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rapper who penned a viral Mandarin pop song poking fun at Chinese nationalists said Monday he had no regrets about being blacklisted by Beijing as his track hit more than 30 million views on YouTub…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British police declare taxi explosion outside Liverpool hospital 'terrorist incident'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/15/uk/liverpool-hospital-car-explosion-monday-gbr-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK police have declared a car explosion that took place in Liverpool on Sunday a terrorist incident. Officers said they believe a man entered a taxi with an improvised explosive device that suddenly went off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein faces trial by proxy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-jeffrey-epstein-new-york-manhattan-ghislaine-maxwell-5efc2669c57697b6c5c65b148cf315b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — After disgraced financier Jeffrey Epstein died by suicide behind bars, a judge invited his accusers to court to vent their anger at a man they called a coward for taking his own life to escape accountability for sexually abusing them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCS lost again, and Brady didn't want to talk about it...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-Buccaneers-lost-again-and-Tom-Brady-didn-t-16621074.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANDOVER, Md. - Tom Brady walked into the cramped office adjacent to the Tampa Bay...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In wake of Bannon indictment, GOP warns of payback...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/in-wake-of-bannon-indictment-republicans-warn-of-payback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Republicans are rallying around former White House adviser Steve Bannon after his indictment on charges of contempt of Congress on Friday, warning that Democrats' efforts to force Bannon to comply with what they say is an unfair subpoena...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk spars with Sanders, offers to sell more TESLA stock...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/elon-musk-spars-with-bernie-sanders-offers-sell-more-tesla-stock-2021-11-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk got into a spat with Bernie Sanders on Sunday after the U.S. senator demanded the wealthy pay their "fair share" of taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba harasses, detains activists on eve of planned protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuba-harasses-detains-activists-on-eve-of-planned-protest/ar-AAQHqP0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appeals court halts Biden vax requirement, delivering big blow...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/federal-appeals-court-halts-biden-administrations-vaccine-requirement-delivering-policy-a-major-blow/ar-AAQE2Dh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden underestimated country's problems -- and Dems fear problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Biden-has-underestimated-problems-facing-the-16620270.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In June, senior White House officials promised that rising inflation was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan in focus at virtual summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/15/biden-xi-summit-taiwan-in-focus-as-us-seeks-to-avoid-a-conflict-with-china.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tariffs and supply chain woes will take a backseat when President Joe Biden holds a virtual summit with Chinese President Xi Jinping Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST employee hospitalized after alleged assault by passenger...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/581487-southwest-employee-hospitalized-after-alleged-assault-by-passenger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest Airlines passenger "verbally and physically" assaulted a female operations agent, who was hospitalized after the incident on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: AUSTRIA ORDERS LOCKDOWN FOR UNVAXXED...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211114114715-3l3ct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRIA (URGENT, PIX):Austria orders non-vaccinated people into COVID-19 lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: REPUBLICANS HOLD LARGEST LEAD IN 40 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/economic-discontent-criticisms-biden-lift-gop-record-early/story?id=81095146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new ABC News/Washington Post poll.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
