<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BENIOFF: San Fran 'train wreck' because 'tech sector'... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Marc-Benioff-Davos-San-Francisco-is-a-train-wreck-13551953.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salesforce CEO Marc Benioff called his hometown of San Francisco a "train wreck" of inequality and he blamed technology companies like his own in an interview at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan Deal in Senate?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/22/us/politics/government-shutdown-senate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under a compromise reached by Senators Mitch McConnell and Chuck Schumer, the Senate will vote Thursday on a Trump measure that will fail and a stopgap spending bill likely to pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller investigating Trump campaign ties to NRA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/22/politics/mueller-nunberg-trump-campaign-nra/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller's team has expressed interest in the Trump campaign's relationship with the National Rifle Association during the 2016 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visitors watch man mauled to death after climbing into lion enclosure...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8245719/horrified-visitors-watch-man-get-mauled-to-death-by-lions-after-he-climbed-into-their-zoo-enclosure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOURISTS could only watch in horror as a man was mauled to death after climbing into the lion enclosure at a zoo in India. The man scaled a 20ft barrier at Chhatbir Zoo, in Punjab, before dropping …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst year on record for polio-like mystery illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cases-polio-acute-flaccid-myelitis-hit-201-2018-cdc-says-n961366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC still does not have a prime suspect for the cause of the condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film festival to screen thriller in coffins...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/entertainment/article224901355.html#storylink=latest_side</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden’s Goteborg Film Festival will lock moviegoers inside coffins next week for special screenings of a dystopian sci-fi film called “Aniara.” The event is touted as “the world’s most claustrophobic cinema.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Stacks Campaign With Team Hillary...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/kamala-harris-stacks-presidential-campaign-with-hillary-clinton-alums/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newly launched Kamala Harris presidential campaign is stacked with top officials from Hillary Clinton's failed 2016 campaign, including Marc Elias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro at odds with Davos focus on environment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1209ab68e41a4d429a6865a72314844e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVOS, Switzerland (AP) — Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro pledged to work "in harmony with the world" to cut carbon emissions, aiming to quell international concerns that his country, the main custodian of the oxygen-rich Amazon, could put economic interests over environmental ones. The environment dominated talks at the World Economic Forum on Tuesday, and the nationalist leader struck a conciliatory tone in a keynote speech — a far cry from the combative one he had taken on the campaign trail when he once threatened to join the United States and pull Brazil out of the Paris climate accord, which set a limit on global warming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover cop says colleagues beat him 'like Rodney King'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/undercover-st-louis-cop-says-colleagues-beat-him-like-rodney/article_395bae27-3ba0-5003-a966-24e49775e418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Search warrants include more details about police detective who was beaten while working undercover during the protests of the verdict in the murder trial of former police Officer Jason Stockley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa Sen. Joni Ernst says husband physically attacked her...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/2019/01/22/joni-ernst-gail-senator-iowa-ia-divorce-congress-politics-trump-republican-washington-des-moines/2637142002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iowa senator and her husband of 26 years divorced this month. Accusations in court records date back over a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyeing address at Texas-Mexico border?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6619643/Trump-RALLY-speech-instead-State-Union-address-Pelosi-doesnt-relent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is working along two separate tracks, assuming the traditional speech will happen on January 29 but preparing for a change of venue, somewhere outside Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Millennials Ditching Doctor...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/01/22/millennials-ditching-the-doctor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More and more millennials are ditching the doctor and many don’t even have a primary care physician, according to a survey by the Kaiser Family Foundation. Some doctors say this could lead to people overlooking serious health issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver rescues 34 kids from burning school bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article224901870.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos from a fire department near Darlington, South Carolina show a school bus on fire after a crash. Fire officials say the bus driver rescued 30 students and no one was seriously hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plastic Cleanup Threatens Ocean's Living Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/01/ocean-cleanup-project-could-destroy-neuston/580693/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home to vibrantly colored, tiny creatures, the ecosystems floating on the ocean’s surface remain all but unknown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge quintupled proposed fine on firm fighting Mueller subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/22/mueller-subpoena-fight-1118242</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the justices allowed the public release of a partially-redacted legal filing that disclosed a few more facts about the dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrist Dems urge Pelosi to break shutdown stalemate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/22/house-democrats-pelosi-shutdown-1118986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of House Democrats is drafting a letter to Pelosi asking her to agree to hold a vote on Trump’s wall after the government is reopened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans feeling more pessimistic about economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/more-americans-are-feeling-more-pessimistic-about-the-economy-2019-01-22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the upside, people seem confident in job availability, a new Gallup survey finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House going forward with State of Union despite bid to cancel...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/white-house-planning-to-proceed-with-state-of-the-union-but-details-up-in-air-after-pelosi-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is still planning to move ahead with next week’s scheduled State of the Union address, but the details remain up in the air after House Speaker Nancy Pelosi strongly urged the president to delay the speech or submit it in writing amid the government shutdown fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: TWITTER's '2 Minutes of Hate' ...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/818951/how-twitter-could-death-liberal-democracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media's rush to judgment is indicative of something ominous that's happening to our political culture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOZELL: 'Now OPENLY ANTAGONISTIC Toward Right'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/facebook-doesnt-really-believe-in-free-speech-what-they-believe-in-and-actively-practice-is-censorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook doesn't really believe in free speech. They believe in and actively practice censorship on a scale almost unimaginable a few years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOKTWITTER still stalk you online even if you DELETE account...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8252363/facebook-still-stalk-you-online-delete-account/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DELETING your social media won’t stop tech firms from tracking your every move. That’s the terrifying conclusion from a new study that investigated how apps like Facebook and Twitter ca…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Tijuana prepared for next caravan? </title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/migrant-caravan/sd-me-caravan-lessons-20190122-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some are hoping the federal government will call the shots if and when the next caravan arrives from Central America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep humans in good jobs in robot era, commission urges...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ilo-robots/keep-humans-in-good-jobs-in-the-robot-era-ilo-commission-urges-idUSKCN1PG1QC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governments must ensure the global economy keeps providing decent jobs - and not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists teach robot dog to get back up after kick it down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/scientists-teach-a-robot-dog-to-get-back-up-after-they-kick-it-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers teach their robot canine to "roll over", which is both terrifying and adorable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK JITTERS RETURN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/22/us-markets-global-economy-us-china-trade-in-focus-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Tuesday, the first trading day of the week, as weak data out of China and lower global growth estimates from the International Monetary Fund renewed fears of the global economy slowing down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNUBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/01/22/oscar-snubs-first-man-a-quiet-place-mary-poppins-blanked-mister-rogers-doc-shock-bradley-cooper-for-director-in-star-is-born-nicole-kidman-emily-blunt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The snubs are always the big story in Oscar nominations. I’ve included some other milestones here. No nod for Morgan Neville’s award winning doc about Mister Rogers, “Won’t …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BLACK PANTHER' MAKES HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/oscars-2019-black-panther-becomes-first-superhero-movie-nominated-for-best-picture-117659</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marvel has broken the Academy's superhero glass ceiling, after films like 'The Dark Knight' and 'Wonder Woman' were snubbed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 74% of Dems would vote for her for president!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-beto-o-rourke-democrats-d69595cc-ea49-41b5-b521-dce94dc2790f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOC and Beto are disrupting Democratic politics ahead of 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian plane bound for Moscow in suspected hijacking...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7281bf2ad60843e280013c5b2f499744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian police detained a drunken man who threatened the crew of an passenger plane flying Tuesday from a Siberian city to Moscow, forcing it to land shortly after take-off. The Russian Investigative Committee said that the man told the Aeroflot crew that he was armed and demanded the diversion of the plane after it had taken off from the Siberian city of Surgut. The plane landed in the city of Khanty-Mansiysk, about 230 kilometers (145 miles) to the west. The plane stood on the runway in Khanty-Mansiysk for more than an hour before law enforcement officials went onboard. The airport was evacuated and the area cordoned off. Aeroflot said no one was hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA,' 'FAVOURITE' LEAD...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/oscar-nominations-2019-list-1203112405/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar nominations for the 91st annual Academy Awards will be announced Tuesday morning from the Samuel Goldwyn Theater in Beverly Hills, Calif. Academy president John Bailey will be joined by “The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NFL bleaux it': Billboards protest missed call...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7179a209a3a147a3a87b2998d73cba81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS, La. (AP) — The Los Angeles Rams and New England Patriots will be welcomed to Atlanta for the Super Bowl by several billboards saying "Saints got robbed" and "NFL bleaux it." WDSU-TV reports Louisiana car dealership owner Matt Bowers paid for 10 billboards across Atlanta through Feb. 3, including one outside Mercedes-Benz Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa prepares for mother of all caucuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/22/iowa-caucuses-2020-1116644</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expecting massive turnout, state Democratic officials are considering wide-ranging changes to how the first-in-the-nation event is conducted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political shifts, sales slump cast shadow over gun industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d2bc4e5279264181bc7cfab1b1f64f4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When gunmakers and dealers gather this week in Las Vegas for the industry's largest annual conference, they will be grappling with slumping sales and a shift in politics that many didn't envision two years ago when gun-friendly Donald Trump and a GOP-controlled Congress took office. Some of the top priorities for the industry — expanding the reach of concealed carry permits and easing restrictions on so-called "silencers" — remain in limbo, and prospects for expanding gun rights are nil for the foreseeable future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems lurch left on top policies as 2020 primary begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4c89676b498d4ab1af09659b29c164f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Democratic presidential contender Julian Castro launched his campaign by pledging support for "Medicare for All," free universal preschool, a large public investment in renewable energy and two years of free college for all Americans. That wasn't enough for some of his party's most liberal members. Critics on social media quickly knocked Castro's plan to provide only two years of free higher education — instead of four — as "half measures," ''scraps" and "corporate Dem doublespeak." Aware of the backlash, the former Obama administration Cabinet member clarified his position in an interview days later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS anchor Bret Baier car flips during vacation, family hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/426347-fox-anchor-baiers-car-flips-during-montana-vacation-family-hospitalized </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News anchor Bret Baier and his family were in a car accident while vacationing in Montana on Monday, which CBS late-night host Stephen Colbert described as "bad, like, jaws of life to get him out of there."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Give 'Zero' F*cks...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/video/stephen-colbert-alexandria-ocasio-cortez/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"On a scale of zero to some..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed with affection, octogenarian is 'octopus whisperer'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/11d27b12504c48b396267b1483d7060e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Wilson Menashi palmed a squid in his left hand and extended his arm into an aquarium tank, watching as a giant Pacific octopus stretched out tentacles to greet him like a friend. Freya latched some of her 2,240 suction cups onto Menashi's arm, using their powers of taste and smell to gather information around the 84-year-old man known as the octopus whisperer — and the seafood treats he was bearing. "She's just contacting me and she's saying, 'You come to me,'" Menashi said of Freya, a 3-year-old predator weighing 35 to 40 pounds (18 kilograms). Her tentacles span 14 feet (4 meters) and pack enough strength to kill sharks and other enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese stars hit with $1.62 billion in 'cold winter' tax crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-entertainment-crackdown-idUSKCN1PG0XO </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have collected more than 11 billion yuan ($1.62 billion) in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake ICBM missile warning over NEST system sends family into panic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/01/21/it-was-five-minutes-of-sheer-terror-hackers-infiltrate-east-bay-familys-nest-surveillance-camera-send-warning-of-incoming-north-korea-missile-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Orinda family endured a terrifying Sunday after hackers gained access to their smart surveillance camera and blasted a nuclear attack warning into the living room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer Chris Brown arrested in Paris on suspicion of rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6618803/R-B-singer-Chris-Brown-arrested-Paris-suspicion-rape.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 24-year-old woman is said to have accused Brown of raping her on the evening of January 15 at a hotel in the French capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Law Would Make 9-Year-Olds Criminally Liable...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/bill-to-make-9-year-olds-criminally-liable-approved-by-11150900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA: Philippine lawmakers have approved a bill to lower the minimum age of criminal liability to nine from the current minimum age of 15, local ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run Faster! Treadmill Generating Electricity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/run-faster-your-gym-s-treadmills-may-soon-be-saving-the-planet#gs.OwYOMkdR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Run Fasterâ€”Your TreadmillÂ Might Be Generating Electricity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to back Juan Guaido?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/426119-us-faces-key-test-as-global-support-for-venezuela-opposition-leader-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is facing a critical test of its hemispheric policy as global support grows for the leader of Venezuela's National Assembly, Juan Guaido, to be the face of opposition against strongman President Nicolas Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars race kicks into high gear with nominations... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/oscar-nominations-2019-academy-award-nominees-list-1202538943/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 91st Oscar nominations are being announced this morning in a presentation by the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, with Tracee Ellis Ross and Kumail Nanjiani revealing nominations in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never mind climate change: 1,500 private jets at Davos!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190122-never-mind-climate-change-davos-prefers-private-jets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never mind climate change, Davos prefers private jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy takes fight to new generation in Mafia sting...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190122-italy-takes-fight-new-generation-mafia-sting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy takes fight to new generation in Mafia sting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's second gene-edited fetus is 12-14 weeks old: scientist...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190122-chinas-second-gene-edited-foetus-12-14-weeks-old-scientist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's second gene-edited foetus is 12-14 weeks old: scientist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tree Man' dreams of cure as rare skin disease returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190122-bangladeshi-tree-man-dreams-cure-rare-skin-disease-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bangladeshi 'Tree Man' dreams of cure as rare skin disease returns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro sells 'new Brazil' to Davos elite...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-leader-rides-far-wave-davos-030934517.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skirting the first political scandal of his new presidency, far-right leader Jair Bolsonaro will tout a "new Brazil" when he addresses the world's business elite in Davos on Tuesday. The president of Latin America's biggest economy is giving the keynote address at this year's World</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air pollution affects happiness... </title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/21/air-pollution-affects-happiness-not-just-health-scientists-find/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air pollution is not just bad for health also makes people unhappy, a new study has shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats out to stop House members from living in offices...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article224506345.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key Democrats are exploring whether to put an end to members of the House of Representatives living in their offices part-time or make the lawmakers pay up for lodging in prime government real estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterrevolution to populism happening all over world...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/opinion/article/The-counterrevolution-to-populism-is-happening-13550087.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not just in the United States. The counterrevolution to populism is happening all over the world, and it's turning the old left-right political axis on its head. In country after country, the rise of anti-immigrant parties or movements is forcing many supporters of traditional center-right parties to recalibrate. Culturally moderate or somewhat liberal, these voters are either turning toward parties they previously shunned or, in some multiparty systems, pushing their leaders to abandon longtime alliances. The first type of reaction is what we've seen in the Anglosphere. In the United States, Britain and Australia, the tradition of a strong two-party system often forces voters to choose the party they dislike the least.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MESS:  Giuliani tries to clean up comments about Trump Tower Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/21/politics/rudy-giuliani-trump-tower/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's attorney Rudy Giuliani said Monday that the President had no recollection of whether discussions about a proposed Trump Tower Moscow project went through the 2016 election, distancing himself from a claim he made Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and zeal over more guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3065b3d7cfad49eea2c363c975ef4fad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO GONCALO, Brazil (AP) — Fearing for his safety amid rising crime in Latin America's largest nation, Paulo Alberto joined a gun club three years ago and learned to shoot. But he says Brazil's tight carry laws that mean he can't take his gun anywhere but to the club limit his ability to protect himself outside his home. "The current laws are very strict and end up helping out the thugs," Alberto said between rounds at the Calibre 12 gun club in this city across Guanabara Bay from Rio de Janeiro. "We need laws to make it easier to both possess and carry guns."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Black Hebrews' taunt...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2019/01/20/covington-catholic-nathan-phillips-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists who uncritically accepted Nathan Phillips' story got this completely wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural beauty of wildlife beneath the waves revealed in stunning pics...</title>
      <link>http://www.uwphotographyguide.com/2018-ocean-art-contest-winners </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.uwphotographyguide.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser Pointed at Brady's Face...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/laser-appears-to-be-pointed-in-tom-bradys-face-during-afc-title-game-against-kansas-city-chiefs/25983371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crowd noise at Arrowhead Stadium may not have been the only adversity the Patriots quarterback faced on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murders in Mexico set new record...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-violence/murders-in-mexico-rise-by-a-third-in-2018-to-new-record-idUSKCN1PF27J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murders in Mexico rose by 33 percent in 2018, breaking the record for a second y...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA calls up National Deployment Officers to operate checkpoints... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/20/tsa-calls-in-backup-officers-as-absences-of-unpaid-workers-rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TSA said unscheduled absences of airport security screeners, who are going unpaid in the partial shutdown, hit a record high of 10 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown damage to exceed cost of wall?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/government-shutdowns-damage-to-u-s-economy-to-soon-exceed-5-7-billion-cost-of-trumps-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Partial closure of government hurts economy to tune of $1.2 billion a week -- and weekly tab swells the longer it lasts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of fraying in military support for Venezuela president...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/82563347aa414f1fab9c80ac87e607e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro launches his second term challenged by a re-energized opposition movement, experts say his hold on power relies more than ever on military backing. Maduro has granted bonuses to rank-and-file soldiers and placed generals in key government posts, including at the helm of the state-run oil company, seeking to cement their support. But with Venezuela sliding into economic collapse, there have been signs in recent years of fraying in military support: ___</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  Giuliani says his comments on Trump Tower talks were 'hypothetical'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/426320-giuliani-says-his-comments-on-trump-tower-talks-were-hypothetical</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's attorney, Rudy Giuliani, on Monday sought to clarify previous statements he made about talks to build a Trump Tower in Moscow during the 2016 election, maintaining that they were "hypothetical."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer for MAGA Hat Teens Threatens Lawsuits Against Media Unless They Retract False Stories...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/lawyer-for-covington-catholic-hs-families-threatens-lawsuits-against-media-unless-they-retract-false-stories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The teens and their families are being threatened and harassed by a hateful online outrage mob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORTEZ CRACKS:  WORLD ENDING IN 12 YEARS!</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-ocasio-cortez-millennials-were-world-going-end-12-years-if-w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘At some point these chronic realities do reach a breaking point’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Existence of Billionaires 'Immoral'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-ocasio-cortez-immoral-our-system-allows-billionaires-exist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘ I don’t think that necessarily means that all billionaires are immoral’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe plan to mine the moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6617301/Europe-wants-moon-2025-ESA-reveals-plan-spark-new-space-race.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Space Agency revealed it has signed up rocket maker ArianeGroup to develop plans for a moon base that could be used to mine material from the lunar surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Diner Builds Bomb While Sitting At Sushi Restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://whotv.com/2019/01/16/police-say-the-grenade-that-a-man-built-at-sushi-restaurant-could-have-killed-customers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whotv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa -- It happened around 6:40 Tuesday Night at Akebono 515 on 10th Street. The owner of the restaurant had no idea what was going on. "Cops talked to my host and said somebody called 911 over here, talking about a bomb," said Nam Tran, the restaurant's owner. "And the host asked me, and said not that we know of. We don't know nothing about, so after that a few cops come in and I asked can I help you? What's going on here? And, he said well, somebody called over here and said, you know, a bomb over here. I said not that I know of."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY MAKING MUELLER MAD?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/21/us/politics/giuliani-trump-tower-russia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s personal lawyer, Rudolph W. Giuliani, said his own widely reported statements about when talks about the skyscraper project might have ended were only “hypothetical.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stressed out and at risk: Inside UBER special investigations unit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/21/tech/uber-investigations-unit-report/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internal investigators tasked with keeping Uber safe were overworked, underpaid and at times emotionally traumatized as they struggled under the burden of nearly 1,200 cases every week, a confidential internal memo obtained by CNN says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant says overweight traveler forced her to wipe his butt...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/21/flight-attendant-says-overweight-passenger-forced-her-to-wipe-his-butt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An overweight passenger aboard a Taiwanese airliner forced flight attendants to remove his pants so he could use the toilet — then wipe his butt as he moaned in pleasure, according to reports. A fl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building sand castles a jailable offense at popular beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/travel/travel-updates/warnings/boracay-police-taking-aim-at-the-islands-iconic-sand-castles-three-months-after-reopening/news-story/99768b25c1a77324f3741089675ebb8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been less than three months since one of the Philippines’ most picturesque islands reopened to the world and police are going to extreme lengths to make sure Boracay doesn’t fall into its old, harmful patterns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge fund tycoon's recent spending on homes at least $664,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/residential-real-estate/122-million-london-purchase-ken-griffin-has-spent-least-664-million-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 Private Jets To Descend On Davos...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-01-21/1500-private-jets-descend-davos-week-50-last-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Sheryl Sandberg 'Typhoid Mary' of Surveillance Capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jan/20/shoshana-zuboff-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-google-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shoshana Zuboff’s new book is a chilling exposé of the business model that underpins the digital world. Observer tech columnist John Naughton explains the importance of Zuboff’s work and asks the author 10 key questions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC DANGEROUS: Gunman Steals Puppies From Lady During Walk...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Pit-Bull-Puppies-Stolen-at-Gunpoint-in-Southeast-DC-504658851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gunman stole two 2-month-old pit bulls from a woman out walking them in Southeast D.C. Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists, Celebs Rush to Delete Tweets Slamming MAGA-Hat Kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/journalists-and-celebs-rush-to-delete-tweets-slamming-maga-hat-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Images Reveal Building Secret War Bunkers...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-01-20/satellite-images-reveal-china-building-secret-war-bunkers-near-indian-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High levels of cocaine in Thames making eels 'hyperactive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/london/eels-in-thames-left-hyperactive-due-to-high-levels-of-cocaine-in-water-a4044001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eels in the Thames are becoming hyperactive because of the high levels of cocaine in the city’s waste water, scientists say. New research by a team at King's College London found that Londoners are using the class A drug consistently throughout the week, with fears that it is hurting the river’s wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel fires half robot staff for incompetence...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/cnet/article/Hotel-fires-half-its-robot-staff-for-sucking-at-13549795.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bye bye, bots. Henn na Hotel in Japan laid off droids that annoyed customers by failing to perform simple tasks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fund border wall with porn tax? Lawmaker says yes...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/opinion/op-ed/laurieroberts/2019/01/18/arizona-legislator-offers-genius-plan-fund-border-wall-tax-porn/2619364002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arizona legislator proposed taxing pornography to raise money for a border wall. Genius idea, that.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
