<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UK and EU agree on future relations after Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/324c49c6a68844dba3cd685041ce6ff2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — The European Union and Britain have agreed on a draft declaration on the future of their political relations after Brexit, European Council President Donald Tusk said Thursday, paving the way for an EU summit this weekend to rubber-stamp the deal. The draft declaration was agreed upon at a technical level by negotiators and endorsed Thursday by the European Commission, the EU's executive arm which is overseeing Brexit negotiations. "The (EU) Commission President has informed me that it has been agreed at negotiators' level and agreed in principle at political level," Tusk said in a tweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Tech will be death of civilization; Humanity self-destructs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/743886/technology-death-civilisation-nick-bostrom-vulnerable-world-future-prediction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BITTER COLD TO SMASH RECORDS</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/thanksgiving-day-2018-may-be-among-coldest-on-record-in-northeastern-us/70006672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROUNDED?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/21/macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-might-not-be-a-nightmare-after-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snoopy, Charlie Brown and even the Grinch may have a lot to be thankful for this year. It looks like winds on Thursday won’t be quite strong enough to ground the balloons at the Macy’s Thanksgiving…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plan would force asylum seekers to wait in Mexico as cases are processed...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-plan-would-force-asylum-seekers-to-wait-in-mexico-as-cases-are-processed-a-major-break-with-current-policy/2018/11/21/5ad47e82-ede8-11e8-9236-bb94154151d2_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Mexican official said that current Mexican immigration law does not allow those seeking asylum in another country to stay in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANNON PLAN FOR FAR RIGHT IN EUROPE IN DISARRAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/21/steve-bannons-rightwing-europe-operation-undermined-by-election-laws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: ambitious plan to campaign in EU elections would fall foul of laws in nine of 13 targeted states</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump thanks Saudi Arabia for lower oil prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-thanks-saudi-arabia-lower-oil-prices-164207215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump on Wednesday ignored criticism that he gave Saudi Arabia a free pass on the murder of a dissident journalist, instead praising the Islamic kingdom for keeping oil prices low. Trump, on holiday at his Florida Mar-a-Lago Club, doubled down on an unusually worded statement from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KINGDOM:  Crown prince a 'red line' in Khashoggi probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/crown-prince-red-line-khashoggi-probe-saudi-fm-230231092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman to be held accountable for the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi are a "red line", Saudi Foreign Minister Adel al-Jubeir said Wednesday. In a BBC television interview, Jubeir said any disparaging discussion about Prince Mohammed or his father</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won House popular vote by largest midterm margin since Watergate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/democrats-won-house-popular-vote-largest-midterm-margin-watergate-n938996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nationally, Democrats have 53.1 percent of all votes counted while Republicans took 45.2 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korean cult leader jailed for raping followers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nation.co.ke/news/world/Cult-pastor-jailed-for-raping-his-followers/1068-4863090-76f46uz/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nation.co.ke&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lee Jaerock's victims say he was 'God' so they could not resist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Departing comms chief says critics were targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/technology/departing-facebook-comms-chief-says-critics-were-targeted-10956942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO: The outgoing head of Facebook's communications team on Wednesday (Nov 21) took responsibility for the hiring of a conservative ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit goes down to wire as May calls last-day talks...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/days-summit-may-takes-brexit-battle-brussels-022357089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negotiations to secure an orderly Brexit deal will go down to the wire after Theresa May said she would return to Brussels for more talks on the eve of a planned signing summit. After an inconclusive trip to Brussels to meet EU chief Jean-Claude Juncker, the British prime minister said she would return</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid wildfire destruction, evacuees find new meaning in Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Amid-wildfire-destruction-evacuees-find-new-13413385.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. - Thanksgiving marks two weeks since the deadliest fire in the state swept through this part of northern California, displacing thousands of families and turning Butte County into a disaster zone of smoke, emergency crews and an all-hands-on-deck effort to help those affected by the blaze. For some of those evacuees, the holiday known for gathering with family in a warm home will be spent in a shelter with strangers or in a tent in the rain. "It doesn't really feel like [a] holiday that much," said Kevin Alcott, whose home was destroyed when the fire flattened the town of Paradise, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New lawsuits use nuisance and racketeering laws to target clergy sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/11/21/church-scandal-new-lawsuits-use-nuisance-and-racketeering-laws-to-target-clergy-sex-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ongoing scandal over sexual abuse by Catholic clergy has led to two new high-profile lawsuits, both aimed at forcing American bishops to divulge secret lists of offenders dating back more than …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolated Indian tribe kill American intruder...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-tourist-killed-arrow-shooting-indian-tribe-073604724.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of one of the world's last tribes untouched by modern civilisation have killed an American who ventured illegally onto their remote island, Indian police said Wednesday. John Allen Chau, 27, was hit by a hail of arrows as he set foot on North Sentinel Island, part of the Indian Andaman Islands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti gripped by tension as president stays out of sight...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/haiti-gripped-tension-president-stays-sight-183928506.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Port-au-Prince (AFP) - A general strike shut down most of Haiti Wednesday as tension and uncertainty gripped the Caribbean country following deadly protests over the weekend and the president's unexplained absence from public. As police patrolled otherwise empty main avenues in normally chaotic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bankrupt iHEARTMEDIA Wants to Pay Top Brass Up to $33 Million in Bonuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/bankrupt-iheartmedia-wants-to-pay-top-brass-up-to-33-million-in-bonuses-1542826300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The payments would go to 11 senior managers at the nation’s largest radio station owner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flurry Of Arrows... </title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/11/21/669909594/american-reportedly-killed-in-flurry-of-arrows-as-tribe-defends-its-island-off-i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian media has identified the man as either an "adventure tourist" or a Christian missionary who landed on remote and restricted North Sentinel in the Andaman and Nicobar Islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan 'human stampede' at border?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/migrant-caravan-members-may-be-planning-human-stampede-at-us-border-to-provoke-us-aid-group</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the migrant caravan, who have spent the past month traveling from Central America through Mexico to reach the U.S. border, are talking about crossing the border en masse as a way to provoke the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada homicide rate spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/statistics-canada-blames-guns-gangs-as-homicide-rate-hits-10-year-high-1.4186494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems close to flipping 40 House seats as final race tilts in favor...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/democrats-close-to-flipping-40-house-seats-as-straggler-tilts-in-their-favor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are on the cusp of flipping 40 seats in the House, solidifying what many prognosticators had long anticipated: a blue wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Apologizes for 'Reminder Not to Overeat' Social Post...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/11/21/sarah-michelle-gellar-apologizes-for-reminding-people-not-to-overeat-on-thanksgiving-terribly-sorry-that-people-were-offended/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Sarah Michelle Gellar apologized to fans Tuesday for saying that she wanted to remind herself "not to overeat" on Thanksgiving, saying that she's "terribly sorry" if she fat-shamed anyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families urged to give DNA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/efa99b0e53864464ae29d05962a8f716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Authorities are using a powerful tool in their effort to identify the scores of people killed by the wildfire that ripped through Northern California: rapid DNA testing that produces results in just two hours. The system can analyze DNA from bone fragments or other remains, then match it to genetic material provided by relatives of the missing. But the technology depends on people coming forward to give a DNA sample via a cheek swab, and so far, there are not nearly as many volunteers as authorities had hoped for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Border troops authorized to use force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4bda56332972408ea0b47095c9ff3109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Defense Secretary Jim Mattis said on Wednesday the White House has given him explicit authority to use military troops to protect Customs and Border Protection personnel, with lethal force if necessary, at the southwest border. This could, under certain circumstances, mean directing troops to temporarily detain migrants in the event of disorder or violence against border patrol agents. "This is minutes -- not even hours" of potential detention, Mattis said, suggesting that he was not planning to use the military to operate migrant detention camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN environment chief resigns after audit reveals unnecessary plane flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/20/un-environment-chief-erik-solheim-resigns-flying-revelations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Erik Solheim quits after Guardian reveals excess travel and rule breaking which led to withholding of funds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON workers plan Black Friday protests against inhumane conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6415035/Amazon-workers-plan-Black-Friday-protests-online-giant-s-UK-warehouses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insiders at the GMB Union have said protests in Rugeley, Milton Keynes, Warrington, Peterborough and Swansea could clash with the shopping surge at the end of this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smart' toilets collect 'health information'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/21/smart-toilets-would-be-a-huge-boon-to-public-health-commentary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both doctors and patients could benefit if we figure out a way to stop flushing away some of our most vital health information, argues Dr. Sameer Berry, a third-year resident physician at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28% holiday shoppers still in debt from LAST year... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/how-to-deal-with-a-holiday-debt-hangover.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 3 in 10 shoppers are still paying off holiday debt from last year. If you're among them, here's how to juggle debt repayment and this year's holiday expenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Condom Fashion Show' at College...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Teaching the Utah kiddos how to have safe, consensual, and pleasurable sex is my jam.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads urge staff to leak secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-46290049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Freedom from Facebook campaign is using the company's own ad tools to encourage staff to share details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars to snub actor over 'N-word' use?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/viggo-mortensen-n-word-green-book-racial-slur-oscar-chances-1203033543/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversy over Viggo Mortensen’s use of the N-word during a recent Q&amp;A for his movie “Green Book” appears to be over, but can he and the film recover enough to emerge as a genuine a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK 'prepares for war' with DC...</title>
      <link>http://uk.businessinsider.com/facebook-hires-doj-lawyer-kate-patchen-on-trump-antitrust-concerns-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has hired Kate Patchen, the chief of the Department of Justice's antitrust division in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food recalls cramp holiday menus...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/11/21/turkey-recall-romaine-lettuce-thanksgiving-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not turkey! Anything but the turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Insurers Spying On Your Sleep...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/you-snooze-you-lose-insurers-make-the-old-adage-literally-true</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of sleep apnea patients rely on CPAP breathing machines to get a good night’s rest. Health insurers use a variety of tactics, including surveillance, to make patients bear the costs. Experts say it’s part of the insurance industry playbook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European privacy search engines aim to challenge GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd8824e6f9424439b66e3992882b5c0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — In the battle for online privacy, Google is a U.S. Goliath facing a handful of European Davids. The backlash over Big Tech's collection of personal data offers new hope to a number of little-known search engines that promise to protect user privacy. Sites like Britain's Mojeek , France's Qwant , Unbubble in Germany and Swisscows don't track user data, filter results or show "behavioral" ads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami ULTRA music fest so loud it's bad for fish?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/environment/article221964565.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week the University of Miami raised objections over moving the Ultra electronic dance music festival to Virginia Key, where research tanks are located, citing potential damage to fish. Turns out ocean noise pollution is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer argues rapper's gangster image is pretend...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/21/tekashi-6six9ines-lawyer-he-only-pretends-to-be-a-gang-member/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“An entertainer who portrays a ‘gangster image’ to promote his music does not make him a member of an enterprise.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Dogs With 'Special Skills' to Protect Crowd...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Police-Dogs-K9-Explosive-Odor-Pursuit-Vapor-Wake-Protecting-Crowd-Security-Thanksgiving-Day-Parade-NYPD-500935842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As thousands of people flock over the holiday for a glimpse of the Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade, NYPD will be on scene to make sure everyone remains safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Aggressive Military Reorganization Prompts Conflict Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2018-11-21/chinas-aggressive-military-reorganization-prompts-fears-of-conflict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in Diabetes to Make Insulin Scarce...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-care-news/articles/2018-11-20/study-insulin-access-will-decrease-by-2030-as-diabetes-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Clinton Foundation Donations Down 90%...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-21/clinton-foundation-donations-plummet-90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Hires DOJ Silicon Valley Antitrust Chief...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/11/21/facebook-has-poached-the-dojs-silicon-valley-antitrust-chief/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has recruited Kate Patchen, a veteran of the U.S. Department of Justice who led its antitrust office in Silicon Valley, to be a director and associate general counsel of litigation. Patchen takes up her post amid ongoing scandals and reputation crises for her new employer, joining Facebook…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Border troops authorized to use force...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/nov/21/border-troops-authorized-use-force/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House sent a memo to the Pentagon this week granting troops stationed at the border permission to engage in some law enforcement tasks, and to use lethal force if they come under danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Woman cooks lover, serves remains with rice  to workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46287259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Moroccan confessed to feeding his remains to Pakistani workers in the UAE in a traditional dish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrecy reaches new levels at public trial of El Chapo...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/21/nyregion/el-chapo-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Numerous private motions and letters have been a part of the case against Joaquín Guzmán Loera. This week, the secrecy reached new levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel uses Papadopoulos tweets against him...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/layer8/george-papadopoulos-tweets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most spend too much time sitting; Death risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/most-americans-spend-too-much-time-sitting-and-not-exercising-at-all-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research finds too many U.S. adults don't get any exercise at all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge 'pseudo-satellite' aircraft to fly high for months...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/huge-high-flying-pseudo-satellite-will-soon-take-skies-ncna938946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Odysseus is one of the biggest unpiloted aircraft ever built.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SPARS WITH CHIEF JUSTICE</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/chief-justice-john-roberts-rebuts-trump-obama-judge/story?id=59344259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts rebutted President Donald Trump's recent criticism of a judge who ruled on his asylum policy as an "Obama judge." Trump responded on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No charges for FEDEX driver who kills man after being called racial slurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2018/11/no-charges-for-fedex-driver-who-fatally-punched-man-calling-him-racial-slurs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FedEx driver in Portland was found legally justified in punching a man who later died in September after the stranger called the worker racial slurs and tried to hit the driver first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA prosecutor declines felony case against Avenatti...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/71d38227507640e796d0db0b9256f038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Los Angeles prosecutors have declined to charge attorney Michael Avenatti with a felony after his girlfriend alleged abuse. The Los Angeles district attorney's office said Wednesday it referred the case to city prosecutors to consider misdemeanor charges. Avenatti was arrested on a felony domestic violence charge last week after his girlfriend told police he roughed her up at his apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ash from Alaska volcano prompts aviation warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2018/11/21/ash-from-alaska-peninsula-volcano-prompts-aviation-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were no immediate reports of ash falling in nearby Perryville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O sells 1.4 million books in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/apnewsbreak-obamas-book-sells-1-4-million-copies-in-a-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Michelle Obama's "Becoming" has become a massive hit. Crown Publishing told The Associated Press on Wednesday that the former first lady's memoir has sold more than 1.4 million copies in all formats in the U.S. and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 suspected bombs found in London apartment...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6415569/Two-suspected-BOMBS-disused-London-flat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspicious devices were found at a flat in Craven Park, Harlesden, this morning and are believed to be improvised explosive devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy rain may trigger mudslides in wildfire areas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/california-fires-containment-search-rescue-air-2018-11-21-camp-woolsey-paradise-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storm could help crews battling California's devastating Camp Fire but also complicate recovery efforts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Secret Plan to Build 5 Nuke Warheads...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-secret-plans-build-five-nuclear-warheads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new bombshell report shows the Iran had concrete plans to manufacture and build at least five nuclear weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economists Predict: 2020 Recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/21/trump-economy-expected-to-slow-down-in-2019-before-possible-recession-in-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The economy's growth could slow to a crawl by the end of next year and fall into recession by 2020, economists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortions in US decline to lowest level in dozen years...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/417876-number-of-abortions-in-us-drops-24-percent-from-2006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of abortions in the United States dropped sharply from 2006 to 2015, according to a new figures from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 60 MPH? Self-driving cars can be bedrooms on wheels...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/traffic/article221930550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The autonomous vehicles of the near future will be spacious enough for eating, drinking, sleeping, working, watching movies and other typical human behaviors -- like having sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental plane flies silently, may lead to quiet drones...</title>
      <link>http://www.wlox.com/2018/11/21/experimental-plane-flies-silently-may-lead-quiet-drones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wlox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nearly silent, drone-sized aircraft has shown it can fly, a possible step toward quieter drones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, SKorea to scale back major military exercise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0b23b9b347a5470c9ed687991c4b71a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Defense Secretary Jim Mattis says the United States and South Korea will scale back a major military exercise next spring to avoid setting back diplomacy over North Korea's nuclear weapons. Mattis told reporters at the Pentagon on Wednesday that the exercise, which is called Foal Eagle and is conducted each spring in South Korea, will be "reduced in scope." The decision had not previously been announced. He did not provide details, but the decision is an extension of efforts by Washington and Seoul to encourage progress in stalled negotiations over the North's nuclear program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straight from the Bible: Tiny First Temple stone weight unearthed in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/straight-from-the-bible-tiny-first-temple-stone-weight-unearthed-in-jerusalem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteer at City of David sifting project finds rare 'beka' measure, used by pilgrims paying half-shekel tax before ascending to Temple Mount, in dirt from dig near Western Wall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Intel Panel Hiring Money-Laundering Sleuths...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/house-intelligence-panel-hiring-money-laundering-sleuths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of President’s biggest foes is taking steps to chase the Trump-Russia money trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Thunderbirds commander fired after bar argument...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2018/11/21/thunderbirds-commander-was-fired-after-grabbing-neck-of-another-pilot-in-bar-argument/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Thunderbirds commander Lt. Col. Jason Heard was fired last November after an investigation found he placed his hands on another pilot’s neck during a “physical altercation” in a Maryland bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUMBLR Removed from App Store for 'Child Sexual Exploitation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/11/20/tumblr-blacklisted-from-apple-app-store-for-child-sexual-exploitation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Popular microblogging platform Tumblr, popular with teenagers and college-aged youth, has been kicked off of the Apple App Store, allegedly over issues with "child sexual exploitation" being posted on the social network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>34 Caravan Migrants Arrested for Drugs, Drunkenness in Tijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/20/tijuana-police-arrest-34-caravan-migrants-for-drugs-drunkenness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local police officers in Tijuana arrested 34 caravan migrants for misdemeanor charges including drug possession and public drunkenness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But she can't Run for President in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/11/20/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-cant-run-for-president-in-2020-trump-should-be-relieved/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Constitution says the president must be at least 35 years old. But age doesn't guarantee wisdom or ability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Reveals 'Tech Error' That Exposed Names, Emails... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/amazon-reveals-technical-error-that-exposed-customer-names-emails-just-in-time-for-holiday-shopping-1202505984/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the holiday shopping season kicks into gear, Amazon has disclosed to select customers that their names and email addresses were “inadvertently disclosed” due to a “technical er…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wins over ANOTHER critic with deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/new-york-congressman-who-signed-letter-against-pelosi-now-says-hell-support-her/2018/11/21/24212438-ed9f-11e8-baac-2a674e91502b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Brian Higgins said he had come to terms after discussions with Pelosi, Senate Minority Leader Charles Schumer and the incoming Ways and Means chairman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MESS:  San Francisco Sidewalks Graffitied with Apparent Feces... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcbayarea.com/multimedia/San-Francisco-Sidewalks-Graffitied-With-Feces-500611001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcbayarea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a survey of San Francisco's dirtiest streets, the NBC Bay Area Investigative Unit discovered what appeared to be graffiti laced with feces along sidewalks on two different blocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Trump wanted to prosecute Comey, Hillary...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/060ca2399a744b4a9554dbd2ec276a90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump told his counsel's office last spring that he wanted to prosecute political adversaries Hillary Clinton and former FBI Director James Comey, an idea that prompted White House lawyers to prepare a memo warning of consequences ranging up to possible impeachment, The New York Times reported Tuesday. Then-counsel Don McGahn told the president he had no authority to order such a prosecution, and he had White House lawyers prepare the memo arguing against such a move, The Associated Press confirmed with a person familiar with the matter who was not authorized to discuss the situation. McGahn said that Trump could request such a probe but that even asking could lead to accusations of abuse of power, the newspaper said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF HER...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/11/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-confounds-house-democrats/576307/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staffers and aides to party leadership say they love her enthusiasm. But they’re worried her approach will threaten caucus unity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART asks fire evacuees to move 'Wallywood' tent city from their parking lot...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article221950100.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camp Fire evacuees in California are being asked to leave the settlement tent city “Wallywood” in a Chico WalMart parking lot. It has grown in size and number of victims after the wildfire destroyed Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular Exercise May Keep Body 30 Years 'Younger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/21/well/move/regular-exercise-may-keep-your-body-30-years-younger.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The muscles of older men and women who have exercised for decades are indistinguishable in many ways from those of healthy 25-year-olds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOROS SOLD BEFORE FALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/george-soros-sold-facebook-stock-just-before-it-tumbled-1542801600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soros Fund Management, which manages the Soros family’s wealth, also sold Netflix and Goldman Sachs stock before shares dropped. It bought Alibaba and Micron Technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Experiment Shows Users' Heart Rates, Blood Pressures Shoot Up After Logging On...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/19/social-media-impact-on-mental-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some spend their lives searching for happiness, and with smartphones close by, many of us look for it online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov't Facial Biometrics Program Catches More Illegals at Airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/11/cbps-facial-biometrics-program-has-caught-26-alleged-imposters/152957/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since its rollout this summer, the biometrics program is finding more success at land borders than airports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Is Holiday racist? College students react... </title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"[W]e're celebrating taking away land from Natives."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDCHILLS NEAR ZERO FOR NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/frigid-winds-to-whip-through-nyc-for-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade/70006658</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaning Tower of Pisa now leaning a little less...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/21/leaning-tower-pisa-now-leaning-little-less-experts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Leaning Tower of Pisa is leaning just a little bit less thanks to years of remedial engineering works, experts have disclosed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome takes bulldozers to gaudy 'mafia' villas...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181121-rome-takes-bulldozers-gaudy-mafia-villas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2016 election cut dinners short. Will 2018 do same?</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2018-elections/2018/11/21/2016-election-cut-thanksgiving-dinners-short-will-2018-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If your relatives make a quick escape from the dinner table this Thanksgiving, it may not be because you served them dry turkey and lumpy mashed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$9 trillion corporate debt bomb 'bubbling' in economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/21/theres-a-9-trillion-corporate-debt-bomb-bubbling-in-the-us-economy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At first glance, it looks like a $9 trillion time bomb is ready to detonate, a corporate debt load that has escalated thanks to easy borrowing terms and a seemingly endless thirst from investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/CNN/status/1065246274725785603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Aerial footage shows traffic gridlock Tuesday night on the 405 Freeway in Los Angeles as the Thanksgiving travel rush begins. Follow along here for live traffic updates from across the US throughout the holiday weekend: https://t.co/VcSBHaqXQd https://t.co/XE27JJQBls”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL ON THE 405...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/21/rush-hour-traffic-for-thanksgiving-in-la-looks-like-a-living-nightmare-8162072/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanksgiving traffic could be the worst since 2005.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump praises Saudi Arabia amid pressure over ally...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181121135654-qitrb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/OIL (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Trump praises Saudi Arabia amid pressure over ally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV presenter suffers heart attack live on air...</title>
      <link> https://www.standardmedia.co.ke/article/2001303507/tv-presenter-suffers-heart-attack-live-on-air-during-sports-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi accused of torturing female activists by electrocution...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/saudi-arabia-women-tortured-activists-human-rights-watch-flogging-electrocution-a8644426.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More millennials moving back home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6410835/More-millennials-moving-home-making-depressed-studies-find.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About a third of millennials in the US live with their parents and it's saving them money but it might be destroying their mental health - and their parents, according to recent German and UK research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsrooms continue to cut jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/newsrooms-continue-to-cut-jobs-struggle-with-diversity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s newsrooms continue to shed jobs despite the uptick in the economy and reader boom in Trump-related stories, according to the latest industry report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrestler rushed to hospital after rival throws concrete block at head...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/7793074/wrestler-hospital-emergency-brain-surgery-blood-clot-concrete-block/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WRESTLER has been rushed to hospital for emergency brain surgery to remove a blood clot from his brain after a rival threw a concrete block at his head. Cuervo, a Puerto Rican wrestler competing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller got some answers, but he's not done with Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/20/mueller-investigation-trump-answers-1009350</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel may have to subpoena the president to get answers about his time in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON employees snapped up NYC real estate before headquarters announcement...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2018/11/20/amazon-employees-snapped-up-ny.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon employees snapped up NYC real estate before headquarters announcement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College student dies from Adenovirus, 5 others diagnosed...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/local-news/university-of-maryland-student-dies-from-adenovirus-5-others-diagnosed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A University of Maryland student has died from a strain of Adenovirus, school officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alzheimer's vaccine?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6410097/New-Alzheimers-shot-safe-mice-cut-cases-half-scientists-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;University of Texas, Southwestern, scientists have developed a new vaccine that supercharged mice's own immune systems to fight Alzheimer's proteins without side effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular Exercise May Keep Body 30 Years 'Younger'...</title>
      <link>Regular Exercise May Keep Body 30 Years 'Younger'...</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American 'adventure tourist' killed by remote tribe with bows and arrows...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181121-us-tourist-killed-arrow-shooting-indian-tribe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Fewer than two in 10 looking forward to talking politics...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/417780-less-than-two-in-10-americans-looking-forward-to-talking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 15 percent of Americans say they are “looking forward” to talking politics at the Thanksgiving dinner table this year, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacked?</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2018-11-21/dolce-gabbana-accused-of-insulting-china-blames-hackers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
DOLCE &amp; GABBANA cancels China show amid racism row...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2018/nov/21/dolce-gabbana-cancels-catwalk-show-amid-ad-row-racist </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Label accused of trivialising Chinese culture in video of model using chopsticks to eat pizza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats see rural gains bolstering fight for White House in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-rural/democrats-see-rural-gains-bolstering-fight-for-white-house-in-2020-idUSKCN1NQ193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats made dramatic gains in this month's U.S. congressional elections ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Chopsticks' ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-dolce-gabbana-china/dolce-gabbana-cancels-shanghai-show-after-chopsticks-advert-goes-viral-idUSKCN1NQ162</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dolce &amp; Gabbana canceled a marquee fashion show in China's commercial hub o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOW SQUALLS THREATEN TRAVEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/snow-squalls-to-threaten-dangerous-travel-in-northeast-on-busiest-driving-day-of-the-year/70006659</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEMPS 35&amp;#176; BELOW AVERAGE!</title>
      <link>http://sandhillsexpress.com/abc_national/blast-of-snow-for-new-england-before-recordcold-thanksgiving-abcid36131389/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sandhillsexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(NEW YORK) — Across the Northeast Tuesday morning, winter weather advisories are in effect, with much of New England anticipating snow. Around 7 a.m. EST snowfall’s expected to begin from western Massachusetts to Albany, New York, as well as in southern Vermont, New Hampshire and Maine. Snow showers from Buffalo to Watertown are also expected [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She's everywhere: Ocasio-Cortez puts trek to Congress online...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7be7579bb83a4c258234d9a61ffaa1c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — She's cooked bean soup live and done laundry in public. She narrated much of what she calls "Congress camp" on Capitol Hill. We know what's in her bank account — less than $7,000 — and what she thinks of reviews of her clothing. Such intimate details have kept Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez's star on the rise since she upset Democratic veteran Joe Crowley in New York's June primary. By the time she takes her seat in the House on Jan. 3 as the youngest woman ever elected to Congress, the 29-year-old Ocasio-Cortez will have blazed a new, more public trail to Washington and literally shed light on the maze of Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Vacations, $100,000 Discounts: Homebuilders Get Desperate...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/free-vacations-100-000-discounts-homebuilders-get-desperate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free Vacations, $100,000 Discounts: Homebuilders Get Desperate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Biggest iPhone Assembler Planning Deep Cost Cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-21/foxconn-apple-s-biggest-iphone-assembler-plans-deep-cost-cuts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW THE RAIN</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/62091347d0b240b5a1379e4ff8ea3970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Rain in the forecast starting Wednesday could aid crews fighting California's deadly wildfires while raising the risk of flash floods and complicating efforts to recover remains of those killed. Residents in communities charred by the Los Angeles-area fire stacked sandbags as they prepared for possible downpours that threatened to unleash runoff from hillsides left barren by flames. In Northern California, teams continued sifting through ash and debris as they searched for bodies in and around the decimated town of Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorean named Interpol president in blow to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2605f7fbb7b149728803f105e15b3a11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — South Korea's Kim Jong Yang was elected as Interpol's president on Wednesday, edging out a longtime veteran of Russia's security services who was strongly opposed by the U.S., Britain and other European nations. Kim's surprise election was seen as a victory for the White House and its European partners, who had lobbied up until the final hours before the vote against Alexander Prokopchuk's attempts to be named the next president of the policing organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American 'adventure tourist' killed by remote tribe with bows and arrows...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/american-tourist-killed-tribe-sentinel-island-john-allen-chau-death-bow-arrow-a8644196.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless Crisis Getting Worse in Richest Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-homeless-crisis-is-getting-worse-in-america-s-richest-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Homeless Crisis Is Getting Worse in Americaâ€™s Richest Cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As FACEBOOK Faces Fire, Heat Turns Up on No. 2 Sandberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/99f610ef159f46e6a118d9b477897e97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For the past decade, Sheryl Sandberg has been the poised, reliable second-in-command to Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg, helping steer Facebook's rapid growth around the world, while also cultivating her brand in ways that hint at aspirations well beyond the social network. But with growing criticism over the company's practices, or lack of oversight, her carefully cultivated image as an eloquent feminist leader is showing cracks. Questions these days aren't so much about whether she'll run for the Senate or even president, but whether she ought to keep her job at Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tidy and quiet teens live longest...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/11/20/tidy-quiet-teens-live-longest-scientists-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quiet and tidy teenagers are more likely to live to old age, the results of a 48-year study suggest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER: Dems Flip Utah House Seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/politics/2018/11/20/its-over-democrat-ben/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Final vote counts Tuesday showed that Democrat Ben McAdams did not jump the gun &lt;a href="https://www.sltrib.com/news/politics/2018/11/19/election-update-utah/" target=_blank&gt;when he declared victory&lt;/a&gt; a day earlier over two-term Republican Rep. Mia Love.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enninful next Anna Wintour? </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Is-Edward-Enninful-the-next-Anna-Wintour-13409216.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edward Enninful, the new editor in chief of British Vogue, is supremely confident in both his aesthetic beliefs and in his worldview. In short order, he has upended a century-old publication, transforming its masthead to be more reflective of the global audience it seeks to serve and crafting some of the most memorable, inspiring and diverse fashion covers of the past year. His work exudes authenticity. He's made inclusiveness look organic and effortless. And he's made fashion look glorious. Yet Enninful, on this day in the middle of Paris Fashion Week, is flummoxed over a coat. Not just any coat, Enninful tells me, but his coat. It's caramel-colored, a gift from Riccardo Tisci, the recently appointed creative director of Burberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bleeding billions: Net worths of top tech execs take massive hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6412511/Top-tech-executives-bleed-billions-Amazon-Apple-Facebook-Google-stocks-plummet.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow closed Tuesday at 24,465, 551 points down from Monday after struggling all day. All of its 2018 gains have now been wiped out, taking a significant toll on CEOs and top investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIDEMIC OF CHILD GAMBLERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6411759/Epidemic-child-gamblers-Experts-blame-explosion-TV-adverts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An audit by the Gambling Commission found that a worrying 450,000 children bet regularly, with an average stake of £16 each week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first total body scanner...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6079357/Watch-scan-takes-3D-images-human-body-world-first.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of California, Davis, have unveiled their new EXPLORER scanner, which is faster and produces higher-quality scans than any other machine used in hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes life meaningful? More Americans say money than faith...</title>
      <link>http://www.pewforum.org/2018/11/20/where-americans-find-meaning-in-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewforum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family is the most common source of meaning in America, but economic, religious and political divides shape where people find meaning in other aspects of life.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
