<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China robot censors crank up...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-tiananmen-censorship-idUSKCN1SW03Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the most sensitive day of the year for China's internet, the anni...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah judge suspended for criticizing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/utah-judge-suspended-criticizing-trump-social-media-court-n1010331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court noted multiple times when Kwan had provided political comments that criticized Donald Trump, as a presidential candidate in 2016 and as president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brennan Security Clearance NOT Revoked...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-targeting-of-intelligence-agencies-gains-a-harder-edge/ar-AABU9Mb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran police chief says raid on journalist may have violated law...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/25/us/san-francisco-police-chief-journalist-raid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Bill Scott said "the news media and the hardworking men and women of the police department deserve better."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence to West Point grads: Expect to see combat...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/education/2019/05/mike-pence-to-address-diverse-graduating-west-point-cadets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence told the most diverse graduating class in the history of the U.S. Military Academy on Saturday that the world is “a dangerous place” and they should expect to see combat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU voters elect new parliament as nationalism mounts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c137002ee4844b7ac4d2f33e626419f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Across the continent of Europe, anti-EU populists and proponents of closer unity made a final push for support Sunday as 21 nations went to the polls in up a continent-wide battle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist killed in shark attack off Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2019/05/25/officials-man-dies-after-shark-incident-off-mauis-kaanapali-shore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 65-year-old man has died after an apparent shark attack off Maui, officials said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron and Le Pen in battle for soul...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190526-macron-le-pen-battle-eus-soul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macron and Le Pen in battle for EU's soul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7071317/Trump-plays-golf-Japanese-Prime-Minister-Shinzo-Abe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president arrived by helicopter at the Mobara Country Club Landing Zone in Chiba on Sunday morning. He shared a quick handshake with his counterpart, Shinzo Abe, who drove the golf cart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado rips through Oklahoma town...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ddd6e68817804acab2089e6ffe60fdac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL RENO, Okla. (AP) — A likely tornado destroyed a motel, swept through a nearby mobile home park and caused significant damage in the Oklahoma City area, according to the National Weather...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Mag Quake Strikes Peru...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3b12f5abea604f19a5ad36d700d090b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIMA, Peru (AP) — A large earthquake with a preliminary magnitude of 8.0 struck the Amazon jungle in north-central Peru early Sunday, the U.S. Geological survey reported. The quake, at a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Has made his every move correct'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jon-voight-trump-greatest-president-since-lincoln-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Jon Voight posted a series of videos on Twitter Friday night hailing President Donald Trump as the "greatest president since Abraham Lincoln."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO'S WINNING?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-s-allies-insist-he-is-winning-in-feud-with-13896757.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - To many Democrats, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi scored a political victory over President Donald Trump this week, making him so incensed that he hurled insults at her and blew up negotiations on the one issue that held the promise of a rare bipartisan deal - infrastructure.  To the president's allies, a weakened Pelosi, D-Calif., needed to mollify her fractious Democratic caucus, with a growing number demanding that she launch an impeachment inquiry, a move that would give the president a fresh argument that he was a victim of overzealous Democrats incapable of legislating and only interested in investigations.  Taking stock of the feud, each side insisted they got the upper hand in a fight that shows no sign of waning 18 months before the 2020 elections, with implications for the economy as the budget and federal borrowing limit remain unresolved while the dispute over oversight between the White House and Congress rages.  Pelosi's allies said she showed up the president and reinforced an image of a chief executive behaving so badly and childishly that he is unfit for office - a clear message to voters next year. But to Trump's backers, the president succeeded in highlighting that an already unpopular politician is struggling not only with the far-left liberals in the Democratic ranks, but even some on her leadership team.  "She has very challenging dynamics in her conference, and she's trying to appease her conference," said Marc Short, chief of staff to Vice President Mike Pence. "She has a very difficult job."  Some White House aides also said it was better for Trump to be fighting with Pelosi than former vice president Joe Biden or other 2020 candidates, as the president has done recently, elevating their status.  For Trump and Pelosi, the series of salvos...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Crazy Is as Crazy Does...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/25/opinion/sunday/donald-trump-nancy-pelosi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi gets to the core of the Trump con, but he just rages on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRED UP, READY TO GO? Hillary energizes 1,500 Dems in Texas...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/fired-up-ready-to-go-angry-hillary-energizes-1500-dems-in-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Hillary Clinton waiting for Joe Biden to collapse so she can launch another yet campaign for president? The failed 2016 candidate got a plum speaking spot before the Harris County Democratic Party in Texas yesterday, and she seemed newly energized to take on Trump and his policies. At times yelling so loudly that the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JON VOIGHT: Trump Greatest President Since Abraham Lincoln...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/jon-voight-declares-trump-the-greatest-president-since-abraham-lincoln-in-late-night-video-message</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Jon Voight expressed his support for President Trump, declaring him "the greatest president since Abraham Lincoln" in a two-part video message posted on Twitter on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BLAST:  Unrelenting heatwave to break records in Southeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/unrelenting-heat-wave-to-raise-risk-for-brush-fires-in-southeast-into-beyond-memorial-day/70008360</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIS TURN?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/51464bb73e2044a4bd7a3689e32328f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The race to succeed British Prime Minister Theresa May is heating up, the field of Conservative contenders is quickly growing and the focus is squarely on how to handle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE HEAT INDEX...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_heat.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JON VOIGHT: Trump Greatest President Since Abraham Lincoln...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/jon-voight-argues-trump-is-greatest-president-abraham-lincoln-1213731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor posted a message to "people of the Republican Party" on Friday night: "Don't be fooled by the political left."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANNES: Bong Joon-ho's 'PARASITE' Takes Palme d'Or...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cannes-bong-joon-hos-parasite-wins-palme-dor-1213729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Banderas nabbed the best actor award for his role as a past-his-prime director in Pedro Almodóvar's 'Pain &amp; Glory,' while Quentin Tarantino's 'Once Upon a Time in Hollywood' came up empty-handed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANNES WINNERS LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2019/05/2019-cannes-winners-palme-dor-1202144785/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alejandro González Iñárritu and his jury will announce the festival's best performances and films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX ROBOTS 'INDISTINGUISHABLE' FROM HUMANS AFTER UPGRADE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/781127/sex-robots-5g-upgrade-harmony-latest-news-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Images Raise Questions About Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/satellite-images-raise-questions-about-iran-threat-experts-say </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a thousand American troops are headed to the region, but questions about the threat persist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Her biggest test awaits...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/For-Pelosi-the-biggest-test-awaits-Impeach-or-13896496.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats, under the leadership of Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., are slowly marching themselves toward the opening of an impeachment inquiry against President Donald Trump. What seemed out of the question earlier in the year now seems, if not inevitable, increasingly difficult to resist.  Pelosi will not say anything like that at this point. She will continue to try to communicate to both sides of her divided party, nodding to hard-liners by suggesting that Trump's actions constitute potentially impeachable offenses while bowing to vulnerable members in swing districts by speaking cautiously about impeachment itself.  "We're not at that place," Pelosi said at a Thursday news conference, when the question of impeachment came up. That caution came after she noted that the investigations currently underway in the House could lead to "a place that is unavoidable in terms of impeachment." She also asserted that the White house "is just crying out" for impeachment, which she likely sees as a trap.  Trump has certainly put the Democrats in a difficult position. His past actions to disrupt and interfere with the investigation of special counsel Robert Mueller are spelled out in detail in Mueller's report. Attorney General William Barr has said the evidence does not constitute obstruction of justice. Others strongly disagree, including many House Democrats who want to hear more about those episodes.  Beyond the contents of the Mueller report and what they say about the question of obstruction, the administration has further inflamed things by blocking virtually all requests from congressional committees for documents for investigations into various Trump-related matters. The president also ordered former White House counsel Donald McGahn not to testify before the House Judiciary Committee. When McGahn defied a subpoena...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Baltimore and Beyond, Stolen NSA Tool Wreaks Havoc...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/25/us/nsa-hacking-tool-baltimore.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American cities are being hijacked with an N.S.A. cyberweapon that has already done billions of dollars in damage overseas. The N.S.A. will say nothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU votes as populists seek historic breakthrough... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/populists-seek-to-break-the-european-union-from-within/ar-AABTL4l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural America On Verge Of Collapse?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-05-20/rural-america-verge-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinics report rise in picketing, vandalism, trespassing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/24/abortion-providers-disruption-intimidation-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, trespassing hit highest level since 1999 while vandalism occurred at highest rate since 1990</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silicon Valley gamed world's toughest privacy rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/25/how-silicon-valley-gamed-the-worlds-toughest-privacy-rules-1466148</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe's data protection overhaul was supposed to help citizens. Instead, it’s helped Big Tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLU SHOT TO LAST LIFETIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7069767/Scientists-claim-just-two-years-away-developing-lifelong-flu-immunisation-jab.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors have joined forces with international medical professionals to work on lifelong protection from illness and disease, in the form of a super immunisation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California show explores Warhol's social, tech foreshadowing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/870c0360e19c482faf8b1a482e548d8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Before Instagram and Facebook, before selfies and filters that perfect selfies, there was Andy Warhol, using his art to imbue friends, family, celebrities — even himself —...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
AUTOMATED: Pilots losing basic flying skills...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2019/05/25/boeing-737-max-8-autopilot-automation-pilots-skills-flying-hours-safety/1219147001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Boeing 737 Max crashes killed 346 people and grounded the jet due to software problems. It also raised bigger questions about flight automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Trash and rodent nightmare in downtown LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-lopez-skid-row-trash-homeless-merchants-20190525-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The homeless often get blamed for the trash on skid row, but area merchants are also fouling their own nests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: CROSSFIT quits FACEBOOK; 'Utopian socialists'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/crossfit-quits-facebook-instagram-accuses-censorship-utopian-socialists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CrossFit, the branded workout regimen, accused Facebook of being “utopian socialists” and left the platform after the social network deleted a group dedicated to a diet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas newspaper gambles on free iPads as the future...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/73fe8939552b44e1aff0d74ed84fc358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOPE, Ark. (AP) — Over a lunch of hamburger steaks, mashed potatoes and green beans, Walter Hussman delivered his pitch to the dozen or so attendees of the Hope, Arkansas, Rotary Club meeting. He...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran claims can sink U.S. warships with 'secret weapons'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran-arms/iran-can-sink-u-s-warships-with-secret-weapons-military-official-says-idUSKCN1SV049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran can sink U.S. warships sent to the Gulf region using missiles and "sec...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes to present Palme d'Or, with history on line...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bc4671cafe74407b8190f716c500c7ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANNES, France (AP) — History could be made when the top award of the Cannes Film Festival, the Palme d'Or, is handed out Saturday. The Palme d'Or is decided by a nine-person jury, headed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young homebuyers scramble as prices rise faster than incomes...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4dba15376df3463c99c7a03bcb28276e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — For millennials looking to buy their first home, the hunt feels like a race against the clock. In the seven years since the housing crash ended, home values in more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke maintainers caught on drinking spree at missile alert site...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2019/05/24/fe-warren-nuke-maintainers-caught-drinking-alcohol-at-missile-alert-facility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global Strike Command regulations prohibit drinking alcohol in missile alert facilities, and a spokesman for the 90th Missile Wing called it an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE DUMPING: Illegals dropped at bus stations as shelters overflow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/migrants-dropped-us-bus-stations-border-patrol-shelters-063811972.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The three white vans bearing the Border Patrol logo slowly make their way into a back alley next to the Greyhound bus station in the city of San Bernardino, east of Los Angeles. As the agents slide open the doors, a group of 36 haggard-looking men, women and children -- most of them from Guatemala -</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews warned against wearing kippah in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jews-warned-against-wearing-kippah-germany-101916747.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's government commissioner on anti-Semitism has warned Jews about the potential dangers of wearing the traditional kippah cap in the face of rising anti-Jewish attacks. "I cannot advise Jews to wear the Kippah everywhere all the time in Germany," Felix Klein said in an interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Military to Trawl Through 350 Billion Social Media Messages...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-military-trawl-350-billion-074320749.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tender for the project, based at the Naval Postgraduate School in Monterey, California, calls for screening messages from at least 200 million users from more than 100 countries in more than 60 languages to better understand “collective expression.” Messages, including user names, will be examined</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
