<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FL teachers can now carry guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article229906419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic attacks spike, killing most Jews in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldextra.com/news/world/anti-semitic-attacks-spike-killing-most-jews-in-decades/article_e546d35f-c4ea-5ec8-a2ae-686de3cf9ffd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israeli researchers reported Wednesday that violent attacks against Jews spiked significantly last year, with the largest reported number of Jews killed in anti-Semitic acts in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG says he DID NOT exonerate President...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/barr-testimony-mueller-report/h_47600d094b183e8048088dd5456b2ca1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr said he did not exonerate President Trump and said that the American people can decide for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information war escalates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/01/media/media-venezuela-information-war/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Venezuelan government and opposition clash on the streets of Caracas another battle is underway: an information war fought over social media and TV networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT eliminating passwords...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/01/microsoft-ciso-bret-arsenault-wants-to-eliminate-passwords.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft's Bret Arsenault, who serves as its top cybersecurity executive, discussed the top issues facing his company and its clients, and offers advice for smaller firms on how they can get better at eliminating the simplest, most devastating attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Huddles With Hillary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/441632-buttigieg-meets-with-hillary-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg sat down with Hillary Clinton on Tuesday, sources tell The Hill. Buttigieg, the mayor of South Bend, Ind., who has been recently surging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man guilty in plane bomb plot involving meat grinder...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/01/australian-man-found-guilty-in-plane-bomb-plot-involving-meat-grinder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE — An Australian court on Wednesday found a man guilty of plotting to blow up an Etihad Airways flight out of Sydney at the behest of the Islamic State militant group by hiding a bomb in t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It was MY baby!'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6981035/Bill-Barr-faces-senators-following-revelation-Mueller-told-TWICE-release-report-summaries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barr clashed with Senate Democrats in his first appearance on Capitol Hill since the release of the special counsel's report, insisting that 'it was my decision how and when to make it public.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicions grow as Baltimore mayor's leave drags on...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/politics/bs-md-ci-pugh-leave-month-20190430-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mayor Catherine Pugh's leave of absence passes the one-month mark, day-to-day city government operations go on as always but the future remains cloudy. In a city with great needs, and a strong-mayor form of government, clarity at the top ranks of City Hall is needed, many say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly ex-poet laureate faces uproar for skinhead past...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/philadelphia-poet-laureate-faces-uproar-for-skinhead-past/SRP0OB5KMxSCfdXTqJLRJP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia's second poet laureate, who focused on taking poetry to neighborhoods and the city's yo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House wants $4.5 billion -- but NOT for wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/trump-seeks-billions-emergency-border-funds-not-his-wall-n1000706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior administration official said the money would be for "the immediate humanitarian crisis."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA could soon lose ability to 'sniff' ChineseRussian subs...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/digital-show-dailies/navy-league/2019/05/01/us-could-lose-a-key-weapon-for-tracking-chinese-and-russian-subs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the one supplier disappearing, Pentagon is preparing to spend cash to find alternatives for sonobuoy production. But the clock has started to run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private payrolls surge by 275,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/01/private-payrolls-surge-by-275000-in-april-blowing-past-estimates-and-the-biggest-gain-since-july.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gain was led by the services sector, which saw jobs increase by the most in more than two years for the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine becomes 1st state to ban single-use foam containers...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2019/05/maine-becomes-1st-state-to-ban-single-use-foam-containers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maine has become the first state to ban single-use food and drink containers made from polystyrene foam, commonly known as Styrofoam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN VIEWERSHIP COLLAPSE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/441557-cnn-sees-ratings-swoon-in-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN's prime-time ratings dropped a whopping 26 percent in April compared to last year, according to Nielsen Media Research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tear Gas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/70f5125f80b34ed0b5b6d9cb1dc3da23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — The Latest on the political crisis in Venezuela (all times local): 11:30 a.m. State security forces are using tear gas to disperse protesters opposed to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House wants $4.5 billion in emergency funds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/37fef1378820455a9beb44d408eb152e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House is asking Congress for an additional $4.5 billion in emergency spending for border security. That's according to two people familiar with the request who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 'WOODSTOCK 50' Festival Collapsed over Massive Crowd Shrinkage...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/05/01/woodstock-50-music-festival-canceled-investors-accommodating-guests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woodstock 50's main investor pulled out because it wasn't anticipating making room for overnight guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia 'secretly installs nukes in Venezuela'... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8977662/russia-nuke-missiles-venezuela-cuban-missile-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has secretly installed nuclear missiles in Venezuela a US politician has sensationally claimed  – in a chilling echo of the Cuban Missile Crisis. Republican congressman Mario Diaz-Bala…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fines? Jail time? All options on table for enforcing subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/fines-jail-time-democrats-leave-options-table-enforcing-subpoenas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats have several options to enforce their subpoena power over the administration, including what is known as inherent contempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Might Give Homeless People Right to Camp ANYWHERE...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/04/29/this-city-might-give-homeless-people-the-right-to-camp-anywhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a half-million people live on the street in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norman Lear Rips NETFLIX: 'Death By Data'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/norman-lear-rita-moreno-one-day-at-a-time-cancellation-1205229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two icons weigh in on how their sitcom reboot became a victim of the streaming algorithm: "There’s a lesson here."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Jinping: Socialism 'Essence of Patriotism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/04/30/xi-jinping-socialism-is-essence-of-patriotism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping tells Chinese youth that patriotism, nationalism, and socialism are inseparable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro vows to resist 'Gringo Empire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/05/01/venezuela-maduro-speech-guaido-uprising/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicolás Maduro denied that he had lost control of the military and vowed to use all his power to crush legitimate President Juan Guaidó.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL: Sharp increase in Congo Ebola deaths as medical teams hit by attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/sharp-increase-in-congo-ebola-deaths-as-medical-teams-hit/article_f42efc86-deee-5029-8136-eb5a09123312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KINSHASA, Congo — Ebola cases and deaths in eastern Congo have risen sharply in the past week, authorities said Tuesday, placing the blame on recurrent attacks on treatment centers and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military stops releasing Afghanistan war information...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/253f6e2504ad4c72aed8a2d0499a673e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Amid a battlefield stalemate in Afghanistan , the U.S. military has stopped releasing information often cited to measure progress in America's longest war, calling it of little...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL GRILL!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff8a0eed70d0451584a941eab7a5d15c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General William Barr defended his handling of special counsel Robert Mueller's Russia report on Wednesday amid new revelations that Mueller expressed frustration to Barr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour out of manhole in busy El Paso intersection...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-illegals-pour-out-of-manhole-in-busy-el-paso-intersection-flee-into-darkness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The invasion across the southern border is now occurring from the ground up. Literally. New video shows several illegal aliens pouring out of a manhole in a busy El Paso, Texas intersection. Watch: Illegal immigrants popping up through a manhole in a busy intersection in El Paso, Texas pic.twitter.com/aOJBdr9vmf — Wojciech Pawelczyk 🇵🇱 (@PolishPatriotTM) May …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agreement reached to have Mueller testify before Congress... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190501134145-z0yg8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/MUELLER (URGENT):Agreement reached to have Mueller testify on Russia probe - lawmaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushed AG Twice to Release Summaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/01/us/politics/mueller-letters-barr.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert S. Mueller III wrote that “there is now public confusion about critical aspects of the results of our investigation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professed ignorance prompts calls for resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Barr-s-professed-ignorance-prompts-calls-for-his-13809829.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In back-to-back congressional hearings on April 9 and 10, Attorney General William Barr disclaimed knowledge of the thinking of special counsel Robert Mueller and members of his team of prosecutors investigating Russian interference in the 2016 election.  "No, I don't," Barr said, when asked by Rep. Charlie Crist, D-Fla., whether he knew what was behind reports that members of Mueller's team were frustrated by the attorney general's summary of their top-level conclusions.  "I don't know," he said the next day, when asked by Sen. Chris Van Hollen, D-Md., whether Mueller supported his finding that there was not sufficient evidence to conclude that President Donald Trump had obstructed justice.  These statements resurfaced Tuesday following the revelation that Mueller had sent a letter to Barr two weeks earlier objecting to the attorney general's characterization of the probe.  Suggesting that Mueller's letter - only portions of which have been made public - belied the sworn testimony of the attorney general, Van Hollen recirculated a clip of his back-and-forth with Barr and declared, "He must resign."  In an interview with The Washington Post, the Maryland Democrat said he believed Barr's answer was "completely misleading because he was well aware of the fact that Bob Mueller had raised questions with the substance of the conclusions stated in the attorney general's letter."  The Justice Department didn't immediately return a request for comment on Van Hollen's accusation.  In the March 27 letter, Mueller protested that Barr's four-page memo "did not fully capture the context, nature, and substance" of his work, according to a copy reviewed by The Post. In a subsequent phone conversation between Mueller and Barr - longtime colleagues whose differences of opinion about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skies darken as millions of locusts invade Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1121121/saudi-arabia-news-locust-swarm-najran-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SWARM of locusts seemingly darken the skies and added a thick layer of insects to trees as they invaded Najran in Saudia Arabia at the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside secret world of CIA's social media team...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/441480-inside-the-secret-world-of-the-cias-social-media-team</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A government agency known for its secrecy is making a splash in a very public forum: Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Flushed Kin's Cremated Remains...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/ashes-get-flushed-482091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 30--After his mother kicked him out of her Pennsylvania residence, a 33-year-old man flushed his grandparents’ ashes down the home's toilet, a bizarre retaliatory move for which he is facing cr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifetime supply of California tap water could increase cancer risk...</title>
      <link>http://www.ktvu.com/news/ktvu-local-news/study-a-lifetime-supply-of-california-tap-water-could-increase-cancer-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study published Tuesday claims that drinking California tap water over the course of a lifetime could potentially increase your risk of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may have to stop borrowing later this year: Treasury...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-treasury-refunding/u-s-may-have-to-stop-borrowing-later-this-year-treasury-idUSKCN1S73U4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government will have to stop borrowing money between July and December ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER CHALLENGED BARR SPIN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mueller-complained-that-barrs-letter-did-not-capture-context-of-trump-probe/ar-AAAKJB8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS to start DNA testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/30/politics/homeland-security-dna-testing-immigration/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest mummies NOT in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/worlds-oldest-mummies-chile/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Space Station hit by major power shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/may/01/international-space-station-hit-by-major-power-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX delivery delayed after old power-switching unit malfunctions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Voters say Trump TWITTER use could cost him reelection...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/01/morning-consult-poll-trump-twitter-1295248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;7 in 10 voters say Trump uses Twitter too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie and Biden Circle Each Other, Using Different Rules of Engagement...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sanders-and-biden-circle-each-other-using-different-rules-of-engagement/ar-AAAKNqg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas shootings add to concerns over ex-military and extremism...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article229854289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Gateway to hell' where Mayans made human sacrifices uncovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/775835/guatemala-flores-Lake-Pet-n-Itz-mayans-gateway-to-underworld-historians</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Armageddon' rioting breaks out in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6980499/Armageddon-rioting-breaks-Paris-extremist-demonstrators-hijack-Day-protests.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Black Bloc anti-capitalist movement were involved in clashes with police this afternoon. By 1pm there had been a total of 165 arrests in the French capital with much of the city on lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President depicted in Mueller report feared being tabbed fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/677b7b2f0c184e65921afe2314e468ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The fear was persistent. As the Russia investigation heated up and threatened to shadow Donald Trump's presidency, he became increasingly concerned. But the portrait...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 4 Americans feel they have no one to confide in...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/30/1-in-4-americans-feel-they-have-no-one-to-confide-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in four people don’t feel they have someone to confide in, according to new research. Even after sharing their feelings, seven in 10 have held back how they really felt from a coworker, friend,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine under investigation for swastika boot photo...
</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/marine-corps-reservist-investigation-photo-boots-forming-swastika/story?id=62728105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Marine Corps reservist is under investigation for posting a photo on Instagram that showed four pairs of boots in the shape of a swastika.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening statement...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2019/4/30/18524880/william-barr-mueller-report-senate-testimony-read</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Attorney General’s remarks were released ahead of his appearance before the Senate Judiciary Committee on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: You SHOULD have sex on first date...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sun-men/8973401/sex-first-date-relationship-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT’S official – if you want a serious relationship, you need to have sex quickly. A new survey has revealed that more than a third of men found love after sleeping with their partner on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exiles dream of returning home as they wait for Maduro fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/30/venezuelan-exiles-dream-of-returning-home-as-they-wait-for-maduros-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exiles converge at embassies and consulates around the world to throw their weight behind the attempt to oust Nicolás Maduro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON facial-recognition supercharging police...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Amazon-s-facial-recognition-technology-is-13808193.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HILLSBORO, Ore. - When workers at an Ace Hardware here reported that a woman had walked out of the store with an $11.99 tank of welding gas that she hadn't paid for in her tote bag, an elaborate high-tech crime-fighting operation sprang into action.  A Washington County sheriff's detective, working with the agency's Special Investigations Unit, ran the store's surveillance footage through an internal facial-recognition program built by Amazon, revealing a possible match.  That woman's license plate was flagged and, three months later, a narcotics officer in an unmarked SUV saw it and radioed other patrol deputies to stop her. A deputy clapped a pair of handcuffs around her wrists, an arrest report states. She said she'd needed the gas to fix her car.  Deputies in this corner of western Oregon outside ultraliberal Portland used to track down criminals the old-fashioned way, faxing caught-on-camera images of a suspect around the office in hope that someone might recognize the face.  Then, in late 2017, the Washington County Sheriff's Office became the first law enforcement agency in the country known to use Amazon's artificial-intelligence tool Rekognition, transforming this thicket of forests and suburbs into a public testing ground for a new wave of experimental police surveillance techniques.  Almost overnight, deputies saw their investigative powers supercharged, allowing them to scan for matches of a suspect's face across more than 300,000 mug shots taken at the county jail since 2001. A grainy picture of someone's face - captured by a security camera, a social media account or a deputy's smartphone - can quickly become a link to their identity, including their name, family and address. More than 1,000 facial-recognition searches were logged last year, said deputies, who sometimes used the results to find a suspect's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives want bishops to declare pope heretic...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-heresy/conservatives-want-catholic-bishops-to-declare-pope-a-heretic-idUSKCN1S73KE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Roman Catholic priests, academics and intellectuals have issued an op...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV viewers turn to antennae to escape cable prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90342475/young-tv-viewers-turn-to-antennas-to-escape-cables-insane-prices </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Survey says 31% of U.S. households now use an antenna, with 45% adoption among 25- to 34-year-olds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating MORE rice could be protective against obesity?</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-04/eaft-iss043019.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE defies record fall in iPhone sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/30/apple-earnings-show-company-moving-beyond-iphone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iPhone is becoming less important to Apple's total sales as the smartphone industry stalls and shrinks globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Bet on Guaido Tested...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-01/trump-s-bet-on-guaido-is-tested-as-maduro-remains-in-caracas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange sentenced to 50 weeks prison in bail-jumping case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-48118908 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wikileaks co-founder is sentenced to 50 weeks after nearly seven years in the Ecuadorian Embassy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris on edge as thousands gather for rallies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/paris-edge-thousands-gather-may-1-rallies-111045279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands began rallying for May Day in Paris on Wednesday, with a heady mix of labour unionists, "yellow vest" demonstrators and hardline troublemakers expected to turn out in a test for France's zero-tolerance policy on protest violence. Authorities have warned that this year's marches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIAGRA could cure heart failure...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-05-sex-drug-effective-heart-failure.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drug used to treat erectile dysfunction has been found by University of Manchester scientists to slow or even reverse the progression of heart failure in sheep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Tax for Infrastructure Sparks Fears of Political Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gas-tax-infrastructure-sparks-fears-080000147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasing the gas tax is so politically fraught that it hasn’t been touched in 26 years and it didn’t even come up at a meeting at the White House Tuesday between President Donald Trump, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer to discuss an infrastructure plan. While they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr faces brutal hearing after Mueller revelation...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/01/barr-hearing-mueller-report-1295274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney general will be in the hot seat after news broke of Mueller's dissatisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt searches of phones, laptops at airports rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/transportation/us-searches-of-phones-and-laptops-at-airports-rising-lawsuit-says-20190430.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly filed papers filed in a federal lawsuit claim that U.S. government searches of phones and laptops at airports are on the rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 2 lawmakers view less-redacted document...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/30/mueller-report-redacted-1295105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats want to see a fully unredacted report. Some Republicans say they simply trust Barr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Welcomes Biden To Race With Broadsides...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/30/us/politics/joe-biden-bernie-sanders-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Biden is trying to stay above the intraparty fray, invoking his years with Obama. Mr. Sanders is taking direct aim at the former vice president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes rock Venezuela as Guaido urges uprising...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6975871/Venezuelas-Juan-Guaido-calls-military-revolt-final-phase-overthrowing-President-Maduro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy gunfire was heard near La Carlota airbase in the Venezuelan capital Caracas on Tuesday, after opposition leader Juan Guaido announced the start of an armed uprising against President Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOW OR NEVER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0153cace08c84c8fbf34f9c6a7bdd4dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Opposition leader Juan Guaidó took a bold step to revive his movement to seize power in Venezuela, taking to the streets Tuesday to call for a military uprising that drew...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. rips INSTA for censorship after pic with wounded vet deleted...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/30/donald-trump-jr-rips-instagram-for-censorship-afte/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump Jr. wants to know why his recent picture with a wounded combat veteran was deemed a violation of Instagram’s terms of service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schmidt GOOGLE Departure Follows Misconduct Cover-Up Reports...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/4/30/18524495/google-alphabet-board-eric-schmidt-steps-down-18-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Departure follows backlash over reports of sexual misconduct cover-ups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Dead, 4 Injured After Shooting at UNC Charlotte...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article229873794.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Patron told no dog inside bar. Then rammed bartender with car...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/communities/southwest/news/greenfield/2019/04/29/police-man-hit-greenfield-bartender-car-outside-fin-n-feather/3615301002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Milwaukee man has been charged with intentionally hitting a bartender with his car after he was told not to bring his dog into a Greenfield tavern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens Cuba as US supports uprising...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8a18145f858e41e88475360b9a7decee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration declared quick and enthusiastic support Tuesday for the Venezuelan opposition effort to spark a military uprising against embattled President Nicolas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg 'joke' on privacy bombs as audience silent...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/mark-zuckerberg-privacy-joke-facebook-f8-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Awkward doesn't begin to cover it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Carrying Cross On Trek Across America...</title>
      <link>https://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/us/2019/april/i-was-one-block-away-from-killing-myself-sc-man-carries-cross-sees-god-at-work-on-trek-to-grand-canyon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Acie Burleson encountered Jesus Christ as his Savior, he learned about the biblical command to deny himself, take up his cross, and follow the Lord as Matthew 16:24 states. Years later, he says he's heard from God and has started a journey to literally carry the cross all the way to the Grand Canyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Highest-paid CEOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/04/30/highest-paid-ceos-at-americas-largest-companies-tim-cook-robert-iger/39389897/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall Street reviewed CEO pay at the largest, publicly traded US companies to identify the best-paid CEOs. Tim Cook and Robert Iger make the list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anything to help get God's word out'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesdaily.com/news/local/cross-bearing-journey-reaches-colbert-county/article_43124db9-92dd-560c-9689-86e656cc3d3a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acie Burleson said when he was saved as a Christian some years ago, along with that came a calling to carry Christ's cross.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang to give voter $12,000 to demonstrate policy plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/2019/04/29/2020-presidential-candidate-andrew-yang-give-freedom-dividend-iowa-thousand-dollars-ubi-democrat/3613590002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 Candidate Andrew Yang wants to select an Iowan to receive $1,000 a month for a year out of his own pocket followed up by a hologram campaign stop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious footprints of mythical Yeti sighted, Indian Army claims...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/mysterious-footprints-of-mythical-beast-yeti-sighted-claims-indian-army/articleshow/69107428.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India News: Indian Army on Tuesday claimed that one of its teams spotted mysterious footprints of mythical creature "Yeti" close to Nepal's Makalu Base Camp. Duri</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Worker Gets 10 Years for Insanely Elaborate $4M Heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alaska-keybank-worker-gets-10-years-for-insanely-elaborate-dollar4-million-heist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gerardo Adan Cazarez Valenzuela planned every detail, down to hiring a private getaway jet, but he didn’t count on Mexican police searching his luggage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military colonel shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/americas/live-news/juan-guaido-venezuela-operation-freedom-live-updates/h_fafa4ed6517202198a3cc759bd85212b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A military colonel was reportedly shot during clashes with the opposition on the Francisco Fajardo highway, Venezuela’s Minister of Defense Vladimir Padrino tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorcyclist Crashes While Flipping Off Woman On Highway...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/04/30/police-motorcyclist-who-crashed-after-flipping-off-woman-critical-condition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A motorcyclist who lost control and crashed after allegedly flipping off a driver on a Texas highway is in critical condition, deputies said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
