<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bond payment  in limbo as countdown to default begins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-payment-confusion-starts-countdown-074403900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia’s Finance Ministry said that it has sent payment orders for the interest on its dollar bonds to its correspondent bank, giving incremental details on a debt settlement that has come to exemplify how Moscow plans to handle its future relations with creditors. Most Read from BloombergPutin Vows to Rid Russia of ‘Traitors’ While Waging Ukraine WarRichest Russian Built NYC Power Over Decades and Lost It in WeeksUkraine Update: U.S. House Set to Revoke Russia’s Trade StatusU.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WNBA star's arrest extended to May 19 by Russian court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brittney-griner-russia-arrest-extended-d769f6dfe03a3b55f23ef24960dae787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Moscow court announced it has extended the arrest of WNBA star Brittney Griner until May 19, according to the Russian state news agency Tass. Griner was detained at a Moscow airport in February after Russian authorities said a search of her luggage revealed vape cartridges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Predictions: Will 'DOG' reign supreme?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-oscars-predictions-1d95a10f6b9385ff2c1acbb5158d5f20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of the 94th Academy Awards, Associated Press Film Writers Lindsey Bahr and Jake Coyle share their predictions for a ceremony with much still up in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico Prepare for New Migrant Wave as Inflation Surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberglinea.com/2022/03/17/us-mexico-prepare-for-new-migrant-wave-as-inflation-surges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberglinea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials from the administrations of Presidents Joe Biden and Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador in recent days discussed their concern about the impact that rising food and energy prices will have on the region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS WARN 'WE'LL RISE AGAINST YOU'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10622821/Russian-soldiers-warn-Putin-RISE-against-terror-acts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three captured Russian air force pilots, warned President Vladimir Putin 'you will not hide this for long' because 'many' troops share the same feelings and 'sooner or later, we will come home'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt sites facing unprecedented cyber attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-russia-internet/russian-government-sites-facing-unprecedented-cyber-attacks-report-idUSKCN2LE0NB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian government websites are facing unprecedented cyber attacks and technical efforts are being made to filter foreign web traffic, the TASS news agency cited the digital ministry as saying on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans frantic to migrate as economy falters, new hurdles arise...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-migrants/cubans-frantic-to-migrate-as-economy-falters-new-hurdles-arise-idUSKCN2LE15I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bray Perez, a 19-year-old Cuban university student, is fast losing friends to a growing wave of migration off the island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN HAS 3 MOVES LEFT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-10622533/Russia-Ukraine-happens-win.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine has to sustain the ability of its forces to continue fighting effectively and counterattacking to regain lost territory if it is to hold out against the Russians, a military expert told MailOnline today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of most basic hotel amenities disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-travel-lifestyle-2bffd3573fb6bd7f33222e13605f4510</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether out of necessity due to staffing shortages, out of respect for social distancing or perhaps just to save money, one of the primary amenities that sets a hotel apart from your home — daily housekeeping — is disappearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruined game plan visible in south...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/defence/russias-ruined-game-plan-for-ukraine-is-visible-in-the-south/articleshow/90291832.cms </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two in Israel hit with variant 'not yet known to world'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/17977307/two-people-israel-covid-variant-not-known-to-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO people in Israel have been struck with a new Covid variant described as “not yet known to the world” by experts. The novel strain caused mild symptoms of fever, headaches and muscle aches in th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With legislation languishing and midterms approaching, Dems pressure Biden to issue orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-legislation-languishing-and-midterms-approaching-democratic-lawmakers-pressure-biden-to-issue-executive-orders/ar-AAVbt2Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More humiliation as kidnapped mayor rescued...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-humiliated-mayor-kidnapped-russian-26489172</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin has suffered another humiliating blow in his faltering Ukraine invasion after a city mayor who had allegedly been captured was rescued in a 'special operation'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How stronger hands lengthen life...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/hand-grip-strength-falling-deaths-8dfd77a1-0561-41be-8359-12532af948ce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stronger hands prevent falls, and higher grip strength is linked to healthier hearts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA WARNS WILL PUT USA IN ITS PLACE</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-will-put-its-enemies-such-united-states-their-place-medvedev-says-2022-03-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia warned the United States on Thursday that Moscow had the might to put the world's pre-eminent superpower in its place and accused the West of stoking a wild Russophobic plot to tear Russia apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer Documents Invasion of His Country...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6158001/ukraine-invasion-in-photos-kyiv-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Maxim Dondyuk, the story was always personal, but never more than over the past few weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Car Designers, EVs Offer Blank Canvas...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/17/for-car-designers-e-v-s-offer-a-blank-canvas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internal combustion engine is exiting stage left. While it provided great transportation and performance thrills for many years, it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolated and vulnerable, Hong Kong elderly taking own lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Isolated-and-vulnerable-amid-the-covid-crisis-17008347.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG - The three people who took their own lives on the same day last week in Hong...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifies 50 elites as targets for global hunt to seize assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-administration-identifies-50-russian-elites-as-targets-for-global-hunt-to-seize-assets/ar-AAV9jlu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineers hoping to perfect masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/engineers-are-hoping-to-perfect-masks-before-the-next-covid-wave-or-pandemic/ar-AAVahnG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep experts say Senate has it wrong: Standard time, not daylight saving, should be permanent!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sleep-experts-say-senate-has-it-wrong-standard-time-not-daylight-saving-should-be-permanent/ar-AAV9l4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indicator of economic hardship flashing red...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bond-traders-stunned-hawkish-fed-000428923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Defying their stock-market counterparts, Treasury traders aren’t buying Jerome Powell’s upbeat pronouncements on growth. In fact, in the aftermath of Wednesday’s policy decision, one bond-market indicator of economic hardship is flashing red for the first time since the darkest days of the pandemic.Most Read from BloombergPowerful Quake Off North Japan Kills 4, More Than 90 InjuredUkraine Update: Biden Offers Kyiv Weapons Including Armed DronesRichest Russian Built NYC Power Over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineers hoping to perfect masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/engineers-are-hoping-to-perfect-masks-before-the-next-covid-wave-or-pandemic/ar-AAVahnG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT ENOUGH TO DENT RUNAWAY INFLATION...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/16/the-fed-needs-to-get-a-lot-tougher-to-stop-soaring-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street loved the Federal Reserve’s quarter-point interest hike Wednesday, soaring 500 points on the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My life's at risk': Mexican journalists fear death every day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lifes-risk-mexican-journalists-fear-012904674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each time Maria Martinez leaves home, she fears it will be the last. Only her bodyguards prevent her from joining the eight journalists murdered already this year in Mexico, she believes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil hikes key interest rate ninth straight time, to 11.75%!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-hikes-key-interest-rate-221710071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's central bank raised its key interest rate for the ninth straight time Wednesday, as Latin America's biggest economy continues to reel from surging inflation, now exacerbated by the Ukraine war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN ISSUES NEW THREAT</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2022-03-16/a-war-of-one-putin-defends-brutal-campaign-in-ukraine-as-global-condemnation-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian leader attempted to justify his decision to begin a brutal and bloody assault on Ukraine while also expressing some recognition of the threats to his own grip on power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five people charged with acting as Chinese secret police to spy on, harass U.S. residents critical of Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/five-people-charged-with-acting-as-chinese-government-agents-to-spy-on-harass-us-residents-critical-of-beijing/ar-AAV8SVX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifies 50 elites as targets for global hunt to seize assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-administration-identifies-50-russian-elites-as-targets-for-global-hunt-to-seize-assets/ar-AAV9jlu?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep experts say Senate has it wrong: Standard time, not daylight saving, should be permanent!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sleep-experts-say-senate-has-it-wrong-standard-time-not-daylight-saving-should-be-permanent/ar-AAV9l4d?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Black students sold in 'slave auction' at NC school...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/north-carolina-school-blasted-for-mock-slave-auction-of-black-students</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mother was outraged after finding out that Black students were allegedly "sold" at a mock "slave auction" by their white classmates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First deepfake appears...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/hackers-zelensky-deepfake-surrender-ukraine-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deepfake video showing Ukrainian President Zelensky asking his soldiers to surrender has surfaced online amid Russia's ongoing invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/piers-morgan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail Sales Soften as Gas Prices Bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.ttnews.com/articles/retail-sales-soften-high-gasoline-costs-begin-bite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ttnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growth in U.S. retail sales slowed in February after surging a month earlier, suggesting that consumers tempered their spending in some categories as inflation limited purchasing power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany record infections again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germany-reports-another-record-covid-074032735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany reported another record high seven-day incidence of the coronavirus on Wednesday even as the country prepares to ease restrictions. The Robert Koch Institute (RKI) registered 262,593 new infections, a 22% jump compared to a week ago, bringing the total number of infections to nearly 17.7 million. Infections have been rising again since the start of March after rules preventing unvaccinated people from accessing many indoor public spaces started to be eased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Smollett Released From Jail After Less Than Week...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/jussie-smollett-free-jail-appeal-judge-hate-crime-1234980729/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After less than a week behind bars on a 150-day sentence for faking a hate crime, Jussie Smollett will be walking out of the Cook County Jail today. A one-page order unceremoniously released by the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Schultz Back as STARBUCKS CEO as Thousands of Baristas Unionize...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awp4b/howard-schultz-takes-over-as-starbucks-ceo-as-thousands-of-baristas-unionize</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We encourage Howard Schultz to put union-busting behind him and embrace Starbucks’ unionized future.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV comedy that launched Zelensky back on NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220316-tv-comedy-that-launched-zelensky-to-presidency-back-on-netflix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedy satire in which Volodymyr Zelensky unexpectedly becomes Ukraine's president -- his now war-time job in real life -- will be aired again on Netflix, the streaming platform announced Wednesd…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Academic Grudge Turned Into #MeToo Panic...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/03/14/how-an-academic-grudge-turned-into-a-metoo-panic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the weaponization of sexual misconduct allegations wrecked Florian Jaeger's life and cost his university millions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad's wild rant to 'scum' West...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/europe/russia-ukraine-live-updates-vladimir-putins-wild-rant-to-scum-west/news-story/344c9ceac26156761f6c173a3a63c5dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been three weeks since Russian President Vladimir Putin ordered troops to invade Ukraine on February 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITI to pay expenses for staff seeking abortion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/citi-cover-travel-expenses-u-145324689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As states increasingly pass new abortion restrictions, Citigroup will now cover travel costs for U.S.-based employees seeking an abortion.Driving the news: "In response to changes in reproductive healthcare laws in certain states in the U.S., beginning in 2022 we provide travel benefits to facilitate access to adequate resources," Citi wrote in a filing for its shareholders' meetings set for next month. Get market news worthy of your time with Axios Markets. Subscribe for free.The policy will co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fully focused' Webb telescope beats expectations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-60771210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineers align the mirrors of the $10bn observatory to produce a pin-sharp image of a star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Calls Putin 'War Criminal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/16/politics/biden-calls-putin-a-war-criminal/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden called Russian President Vladimir Putin a "war criminal" on Wednesday as Russia intensifies its attack on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Gov. Considers Running Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/16/former-ny-gov-andrew-cuomo-considers-running-against-kathy-hochul-despite-opposition-from-party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Cuomo is speaking with allies about possibly running against New York Gov. Kathy Hochul. Democratic Party officials scoff at the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South American burglary gang filmed EMPTYING luxury California homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10619547/Spate-home-burglaries-California-linked-criminal-tourists-target-rich.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are blaming a spate of home burglaries in California on South American 'crime tourists' who target wealthy neighborhoods for their robberies before returning home with the loot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willingness to sacrifice growth to stop inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/16/feds-aggressive-interest-rate-forecast-signals-willingness-to-sacrifice-growth-to-stop-inflation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bonds sold off and stocks seesawed in volatile trading after the Fed released a forecast for a slightly more aggressive series of rate hikes than expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State TV discusses invasion plan for seizing Baltic states...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17965158/russian-state-tv-discusses-invasion-seizing-baltic-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN state TV has aired a discussion on seizing the Baltic states as Nato bolster Eastern European allies with thousands more troops. A former senior officer laid out a chilling scenario for Put…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fire engulfs Indianapolis WALMART distribution center... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/massive-fire-engulfs-walmart-distribution-center-near-indianapolis/7XIQLI6TIREHVMDNIUV46GAXNU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive fire at the Walmart distribution center northwest of Indianapolis is sending a large plume of smoke into the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How cigarette tin launched zoo's 50-year love affair with pandas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-chinese-cigarette-tin-launched-dc-e2-80-99s-50-year-love-affair-with-pandas/ar-AAV8dBx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theater where hundreds had taken refuge bombed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/16/europe/ukraine-mariupol-bombing-theater-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A theater where hundreds of people are said to have taken shelter in the besieged Ukrainian city of Mariupol was mostly reduced to rubble on Wednesday, according to an image shared by its city council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sees 6 more ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/16/federal-reserve-meeting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve on Wednesday approved its first interest rate increase in more than three years, and said it expects to keep raising through the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops 'shot, killed 10 people standing in bread line'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-troops-ukraine-kill-10-cherihiv-bread-line-us-embassy-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. embassy in Ukraine says "such horrific attacks must stop," and notes it is "considering all available options to ensure accountability for any atrocity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State TV hit by stream of resignations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60763494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marina Ovsyannikova's protest highlighted a growing number of journalists leaving their jobs at Kremlin-run TV channels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWIII 'MAY HAVE ALREADY STARTED'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/world-war-iii-may-already-started-russian-invasion-zelenskyy-says-rcna19967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outcome of this war has the whole of civilization at stake, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy told "NBC Nightly News" anchor Lester Holt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden sending more anti-aircraft systems, drones...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/white-house/2022/03/zelenskyy-center-stage-facing-congress-pleading-for-help-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy cited Pearl Harbor and the terror attacks of Sept. 11, 2001 on Wednesday as he appealed to the U.S. Congress to do more to help Ukraine’s fight against Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Big Tech made compromises with Kremlin in recent years...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putins-pre-war-moves-against-145840120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian agents came to the home of Google's top executive in Moscow to deliver a frightening ultimatum last September: take down an app that had drawn the ire of Russian President Vladimir Putin within 24 hours or be taken to prison. Google quickly moved the woman to a hotel where she checked in under an assumed name and might be protected by the presence of other guests and hotel security, according to people with knowledge of the matter. The same agents - believed by company officials to be fr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory fight over anonymity is future of internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/anonymous-internet-jeff-koseff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Kosseff on the technological and regulatory fight between those who want to stay anonymous and those who would unmask them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham threatened 25th Amendment to remove Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jonathan-martin-alex-burns-book-biden-sinema-94352832-b1e8-465f-ada0-521729691c73.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person likened Biden's perplexity at Sinema to his difficulty grasping TikTok.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes &amp; Covid: Scientists explore potential connection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-science-health-indiana-diabetes-e1193bc9891e45d589337f7a092f6c4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CROWN POINT, Ind. (AP) — When their 11-year-old son started losing weight and drinking lots of water, Tabitha and Bryan Balcitis chalked it up to a growth spurt and advice from his health class. But unusual crankiness and lethargy raised their concern, and tests showed his blood sugar levels were off the charts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200mph bullet train 'DERAILED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17968773/japan-earthquake-tsunami-warning-bullet-train-derailed-fukushima/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MASSIVE 7.3 earthquake has struck Fukushima nuclear plant and has shaken Tokyo for two minutes triggering a tsunami warning. The Japan Meteorological Agency has released a warning for an over 3ft…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Poaches Buck, Aikman From FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/espn-joe-buck-monday-night-football-1235109536/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buck and Aikman will be the lead play-by-play voice and analyst, respectively, for Monday Night Football.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA accuses Chinese agent of scheme to undermine congressional candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-accuses-chinese-agent-of-scheme-to-undermine-congressional-candidate/ar-AAV8xXW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buildings shake in Tokyo...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/japan-earthquake-fukushima-live-tsunami-26484274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7.3 magnitude earthquake has struck off the coast of Fukushima, leaving two million households without power as the tremor rocked buildings throughout the region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toad breaks silence after 100 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220316-ecuadoran-toad-breaks-its-silence-after-100-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuadoran biologist Jorge Brito was trekking through the forest when he heard what he thought was the chirp of a cricket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coumo Hits CNN With $125M Demand; Says Zucker Behind Everything...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/chris-cuomo-arbitration-demand-cnn-jeff-zucker-1234979631/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: After months of legal anticipation following his December 2021 firing by Jeff Zucker, Chris Cuomo has just launched the official opening salvo in what looks to be protracted battle with …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii man's body was found in bathtub filled with concrete. Police say lover killed him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-hawaii-man-e2-80-99s-body-was-found-in-a-bathtub-filled-with-concrete-his-lover-has-been-charged-with-murder/ar-AAV83bV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/at00r8udwu/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3 mag quake hits north Japan, tsunami alert issued...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-world-news-japan-earthquakes-tsunamis-1e5f510a574d31d6c2048c8c98a3b47b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A powerful 7.3 magnitude earthquake shook off the coast of Fukushima in northern Japan on Wednesday evening, triggering a tsunami advisory. The Japan Meteorological Agency said the quake struck 60 kilometers (36 miles) below the sea.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
