<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Beijing seeks to boost 'masculinity' of students with more gym classes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-seeks-to-boost-masculinity-of-students-with-more-gym-classes/ar-BB1doJ6Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's controversial "Proposal on Preventing the Feminization of Male and Adolescents" aims to "cultivate masculinity" of young students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily death toll stubbornly high...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-pandemics-coronavirus-pandemic-infectious-diseases-california-3dcd7ecda72b30501220ae9c2d2e40ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus deaths in the United States surpassed 450,000 on Thursday, and daily deaths remain stubbornly high at more than 3,000 a day, despite falling infections and the arrival of multiple...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Diplomat' accused of killing British teen was working for U.S. intel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/anne-sacoolas-accused-of-killing-british-teen-harry-dunn-was-working-for-u-s-intelligence-lawyer-testifies/ar-BB1doDN3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The assertion reopens questions about whether she had diplomatic immunity when she fled the U.K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dramatic video shows snow shoveling dispute that escalated to murder-suicide...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/04/video-shows-snow-shoveling-fight-that-escalated-to-murder-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disturbing new video captured the dramatic clash between a man and his neighbors shoveling snow in Pennsylvania that escalated to a murder-suicide. Surveillance footage showed the married coup…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car stolen with 30 vials of inside...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/car-stolen-covid-19-vaccines-inside-police/story?id=75681934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Florida are searching for a man who stole a car containing vials of the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney has plan to give parents up to $15,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/22264520/mitt-romney-checks-parents-4200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Family Security Act would offer up to $350 per month, per kid, to help parents raise their children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 0.06% Israelis sick after 2 shots, no one serious...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/covid-just-006-percent-israelis-sick-after-two-shots-no-one-serious-study-657871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a study conducted by the Maccabi Healthcare Services, immunity appears to further strengthen even after seven days from the second injection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Holocaust research in Poland hinges on libel case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-world-war-ii-trials-poland-germany-f49788cd4ec3e3d161beaa75ba0df7da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Two Polish historians are facing a libel trial for a scholarly examination of Polish behavior during World War II, a case whose outcome is expected to determine the fate of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Propose New Particle -- Portal to 5th Dimension...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3vkny/scientists-have-proposed-a-new-particle-that-is-a-portal-to-a-5th-dimension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The path to dark matter and other fundamental enigmas may be through a warped extra dimension, according to a new study that proposes a new theory of the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area gym open in defiance hit with $550,000 fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Bay-Area-gym-stays-open-defy-COVID-safety-San-Jose-15924899.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Ripped Fitness marches on, remaining open despite more than $500,000 in fines...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaccine rabbi dismissed by Jewish org...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/public-health-massachusetts-coronavirus-pandemic-e5c24eb21e09fd4b9af3f047c8c0fb7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — A prominent Jewish organization is cutting ties with a longtime Massachusetts rabbi for his anti-vaccine views and strident opposition to public health efforts to rein in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PILLOW FIGHT:  David Hogg launching competitor to Mike Lindell...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/david-hogg-pillow-mike-lindell-mypillow-legate-6d23b1a7-50b1-4f31-9391-53e69e36ca58.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindell is one of former President Trump's most adamant defenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy Has Tech to 'Engineer Fabric of Reality'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4adpv9/us-navy-has-patents-on-tech-it-says-will-engineer-the-fabric-of-reality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy's “UFO patents” sound like they've been ripped from a science fiction novel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'$2m advance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9223909/Hunter-Bidens-memoir-Beautiful-Things-April.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beautiful Things is to be published on April 6 by an imprint of Simon &amp; Schuster. The president's sole surviving son has battled drugs but also faced scrutiny on his business dealings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON faces spying claims over AI cameras in vans...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-55938494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The firm says the camera system improves safety but not all drivers are convinced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene regrets 'words of past,' without specific apology...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/house-gop-votes-greene-d00c46241478d39db3996a36f5cbf91e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Embattled Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, facing a House vote to strip her of committee assignments, said Thursday that she regrets some “words of the past,” but she did not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitting on billions, Catholic dioceses amassed taxpayer aid
...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/catholic-church-get-aid-investigation-39a404f55c82fea84902cd16f04e37b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the coronavirus forced churches to close their doors and give up Sunday collections, the Roman Catholic Diocese of Charlotte turned to the federal government’s signature small business relief...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Hated Man in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/02/josh-hawley-future-capitol-president/617873/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The elite conservative world saw Josh Hawley as America’s next great statesman. Instead, he’s revealed uncomfortable truths about the movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems ask to testify under oath for impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-impeachments-us-news-trump-impeachment-8fd6b9f5724f48cc0f4e045ec8c37000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats on Thursday asked Donald Trump to testify under oath for his Senate impeachment trial, saying the former president must explain why he and his lawyers have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting company sues FOX, Giuliani over election fraud claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/business/nation/story/2021-02-04/voting-company-sues-fox-giuliani-over-election-fraud-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A voting technology company is suing Fox News, three of its top hosts, Rudy Giuliani and Sidney Powell for $2.7 billion, charging that the defendants conspired to spread false claims that the company helped steal the U.S. presidential election away from former President Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny urges supporters to free Russia from 'thieves in power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/navalny-urges-russians-from-jail-to-overcome-their-fear/ar-BB1do4Pi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — In a note from jail, opposition leader Alexei Navalny urged Russians Thursday to overcome their fear and “free” the country from a “bunch of thieves,” while the Kremlin cast the arrests of thousands of protesters as a due response to the unsanctioned rallies. Navalny, who was sentenced to two years and eight months in prison earlier this week, said in a statement posted on his Instagram account that “iron doors slammed behind my...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Trump prove that governments with presidents just don't work?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/opinion/article/Did-Trump-prove-that-governments-with-presidents-15924773.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty years ago, a political scientist named Juan Linz wrote a series of influential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman survives being snowed into vehicle in Newark for 5 days!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/elderly-woman-trapped-in-snow-covered-van-for-3-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newark Police are responding to reports of a woman found inside a a van covered in snow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant FL Supermarket Sparks Outrage After Employees, Customers Openly Reject Mask-Wearing...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/florida-supermarket-sparks-outrage-over-customers-employees-rejecting-mask-wearing-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the ongoing coronavirus pandemic, a Florida supermarket is sparking outrage online after [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letters reveal rare look into Jackie O's secret White House visit after JFK assassination...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/nixon-throwback-jackie-kennedy-visited-white-house-jfk-assassination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare look at letters by the Kennedys to the Nixons details the then-secret 1971 meeting: "Can you imagine the gift you gave me?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Cursed Out Teammate For Crying After Championship Game...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/03/tom-brady-cursed-out-teammate-crying-nfc-championship-victory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Making it to a Super Bowl is a big deal for most players. An enormous deal. But not for Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden cancels Elon's adventures in space?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/3/biden-cancels-elon-musks-adventures-in-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is in a titanic struggle with the People’s Republic of China for the dominance of space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUPERT RIGHTS FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/02/fox-news-rupert-murdoch-stepping-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the network’s ratings fall behind those of CNN, the nearly 90-year-old Fox cofounder is apparently taking a special interest in programming changes designed to get Fox back on top. Will it be enough?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TENT CIRCUS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/qanon-fight-impeachment-fallout-expose-republicans-post-trump-rift-n1256627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After having kept Liz Cheney in leadership, Republicans are faced with questions about Marjorie Taylor Greene's future in the caucus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet-loving sleuths hailed after tracking down stolen van with 12 dogs inside...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/04/portland-dog-van-stolen-found</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portland man sped away with van while keys were in ignition, but group of dog lovers worked to get the dogs home safe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden, Denmark to develop digital 'passports'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sweden-plans-digital-coronavirus-vaccine-125927655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden plans to launch a digital coronavirus "vaccine passport" by summer, assuming there is an international standard in place for the document by then, the government said on Thursday. "When Sweden and countries around us start to open up our societies again, vaccination certificates are likely to be required for travel and possibly for taking part in other activities," Swedish digitalisation minister Anders Ygeman told a news conference. Denmark said on Wednesday that it would launch a first version of a coronavirus vaccination passport by the end of February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter memoir will center on struggles with substance abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-business-stephen-king-dave-eggers-84f0218fb720f7f29e79c517962d0011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hunter Biden, son of President Joe Biden and an ongoing target for conservatives, has a memoir coming out April 6. The book is called “Beautiful Things” and will center on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin 'fears being killed like Gaddafi'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/13935361/vladimir-putin-killed-gaddafi-navalny-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin is terrified of being killed like Libyan tyrant Gaddafi in a revolution as protests sweep Russia over the jailing of Alexi Navalny, a leading expert has said. Putin enemy Yuri Felsht…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-China propaganda campaign exploits U.S. divisions in videos emphasizing Capitol attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/pro-china-propaganda-campaign-exploits-us-divisions-in-videos-emphasizing-capitol-attack/ar-BB1do5Ci</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The videos promote pro-Chinese propaganda delivered by a robotic voice speaking fractured and sometimes-ungrammatical English.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Republican Support for Trump '24 run craters...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/shock-poll-republican-support-for-trump-2024-plummets-by-a-whopping-20-points-since-december/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Support for a 2024 run by former President Donald Trump has cratered by 20 points since December, in a stunning poll that illustrates the political bind many Republicans find themselves in. The new survey from Echelon Insights found that only 45 percent of Republicans would “like to see Donald Trump run for president in 2024,” […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Polls sinking. Dems mobilizing. Newsom recall just got real...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/04/newsom-allies-recall-465717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campaign to oust Newsom went from unlikely to unavoidable this week as pervasive frustration with Newsom’s pandemic management cut sharply into his approval numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Holy Grail' Injection Kills Skin Cancer Cells...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/holy-grail-nanoparticles-treats-skin-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The injections consist of polymer-based nanoparticles that latch onto cancer cells long enough to inflict some serious damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World faces 4,000 variants...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210204102538-eo787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-World faces around 4,000 COVID-19 variants as Britain explores mixed vaccine shots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy Claims Q Ignorance...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kevin-mccarthy-claims-qanon-ignorance-after-denouncing-it-last-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don't know if I say it right, I don't even know what it is,” the GOP leader said after specifically saying QAnon “has no place” in the Republican Party last August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turks Escape to Country as Locked-Down Istanbul Loses Shine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/turks-escape-to-country-as-locked-down-istanbul-loses-its-shine/ar-BB1do47F </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applications for second passports rise sharply...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/lifestyle/travel/article/A-second-passport-is-not-easy-to-get-but-worth-15921992.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Conolly is American and Irish. He's also lucky: A second passport may be the most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uneasy truce...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-congress-republicans/in-uneasy-truce-house-republicans-fail-to-punish-greene-or-cheney-idUSKBN2A31JL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. House Republicans opted on Wednesday not to punish newcomer Marjorie Taylor Greene for incendiary comments, including support for violence against Democrats, and turned back an attempt to oust a leader who had voted to impeach President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual Rocket Thruster Will Send Humans to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/space/rockets/a35393411/magnetic-rocket-thruster-spaceflight-mars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plasma + magnets = magic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E.V.s Force Carmakers to Reinvent Wheel, and Brakes, and Mirrors...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/04/e-v-s-force-carmakers-to-reinvent-the-wheel-and-brakes-and-mirrors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking a cue from its Swedish colleagues at Volvo and the pragmatic views of automotive product planners worldwide, General Motors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitting on billions, Catholic dioceses amassed taxpayer aid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/personal-taxes-small-business-charlotte-health-coronavirus-pandemic-39a404f55c82fea84902cd16f04e37b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the coronavirus forced churches to close their doors and give up Sunday collections, the Roman Catholic Diocese of Charlotte turned to the federal government’s signature small business relief...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team under pressure to ditch tomahawk chop celebration...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-kansas-city-super-bowl-football-f1c4aa9c53e44a093c43c858bc8380c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure is mounting for the Super Bowl-bound Kansas City Chiefs to abandon a popular tradition in which fans break into a “war chant” while making a chopping hand motion designed to mimic the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prayer breakfast gives Biden fresh chance to call for unity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-capitol-siege-politics-christianity-ac782a7f78734012ea880e51be6fec79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is expected to address the National Prayer Breakfast, a Washington tradition that calls on political combatants to set aside their differences for one...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Versus World: Letitia James Picking Big Fights...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-york-versus-the-world-letitia-james-is-picking-big-fights/ar-BB1dnSHM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ambitious attorney general takes on Trump and Silicon Valley in her toughest test yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Head Into Showdown With GOP Over Punishing Greene...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-head-into-showdown-with-gop-over-punishing-greene/ar-BB1dnzew </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-road, off-grid: Modern nomads wandering America's back country...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/off-road-off-grid-modern-100032869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across US public lands thousands of people are taking to van life, as featured in the Oscar-tipped film Nomadland Bob Wells: ‘Then came the first of the month, and something clicked: he didn’t have to pay rent.’ Photograph: Bob Wells If you look closely on city streets, campgrounds and stretches of desert run by the Bureau of Land Management, you’ll see more Americans living in vehicles than ever before. It was never their plan. “I wasn’t prepared when I had to move into my SUV. The transmission was going. I had no money saved. I was really scared,” said April Craren, 52, bundled in blankets atop a cot inside her new minivan, a 2003 Toyota Sienna. She flipped the camera on her phone to show me the camp stove she uses to make coffee and her view of the sun rising over the Colorado River. She has no toilet, shower or refrigeration. After separating from her husband, April found herself homeless in June 2020, exacerbating the depressive disorder for which she receives $1,100 a month in disability benefits. “I could have gotten an apartment but in a crappy unsafe place with no money to do anything at all,” she explained. Last year, where April lived in Nixa, Missouri, the average rent for an apartment was $762, slightly less than the national average. Like nearly half of American renters, she would have been crippled by the cost. April and Cliff, a veteran nomad, camped next to each other on Bureau of Land Management lands. Photograph: April Craren It’s not surprising, then, that job loss, divorce or, say, the sudden onset of a global health or financial crisis can push so many over the edge. “If the Great Recession was a crack in the system, Covid and climate change will be the chasm,” says Bob Wells, 65, the nomad who plays himself in the film Nomadland, an early Oscar contender starring Frances McDormand. Bob helped April to adopt the nomad way of life and change her life in the process. Today, he lives exclusively on public lands in his GMC Savana fitted with 400 watts of solar power and a 12-volt refrigerator. His life mission is to promote nomadic tribalism in a car, van or RV as a way to prevent homelessness and live more sustainably. ••• Before becoming a nomad in 1995, Bob lived in Anchorage, Alaska, with his wife and two boys. He worked as a union clerk at the same Safeway where his father had worked until retirement, only to die two years later. Bob didn’t want his father’s fate, but there he was. As days became decades, he went to a job he hated, worked with people he didn’t like, to buy things he didn’t want. By his own telling, he was the living embodiment of Thoreau’s “quiet desperation”. He knew he wasn’t happy, but it never occurred to him to live differently. After all, this was the American dream, right? Then, when he was 40 years old, the divorce happened. After paying alimony and child support, he was taking home $1,200 a month, $800 of which went towards rent. Bob Wells: by his own telling, he was the living embodiment of Thoreau’s ‘quiet desperation’. Photograph: Bob Wells One day, fretting about impossible finances, he saw a green box van for sale and thought: “Why don’t I buy that van and move into it?” The idea struck him as crazy, but with the prospect of homelessness closing in, he drained the last $1,500 in his savings account and bought the van that was just “too ratty-looking” for its previous owner. He gave his landlord notice that night, threw a sleeping pad in the back of his new home, and cried himself to sleep. Then came the first of the month, and something clicked: he didn’t have to pay rent. As his finances improved, he installed insulation, a proper bed, even a dream-come-true PlayStation fortress for his boys. He started working only 32 hours a week, and since every weekend was a three-day weekend, he spent more time camping with his kids, which “tremendously helped” his mental outlook on life. Finally, he was truly happy. Realizing he had something valuable to share, he bought the domain name Cheap RV Living in 2005. He posted tips and tricks about better vehicle-dwelling, but what he was really offering was a road map to a better life. Four years later, when close to 10 million Americans were displaced after the Great Recession, traffic to his site exploded. Finding himself at the center of a growing online community, he decided to create a meet-up in Quartzsite, Arizona. He dubbed it the Rubber Tramp Rendezvous (RTR), and in January 2011, 45 vehicles showed up. Eight years later, an estimated 10,000 vehicles convened for what was said to be the largest nomad gathering in the world. The event’s explosive growth is undoubtedly a reflection of America’s increasing interest in van life as an answer to the affordable housing crisis, an idea made accessible by Bob on his YouTube channel, also named Cheap RV Living, created in 2015. Whether he’s sharing a philosophical exploration, as in Why I Live in a Van, or explaining the mechanics of Pooping in a Car, Van, or RV, Bob’s videos are a prized free resource, making him a beloved celebrity in the nomad community. With 460,000 subscribers, the videos are also making him money via ad and affiliate sales. His most popular video, Living in a Car on $800 a month, has more than 4m views. Fame, however, isn’t Bob’s jam. He doesn’t like the term “follower” and definitely doesn’t want to be thought of as a guru. Rather, he’s driven by a quieter demon-cum-angel. After the devastating loss of his eldest son in 2011, he was plagued by despair and, for the first time, suicidal thoughts. “Why am I alive when my son isn’t?” he asked himself obsessively. With a desperate plea to a higher power, he finally found the will to bear the pain by being of service and building a community. “If I’m going to be alive, there’d better be a reason, and this is the reason. You are the reason,” he said to a crowd at the RTR in 2020, in what was published later as a video about mental illness for his online audience. The culmination of this drive to serve is the Home on Wheels Alliance (Howa), a charitable 501(c)(3) non-profit he founded in 2018. With the help of his team and volunteers, Bob helps advance clients who are being squeezed out of traditional housing from a state of crisis to financial stability to finally being contributing members of the mobile community. To date, funded by sponsors and donations, Howa has given away seven minivans, two trailers, one skoolie (a converted school bus) and too many tents, brake pads and tires to count. April had been watching Bob’s videos for years when a nomad friend online suggested she apply to Howa for assistance. “That’s really for someone more needy,” she replied. April’s car. Photograph: April Craren At the time, she was living in her car with the faulty transmission. “I don’t know, April, you’re pretty needy,” her friend prodded. April conceded and applied. “When I found out I was awarded the minivan, that changed everything,” she said. To join Howa’s program, April had to sign a three-year contract, prove she had sufficient income to regularly maintain her vehicle, and agree to put $200 a month in an escrow account until she reached the value of the minivan, after which the vehicle title and escrow account would be released to her. “Most of Howa’s applicants are older women. They’re disabled, or retired and divorced without sufficient SSI [supplemental security income] because they were homemakers, or simply don’t earn enough to afford rent,” Bob explained. By learning to save money and live rent-free in their vehicles, Howa’s clients preserve their independence, self-sufficiency and dignity while also making friends within the larger nomad community. ••• Today, April camps on public land alongside Cliff, a veteran nomad and Howa volunteer. Together, they make runs to a nearby laundromat, grocery store and gym where she works out and showers. She’s lost 20lb and feels healthier, thanks to eating fresh foods at Cliff’s urging and living a more active outdoor lifestyle. “I’m not just surviving, I’m thriving,” she said. After Covid, she’d like to volunteer and join a caravan, a popular program Howa organized to help nomads stay safe and fend off loneliness. Howa vets establish camping locations and then members use Meetup to learn where groups are headed. Some caravans are small, while others have gotten as big as 45 rigs. “I heard it’s like a party,” April chirped. Expecting homelessness to continue rising, in part due to climate disaster, Bob’s dream for the tribe is to see the expansion of Long-Term Visitor Land (LTVA), including areas in national forests. Most public lands allow visitors to camp for only two weeks, but LTVA campers can stay for as long as seven months. These campgrounds don’t offer hookups – most nomads use solar power, anyway – though a few do have dump stations and fresh water. “Thousands of nomads could winter in the south and summer in the forest for longer stretches of time,” he explained. While Bob concedes the limits of his solution – it doesn’t address PTSD, mental illness or drug addiction, three main causes of homelessness – he does see it as a way to lower our carbon footprint and make ourselves more financially resilient in trying times ahead. “I want to leave a world behind that’s habitable. For every person I’m able to help into a vehicle, that’s one less person in a house,” he reasoned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some countries ban rivals' vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Stuck-between-the-pandemic-and-politics-some-15920660.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governments around the world are desperate for coronavirus vaccines, with many battling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASH OF THE TITANS:  With Bezos out, Zuckerberg is the last man standing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/with-bezos-out-as-amazon-ceo-zuckerberg-is-the-last-man-standing/ar-BB1dmkQq?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Bezos out as CEO after 27 years, Mark Zuckerberg is the last founder to run a tech giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  COVID CASES, HOSPITALIZATIONS CONTINUE FALL...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EtV1YDnUYAQtXfX?format=jpg&amp;name=large</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rules against heirs of Jewish art dealers in Nazi era...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/supreme-court-rules-against-heirs-183708734.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court shields Germany from being sued by the heirs of Jewish art dealers, including Los Angeles music producer Jed Leiber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-haul cases cast new light on chronic fatigue sufferers...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/long-haul-covid-cases-cast-new-light-on-chronic-fatigue-sufferers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both conditions are linked to viral infections in ways that are poorly understood. But the outpouring of sympathy — and research dollars — produced by “long covid” has given hope to those who strug…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 Iranians arrested in Arizona after jumping U.S.-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/3/iranians-arrested-border-parol-jumping-us-border-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents arrested 11 Iranians Monday after they snuck across the border into Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST MASS VAX SITE OPENS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/federal-government-opening-first-mass-covid-19-vaccination-sites-california-n1256611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort is a change in course from the Trump administration, which left vaccine administration largely to the states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry took private jet to 'environmental' award...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/john-kerry-private-jet-iceland-climate-award </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARLER CEO Ousted by Mercer...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/media/parler-ceo-john-matze-says-hes-been-terminated-by-board-i-did-not-participate-in-this-decision</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parler has terminated CEO John Matze, according to a memo Matze sent to staffers that has been obtained by Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors can't find Kyle Rittenhouse, seek arrest warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.wisn.com/article/prosecutors-kyle-rittenhouse-violated-conditions-of-release/35410096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wisn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge allowed Rittenhouse, now 18, of Antioch, Illinois, to be released in November on $2 million cash bail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tries to board flight from Florida with 22 pounds of meth...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/03/man-tries-to-board-flight-from-florida-with-22-pounds-of-meth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger at Orlando International Airport in Florida was arrested for trying to board his flight with 22 pounds of crystal meth, authorities said. A TSA agent stopped Eli Brown at a gate around …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
