<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>200,000 'never-before-seen' viruses discovered lurking in ocean...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8961505/almost-200000-never-before-seen-viruses-are-discovered-lurking-in-the-ocean/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRUSES that have never been seen before have been discovered hidden deep in the ocean. Almost 200,000 of the infectious pathogens were found during a global marine life expedition, which took over…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboards tracking shoppers with cameras; Target ads based on mood...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8960640/creepy-billboards-track-with-cameras/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURVEILLANCE cameras in shopping centre billboards are being used to spy on you so you can be targeted with the ‘correct’ advertisements. The giant screens contain technology that can w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm going to kill you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-san-diego-synagogue-shooting-hero-20190428-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar Stewart, a 51-year-old Army veteran, was at Chabad of Poway on Saturday when the sound of shots rang out. Something, he thinks it might have been the "hand of God," propelled him to the lobby, where he confronted the shooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Topple All-Time Record?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/box-office-can-avengers-endgame-topple-avatars-28b-record-1205456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marvel and Disney's superhero pic opened to an epic, record-shattering $1.2 billion globally, but the road to the highest-grossing film ever is steep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA scientist claims time travel possible because 'speed of light changing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/775350/Time-travel-proof-NASA-insider-possible-speed-of-light-changing-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS NEW HIGHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/29/stock-market-earnings-data-and-us-china-trade-talks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks traded along the flatline on Monday as investors braced for a busy week including a flurry of corporate earnings reports, economic data and an announcement from the Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incredible rise of Dubai as world's air travel hub...</title>
      <link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/incredible-rise-dubai-worlds-air-121500920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty years ago Dubai was little more than a village. Pearling and fishing propped up the economy and around 25,000 called it home. To put that into perspective, more people attend Sunderland’s football matches on a typical Saturday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMBAT VET WHO STOPPED SYNAGOGUE SHOOTER...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/04/28/combat-vet-stopped-san-diego-synagogue-shooter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar Stewart stopped the gunman inside the Chabad of Poway synagogue in San Diego on Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day in the Life of Facialist to the Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-day-in-the-life-of-dr-barbara-sturm-facialist-to-the-stars-11556541795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s treated Gwyneth Paltrow, Angela Bassett and at least one Hadid. How Dr. Barbara Sturm, 47, has grown her skincare business 300 percent over the last two years—entirely on word of mouth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer spending posts biggest gain since '09...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy/u-s-consumer-spending-posts-biggest-gain-since-2009-idUSKCN1S516T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. consumer spending increased by the most in more than 9-1/2 years in March, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Want Him on Everything': Meet Woman Behind Mayor Pete Media Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/29/lis-smith-buttigieg-2020-president-campaign-manager-226756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How hard-charging New York operative Lis Smith helped&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;turn an obscure Indiana mayor into a national name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global military spending at new post-Cold War high...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190429105059-m8xz0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORLD-DEFENCE/SPENDING (PIX):Global military spending at new post-Cold War high, fueled by US, China - think-tank</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen's Last Days of Freedom...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2019/05/06/michael-cohens-last-days-of-freedom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These days, the President’s former lawyer, and the fall guy in his web of misconduct, looks like a victim as well as a perpetrator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Populist economic frustration threatens Trump's strongest reelection issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Populist-economic-frustration-threatens-Trump-s-13803043.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's strongest case for reelection remains the country's healthy economy, but the potency of that issue for him is complicated by a widespread belief that the economy mainly benefits people already in power, a Washington Post-ABC News poll finds.  The result previews a fresh wave of populism that could reshape yet another presidential campaign with about 18 months to go before voters decide whether to return Trump to the White House.  This sentiment runs the deepest among Democratic and independent registered voters, but also exists among a significant slice of Republicans. About 8 in 10 Democrats and more than 6 in 10 independents say the country's economic system gives an advantage to those already in power, while nearly a third of Republicans share that view.  The survey finds broad dissatisfaction with the country's economic and political systems. Overall, 60 percent of all voters say the country's economic system mainly benefits those in power, while 72 percent say the same for the nation's political structures.  The polling results in many ways echo the populist fervor that swept Trump to an unlikely victory over more than a dozen Republican challengers in the 2016 presidential primary campaign and an improbable win over Democrat Hillary Clinton that November.  But the findings show that, ahead of 2020, the sentiment is also animating Democrats.  The message of economic populism is carried most prominently in the Democratic presidential field by Sen. Bernie Sanders of Vermont, who since his unsuccessful 2016 campaign has pushed the party leftward on a range of issues, and Sen. Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts, who has proposed ideas such as a massive student loan forgiveness program and free tuition at public colleges paid for by taxing the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beluga whale with Russian harness raises alarm in Norway...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8515d3a6ea4a48dda70583a616beca05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — A beluga whale found with a tight harness that appeared to be Russian made has raised the alarm of Norwegian officials and prompted speculation that the animal may have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges hairdressers to cut gossip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-urges-hairdressers-cut-gossip-114746780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Monday welcomed hairdressers, hairstylists and beauticians to the Vatican but warned them not to indulge in gossip while feathering locks or painting fingernails. Snip split ends and wax limbs while "avoiding giving in to the temptation of chatter that easily creeps into your work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cute or creepy: Why humans love some species, loathe others...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cute-creepy-why-humans-love-species-loathe-others-100326235.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese giant salamander, the largest amphibian in the world, is not cute. Weighing as much as an adult human, it has slimy brown skin, a giant mouth curled to a gormless grin, and puny, mistrustful eyes. It is also one of the world's most endangered species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women Wanted: Blue-Collar Fields Find New Workforce...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/women-wanted-blue-collar-fields-find-new-workforce-11556530201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of women are taking jobs in blue-collar roles that have long been—and still are—mostly men. The share of truck drivers, electricians, plumbers and mechanics who are women recently touched the highest level in at least 25 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight Quarantined at JFK Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Measles-JFK-Airport-JetBlue-Flight-Dominican-Republic-509199941.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A measles scare onboard a plane from the Dominican Republic to JFK held up the arrival for passengers on a JetBlue flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burkina Faso church attack: At least five killed including priest...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/burkina-faso-church-attack-soum-silgadji-priest-killed-terror-police-a8890866.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil at $100 a Barrel?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-29/what-oil-at-100-a-barrel-would-mean-for-the-world-economy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN biodiversity conference to lay groundwork for Nature rescue plan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-report-highlight-urgent-nature-rescue-plan-030810208.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diplomats from 130 nations gathered in Paris on Monday to validate a grim UN assessment of the state of Nature and lay the groundwork for a rescue plan for life on Earth. The destruction of Nature threatens humanity "at least as much as human-induced climate change," UN biodiversity chief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burqa ban: Sri Lanka bars wearing face veils...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/sri-lanka-attacks-latest-burqa-ban-face-veil-muslim-women-emergency-law-easter-sunday-bombings-a8890541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines eye crueler ways of making passengers miserable...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/business-economy/2019/04/27/airlines-eye-crueler-ways-of-making-passengers-miserable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Delta’s case, the airline is testing reduced-recline seats on its entire A320 fleet. The idea, Delta insists, isn’t to squeeze more seats into the economy cabin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers making bank ratting out idling drivers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/28/how-new-yorkers-are-making-bank-ratting-out-idling-drivers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dropping a dime on trucks and buses that keep their engines running while parked is paying big bucks to some New Yorkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife arrested after calling cops on cheating husband...</title>
      <link>https://www.montgomeryadvertiser.com/story/news/crime/2019/04/28/millbrook-woman-arrested-for-making-false-report/3608678002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.montgomeryadvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 9 a.m. Wednesday morning, Millbrook police received a call from a woman who reported a burglary in progress at her home.Â There was no burglar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor union concern over AMAZON move to one-day shipping...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/labor-union-raises-concern-over-amazons-move-to-one-day-shipping-2019-04-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc.’s move toward one-day free shipping may be good news for Prime subscribers, but not necessarily for those who work in Amazon’s warehouses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pill that pings doctors shows promise, pitfalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/business/article/Pill-that-pings-doctors-shows-promise-pitfalls-13802445.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Food and Drug Administration approved in late 2017 a schizophrenia pill that sends a signal to a patient's doctor when ingested, it was seen not only as a major step forward for the disease but as a new frontier of internet-connected medicine.  Patients who have schizophrenia often stop taking their medicine, triggering psychotic episodes that can have severe consequences. So the pill, a 16-year-old medication combined with a tiny microchip, would help doctors intervene before a patient went dangerously off course.  Seventeen months later, few patients use the medication, known as Abilify MyCite. Doctors and insurance companies say it is a case in which real-world limitations, as well as costs, outweigh the innovations that the medical industry can produce.  In the case of schizophrenics, some doctors warn that Abilify MyCite could exacerbate the very delusions that the medication is designed to prevent.  "Patients who have a lot of paranoia might be uncomfortable with the idea of a medicine that is transmitting signals. The patient may be afraid to take it," said Richmond psychiatrist James Levenson. "The science of this one is kind of ahead of the data."  The debate over Abilify MyCite underscores a dilemma American health care will increasingly face as the medical industry and Silicon Valley try to promote innovation. For decades, medicine has been effectively delivered through a few simple mechanisms: a pill, a cream, a nose spray, a needle.  But in the hopes of improving outcomes further, the industry is turning to an array of new technologies against one of the biggest, and most human, challenges in treating disease: getting people to take their medicine in a consistent way.  Companies are producing apps for substance abuse treatment, diabetes management, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>272 Indonesian ballot counters die of exhaustion following election...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/work/1606850/nearly-300-ballot-counters-die-of-exhaustion-in-indonesia-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up to 750 million ballots need to be counted in Indonesia—by hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of 'Salvator Mundi', world's most costly painting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20190428/mystery-of-salvator-mundi-the-worlds-most-costly-painting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later this year, the Louvre in Paris will host an exhibition of masterpieces by the Italian painter Leonardo da Vinci to mark his death 500 years ago in France. But the work that in recent months has been the intense focus of scrutiny by the media and da Vinci specialists, may not be on show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker speech interrupted by van crashing into venue!</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article229778754.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Anita Hill In 1998: 'She Was Lying'...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/04/28/joe-biden-on-anita-hill-in-1998-she-was-lying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diver ran out of air at bottom of ocean -- and lived...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20190423-the-man-who-ran-out-of-air-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science tells us the human body can only survive for a few minutes without oxygen. But some people are defying this accepted truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL rookie shot hours after selected...</title>
      <link>https://www.wibw.com/content/news/One-person-dead-following-overnight-shooting-in-Topeka-509179821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wibw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Washburn football player was killed in an overnight shooting in central Topeka that also wounded a former player, according to Washburn University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model dies on catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8956363/model-tales-soares-dies-catwalk-sao-paulo/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MALE model who died after collapsing on the catwalk during Sao Paulo’s Fashion Week may have had an undiagnosed congenital illness, doctors said. Tales Soares, 26, was attended to by parame…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded dolphin in Florida had plastic bags, balloon in stomach... </title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida/2019/04/28/stranded-dolphin-in-florida-had-plastic-bags-balloon-in-stomach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The female rough-toothed dolphin had to be euthanized after washing up on Fort Myers Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto accuses  White House of dictating FOXNEWS content...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-orourke/democrat-orourke-accuses-trump-white-house-of-dictating-fox-news-content-idUSKCN1S40UN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Democratic presidential candidate Beto O'Rourke attacked the close tie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialists win Spain election...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spain-election/spanish-voters-put-socialists-in-pole-position-to-regain-power-idUSKCN1S30MB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's Socialist prime minister, Pedro Sanchez, emerged from inconclusive ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Bernie likable enough to become president?</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2019/04/28/bernie-sanders-likable-enough-become-president/svONYPDuGqprm1gdD56cXO/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many voters, the Vermont senator’s gruff manner is evidence of his authenticity. But with a record number of women running for the Democratic presidential nomination, some in the party feel he has not been subjected to the same personality-based critiques as female candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewer rushed to hospital for crying uncontrollably...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/a-woman-lands-up-at-the-hospital-after-crying-too-much-watching-the-avengers/articleshow/69081306.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman had to be rushed to the hospital where she was then given oxygen to settle her breathing. According to reports, the woman cried so much that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congregants Tell of Quick Action to Save Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/synagogue-congregants-tell-of-quick-action-to-save-children-amid-chaos-of-attack-11556490153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack on a synagogue in Poway, Calif., was a chaotic yet short-lived episode in which congregants recognized quickly that a shooter was in their midst and took action. They told how they covered one another and corralled children toward exits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Returns With Tensions Running High...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/congress-returns-with-tensions-running-high-11556449239</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers will return this week to a Washington landscape transformed by the unveiling of special counsel Robert Mueller’s report, which has sparked an intensifying fight between Capitol Hill and the White House over Democrats’ push to probe the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, once vaccine skeptic, changes his tune amid measles outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/04/26/trump-vaccinations-measles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They have to get the shots. The vaccinations are so important," President Trump told reporters as he left the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialists win Spain election...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spain-election-no-majority/leftist-bloc-holds-advantage-in-spains-election-with-95-percent-of-votes-counted-idUSKCN1S40SA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leftist political bloc in Spain held the advantage over its rightist rivals ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans women fighting transgender military ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/meet-trans-women-fighting-transgender-military-ban-20190428.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deirdre Hendrick and Alice Ashton, both stationed at Fort Meade in Maryland, knew the ban had been coming since President Donald Trump tweeted about it in July 2017, but with nationwide lawsuits, it wasn’t clear until March 12 that the ban would officially kick in on April 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Feel Little Pressure From Voters to Impeach... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/kids/other/house-democrats-feel-little-pressure-from-voters-to-impeach-trump/ar-BBWnj7y?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAT EPIDEMIC WARNING!</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2019-04-29/obesity-significantly-increases-risk-of-serious-disease-researchers-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Dead, 6 People Shot near Baltimore church... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6970119/Seven-people-shot-near-Baltimore-church.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven people have been shot outside a Maryland church. The shooting occurred close to the Perkins Square Baptist Church in Baltimore at about 5.30pm on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botox and veneers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6970041/How-Joe-Biden-underwent-cosmetic-overhaul-make-appealing-voters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden has altered his hairline, filled in the wrinkles on his face and forehead, and installed dental veneers, according to plastic surgeons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shuls struggle with security...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2202481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES -- Rabbi Yonah Bookstein of Los Angeles' Pico Shul was at home Saturday afternoon, observing the Sabbath, when someone on the synagogue's security team alerted him about the deadly shooting at the Chabad of Poway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese and De Niro look back ahead of 'THE IRISHMAN'... </title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d07f7374825b4d7fa7000229ada13513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ahead of their much-anticipated and most recent collaboration, "The Irishman," Martin Scorsese and Robert De Niro convened at the Tribeca Film Festival to look back on their long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions about immunity in adults...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190428140644-ao7d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEASLES/ (PIX):U.S. measles outbreak raises questions about immunity in adults</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Needs more executioners...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8957769/saudi-arabia-beheadings-execution-jobs/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ruthless Saudi government is beheading so many people it needs to recruit a deadly new squad of sword-wielding executioners. The news comes after it slaughtered 37 people in one bloody day last…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun miraculously jammed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8191b03a1090479f9a305d65c83deb06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWAY, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on the shooting at a California synagogue (all times local): 2:30 p.m. Rabbi Yisroel Goldstein says the gunman fled after the weapon used in the attack...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady's heir? Patriots draft Stidham...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/patriots/2019/04/27/2019-nfl-draft-patriots-jarrett-stidham-quarterback-tom-brady/3599751002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots' selection of Auburn's Jarrett Stidham in the fourth round of the NFL draft adds some intrigue to their quarterback room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA PUSHED BIDEN NOT TO RUN IN '16</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/politics/the-long-run-biden-and-obamas-odd-couple-relationship-aged-into-family-ties/ar-BBWmF5i?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 85:  JOAN COLLINS SHARES #METOO MOMENTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6969285/Joan-Collins-says-studio-head-offered-Liz-Taylors-Cleopatra-role-slept-him.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joan Collins touched on some of the may men in her life, from her love affair with Warren Beatty and on-set romance with Harry Belafonte to her five husbands - whom she ranked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/sunday-profile-dynasty-star-joan-collins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the scheming Alexis Carrington on the '80s TV series "Dynasty," British actress Joan Collins was really good at being bad. Mo Rocca talks with Collins about her film and TV career, her five husbands, and her catfights with "Dynasty" co-star Linda Evans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Attorney General Investigates...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/oliver-north-out-as-nra-president-11556376506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York attorney general’s office is investigating potential financial and disclosure problems at the National Rifle Association, amid boardroom turmoil at the group that led Saturday to the departure of NRA President Oliver North after a bruising internal political battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Whistleblower Complaints Emerge against BOEING 737 MAX... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/more-whistleblower-complaints-emerge-in-boeing-737-max-safety-inquiries-11556418721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators are looking into complaints by roughly a dozen purported whistleblowers alleging safety problems with Boeing’s 737 MAX jets, according to officials familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD OF CONDEMNATIONS OF NYT FOR ANTISEMITIC CARTOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Diaspora/Antisemitism/Flood-of-condemnations-of-NYT-for-anti-Semitic-cartoon-588044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressmen join former ambassador to Israel and journalists in slamming the newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite record diversity, 70-something white men rule 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/despite-record-diversity-70-something-white-men-rule-013121612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats seeking to reclaim the White House are calling for generational change. President Donald Trump is a 72-year-old billionaire, and for many he epitomizes the white male privilege that Democrats often decry. Former vice president Joe Biden, who jumped into the race Thursday, is 76 and has spent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENTS DINNER OPENS WITH DARK SERMON ON TRUMP ENDANGERING JOURNALISTS...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-lieu-comedy-whcd-opens-dark-sermon-trump-endangering-journal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘My son asked me, “Is Donald Trump going to put you in prison?”‘</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' $1.2 BILLION Weekend!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/798efe76562549c687eceb78820838e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — "Avengers: Endgame" has shattered the record for biggest opening weekend with an estimated $350 million in domestic ticket sales and $1.2 billion globally. The Marvel Studios...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation reels from deadly synagogue attack on final day of Passover...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14d2196c6d584b1287bc862a0e53c00a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWAY, Calif. (AP) — The rabbi who led a service on the last day of Passover suffered a gunshot wound to his hands and two others endured shrapnel wounds as political, civic and religious leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model dies on catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8956363/model-tales-soares-dies-catwalk-sao-paulo/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MALE model has died after collapsing on the catwalk during Sao Paulo’s Fashion Week. Tales Soares, 26, was attended to by paramedics in front of horrified onlookers after being taken ill du…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
