<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rioter posed as 'Antifa,' then boasted he beat police who 'got exactly what they deserved'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-Capitol-rioter-said-he-posed-as-Antifa-feds-15992531.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The day before a pro-Trump mob stormed the U.S. Capitol, William Robert...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home-security cameras fruitful resource for law enforcement -- and fatal risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Home-security-cameras-have-become-a-fruitful-15992558.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police forces across the U.S. made more than 20,000 requests last year for footage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns mankind faces second 'great flood'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9316549/Pope-Francis-warns-mankind-faces-second-great-flood-caused-global-warming.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis warned that rising temperatures and melting ice caps could combine to produce a second great flood unless world leaders act to stop corruption and injustice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tina Turner bids farewell to fans with emotional new doc..</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tina-turner-bids-farewell-fans-123455610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music legend Tina Turner is the subject of one of the most successful biopics ever made but she tells the makers of a new documentary there's much more to her story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarkozy's conviction carries echoes for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Sarkozy-s-conviction-carries-echoes-for-Trump-15992485.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president was a polarizing figure, a firebrand who relished in ruffling the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Painstaking study of 'Little Foot' fossil sheds light on human origins...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210302065749-2c4g8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-AUSTRALOPITHECUS/ (TV, PIX):Painstaking study of 'Little Foot' fossil sheds light on human origins</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fuels attacks on health workers globally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-california-covid-19-pandemic-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-92b2df8f56118ffce9d3507a62ae941e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Nigerian nurses were attacked by the family of a deceased COVID-19 patient. One nurse had her hair ripped out and suffered a fracture. The second was beaten into a coma. Following the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Space hurricane' observed above North Pole...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencefocus.com/news/space-hurricane-observed-above-the-north-pole/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencefocus.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space hurricane was detected in the Earth's upper atmosphere and 'rained electrons' over the North Pole for nearly eight hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks that glow in dark? Scientists discover luminous deep-sea predators...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/sharks-glow-dark-scientists-discover-luminous-deep-sea-predators-new-n1259252</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the three glowing sharks, the kitefin shark is now the largest-known luminous underwater creature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland Declares State of Emergency as Pandemic Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/finland-declares-state-emergency-covid-113151118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Finnish government declared a state of emergency on Monday due to rising COVID-19 infections, a step that would allow the Nordic country to shutter restaurants and to impose other measures to blunt the pandemic. The decision comes as new variants contribute to a sharp rise in infections in the country, which has already closed its borders. "The government sees it necessary that we all have fewer contacts," Prime Minster Sanna Marin told a news conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Be Compelled to Testify...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/02/cuomo-could-be-compelled-to-testify-in-sexual-harassment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a team of outside investigators begins to examine sex harassment allegations lodged against Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo, its scope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#3:  Cuomo Accused of Unwanted Advance at Wedding...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/gov-cuomo-accused-of-making-unwanted-advances-at-wedding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third woman came forward on Monday to accuse New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo of inappropriate sexual behavior, saying he grabbed and kissed her at a 2019 wedding. Anna Ruch, 33, told The New York Time…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Chris FINALLY addresses bro's scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2432101/chris-cuomo-addresses-sexual-assault-scandal-brother/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN’s Chris Cuomo finally addressed the sexual harassment scandal involving his governor brother, but insisted, “I can’t cover it.” The CNN anchor acknowledged the sexual ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA Director Brennan says he's 'increasingly embarrassed to be white male'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/cia-brennan-embarrassed-white-man</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CIA Director John Brennan lamented his own Whiteness on Monday, suggesting that other men of his race were acting in embarrassing ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil outbreak worse than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/much-of-the-world-is-seeing-coronavirus-cases-fall-but-brazil-e2-80-99s-outbreak-is-worse-than-ever/ar-BB1e7Oj1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals are at capacity, a virus variant is rampaging and vaccines are slow to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Manufacturers hobbled by shortage of tiny silicon chips...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-U-S-manufacturers-were-hobbled-by-a-shortage-15988468.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Semiconductor executive Tom Caulfield knew a crisis was brewing when he started getting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYAL CARIBBEAN 'FULLY VACCINATED' CRUISES</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/cruises/2021/03/01/royal-caribbean-offer-fully-vaccinated-sailing-new-cruise-ship/6871142002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Caribbean's new ship, Odyssey of the Seas is set to debut with departures from Israel with all passengers and crew over 16 vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney left with black eye and stitches after fall knocks him unconscious!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2431704/mitt-romney-black-eye-stitches-fall-jokes-cpac/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REPUBLICAN Senator Mitt Romney with a black eye on Monday revealed he had fallen over the weekend but joked it was from attending the Conservative Political Action Conference. The senator from Utah…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden works to unify Senate Dems on $1.9 trillion bailout bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Biden-administration-Senate-Democrats-retreat-on-15989837.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden launched a lobbying effort targeting fellow Democrats on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS BEST DAY SINCE JUNE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-financial-markets-global-trade-coronavirus-pandemic-asia-9606d330cbfbfec05987a0069d9e317f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street kicked off March with a broad rally Monday that sent the Dow Jones Industrial Average more than 600 points higher and gave the S&amp;P 500 its best day in nine months. The S&amp;P 500...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems grappling with response...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-new-york-andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-pandemic-53449773e6510c0b8218c818535fa0d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Democrats across the country celebrated New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo as the face of governing competence as President Donald Trump fumbled his administration's response to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#3:  Cuomo Accused of Unwanted Advance at Wedding...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2431819/cuomo-accused-sexual-harassment-three-women-wedding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York Gov Andrew Cuomo has been accused of unwanted touching, and asking a young woman if he could kiss her at a 2019 wedding. The story, which 33-year-old Anna Ruch shared on Monday, follows al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jab may be less effective if you're fat...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2427587/pfizers-covid-vaccine-may-less-effective-fat-study-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PFIZER’S Covid vaccine may be less effective if you’re fat, a study has warned. Italian researchers said obese people make half as many antibodies – proteins that attack the virus. 🦠 Read our…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CAN I KISS YOU?'</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/01/nyregion/cuomo-harassment-anna-ruch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The young woman’s account follows two separate accusations that Gov. Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed two female state employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CASES FALL BELOW 50,000</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Evbv63nUcAMnMCb?format=png&amp;name=large</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight Truns to Possible Successor...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/01/new-york-lieutenant-governor-kathy-hochul/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversy swirling around Gov. Andrew Cuomo even has some Democrats calling for his resignation. That puts a spotlight on the woman who would succeed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATES EASE VIRUS RESTRICTIONS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kansas-city-michael-brown-kansas-coronavirus-pandemic-massachusetts-3599a9631d08de3945f5c95f000e5611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — With the U.S. vaccination drive picking up speed and a third formula on the way, states eager to reopen for business are easing coronavirus restrictions despite warnings from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Hill on high alert as QAnon claims Trump will be president on March 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2429769/capitol-qanon-march-4-donald-trump-joe-biden-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Capitol will remain on high-alert until mid-March amid a bizarre theory that Donald Trump will become president this week. Thousands of National Guard troops will remain in Washington over f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEGOOGLE lobbyists swarm AZ over bill that would reform app store...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/Policy/apple-google-lobbyists-arizona-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HB2005 would allow app developers to use third-party payment systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Investigating Donald Focus on His Finance Chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/prosecutors-investigating-trump-focus-on-his-finance-chief/ar-BB1e7Zu6?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State prosecutors in Manhattan who are investigating former President Donald J. Trump and his family business are sharpening their focus on the company’s long-serving chief financial officer, asking witnesses questions about his dealings at the company, according to people with knowledge of the matter. The increased focus on the executive, Allen H. Weisselberg, could step up pressure on him to cooperate with the investigation if the prosecutors...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic locust plague turns the sky black as swarms ravage Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/apocalyptic-locust-plague-turns-sky-23588314</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swarm of locusts flies through Saudi Arabia as stunned people stare and watch and record on their phones. The desert locust has been active since 2020 following a period of wet weather</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY attorney general sounds alarm on cryptocurrency industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/01/new-york-attorney-general-warns-cryptocurrency-industry-play-by-the-rules-or-we-will-shut-you-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire State's attorney general warned individual investors and crypto industry players of the perils of digital assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churchill Painting Sells For Record $12 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/carlieporterfield/2021/03/01/angelina-jolies-winston-churchill-painting-sells-for-a-record-12-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the most expensive painting by the prime minister to sell at auction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA 'unprepared' to defend against new AI threats...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/541094-us-unprepared-to-defend-against-new-artificial-intelligence-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government is "unprepared" to defend the nation against new threats posed by the increased adoption of artificial intelligence technologies, according to a report released Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas top utility regulator quits in fallout over blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/storms-utilities-greg-abbott-weather-texas-38d0d0ae95ffaf44e41cf6bc17b3169a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas' top utilities regulator resigned Monday in the widening fallout from blackouts triggered by an unusually heavy and widespread winter storm that left millions in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent evangelical adoption agency to work with LGBTQ parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/lgbtq-parents-bethany-christian-services-495c1b53-406c-438f-8455-3a7d28ff88b9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We’re taking an 'all hands on deck' approach where all are welcome," the agency's president and chief executive wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechs send 30,000 police, soldiers to enforce travel limits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-czech-republic-andrej-babis-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-de9bba833dd336e2c1d4747842e8482e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRAGUE (AP) — Police and military forces in the Czech Republic set up 500 checkpoints across the country as one of the European Union's hardest-hit nations marked the first anniversary of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO HIRES HARVEY WEINSTEIN'S LAWYER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cuomo-hires-elkan-abramowitz-to-defend-executive-chamber-in-federal-nursing-home-probe/ar-BB1e7PRO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Elkan Abramowitz confirmed to the Daily News he and his firm are representing Gov. Cuomo and his top officials in relation to the the nursing home inquiry, but have “not been retained on the sexual harassment matter.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  7-hour line at HEATHROW...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-56209431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travellers complain of having to queue for up to seven hours because of new Covid measures at border control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG to launch 'harass' probe...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/ag-gets-cuomo-harass-probe-admin-lawyers-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Attorney General Letitia James on Monday received a formal green-light to launch an independent investigation into sexual harassment allegations lodged against Gov. Andrew Cuomo — as the admi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Secretly Got Dosed at White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9313945/Donald-Melania-Trump-got-COVID-vaccine-leaving-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald and Melania Trump got the COVID vaccine in January before they left the White House, a Trump adviser told DailyMail.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most transgender murder cases remain unsolved...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/most-transgender-murder-cases-remain-unsolved-as-police-struggle-to-connect-in-lgbtq-2b-communities/ar-BB1e7wR2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — In the nearly eight months since a transgender woman was shot dead in the middle of a crowded South Florida street, Bree Black’s case has all but gone cold. No one has come forward with any leads, police say. It’s a phenomenon that experts and advocates who study violence against transgender people know all too well. They say the problem stems from the lack of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Tech 'Dine And Dash' Forces Popular LA Restaurant To Close...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/02/27/high-tech-dine-and-dash-forces-popular-korean-fusion-cafe-to-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though many restaurants remain closed during the pandemic, dining and dashing still remains a problem, and even forced one restaurant owner to close up shop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratings Crash To New Low...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/golden-globes-ratings-fall-nbc-hfpa-tina-fey-amy-poehler-1234704025/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winners notwithstanding, the obvious shortcomings of the 78th annual Golden Globes on-screen last night were reflected in the ratings for the NBC broadcast ceremony today. Though the Comcast-owned …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Sued for Alleged Racial Discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-01/amazon-is-sued-for-alleged-racial-and-gender-discrimination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. was hit with a federal lawsuit for allegedly discriminating against Black and female workers in hiring employees for its corporate offices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poly throuple makes history: 3 dads on birth certificate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/poly-throuple-makes-history-3-dads-on-a-birth-certificate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family spent more than $120,000 on legal fees, contracts, implantations and tests to have daughter Piper, now 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. Watt's Move to Arizona Shakes Up NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/30985209/jj-watt-announces-signing-arizona-cardinals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star defensive end J.J. Watt has agreed to a two-year contract with the Cardinals after being released by the Texans last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another victim: Sex between married couples...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-another-victim-of-covid-19-sex-between-married-couples/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The forced domesticity of lockdown may not be conducive to intimacy, but relationship experts advise partners to set aside some time to connect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Job Interview May Be With a Robot...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/03/artificial-intelligence-job-interview-problems-bias-tips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major companies such as Hilton and Unilever have used AI interview software, and an estimated 83 percent of US companies use some form of AI in their HR processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most transgender murder cases remain unsolved...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/most-transgender-murder-cases-remain-unsolved-as-police-struggle-to-connect-in-lgbtq-2b-communities/ar-BB1e7wR2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — In the nearly eight months since a transgender woman was shot dead in the middle of a crowded South Florida street, Bree Black’s case has all but gone cold. No one has come forward with any leads, police say. It’s a phenomenon that experts and advocates who study violence against transgender people know all too well. They say the problem stems from the lack of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfer drowns trying to retrieve ball from pond...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/golfer-may-have-drowned-searching-for-ball-in-pond-deputies-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hermilo Jazmines, 74, died on Sunday after deputies found him in a pond at the East Lake Woodlands Country Club, according to the Pinellas County Sheriff's Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RISE MOST IN MONTHS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/28/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Market breadth was strong on Monday with only about 8 stocks trading lower in the whole S&amp;P 500</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities are starting to ban new gas stations...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cities-ban-gas-pollution-fb61cf2f-9893-466f-9559-9c4d27bbc3b6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movement to outlaw new gas stations is spreading in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS SET TO AIR PRIMETIME SPECIAL...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/royals/meghan-markle-prince-harry-oprah-winfrey-first-teaser-of-sit-down-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Were you silent or were you silenced?" Oprah Winfrey asks the Duchess of Sussex during Oprah with Meghan and Harry: A CBS Primetime Special, airing on March 7</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU vaccine passports for summer... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-eu-von-der-leyen-idUSKCN2AT2DN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Commission will propose this month an EU-wide digital certificate providing proof of a COVID-19 vaccination that could allow Europeans to travel more freely over the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/nyc-mayor-attacks-longtime-nemesis-cuomo-over-harassment-claims/ar-BB1e7rCu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio railed against Governor Andrew Cuomo over the second sexual-harassment allegation that emerged over the weekend and said the governor’s behavior can no longer be “swept under the rug.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop shot and killed trying to enforce mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/louisiana-police-officer-fatally-shot-over-alleged-mask-dispute-at-high-school-basketball-game</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Louisiana police officer working security at a high school basketball game was shot and killed following a mask-related dispute, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK searches for person infected with Brazil mutation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/01/uk-search-mystery-person-infected-with-brazil-covid-variant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. health officials are anxious to trace one of six individuals infected with a more contagious variant of the coronavirus, initially identified in Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRED NYT REPORTER:  JOURNALISTS ARE JACKALS!</title>
      <link>https://donaldgmcneiljr1954.medium.com/nytimes-peru-n-word-part-one-introduction-57eb6a3e0d95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;donaldgmcneiljr1954.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On February 5 this year, one week after an article about me appeared in the Daily Beast, The New York Times announced that I would be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: THE GOLDEN GLOBES DISASTER...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globe-awards-show-review-2021-disastor-hfpa-inclusion-timesupglobes-tina-fey-amy-poehler-jan-fonda-dan-levy-1234703184/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 78th annual Golden Globes had a unique opportunity to right some wrongs and take Hollywood’s awards season into a new realm coming out of the coronavirus pandemic. Unless disaster was the inten…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted NYT Reporter Speaks Out: 'I've Been a Jackal Circled by Jackals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/mcneil-new-york-times-medium-defense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first of a series of four Medium posts explaining his ouster, McNeil reflected on his decision to self-publish his defense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Mystery bright lights appear in sky 'falling' in different directions...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/brit-stunned-mystery-bright-lights-23585976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aiden Macartain said he saw the lights in the early hours on Saturday and suspected they were aircraft display. His video showed the lights came hurtling down towards Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA reports record number of variant coronavirus cases...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/540982-us-reports-record-number-of-variant-coronavirus-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. on Sunday reported an all-time high of 306 cases of coronavirus variants, with the majority concentrated in Florida, Michigan and Texas,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How internet platform accountability is changing under Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/debate-over-holding-internet-platforms-130005261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Section 230 has been a 'brick wall' for anyone seeking to sue internet companies over user-generated content, but bills and legal strategies under consideration could represent an opportunity to change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAB Hacked; Group Promises 'Gold Mine' Of Info On 'Militias, Neo-Nazis, QANON'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/gab-hack-data-breach-ddosecrets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transparency group DDoSecrets says it will make the 70 GB of passwords, private posts, and more available to researchers, journalists, and social scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hosting Turned Into Massive HYATT Public Relations Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/suzannerowankelleher/2021/03/01/how-hosting-cpac-turned-into-a-massive-hyatt-public-relations-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not every day that a major hotel chain is compelled to disavow any association with Nazism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK meteor: Fragments of fireball hit Earth at 30,000mph?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1404082/uk-meteor-fireball-video-space-meteorite-ukfall-astronomy-evg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FIREBALL which boomed over Britain last night may have made landfall, according to researchers who believe segments of the incoming space rock may have dropped around southwest England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first space HOTEL to begin construction in 2025...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9311791/Worlds-space-HOTEL-begin-construction-low-Earth-orbit-2025.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developed by the Orbital Assembly Corporation (OAC), the Voyager Station could be operational as early as 2027, with the infrastructure built in orbit around the Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley teacher union president drops daughter off at private school after calling in-person learning 'unsafe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kqed.org/news/11862469/after-leading-school-closures-berkeley-teachers-union-president-spotted-dropping-daughter-off-at-in-person-preschool</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kqed.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents shoot video of Matt Meyer, president of the Berkeley Federation of Teachers, dropping his 2-year-old off for in-person instruction even as he fights against in-person instruction for Berkeley public school teachers until they are all vaccinated, which the parents' groups view as hypocrisy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Gut May Determine How Long You'll Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gut-microbiome-key-to-long-healthy-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patterns in a person’s microbiome -- the organisms living in the gut -- could determine whether a person is going to age well or die early, say scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubble risk: Reckoning in markets as economy recovers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/01/bidens-market-bubbles-economic-risk-471835</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I mean, Shaq has a SPAC. What could go wrong?” one economist says of the euphoria rippling through Wall Street and raising a new round of worries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Chapo: Inside look at hunt for El Mencho, Mexico's bloodiest drug lord...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/new-chapo-inside-look-hunt-el-mencho-mexico-s-bloodiest-n1113761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DEA is targeting a cartel kingpin the agency says is responsible for tons of meth flowing into the U.S. each month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-Year-Old Girl Dies After Caned During Ritual...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/girl-dies-exorcism-sri-lanka/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two suspects - the woman performing the exorcism and the girl's mother - were arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EAT THE WHOLE SAUSAGE'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/01/cuomo-accused-of-pressuring-reporter-to-eat-whole-sausage-in-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video showing Gov. Andrew Cuomo challenging a female journalist to “eat the whole sausage” in front of him at the 2016 New York State Fair has resurfaced on social media — amid …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Sarkozy convicted of corruption, sentenced to jail... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/paris-trials-nicolas-sarkozy-france-jacques-chirac-6ee89cb03ba8f3888ac64447ebf61f28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A Paris court on Monday found French former President Nicolas Sarkozy guilty of corruption and influence peddling and sentenced him to one year in prison and a two-year suspended...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
