<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO THE MIDDLE</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/05/joe-biden-rally-trump-philadelphia/589780/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In many ways, he’s running the same kind of campaign he would have in a pre-Trump, pre-Sanders era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami flying car port almost ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article230533194.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland votes to tighten gun control...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2019/05/18/are-switzerland-s-gun-laws-about-to-change-euronews-answers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland — one of the most heavily armed countries in Europe — voted to comply with stricter European Union gun laws in a referendum Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol flies migrants--to California!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/19/border-patrol-flies-migrants-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Border Patrol said it would fly hundreds of migrant families from south Texas to San Diego for processing and that it was considering flights to Detroit, Miami and Buffalo, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Peculiar Blindness of Experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/06/how-to-predict-the-future/588040/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentialed authorities are comically bad at predicting the future. But reliable forecasting is possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President May Pardon Servicemen Convicted of War Crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-shows-signs-he-will-pardon-servicemen-accused-or-convicted-of-war-crimes/ar-AABytFb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi calls urgent summit with Arab leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190519-saudi-arabia-calls-urgent-summit-gulf-arab-league-leaders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has called for urgent meetings of the regional Gulf Cooperation Council and the Arab League to discuss escalating tensions in the region, the kingdom’s official news agency said on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder-for-hire plot rocks NYPD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/18/the-twisted-motive-behind-the-alleged-murder-for-hire-plot-thats-rocked-the-nypd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The feds allege that Valerie Cincinelli, who is accused of plotting with her boyfriend John DiRubba to kill her estranged husband, also wanted DiRubba's 15-year-old daughter killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants exceptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/05/19/donald-trump-comments-on-abortion-laws/3731000002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets Saturday, Trump seemed to suggest the Alabma law might have gone too far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR driver throws punches after All-Star Race...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/19/nascar-driver-throws-punches-after-end-of-all-star-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, N.C. — Clint Bowyer had a lot more to say to Ryan Newman after the checkered flag flew at the NASCAR All-Star Race. He made sure his fists sent that message. Bowyer rushed Newman’s c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotels roll out automation; Workers worry...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/as-seattles-new-hotels-roll-out-automation-to-serve-guests-workers-worry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From automated check-in to droids that carry bags to rooms, artificial-intelligence technology is transforming the hospitality industry worldwide. As a result, hotel workers around the nation are seeking a say in the introduction of devices that could threaten their jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian govt collapses as far right leader caught in video sting...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-austria-politics-freedom-party/austrian-government-collapses-as-far-right-leader-caught-in-video-sting-idUSKCN1SN2RA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria raced on Saturday toward a snap election as Chancellor Sebastian Kurz pu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blame Bieber: Iceland canyon too popular...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/blame-it-bieber-iceland-canyon-too-popular-visitors-n1007446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Icelandic environmental officials have had to close off the Fjadrárgljúfur canyon to protect it from the hordes of Justin Bieber fans who are determined to visit the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riderless colt races to Preakness finish...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/sports/2019/05/19/horsing-around-riderless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore • Unencumbered by a jockey and suddenly free to run wherever he darn pleased, Bodexpress decided to take a shot at winning the Preakness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state braces for eco-friendly 'human composting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/washington-state-braces-for-eco-friendly-human-composting/ar-AABzXSk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're all in this together'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/At-rally-Biden-pledges-to-unite-the-country-13856573.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA - Former vice president Joe Biden offered himself to voters as a leader uniquely positioned to unify a divided country during a rally Saturday afternoon. The event, the largest of his nascent campaign, was intended to bookend the opening phase of his White House bid.  "We're all in this together," Biden told the crowd. "We need to remember that today, I think, more than any time in my career."  He added a note of optimism: "In this great experiment of equality and opportunity and decency, we haven't lived up - but we've never given up on it."  Biden walked onstage with his signature swagger, wearing a pair of aviator sunglasses that he shed, along with a sport coat, before speaking to an audience of about 6,000, according to an estimate from a security firm hired by the campaign.  Biden took repeated and direct aim at President Donald Trump, comparing his tactics to those used by dictators. At one point, he quoted Abraham Lincoln's Gettysburg Address, delivered during the Civil War on a Pennsylvania battlefield, to drive home the importance of uniting the country.  "Will we be the ones to let the government of, by, and for the people perish from the face of the earth?" Biden asked. "Dare we let that happen? Dare we let that happen? Absolutely not. We will not."  Biden entered the race three weeks ago with a video that spotlighted Trump's reaction to the violent 2017 "United the Right" rally in Charlottesville, Virginia, where white supremacists marched and clashed with protesters.  The president said at the time there were "very fine people on both sides" of the conflict, which prompted Biden to pen an opinion piece in the Atlantic titled "We Are Living Through a Battle for the Soul of This Nation." The former vice president has made restoring the nation's soul...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  Do Obama, Trump signal shift in future of presidency? </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Do-Obama-Trump-signal-shift-in-future-of-13856548.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than two centuries, until the election of 2008, American presidents all looked alike. They were white and male and every one of them came to office with experience in the government, military or both. Barack Obama, the first African-American president, broke one mold. Donald Trump, who had neither military nor government experience, broke the other.  In their own ways, Obama and Trump were two of the most unlikely people ever elected to the presidency, raising the question of whether voters in America are using a new lens through which to judge the qualities and qualifications of presidential aspirants. Trump's presidency continues that experiment, as does the competition among the candidates seeking the Democratic nomination to oppose him in 2020.  Bob Tyson is a retired database consultant who lives in Chapel Hill, North Carolina. He is a Trump supporter and says the president has helped change his thinking about the qualities needed for someone to hold the nation's highest office.  "Having that celebrity personality and projecting an image in the media is more important than traditional qualifications," he said. "It's made me think differently about what it takes to be elected president. The traditional path of being a state governor or U.S. senator doesn't seem to count as much. It's being able to manage your image in the media and galvanizing your base."  Will and Wendy Keen were in the audience at the Big Grove Brewery and Taproom in Iowa City a few weeks ago, awaiting the arrival of former vice president Joe Biden. They have been making what Will called "a diligent effort to connect with each of the candidates" campaigning in their state.  One person who has caught their eye is South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg, a candidate who, at age 37 and the leader of a relatively small city, might not have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE SUNDAY:  Americans are increasingly migrating to Mexico!</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/the-little-noticed-surge-across-the-u-s-mexico-border-americans-heading-south/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN MIGUEL DE ALLENDE, Mexico — Spanish friars brought the faith to this colonial city in Mexico's central highlands. The silver barons of the 18th century built its mansions. Now comes the pickleball invasion. It started with just a few...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For corporate America, abortion is just too hot to handle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/corporate-america-abortion-just-too-hot-handle-012222697.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some subjects are just too sensitive for corporate America. When it comes to the draconian new abortion laws passed recently by some conservative US states, the country's biggest companies have been conspicuously silent. When corporate America ponders abortion -- an intensely personal matter that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboard in Times Square Catches Fire... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/billboard-yorks-times-square-catches-fire-221232338.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the large digital billboards dotting New York's iconic Times Square briefly caught fire Saturday, before the blaze was extinguished with no reported injuries, officials said. Flames started bursting out of the billboard around 3:00 pm (1900 GMT). Social media users posted images and video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop fighting, 'start fixing'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-call-unity-knock-trump-2020-launch-141833290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Joe Biden made a passionate appeal for national unity Saturday but also took square political aim at Donald Trump, branding the president a "divider in chief" who must be ousted in 2020. "Our president is the divider in chief," he added, accusing Trump of demonizing opponents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bRpw1dLPfgM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duncan Laurence - Arcade, live at Dutch talkshow De Wereld Draait Door. For licensing info contact: sales@bnnvara.nl Duncan will represent The Netherlands at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna dancers hug wearing Israeli and Palestinian flags... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/9105962/madonna-eurovision-dancers-israel-palestine-flags/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADONNA shocked Eurovision organisers and millions of viewers when two of her dancers hugged wearing Israeli and Palestinian flags in an unrehearsed moment. The Queen of Pop did not have permission…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bricks Thrown at Tommy Robinson and Supporters at Campaign Stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/05/muslim-defence-league-throw-bricks-at-tommy-robinson-and-supporters-at-campaign-stop-livestream-the-attack-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Voters Gravitating...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/why-black-voters-are-gravitating-to-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, his civil-rights record is spotty. But Joe Biden had Barack Obama’s back for eight years, and people will remember that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden offers unity to replace Trump's 'hatred'...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/politics/joe-biden-rally-philadelphia-donald-trump-presidential-election-20190518.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embracing a more moderate tone than many of his Democratic rivals, Biden doubled-down on his pledges to work with Republicans, even while noting that the sentiment has drawn criticism from the left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS surprising poll results: Muellers more trusted than Trump and Barr!</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-fox-new-poll-trump-mueller-20190518-flmgbtawonbzvnebgp4vz4l254-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News poll finds that 45% of respondents trust Mueller to tell the truth, and 27% trust Trump to do the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/biden-makes-appeal-for-unity-at-campaign-rally-i-dont-believe-democrats-need-to-be-angry-to-win-nomination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former vice president Joe Biden held a campaign rally in Philadelphia this afternoon and said he rejects the idea that Democrats need to be "angry" if they want a chance at winning the nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems shift to seize on Supreme Court as 2020 issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/state-nation-world/democrats-shift-to-seize-on-supreme-court-as-2020-campaign-issue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Democrats are attempting to turn the Supreme Court into a campaign issue as they confront President Donald Trump’s success at reshaping the federal judiciary with young, conservative judges and the prospect that abortion rights are close to being eliminated. It’s a shift after decades o</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Storm chaser survives wild close-up encounter with powerhouse tornado...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/reed-timmer-survives-wild-close-up-encounter-with-powerhouse-tornado-in-nebraska/70008307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smog chokes Mexico City as fires fan pollution...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-pollution-alert-extended-smog-stagnates-012800919.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico City authorities have announced a second straight day of school closures for Friday and extended a pollution alert as a cloud of smog continued to blanket the sprawling capital. Dozens of wildfires have combined with hot, dry weather to cause a sharp rise in air pollution across a swathe of central</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netherlands wins Eurovision Song Contest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98568e206f094b329bc8cb9f4059e4c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — The Netherlands won the 2019 Eurovision Song Contest in Tel Aviv Saturday, with Duncan Laurence's doleful piano ballad "Arcade" crowned champion of Europe's annual music...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO THE MIDDLE:  Rejects Dems anger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/254643092cb74f17a78e1a1c7974816c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — His party may be enraged by Donald Trump's presidency, but Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden insisted Saturday that Democrats will not defeat the Republican president...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURGER KING Suggests People Assault Farage with Milkshakes?</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/05/burger-king-hints-that-people-should-throw-milk-shakes-at-nigel-farage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bungled from beginning': How Robert Kraft sex sting was marred by cops' missteps...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-cb-robert-kraft-spa-cases-failings-20190518-gqduneepjvcq3lykburpemy35a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mission to bust criminal activity in massage parlors across Florida turned into a monumental legal victory for Super Bowl champion owner Robert Kraft. The billionaire's lawyers successfully argued that the sneak-and-peek warrant allowing the covert surveillance was an unlawful invasion of privacy. Legal observers who watched the prostitution case unravel say the sting was doomed from the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>District attorneys near Atlanta vow not to prosecute women...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/444403-district-attorneys-near-atlanta-vow-not-to-prosecute-women-who-get</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;District attorneys across the Atlanta area have vowed not to prosecute women who seek an abortion despite Georgia’s new fetal “heartbeat” abortion ban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fran Lebowitz Sparks Outrage For Saying President 'Deserves' What Khashoggi Got...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fran-lebowitz-apologizes-after-telling-bill-maher-that-trump-deserves-what-khashoggi-got-from-the-saudis-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humorist walks back comment made on HBO's "Real Time"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of graduates, faculty walk out before Pence commencement address...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/news/2019/05/18/mike-pence-taylor-university-vice-president-delivered-commencement-address-saturday/3682511002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president delivered a commencement address at Taylor University on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US pastor runs network giving 50,000 Ugandans bleach-based 'miracle cure'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/18/bleach-miracle-cure-uganda-us-pastor-robert-baldwin-sam-little</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group led by Robert Baldwin and part-funded by Sam Little claims drinking toxic fluid will eradicate HIV/Aids and other diseases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie mystery Soviet tapes revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/17/bernie-sanders-mystery-soviet-video-revealed-1330347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unseen by the public for three decades, a POLITICO reporter views hours of footage from his 1988 'honeymoon' to the USSR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls Get It WRONG...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/national/federal-election/scott-morrison-clinches-unlikely-victory-over-bill-shorten-in-bombshell-election-result/news-story/c5cc6418729e21fc01e0f7e442771300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Morrison has swept to victory in a sensational federal election result that defied the polls and cements the Coalition’s power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DROP-KICKED</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7044583/Shocking-moment-Arnold-Schwarzenegger-DROP-KICKED-South-Africa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arnold Schwarzenegger can be seen talking to people in a gymnasium as he is surrounded by children when seemingly out of nowhere he is attacked in South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden rejecting Dem anger in call for national unity...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/254643092cb74f17a78e1a1c7974816c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WON'T SEND TO FLORIDA AFTER BACKLASH...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/444391-trump-admin-wont-be-sending-migrants-to-florida-after-backlash </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's new 'social credit system' turns Orwell's '1984' into reality...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/18/chinas-new-social-credit-system-turns-orwells-1984-into-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine calling a friend. Only instead of hearing a ring tone you hear a police siren, and then a voice intoning, “Be careful in your dealings with this person.” Would that put a damper on your rel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ZpFhwJ4eGM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALVIN KLEIN apologizes to LGBT community for ad of model kissing female robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2019/05/18/calvin-klein-apologizes-lgbt-community-bella-hadid-lil-miquela-kissing-ad/3718939002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calvin Klein is apologizing after the fashion label came under fire for aÂ video campaign showing Bella Hadid kissing female robotÂ Lil Miquela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite Iranian force raids modeling agencies for 'promoting vulgarity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-fashion-arrests/elite-iranian-force-raids-modeling-agencies-for-promoting-vulgarity-idUSKCN1SO0EH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards force has raided three underground modeli...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope tells press: Church on your side; Denounces fake news...</title>
      <link>https://www.americamagazine.org/faith/2019/05/18/pope-francis-tells-press-church-your-side-denounces-fake-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.americamagazine.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“One of the first things that dictators do is to remove the freedom of the press,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I don't have to be 'angry' to win...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/444386-biden-at-campaign-kickoff-event-i-dont-have-to-be-angry-to-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden is touting a theme of unity and pushing back on those who may urge Democratic presidential candidates to be "angry" in their bid to take on President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger attacked in South Africa...</title>
      <link>https://sandtonchronicle.co.za/226372/watch-man-kicks-arnold-schwarzenegger-back-arnold-classic-africa-sandton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sandtonchronicle.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANDTON – The man ran up, jumped and kicked Schwarzenegger in the back and was then swiftly pinned down by security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirchner Roils Argentina With Surprise Bid for Vice-Presidency...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kirchner-roils-argentina-surprise-bid-141141755.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kirchner, 66, will run on the same ticket as Alberto Fernandez, her late husband’s former cabinet chief, she said in message broadcast Saturday on her official YouTube channel. “The overwhelming and unnecessary indebtedness of the country is starting to show the first symptoms of a reality that will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth about sex: We are not getting enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/may/18/truth-about-sex-we-are-not-getting-enough </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEREST, MOST CONTROVERSIAL YET?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/eurovision-2019-queerest-most-controversial-yet-n1007201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gay Muslim teen and BDSM anarchists will vie for this year's Eurovision Song Contest, as the competition's only trans and drag champions return.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
