<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Waking To Music Makes More Alert, Less Groggy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/favorite-song-wake-up-more-alert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Melodic” tones, regardless of the musical genre, more effectively reduce sleep inertia in comparison to “unmelodic” beeping alarms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker villainizes journalists. Then threats pour in...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Tucker-Carlson-villainizes-journalists-on-his-16103197.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brandy Zadrozny, a reporter for NBC News who covers online extremism, was working on a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Learns To Flirt...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/14/janelle-shane-artificial-intelligence-flirt-colorado-scientist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence is learning to flirt thanks to a Colorado scientist. The pickup lines generated are perfectly awkward and hilarious, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW RECORD HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/14/stock-futures-inch-higher-after-sp-500-retreats-from-record.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail sales surged 9.8% in March as additional stimulus sent consumer spending soaring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN news crew attacked while covering protests...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/548368-cnn-news-crew-attacked-while-covering-minnesota-police-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CNN crew member collapsed after being hit in the head by a water bottle while covering the protests over the fatal police shooting of Daunte Wright in Brooklyn City, Minn., Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Earth Time-Lapse Feature Shows 'How Humans Affecting Planet'...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/google-earths-new-3d-time-lapse-feature-shows-how-human-1846685339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google wants to help people understand how the planet is changing before our eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mindfulness Can Make People More Selfish, Less Charitable...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mindfulness-makes-people-more-selfish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results reveal mindfulness training led to less prosocial behavior among more independent participants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden carrying out some of Trump's biggest campaign promises...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/15/politics/joe-biden-afghanistan-troop-withdrawal/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is carrying out some of Donald Trump's biggest campaign promises by leaving America's longest war, targeting economic aid at forgotten Americans and building an infrastructure plan that may actually happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily U.S. Covid cases remain above 70,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/15/covid-19-cases-deaths-vaccinations-daily-update.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rate of new U.S. Covid cases remains elevated as the country continues efforts to ramp up its vaccination campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS puts site behind paywall...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/15/reuters-puts-its-website-behind-a-paywall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters will begin charging for access to its website as it tries to capture a slice of the digital subscription</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RETAIL SALES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/15/us-retail-sales-march-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail sales were expected to rise 6.1% in March, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans will likely have to navigate maze of vaccine 'passports'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/vaccine-passports-republicans-economy-coronavirus-8fb97580-90e7-4456-b993-71382526ab5b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The private sector will likely use them no matter what Republicans say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA imposes sweeping sanctions targeting Russian economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/russia-sanctions-solarwinds-cyber-39561a8d-76c0-46ec-9047-6309153d1382.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sanctions bar U.S. banks from buying Russian sovereign debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Battle to Run CBSNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/inside-the-battle-to-run-cbs-news/ar-BB1fF9kf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News’ Wednesday announcement of the historic appointment of former top CBS News executive Kim Godwin as the first Black woman, indeed the first woman, to lead the Disney-owned network’s news division was the initial step in an unprecedented game of broadcast news musical chairs involving ABC and CBS. Godwin’s departure from CBS, where she was the influential executive vice president in charge of global news gathering operations, comes a day...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We instinctively add on new features and fixes. Why don't we subtract instead?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-we-instinctively-add-on-new-features-and-fixes-why-don-e2-80-99t-we-subtract-instead/ar-BB1fFXE6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Less is more” is often easier said than done, experiments show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden faces sperm deficit as pandemic keeps donors away from clinics...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210415055436-83qao</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPERMDONATION (PIX):Sweden faces sperm deficit as pandemic keeps donors away from clinics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twists aplenty in Oz Navy twerking controversy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210415044804-fy6ip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTRALIA-DEFENCE/TWERKING (TV):Twists aplenty in Australian Navy twerking controversy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to unveil bill to expand Supreme Court by four justices...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210414235420-d6xaq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/EXPANSION (PIX):Democrats to unveil bill to expand U.S. Supreme Court by four justices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA Joins Bonanza as Wall St Units Drive Solid Quarter...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/bofa-joins-bonanza-wall-street-095828445.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bank of America Corp.’s traders and investment bankers reaped another windfall, joining their Wall Street rivals in capitalizing on the stock market’s wild ride this year.Revenue from sales and trading rose 17%, a bigger jump than expected, while equity underwriting fees more than tripled. The results echo blockbuster profits at JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. and Goldman Sachs Group Inc., which benefited from increased trading amid stock-market volatility and a flurry of activity by blank-check companies.As the Covid-19 pandemic drags on, U.S. banking giants have remained resilient. Their Wall Street operations picked up the slack for other divisions, bringing in deal fees and activity from clients who were reacting to financial-market gyrations. Main Street units fared worse, as millions of Americans lost their jobs and businesses were shuttered. But there are some indications that consumers are starting to spend again as the vaccine rollout and stimulus efforts help the economic recovery pick up steam.”While low interest rates continued to challenge revenue, credit costs improved and we believe that progress in the health crisis and the economy point to an accelerating recovery,” Chief Executive Officer Brian Moynihan said in a statement Thursday.Bank of America’s fixed-income traders delivered a 22% climb in revenue, while its stock desks saw a 10% increase. The overall jump didn’t reach the blowout numbers that JPMorgan and Goldman Sachs announced yesterday, but the bank’s total haul of $5.1 billion beat analysts’ $4.37 billion forecast.Investment banking fees surged more than 60% to $2.25 billion, led by a surge in equity-underwriting fees to $900 million.Shares of the bank rose about 1% at 6:44 a.m. in early New York trading.Noninterest expenses rose 15% to $15.5 billion, driven by costs linked to Covid-19, compensation changes and charges for shrinking the bank’s real estate footprint.“We saw strong growth in our capital markets and wealth management businesses, which allowed us to absorb additional expenses,” Chief Financial Officer Paul Donofrio said in the statement.The bank’s net interest income, or revenue from customer loan payments minus what the company pays depositors, decreased 16% to $10.2 billion. Loans in the consumer banking unit dropped 8%.The bank joined rivals in releasing reserves as the worst-case pandemic scenarios didn’t play out. It released $2.7 billion from its stockpile last quarter after stashing away more than $11 billion last year to cover loans likely to sour.Also in the first-quarter results:Net income rose to $8.05 billion from $4.01 billion a year earlier. It exceeded the $6.25 billion estimate of 13 analysts. Per-share earnings of 86 cents beat analysts’ 66-cent forecast.Total revenue increased slightly to $22.8 billion.Bank of America also said Thursday that it plans to boost its capital returns once restrictions from the Federal Reserve are lifted. The bank’s board authorized $25 billion of stock buybacks over time.(Updates with CEO’s comment in fourth paragraph, buybacks in last bullet. An earlier version of this story corrected the year-earlier net income figure.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic mushrooms show promise in treatment for depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/apr/14/magic-mushroom-psilocybin-show-promise-treatment-depression-clinical-trial-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trial suggests psilocybin combined with psychological therapy is as effective as antidepressant drug</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Hospitals Near Breaking Point, With Cases Still Rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/german-hospitals-near-breaking-point-with-cases-still-rising/ar-BB1fG2Xm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany’s health-care system is getting stretched to the brink, with many hospitals overwhelmed with Covid-19 patients and rising case numbers pointing to tougher days ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcano continues rocking Caribbean island. UN appeals for help...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/volcano-continues-rocking-caribbean-island-of-st-vincent-un-appeals-for-international-help/article_2a986c68-0180-54b3-abf5-1053c32db184.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an explosive volcano continues to rock the eastern Caribbean island of St. Vincent and the Grenadines Wednesday, the country’s prime minister once more appealed to those still remaining in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In year of reckoning, slavery reparations bill moves forward in House...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/in-a-year-of-reckoning-slavery-reparations-bill-moves-forward-in-the-house/article_13b83c05-333d-5c6f-8678-f417b4b00eb6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A House committee late Wednesday advanced legislation, first introduced in 1989, that would study the issue of awarding reparations to the descendants of American slaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious goat appears in Death Valley. That's bad news, rangers say...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mysterious-goat-appears-death-valley-194225003.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You shouldn’t see a goat during your visit to the park, rangers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO EXCHANGE SOARS AFTER LANDMARK DEBUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/15/coinbase-coin-climbs-11percent-in-premarket-after-nasdaq-debut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coinbase shares surged in premarket trading on Thursday, a day after the cryptocurrency exchange went public in a blockbuster direct listing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy chiefs warn of 'unparalleled' China threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210414133410-05x38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SECURITY/ (PIX):U.S. spy chiefs warn of 'unparalleled' China threat in return to Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark ditches ASTRA shot...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210414120829-sk2wi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DENMARK-VACCINE (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-In world first, Denmark ditches AstraZeneca's COVID-19 shot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Nearly Went Dark Again Because Officials Misjudged Weather...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-nearly-went-dark-again-153640257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Texas came uncomfortably close to another round of rolling blackouts Tuesday night because grid operators misjudged the weather.The Electric Reliability Council of Texas, which manages most of the state’s grid, had counted on a mild cold front sweeping the state, lowering demand for power. It didn’t happen. As a result, demand on the grid was about 3,000 megawatts higher than anticipated -- or the equivalent of 600,000 homes.The forecasting error, coming as 25% of power generation was off line for seasonal repairs, was another grim reminder of the vulnerability of Texas’s grid. Two months ago, a deep winter freeze knocked out almost half the state’s generating capacity, leaving millions of people in the dark for days. But Tuesday’s weather was hardly extreme, and the close call has raised questions about whether the grid operator, known as Ercot, can prevent a repeat of the February energy crisis.“It’s a disgrace for a power grid in modern times to struggle to keep the lights on during a mild day,” said Daniel Cohan, an associate professor of environmental engineering at Rice University. “We’ll be in trouble when a summer heat wave comes in and demand is one-and-a-half times as much as it was yesterday.”Shoulder SeasonWeather typically usually doesn’t have a big impact on electricity demand in spring and fall. Those are the so-called shoulder seasons when customers are neither cranking their heaters nor blasting their air conditioners. On Tuesday, temperatures in Dallas, Brownsville and Houston were moderately higher than normal, reaching or exceeding 80 degrees Fahrenheit (27 Celsius). That, combined with a dearth of generation, prompted Ercot to ask for conservation efforts for almost four hours.“Yesterday was an odd day,” said Matt Rogers, president of the Commodity Weather Group LLC in Bethesda, Maryland. “There were thunderstorms in West Texas that kept wind generation lower than normal. They are going to have another West Texas wind dip today, but not as much as yesterday.”Ercot on Wednesday warned that it was again anticipating tight grid conditions, but didn’t call for conservation. The grid operator forecasted low wind and solar output for the day, while a forced power-plant outage in the Rio Grande Valley added to the large number of plants already down for maintenance.Texas has long taken a laissez-faire approach to its power grid, allowing market forces -- rather than regulations -- to ensure there’s enough power on hand to satisfy demand. State lawmakers have been reluctant to rethink that method as they consider addressing the problems that led to the crisis in February.The market is designed to operate with thin reserve margins. Unless lawmakers intervene to change that, weather will continue to beget volatility and chaos, said Katie Bays, an analyst at FiscalNote Markets.“Texas is a goat rodeo,” Bays said in an interview. “The state doesn’t want to intervene in the market, but the way that Ercot is operating is a feature -- not a bug.”Role of RenewablesErcot officials emphasized during a press call Tuesday that the amount of generation down for maintenance wasn’t unusual for this time of year, as utilities often schedule repairs for the spring when weather is mild and demand is lower. They added that solar and wind generation came in lower than expected Tuesday, a claim that may be used as ammunition by Texas lawmakers who view renewable energy as inherently less reliable than that from fossil fuels.Clean-energy advocates pushed back on Ercot’s explanation. Thought solar output was weaker than normal on Tuesday, it actually met or exceeded the forecast for most of the day, according to the Advanced Power Alliance. Wind generation similarly met or exceeded forecasts for most of the day, said Jeff Clark, the group’s president.“We have close to half of our state’s thermal generation off line for maintenance, and that’s what killing us,” he said, referring to coal, gas and nuclear plants. “We have plenty of generation in the state, but it has to run.”Tests AheadThe coming weekend may present another test for grid operators. Temperatures are set to dip into the 40s across Dallas, Fort Worth and Austin and fall to the 50s in Houston and San Antonio. While hardly the frigid readings that sparked the winter crisis in Texas in February, that could drive heating demand that’s largely powered by electricity in the state.“That’s chilly for them for late April and could invoke a bit of overnight to morning heating demand,” Rogers said.Summer could be ever worse. Already, almost 75% of Texas is gripped by drought, and more than 91% is abnormally dry. Drought makes heat worse because the sun’s energy goes into warming the air rather than evaporating ground moisture.“This doesn’t bode well for summer when they are already issuing these kind of alerts,” said Jim Rouiller, lead meteorologist at the Energy Weather Group. “The cold killed people. The heat will kill a lot more people.”(Adds Wednesday grid conditions in seventh paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Minnesota cop faces hearing in shooting of Black motorist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-death-of-daunte-wright-shootings-police-minnesota-df3e6aba6c750f9b89bab30b46c24f48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOKLYN CENTER, Minn. (AP) — A white former police officer faced her first court appearance Thursday in the traffic-stop shooting of a Black motorist that has engulfed a small Minneapolis suburb...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier charged after video of confrontation with Black man...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-us-news-columbia-south-carolina-29886e0c4e4457e7b237a62f9e7af8c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — A white Army non-commissioned officer depicted in a viral video accosting and shoving a Black man in a South Carolina neighborhood has been charged with third-degree...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India's biggest cities shut down as new virus cases hit 200K...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/migrant-workers-mumbai-weddings-india-coronavirus-pandemic-766287564341fc7b4281b208bfdad630</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — India's two largest cities imposed stringent restrictions on movement and one planned to use hotels and banquet halls to treat coronavirus patients as new infections in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken in Afghanistan to sell Biden troop withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-afghanistan-troop-withdrawals-antony-blinken-ashraf-ghani-49477ad06972282faa6097e38865e57f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken made an unannounced visit to Afghanistan on Thursday to sell Afghan leaders and a wary public on President Joe Biden’s decision to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUCCI heirs worry over family depiction in Ridley Scott film...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-lady-gaga-adam-driver-ridley-scott-crime-929388bfb17bede59522c188370b75fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — The great-grandchildren of Guccio Gucci, who founded the luxury fashion house that bears his name nearly a century ago in Florence, are appealing to filmmaker Ridley Scott to respect...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Months after hack, USA to announce sanctions on Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-us-news-elections-campaigns-vladimir-putin-6a8a54c7932ee8cbe51b0ce505121995</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration is preparing to announce sanctions in response to a massive Russian hacking campaign that breached vital federal agencies, as well as for election...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADOFF IN HELL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bernie-madoff-dead-9d9bd8065708384e0bf0c840bd1ae711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Bernard Madoff, the infamous architect of an epic securities swindle that burned thousands of investors, outfoxed regulators and earned him a 150-year prison term, died behind bars...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC teacher killed in shootout with Mexican drug cartel after stash house heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsoctv.com/news/local/sheriff-popular-union-county-coach-killed-shootout-with-mexican-drug-cartel/P4M26CUMNVGTHPE7KRIQMQC42M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsoctv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Union County teacher and coach was killed in a shootout last week with a Mexican drug cartel, according to the Alamance County Sheriff’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'How can democracy function if we can't talk to one another?' U.S. justices ask...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-justices-idUSKBN2C12VN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two U.S. Supreme Court justices from opposite ends of the ideological spectrum are calling on Americans to learn to talk civilly to each other or risk lasting damage to the nation's democratic system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biz Forced to Pay $136,000 After Prohibiting Employees, Customers From Wearing...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/04/14/liberty-tax-service-lynn-covid-fine-osha/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii 'train to nowhere' rakes in taxpayer cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/14/hawaiis-train-nowhere-rakes-taxpayer-cash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’d be forgiven for wondering what a light rail system in Honolulu has to do with crushing the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World struggles to maintain immunization drives after mounting side effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2021/04/14/coronavirus-covid-live-updates-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To date, more than 45 percent of the eligible U.S. population has received at least one vaccine dose though the number of new cases continued to trend upward at an average of 11 percent over the past week. At least 562,000 people have died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone images show shocking growth of child migrant facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/new-images-expansion-migrant-facility-in-donna-texas-as-crisis-rages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New images show the extent to which the migrant facility in Donna, Texas has expanded in recent weeks as authorities scramble to find space to house an overwhelming surge of underage people coming across the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ABCNEWS names Kimberly Godwin new president...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-walt-disney-abc-news-kimberly-godwin/cbs-news-executive-kimberly-godwin-to-lead-abc-news-idUSKBN2C12SK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News executive Kimberly Godwin has been named president of Walt Disney Co's ABC News, the media company said on Wednesday, becoming the first Black woman to lead the news division of a major broadcast television network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy running on stimulus-fueled high. What will happen when it wears off?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/14/policy-and-fiscal-risk-could-hamper-a-long-term-economic-recovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The path beyond this rocket-fueled year looks far less clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soars in debut, valued at $86 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/14/coinbase-to-debut-on-nasdaq-in-direct-listing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coinbase held its direct listing Wednesday on the Nasdaq, luring public market investors who've been waiting to get into the cryptocurrency exchange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland trooper shoots, kills white teen who had airsoft gun...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/shooting-occurs-near-maryland-state-190731044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Maryland State Police trooper responding to a pair of 911 calls shot and killed a teenager who was pointing what investigators determined was an airsoft gun at him, authorities said Tuesday. The shooting occurred after state police received two 911 calls about someone acting suspicious, Superintendent Woodrow Jones II told a news conference. A second caller gave a street address for the suspicious person that was a short distance from the Leonardtown barracks, but the caller hung up before identifying themselves, Jones said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Correspondents' Association cancels dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/14/white-house-correspondents-dinner-cancelled-481502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the second year in a row that the annual event has been axed because of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ABCNEWS names Kimberly Godwin new president...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/04/14/business/media/abc-news-president-kimberly-godwin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her new role is just one of several changes in the world of broadcast news as the industry adjusts to a drastically changed news cycle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to pull US troops from Afghanistan, end 'forever war'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-troop-withdrawal-afghanistan-september-11-d2c7426736f9f530e0e62f2295a44d28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said Wednesday he will withdraw remaining U.S. troops from the "forever war” in Afghanistan, declaring that the Sept. 11 terror attacks of 20 years ago cannot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving seat open during flight reduces transmission up to 57%...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/covid-leaving-seat-open-during-flight-reduces-transmission-by-up-to-57-percent-665161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A laboratory model showed that leaving the middle seat in each airplane aisle vacant reduced COVID transmission by 23% to 57%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Defensive Player Of Year Accused Of Unprovoked Nightclub Assault...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/04/14/aaron-donald-assault-lawsuit-todd-hollis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pittsburgh attorney says he is planning to file assault charges against former Pitt Football star Aaron Donald.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potter arrested, charged with 2nd degree manslaughter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/14/officer-kimberly-potter-charged-in-daunte-wright-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Potter, the former Minnesota police officer who fatally shot Daunte Wright after mistakenly drawing her gun instead of her Taser, was arrested Wednesday and will be charged with second-deg…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy environments can have detrimental effect on plants, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/apr/14/noisy-environments-have-detrimental-effect-plants-new-mexico-study-finds-persistent-noise-natural-gas-wells</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Persistent noise from natural gas wells in New Mexico disrupted birds that feed on and distribute pinyon seeds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERCOT Emergency Warning Shocks Texans On Mild April Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2021/04/14/ercot-emergency-warning-shocks-texans-on-mild-april-day/?sh=286640347b64</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were a few scattered thunderstorms over a small portion of northwest Texas, but otherwise the state experienced calm weather on a very mild spring day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas set to come out of Covid better than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/las-vegas-new-casinos-attractions-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New casino resorts, innovative restaurants, expanded convention space and one-of-a-kind cultural destinations characterize the latest iteration of Las Vegas, which continues to reinvent itself in the face of adversity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is obsessive coronavirus cleaning over?</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/coronavirus/2021/04/is-the-time-of-obsessive-coronavirus-cleaning-over/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you still obsessively cleaning to try to fend off the coronavirus? A local scientist says it’s time to stop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI quietly accessing hundreds of American computers hacked via MICROSOFT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/fbi-might-gone-ahead-fixed-microsoft-email-server-rcna680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not updating your critical software? The FBI might just do it for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors: No charges for officer in Capitol riot shooting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-politics-shootings-veterans-cef4da2291ce3c98b0d232220bd288e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal prosecutors will not charge a police officer who shot and killed a woman as she climbed through the broken part of a door during the insurrection at the U.S. Capitol on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCRABBLE ban on racial slurs angers top players...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/scrabble-bans-racial-slurs-b929572.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three prominent members of the global Scrabble players’ organisation quit in response to the changes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Navy Celebrates New $2 Billion Ship With Ceremonial Twerking...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9468717/Bizarre-video-shows-dancers-twerking-Commissioning-new-Australian-Navy-ship-Sydney.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of scantily clad women twerking has launched a new ship. The ceremony was attended by the Governor General and head of the Navy in Sydney on the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX show to teach viewers how to fall asleep...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/netflix-show-to-teach-subscribers-how-to-fall-asleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming giant has released a trailer for a new series from meditation app Headspace that attempts to explain how not to be awake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W BUSH TO BREAK SILENCE IN TV INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/george-w-bush-calls-not-passing-immigration-reform-one-of-his-biggest-regrets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preview: In an interview for "CBS Sunday Morning," the former president talks politics, painting, and his new book, "Out of Many, One: Portraits of America's Immigrants."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ELLEN' Talk Show Drops to All Time Low Ratings; Now Under Million Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/04/14/afternoon-emergency-ellen-degeneres-daytime-talk-show-drops-to-all-time-low-ratings-down-11-in-one-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen DeGeneres is really having a serious problem now. Maybe that’s why she keeps flipping $40 million houses. For the week of April 4th, Ellen’s afternoon talk show hit an all time lo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Penthouse Offered for Sale at $241 Million!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/london-penthouse-offered-for-sale-for-dollar241-million-by-entrepreneur-nick-candy/ar-BB1fEaA6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A penthouse at the One Hyde Park project in London’s upscale Knightsbridge district is being offered for sale for 175 million pounds ($241 million), according to a person with knowledge of the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain fog: How trauma, uncertainty and isolation have affected our minds and memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/apr/14/brain-fog-how-trauma-uncertainty-and-isolation-have-affected-our-minds-and-memory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a year of lockdown, many of us are finding it hard to think clearly, or remember what happened when. Neuroscientists and behavioural experts explain why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A minor investigation into the Bidens' Major problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-minor-investigation-into-the-bidens-e2-80-99-major-problem/ar-BB1fDmDU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s eating the first family’s youngest dog?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: REDEMPTION OF BIEBER...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/justin-bieber-cover-profile-may-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He made every mistake a child star can make, including the ones that nearly destroyed him. Now—fortified by God, marriage, and a new album, "Justice"—Justin Bieber is putting his life back together, one positive, deliberate step at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W BUSH TO BREAK SILENCE IN TV INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/entertainment/television/george-w-bush-today-show/73-8196f871-cf17-4c3e-9766-e2256bb90278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hoda Kotb will sit down with President Bush for his first live television interview in 3 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORYLINES:  Former 'BACHELOR' Comes Out As Gay on 'GMA'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Culture/bachelor-star-colton-underwood-gay/story?id=77057551&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_16_post_hero_card_hed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former "Bachelor" star Colton Underwood came out as gay in an exclusive interview with Robin Roberts on "Good Morning America."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADDRESS LEAK:  Enraged rioters force cop to flee her home after Daunte Wright shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2697369/daunte-wright-rioters-clash-cops-flashbangs-violence-minnesota/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A THIRD night of riots erupted following the death of Daunte Wright that lead to protesters burning down a police building and forcing a cop to flee her home after her address leaked. More than 60 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds seized his iPhone last winter!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/13/gaetz-bahamas-investigation-481273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents executed a search warrant and seized the Florida congressman’s iPhone last winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAILOUTS CONTINUE?</title>
      <link>https://www.fool.com/the-ascent/personal-finance/articles/biden-facing-pressure-to-include-a-fourth-stimulus-check-in-upcoming-infrastructure-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fool.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is working on a big stimulus bill. Will it include another COVID-19 relief check?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/13/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Goldman Sachs climbed 2% after the bank blew past analysts' expectations with record first-quarter net profits and revenues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Monkey Experiment Raises Questions...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/04/elon-musk-neuralink-monkey-demo-draw-skepticism-scientist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some scientists note that similar tech has been around for 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry as Video Shows Robodog Patrolling With NYPD...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/outcry-video-robodog-patrolling-nypd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I ain't never seen nothing like this in my life."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Fines Students $50 For Bareface...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/04/13/saint-josephs-college-fines-students-50-for-not-wearing-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saint Joseph’s College in Maine is giving $50 tickets to students who violate the school's face mask requirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE: Republican Rep Retires...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/04/14/kevin-brady-congress-texas-retirement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Montgomery County Republican has served in Congress for more than two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ULTIMATE SCHEMER</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/the-ultimate-schemer-cnbcs-jim-cramer-and-colleagues-reflect-on-the-dark-legacy-of-bernie-madoff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC's Jim Cramer reflected on Bernie Madoff's disgraced legacy as he and his colleagues reported on the financier's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>37,000 VICTIMS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/14/bernie-madoff-infamous-ponzi-schemer-dead-at-82/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Madoff, whose $65 billion Ponzi scheme made him one of the world’s most hated criminals and destroyed even his own family, died Wednesday at the secure federal medical center in Bu…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
