<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SHEP SMITH TO MSNBC?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jitters-at-msnbc-as-brass-eyes-moving-chuck-todd-and-talks-to-shep-smith</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chuck Todd’s daily show could move to mornings, causing angst among the show’s staff. Other potential changes could alter weekends and, eventually, the network’s primetime roster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP leadership: There aren't 51 votes to dismiss articles of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478080-gop-leadership-there-arent-51-votes-to-dismiss-trump-articles-of-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  66% Want To See Bolton Testify In Senate Impeachment Trial...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/national/release-detail?ReleaseID=3653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters Divided On Killing Of A Top Iranian General, Quinnipiac University National Poll Finds; 66% Want To See Bolton Testify In Senate Impeachment Trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 73: Suzanne Somers Boasts About Libido,  '8 Orgasms In Couple Hours'... </title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/suzanne-somers-new-way-to-age-threes-company-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor and author discusses her life at 73 and reminisces about her days on Three's Company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 teen hunters charged with animal cruelty after attack on wounded deer...</title>
      <link>https://fox43.com/2020/01/10/teens-accused-of-torturing-deer-on-video-charged-with-animal-cruelty-related-offenses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox43.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFERSON COUNTY -- One of the two teens allegedly seen torturing a whitetail deer in a video that went viral last month has been charged with aggravated animal cruelty and related offenses, court documents show. Alexander Brock Smith, 18, of Brookville, Jefferson County, is charged with four felony counts of aggravated cruelty to animals, one misdemeanor count of corruption of minors, a misdemeanor count of cruelty to animals, a misdemeanor count of altering or destroying physical evidence, and summary offenses of disturbance of animal or wildlife, unlawful taking of game or wildlife, unlawful hunting devices or methods, and a hunting violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems unveil billboard showing Trump tossing paper towels as Pence plans to visit Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/politics/os-ne-trump-billboard-kissimmee-20200113-kxgbg6wqgbd4vf3ks7q7tafs7a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billboard shows a photo of Trump throwing rolls of paper towels to victims of the hurricane in Puerto Rico and includes the phrase “Prohibido Olvidar,” which in English translates to “Never Forget.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN MOVES TO TOP IN IOWA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-leads-democratic-field-in-poll-of-iowa-caucus-goers/ar-BBYUN1M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's father of 4 and worked as a chemist. Now he's accused of murder and cannibalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/2020/01/13/accused-grindr-killer-cannibal-father-4-worked-chemist/4439756002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Latunski had a high paying job as a chemist and has 4 kids. Now he is accused of killing and eating parts of Kevin Bacon, a man he met on Grindr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Hollywood less trustworthy than govt or Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90451213/sorry-tom-hanks-and-oprah-americans-think-amazon-and-google-are-much-more-trustworthy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USPS, Amazon, Google, PayPal, The Weather Channel, and Chick-fil-A, are among the most trusted brands in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX launches 'FOX SOUL' channel targeting black audience...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2020/01/13/fox-launches-fox-soul-streaming-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Soul includes original content featuring Los Angeles radio host Tammi Mac; Mike Hill and Donny Harrell; and Keyshia Cole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Of-A-Kind Storm-Chasing Vehicle; Withstands 175 MPH Winds...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/tornado-intercept-vehicle-ryan-shepard-colorado-storm-chasing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A storm chaser who has spent more than a decade following severe weather has brought a unique tool to Colorado so he can travel toward tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo says Iraqi leaders privately want American troops...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pompeo-says-iraqi-leaders-privately-want-us-troops-210738727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo alleged Monday that Iraqi leaders have told him privately they support the US troop presence, despite public appeals for them to leave. The Iraqi parliament last week voted to rescind the invitation to foreign troops after a US strike at the Baghdad airport killed a top</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California weighs unique intersex surgery ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aa38740d8906996ce1e137c30d814823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California lawmakers are considering a first-of-its-kind ban on medically unnecessary surgeries for children born with ambiguous or conflicting genitalia until they are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department security officials weren't notified of 'imminent' threats to US embassies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/13/politics/state-embassy-threat-iran-blindsideded/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Department officials involved in US embassy security were not made aware of imminent threats to four specific US embassies, two State Department officials tell CNN, further undermining President Donald Trump's claims that the top Iranian general he ordered killed earlier this month posed an imminent threat to the diplomatic outposts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard prof sues NYTIMES over Epstein donations story...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/478025-harvard-professor-sues-nyt-over-epstein-donations-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Harvard law professor is suing The New York Times, accusing the paper of publishing "false and defamatory" information and employing "clickbait" in an article about him. Lawrence Lessig, the legal scholar and politic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at Pensacola Navy base was 'act of terrorism,' AG says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/01/13/naval-air-station-pensacola-shooting-act-terrorism-attorney-general-says/4454574002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi pilot Mohammed Alshamrani opened fire on Dec. 6 on service members at Naval Air Station Pensacola, killing three and injuring eight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's campaign rallies Wall Street donors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/13/joe-biden-campaign-chairman-rallies-wall-street-donors-for-fundraising-push.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's campaign chairman privately met with some of Wall Street's top donors last week in an attempt to rally them around the former vice president's push for the Democratic nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX Manager to Get Crushed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/13/red-soxs-alex-cora-is-going-to-get-crushed-after-astros-cheating-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you thought the punishments levied at the Astros following MLB’s investigation into sign-stealing were harsh, just wait. Current Red Sox skipper and former Houston coach Alex Cora likely still f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US budget deficit running 11.8% higher this year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/179b7a049feebdc199d1699408bb5310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. budget deficit through the first three months of this budget year is up 11.8% from the same period a year ago, putting the country on track to record its first $1 trillion deficit in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain secretly funded REUTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-media/britain-secretly-funded-reuters-in-1960s-and-1970s-documents-idUSKBN1ZC20H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British government secretly funded Reuters in the 1960s and 1970s at the beh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb in Van of NJ Shooting Attack Suspects Could've Killed People 5 Football Fields Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/bomb-in-van-of-nj-shooting-attack-suspects-couldve-killed-people-5-football-fields-away-officials/2259079/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. attorney in New Jersey and the head of the local FBI said Monday that the bomb found in the van of alleged domestic terrorists Francine Graham and David Anderson could have killed or maimed people up to five football fields away. They also said there was enough material in the van to make a second bomb. Four innocent…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTROS GM, Manager Suspended 1 Year for 'Cheating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28476780/sources-houston-astros-jeff-luhnow-aj-hinch-suspended-1-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astros GM Jeff Luhnow and manager AJ Hinch have been suspended for one year after an MLB investigation found the team used technology to cheat during its World Series-winning 2017 season, it was announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How High Schooler Uses Online Trick To Scoop CNN...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/01/11/dublin-teens-url-sleuthing-trick-scoops-cnns-iowa-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN unveiled a much-anticipated Iowa Democratic primary poll, but Dublin High School senior Arjav Rawal had already done it for them, tweeting out the numbers 20 minutes earlier. How?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Entertainment, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE SAYS A WOMAN CAN'T WIN?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/13/politics/bernie-sanders-elizabeth-warren-meeting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stakes were high when Bernie Sanders and Elizabeth Warren met at Warren's apartment in Washington, DC, one evening in December 2018. The longtime friends knew that they could soon be running against each other for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Yoga instructor punched, kicked man for using phone during 'ONCE UPON TIME IN HOLLYWOOD' screening...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/once-upon-an-assault-287569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANUARY 13--An Iowa yoga instructor allegedly pummeled a fellow moviegoer whose use of a phone during a showing of “Once Upon a Time in Hollywood” was purportedly responsible for “ruining the film” f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD'S CHEAPEST MAN:  Bezos gives Oz fire victims just $690,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/249608/jeff-bezos-slammed-for-giving-australia-fire-victims-just-690000-the-same-as-you-giving-0-0006-of-your-salary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON billionaire Jeff Bezos has been slammed for donating a tiny fraction of his mega-wealth to the Australian bush fire fund. The uber-rich tech tycoon has pledged $690,000 ($1m Aus) to the reli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight polls, impeachment, billionaire wild cards: Uncertainty reigns in  2020 Dem race...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/tight-polls-impeachment-billionaire-wild-cards-uncertainty-reigns-in-the-2020-democratic-race/ar-BBYUr9K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein spy says he's not sorry for secretly trailing 91 Hollywood figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7881959/Harvey-Weinstein-SPY-says-hes-not-sorry-trailing-91-Hollywood-figures-including-Rose-McGowan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seth Freedman, left, worked for private intelligence agency Black Cube. They were hired by Weinstein, right with accuser McGowan, in July 2017 to look into 'a plot against him'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stadium Ran Out Of Fireworks During Scoring Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/chiefs-run-out-of-fireworks-at-arrowhead-stadium-during-51-point-scoring-blitz-in-playoff-win-over-texans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was so much Kansas City offense that Arrowhead couldn't keep up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/av/stories-51061969/hired-by-weinstein-to-spy-on-celebrities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spy posed as a journalist to extract information from Hollywood stars for Weinstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royals present united front...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/queen-gathers-royals-crisis-meeting-prince-harry-055916398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry and his brother Prince William put on a united front as they were summoned to showdown talks Monday on Harry's future after he and his wife Meghan unilaterally announced they were quitting as front-line British royalty. William, 37, and 35-year-old Harry formed a close bond following</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Denies Gun Confiscation Request For First Time Under Red Flag Law In Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/12/colorado-judge-red-flag-confiscation-request/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, a judge has denied a request to take away a man's guns under Colorado's new red flag law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court refuses to 'Free the Nipple' in topless women case...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113140914-x3iun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TOPLESS (PIX):U.S. Supreme Court refuses to 'Free the Nipple' in topless women case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumbling volcano shuts down Philippine capital...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113050635-e0zn3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands evacuated as seismologists warn that a hazardous eruption could happen any time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass Panic: It's Not Clear That Colorado's Mystery Drones Even Exist...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/pkeb9k/mass-panic-its-not-clear-that-colorados-mystery-drones-even-exist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drone hobbyists say the media and the FAA regularly uses drone panic to enact strict regulations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women Scored Record 31% of All Contenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/oscars-2020-women-record-31-percent-nominations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;65 of the 209 nominees this year were women despite leaving out "Little Women" filmmaker Greta Gerwig</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: William Barr, President's Sword and Shield...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2020/01/20/william-barr-trumps-sword-and-shield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Attorney General’s mission to maximize executive power and protect the Presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Nets Blast Trump with 93% Neg News...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/rich-noyes/2020/01/13/tvs-trump-news-three-fourths-impeachment-and-93-negative</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first 100 days since House Democrats began their impeachment push, ABC, CBS and NBC have aggressively aided the effort. An MRC analysis finds the Big Three evening newscasts battered the President with 93% negative coverage and promoted impeachment at the expense of nearly all other Trump news. At the same time, the broadcast networks donated at least 124 hours of wall-to-wall live coverage as they pre-empted regular programming in favor of House Democrat-led impeachment activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX LEADS ALL STUDIOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/oscars-netflix-leads-all-hollywood-studios-24-nominations-1268945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Disney empire picked up 23 nods, while Sony makes a huge comeback with 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will alleged CIA misbehavior set Assange free?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/477939-will-cia-misbehavior-set-julian-assange-free</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The behavior of UC Global and the CIA seems indistinguishable from the government’s behavior in the Ellsberg case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: ESPN Planning 'Historic' Offer for Tony Romo; Between $10-14M?</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/report-espn-to-make-cbs-tony-romo-a-historic-offer-to-join-its-nfl-coverage-033157777.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Romo was an instant star at CBS, and ESPN reportedly wants him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker suspends... </title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/sen-cory-booker-suspends-presidential-campaign/story?id=67472609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Cory Booker ends presidential campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You Need a Boat.' Water Main Break Floods NYC Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/boat-water-main-break-floods-135547858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water main break flooded streets on Manhattan&amp;#39;s Upper West Side near Lincoln Center and hampered subway service during the Monday morning rush hour. The Fire Department of New York responded to the flooding around 5 a.m. near Broadway and West 62nd Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANDERS SURGES</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/13/sanders-progressives-flock-warren-098065</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consolidation of left-wing support is a remarkable turnaround for Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen hosts royal family summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7879471/Deeply-Hurt-Queen-gathers-Royals-Megxit-crisis-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of Sussex wants his 93-year-old grandmother, father and brother to let him and his wife keep their royal titles while living in Canada while grabbing 'financial independence'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabbing spree in Colorado Springs leaves 8 injured... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/13/us/colorado-springs-stabbings/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man allegedly stabbed eight people at several locations in Colorado Springs, Colorado, early Monday morning in what police said was a random spree of violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Teases Talking Car...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/13/elon-musk-teases-a-new-talking-car-feature-for-tesla.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a clip Musk shared on Twitter, a Model 3 rolls by as the speakers play, "Well don't just stand there staring. Hop in."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suddenly, Eruptions Across Globe...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/why-are-volcanoes-all-over-the-globe-suddenly-shooting-giant-clouds-of-ash-miles-into-the-air</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There certainly hasn't been a lack of seismic activity so far in 2020.  Just a few days ago, I wrote about the horrific earthquake swarm that Puerto Rico is currently experiencing.  More than 1,000 earthquakes have rattled Puerto Rico so far, and as you will see below, it was just hit by another ver</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPLETE LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/oscar-nominations-2020-the-complete-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 92nd Academy Awards take place on Feb. 9</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE NIRO, J.LO SHUT OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/01/13/updating-oscar-nominations-snubs-include-jlo-for-hustlers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2020 Oscar nominations are here. Snubs  include Jennifer Lopez for “Hustlers.” Eddie Murphy for “Dolemite” and everything for that movie. But I’m really shocked th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts leading trial, but this woman is shaping it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/13/john-roberts-senate-impeachment-whisperer-098050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first female Senate parliamentarian will be advising the chief justice on how to address arcane procedural questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PARASITE' MAKES HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/parasite-oscar-nominations-best-picture-international-film-1203464351/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Parasite” made history on Monday, becoming the first South Korean movie to be nominated for best picture and best international film. Given South Korea’s rich film history, it&amp;#8…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNUBS, SURPRISES...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/2020-oscar-nominations-snubs-surprises-jennifer-lopez-robert-de-niro-awkwafina-women-directors-1202828716/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Similar to last year, the 92nd Academy Awards will be going hostless on February 9, but this morning’s Oscar nominations certainly had their fair share of unexpected disclosure for Hollywood’s bigg…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' LEADS OSCAR NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/907139138b9271a3cfb4637e4e2f4334</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Phillips’ much-debated supervillain origin story and R-rated box-office smash “Joker” topped all films with 11 Academy Awards nominations, while Martin Scorsese’s elegiac crime epic “The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: OSCAR NOMINATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BEho_CNX43s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 92nd Oscar nominations are almost here! Join us live on Monday, January 13, at 5:18am PT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could A Pill Replace Exercise? </title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sestrin-could-pill-replace-exercise-protein-mimics-effects-of-working-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds the naturally occurring protein Sestrin appears to mimic the effects of exercise on both flies and mice in clinical trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Republican case for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/The-Republican-case-for-Biden-14970558.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It isn't easy to support a Democrat after an attachment to Republican politics that began when I watched the 1992 GOP convention at age 12. Eventually I worked on Capitol Hill as a Republican senior counsel for the House Financial Services Committee, where I helped conduct oversight of the Obama administration. I worked on the presidential campaigns of John McCain, Mitt Romney and Marco Rubio, and even worked for the Trump transition team in 2016 as an economic adviser.  But I'm happy to urge my fellow Republicans to back Joe Biden for president. If you're a Republican living in an open-primary state, help him get the Democratic nomination. Once he has it, vote for him in November.  Plenty of Republicans see President Donald Trump's moral and political failures clearly. About 10 percentof Republican voters believe that Trump should be removed from office. Those voters will be up for grabs in the 2020 election. They should be relieved that Biden is the Democratic front-runner right now.  For one thing, Biden surely would score high on the "have a beer with the guy" electability test. Biden doesn't even drink beer, or any alcohol, but he's still able to inspire a sense of collegial good feeling. I saw as much at the November 2006Return Day ceremony, a post-election tradition in Sussex County, Delaware, when politicians from both sides gather and literally bury a hatchet to symbolize goodwill. Lots of beer is consumed on Return Day, but one of the most convivial participants I saw was the teetotal Biden. Washington could use a few more old-school politicians who understand that spirit of bipartisanship.  For some Democrats, the idea of wooing dissatisfied Republicans is nauseating. Yet the best outcome for the country may require the left-of-center to find common ground with the right-of-center, especially on trade,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soleimani killing authorized seven months ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/trump-authorized-soleimani-s-killing-7-months-ago-conditions-n1113271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The timing raises new questions about the Trump administration's stated justification for taking out the top Iranian general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle Age Misery Peaks at Age of 47.2, Economist Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/middle-age-misery-peaks-at-age-of-47-2-economist-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Middle Age Misery Peaks at Age of 47.2, Economist Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Expands Robotic Workforce to 650 Additional Stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/walmart-expands-its-robotic-workforce-to-650-additional-stores</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart Expands Its Robotic Workforce to 650 Additional Stores</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to Face Unprecedented Protests During India Trip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-bezos-face-unprecedented-protests-095958681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Amazon.com Inc. founder Jeff Bezos is likely to be greeted by an unprecedented show of opposition during his short India visit this week, after thousands of small-time local retailers pledged to protest its pricing and exclusive-selling practices.The Amazon chief executive is slated to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese woman with mystery virus quarantined in Thailand...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113103056-2bhmv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/PNEUMONIA-THAILAND:Chinese woman with mystery virus quarantined in Thailand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight for Bolton testimony echoes Lewinsky...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200113102655-ka82i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-CLINTON (PIX):Trump impeachment trial fight for Bolton testimony echoes Monica Lewinsky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders Says He'd Consider Releasing List of Supreme Court Picks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/bernie-sanders-says-hed-consider-releasing-list-of-supreme-court-picks/ar-BBYTNpb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biblical prophecy 'fulfilled' as floodwater 'flows from Jerusalem into Dead Sea'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/biblical-prophecy-fulfilled-floodwater-flows-21269525</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some have bizarrely claimed that a Bible prophecy in the Book of Ezekiel – one of the major prophetic books in the Old Testament – has been fulfilled after footage emerged of floodwater appearing to flow eastwards from Jerusalem towards the Dead Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters disrupt Pete rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/477928-protesters-interrupt-buttigieg-at-iowa-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters with a local Black Lives Matter group disrupted an event being held in Des Moines, Iowa, by South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg (D) on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In McGahn Case, an Epic Constitutional Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/01/13/in-mcgahn-case-an-epic-constitutional-showdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — “Has there ever been,” the judge asked, “an instance of such broad-scale defiance of a congressional request for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Iranian security forces fire live ammunition to disperse protesters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b5f51dc8712b6fcddc2010bbd9de31f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iranian security forces fired both live ammunition and tear gas to disperse demonstrators protesting against the Islamic Republic's initial denial that it shot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PACKERS SILENCE SEAHAWKS.... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001096372/article/packers-top-seahawks-to-advance-to-nfc-championship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been four years but the Green Bay Packers are one win away from the Super Bowl, beating the Seattle Seahawks at Lambeau Field to earn a spot against the 49ers in the NFC Championship game.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
