<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Wife accused of cutting off husband's penis...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/sep/10/victoria-thomas-frabutt-accused-cutting-husbands-p/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in North Carolina have locked up a woman accused of cutting off her husband’s penis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  Malcolm Gladwell Reaches His Tipping Point...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/09/when-malcolm-gladwell-says-nothing-at-all/597697/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 20 years, has the author’s formula at last been exhausted?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket blast at Embassy in Kabul on 9/11 anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3bdfd6bdd52a4f5f9ec7bfc383ee487c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — A rocket exploded at the U.S. Embassy in Afghanistan just minutes into Wednesday, the anniversary of the 9/11 attack on the United States, but officials at the compound...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NKorea carried out super-large multiple rocket launcher test...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190910204724-nzj8i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (URGENT):N.Korea carried out super-large multiple rocket launcher test on Tuesday -KCNA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged for 'doing donuts' on Trump's putting greens...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/10/new-jersey-man-charged-with-vandalism-at-trump-bedminster-golf-course.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard McEwan of Milford, New Jersey, was charged for two alleged acts of vandalism at Trump National Golf Course, Bedminster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare 'Micro' Harvest Full Moon Set For Friday The 13th...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/10/rare-micro-harvest-full-moon-set-for-friday-the-13th/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers rejoice! Friday the 13th is your lucky day as a rare "Harvest" Moon will appear across the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As frustration with Bolton mounted, Trump reached out to ex-adviser McMaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/frustration-bolton-mounted-trump-reached-out-ex-adviser-mcmaster-n1051996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In phone calls to McMaster, Trump told his second national security adviser that he missed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans piling on credit card debt, despite recession warnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/consumer/americans-are-piling-credit-card-debt-despite-recession-warnings-n1052041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credit card debt usually increases around the holiday shopping season — not in the middle of July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falwell Calls FBI To Investigate 'Criminal Conspiracy' At Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/460699-jerry-fallwell-jr-calls-fbi-to-investigate-criminal-conspiracy-at-liberty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberty University President Jerry Falwell Jr. told Hill.TV on Tuesday that he has begun sharing information with the FBI in what he alleged was a criminal conspiracy against him by former board members at the school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope says US critics use 'rigid ideology' to mask failings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7078a805c9ea4585874cd22559f0046a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABOARD THE PAPAL PLANE (AP) — Pope Francis said Tuesday he wasn't afraid of a U.S. Catholic Church schism led by his conservative critics, but sees a "rigid" ideology opponents use to mask their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu whisked from campaign event because of Palestinian rocket fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-september-10-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International body says if Netanyahu acts on his campaign pledge it would be 'devastating to regional peace, and the very essence of a two-state solution'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA drops 40 tons of bombs on ISIS-'infested' island in Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-drops-40-tons-of-bombs-on-IS-infested-island-14428134.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) - The U.S.-led coalition says American warplanes have dropped 36,000 kilograms (40 tons) of bombs on an Island in the Tigris River "infested" with members of the Islamic State group.  The coalition said F15 and F35 warplanes took part in the bombing on Qanus Island in the central province of Salaheddine, north of the capital Baghdad.  Tuesday's attack is part of operations carried out by Iraqi forces and the U.S.-led coalition against IS, which was defeated in Iraq in 2017.  IS sleeper cells have since carried out deadly bombings in Iraq.  IS controlled large swathes of Syria and Iraq where they declared a caliphate in 2014.  A video released by the military showed massive explosions creating mushroom clouds billowing from the island that appeared to have been subjected to carpet bombing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train derailment in Illinois prompts evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2019/09/10/massive-fire-after-train-derailment-in-dupo-illinois/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST CARONDELET, Ill. – First responders are at the scene of a train derailment in the 4400 block of Carondelet Avenue near Dupo, Illinois, KTVI reports. Video from our sister station's SkyFOX helicopter shows a massive fire and smoke billowing into the air after the crash. Vertex Chemical Corporation is located near the scene of the crash. Firefighters are working to stop the spread of the fire to that business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to Annex Jordan Valley If Re-Elected...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Prime-Minister-Netanyahu-expected-to-announce-annexation-of-Jordan-Valley-601207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House: No change in policy, Likud: US Oked announcement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE unveils iPhone 11...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/10/apple-hardware-event-new-iphones-apple-watches-and-more.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is hosting its annual September product launch on Tuesday and is expected to unveil new iPhones and Apple Watches, among other announcements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS: Gun Control Support Slipping...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/polls-show-gun-control-support-trending-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two new polls show support for most gun control proposals has receded or remained constant despite a spate of mass shootings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA sues San Francisco over terrorist declaration...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/nra-sues-san-francisco-terrorist-declaration-65498939</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City officials recently declared the gun-rights lobby a terrorist organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I RESIGNED!</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/09/10/national-security-adviser-john-bolton-resigns-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump announced Tuesday that National Security Adviser John Bolton is resigning from the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to boost Serb military with drones...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c19a207d89b34dd7aa0f608933ef607b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELGRADE, Serbia (AP) — Serbia praised China on Tuesday for boosting the Balkan nation's military with drones and other equipment amid Western concerns that the arms buildup could threaten fragile...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun sales surge 15%, driven by self-protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/gun-sales-surge-15-driven-by-self-protection-pelosi-schumer-demand-for-limits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leading indicator of gun sales jumped in August, driven in part by Americans seeking self-protection and deep concerns congressional Democrats are going to push through expanded gun control legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential candidates cursing with unusual abandon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/beto-orourke-donald-trump-politics-of-profanity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump lowered the bar, and now some Democratic presidential candidates like Beto O'Rourke are cursing with unusual abandon. Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drags Oscar Race Into Darkness...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/a-majestic-joker-drags-the-oscar-race-into-the-darkness-in-toronto-premiere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto Film Festival 2019: Joaquin Phoenix says, "It wasn't an easy decision" to play the role. "Honestly, I didn't f---ing know"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslims festival sees children left covered in blood as devout use knives to slice heads...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9898973/ashura-festival-blood-devout-muslims-knives-heads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FASCINATING images show devout Muslims using knives to cut open their heads during a traditional show of faith. Every year, thousands of Shia worshippers take part in the ceremonies, performed to m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California bans schools from suspending disruptive kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article234912107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CHOPS ANOTHER ONE</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-fires-john-bolton-his-services-are-no-longer-needed-at-the-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump wrote on Twitter that he "disagreed strongly with many of his suggestions"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Naps good for heart health...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/napping-benefits-health-may-reduce-heart-attacks-strokes-heart-disease-study-finds-today-2019-09-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New study finds one or two naps a week may be beneficial for heart health – but more isn't better</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Creepy costumed characters out of control...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/09/times-squares-creepy-costumed-characters-are-out-of-control-survey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That’s a lot of tickling. The Times Square Elmo busted for grabbing a 14-year-old girl’s rear while posing for a photo is far from an isolated incident, according to a new report that found the han…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 TEST IN NC... DEVELOPING... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7c3af0e48dec4fe187d1fbce9b43eb3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAYETTEVILLE, N.C. (AP) — Republicans are hoping an eleventh-hour pep talk from President Donald Trump will propel them to a special election victory Tuesday in a GOP-friendly House district in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane survivors struggle to start new life in Bahamas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0845b5f7c22344d984d7aa62aa3dad10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASSAU, Bahamas (AP) — Thousands of hurricane survivors are filing off boats and planes in the capital of the Bahamas, facing the prospect of starting their lives over but with little idea of how...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority say recession likely...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/ten-call-recession-trump-approval-drops-points-poll/story?id=65414875</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;6 in 10 Americans say a recession is likely in the next year and Trump approval drops by 6 points in the new ABC News/Washington Post poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: 50 best cities to live in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/09/10/americas-50-best-cities-to-live/40089949/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall St. analyzed over two dozen measures from sources like the U.S. Census Bureau and the FBI to identify 50 of the best cities to live in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plotting Against Him Since '03...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/09/10/gwyneth-paltrow-has-been-plotting-against-harvey-weinstein-for-a-long-time-since-at-least-2003-but-no-one-knew-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gwyneth Paltrow’s participation in the downfall of Harvey Weinstein is not a surprise. She’s been plotting the former movie mogul’s demise for years, at least since 2003. Back the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech to fix posture by blurring screen when slouch...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7447795/Website-aims-fix-computer-users-posture.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Computer users can now check their posture using a website which makes text on their screen appear blurry if they are slouched over. When they are positioned correctly, the text appears normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm can predict when workers about to quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/10/this-algorithm-can-predict-when-workers-are-about-to-quitheres-how.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what could happen when employers tap machine learning to identify workers who are at risk of leaving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDI:  WE'RE TEARING OURSELVES APART...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/condoleezza-rice-im-relieved-that-u-s-walked-away-from-talks-with-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rice said there were some "bad tell-tale signs" that the Taliban was not willing to negotiate seriously with the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian female soccer fan dies after setting self on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ab977f8920714b4fa77c142ed251f1f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — An Iranian woman detained for dressing as a man to sneak into a soccer stadium to watch a match has died after setting herself on fire upon learning she could...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Japan May Dump Radioactive Fukushima Water Into Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-09-10/japan-may-be-forced-to-dump-radioactive-fukushima-water-into-the-pacific </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOROS PRAISES TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/10/soros-offers-rare-praise-for-trumps-handling-of-huawei-in-trade-war.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an op-ed Tuesday, liberal financier George Soros said Huawei should not be removed from the U.S. entity list without Congress' consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspapers turn to Congress for help against tech companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newspapers-lobbying-congress-facebook-google-9129b34b-5851-4e3d-a262-7e0c70a8c869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our belief is that the current antitrust laws don’t allow us to work together."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She played pivotal role in bringing down...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/09/10/gwyneth-paltrow-played-a-pivotal-role-in-harvey-weinstein-expose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress, who starred in the Weinstein-produced “Shakespeare in Love,” was one of the first in Hollywood to get in touch with New York Times reporters Megan Twohey and Jodi Kantor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VESTAGER: Silicon Valley's Worst Enemy Returns With Even More Power...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/margrethe-vestager-silicon-valley-worst-111917069.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The regulator who’s made a name for herself by cracking down on tech giants is about to get even more power.Margrethe Vestager was picked Tuesday by EU Commission President-elect Ursula von der Leyen to be her executive vice president in charge of the bloc’s digital affairs –- a post that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shia LaBeouf opens up about writing in rehab, becoming dad in movie...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2019/09/09/shia-labeouf-honey-boy-rehab-dad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say artists are really just exorcising their own demons in the work they create — but for Shia LaBeouf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Teens Who Abstain From Dating Happier, Have Better Social Skills...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-teens-who-hold-off-on-dating-have-better-social-skills-less-depressed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has found that teens who don't date are happier, less depressed, and more adept at dealing with a variety of social situations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physically Fit People Have Sharper Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sound-body-sound-mind-physically-fit-people-have-stronger-sharper-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of German scientists say that physical fitness is associated with better brain structure and functioning in young adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans brace for recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/10/poll-trump-approval-falls-recession-1487905</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of Americans believe a recession is likely to occur in 2020, according to the survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation Finds No 'New' Sections of Wall Built...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/investigation-finds-trump-administration-hasnt-built-any-new-sections-of-the-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, this is awkward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S to automate drive-thru...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/10/mcdonalds-acquires-ai-company-trying-to-automate-the-drive-thru.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apprente, a Silicon Valley company founded in 2017, uses artificial intelligence to understand drive-thru orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest warning signs for reelection bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/09/these-are-the-three-biggest-warning-signs-for-trumps-reelection-bid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For three overlapping reasons, 2018 sent a stronger-than-usual signal about the upcoming White House contest, writes John Harwood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun rights activists test WALMART request not to open-carry guns into store...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/460652-gun-rights-activists-test-walmart-request-not-to-open-carry-guns-into-store</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gun rights activists in Texas are testing Walmart’s request not to open-carry in stores by doing just that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Naps good for heart health...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/5527967/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study says go ahead and nap to your heart's content because it could be good for your heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iPhone? No thanks. Older-model owners don't need or want...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2019/09/09/5-s-holdouts-say-who-needs-a-new-shiny-iphone/2268000001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple stopped supporting the iPhone 5S with updates in September 2018 and this year will discontinue the iPhone 6. But these consumers don't care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful see miracle...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-weeping-icon-chicago-church-20190909-dvy34h3uo5gytpgnum3bvwkote-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A priest at a Greek Orthodox church on the Northwest Side says a member of his staff alerted him Sunday that an icon of the Virgin Mary was weeping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concerts More Expensive Than Ever -- and Fans Keep Paying Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/concerts-are-more-expensive-than-ever-and-fans-keep-paying-up-1.1313653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not your imagination: Concert ticket prices are going through the roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 TEST IN NC</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7c3af0e48dec4fe187d1fbce9b43eb3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAYETTEVILLE, N.C. (AP) — Republicans are hoping an eleventh-hour pep talk from President Donald Trump will help them win Tuesday's special congressional election in North Carolina. The race could...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest Could Lose Hundreds of Billions Under Warren Wealth Tax...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/richest-could-lose-hundreds-billions-080000068.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Billionaires such as Jeff Bezos, Bill Gates and Warren Buffett could have collectively lost hundreds of billions of dollars in net worth over decades if presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren’s wealth tax plan had been in effect -- and they had done nothing to avoid it.That’s according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Ma Ends 20-Year Reign Over ALIBABA Wealth Creation Empire...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jack-ma-ends-20-reign-031456905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Jack Ma is giving up the reins of Alibaba Group Holding Ltd. after presiding over one of the most spectacular creations of wealth the world has ever seen.The former English teacher steps down as executive chairman of China’s largest company on his 55th birthday after amassing a $41.8 billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influential tribe set to play key role in NC election...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/460610-influential-tribe-set-to-play-key-role-in-nc-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans and Democrats are working in a last-ditch effort to turn out voters from North Carolina’s Lumbee Tribe ahead of the critical special election in the 9th District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Soiled car' reports on rise in NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/09/nycs-gross-subway-cars-are-actually-getting-worse-and-causing-delays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not your imagination — the subways are getting even grosser. Complaints of “soiled” subways are piling up, with skeeved straphangers reporting more cars caked with garbage, food spills and hum…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worshipers flock to mysterious crying Virgin Mary icon...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/community-events/crying-virgin-mary-attracts-crowds-as-historic-church-up-for-sale/5527885/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The residue of the oil-like substance streaming from the Virgin Mary's eyes remained, with many believing the oil has healing properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Ford entices fashion crowd into an old subway station...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/tom-ford-entices-fashion-crowd-031912148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Ford enticed the fashion crowd into an abandoned subway station downtown by serving up dumplings before a precarious three-story walk to the rails, and, yes, heels were involved. Miley Cyrus, sitting front row Monday in a floppy black hat, could easily pull off any of his bra tops in metallic green</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STANDING O  FOR 'JOKER' IN TORONTO...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/09/09/toronto-cheers-for-joaquin-phoenix-astonishing-performance-as-the-joker-in-violent-comic-book-opera</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin Phoenix received cheers and a standing ovation tonight in Toronto for his starring performance as the “Joker.” Todd Phillips’ origin story of Batman’s villain is sup…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 deficit surpasses $1 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/460603-deficit-surpasses-1-trillion-cbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal deficit surpassed $1 trillion in the first 11 months of fiscal 2019, the Congressional Budget Office (CBO) said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is dengue so widespread this year? </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dengue-why-widespread-031859064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed "breakbone fever", dengue is one of the world's leading mosquito-borne illnesses and infects tens of millions across the globe annually. Explosive outbreaks have ravaged Southeast Asia this year, infecting hundreds of thousands, killing hundreds, and crippling health care systems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 countries cited for extreme media censorship...</title>
      <link>https://cpj.org/reports/2019/09/10-most-censored-eritrea-north-korea-turkmenistan-journalist.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cpj.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps may tell FACEBOOK last time users had sex..</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/apps-may-tell-facebook-about-last-time-users-had-sex-study-2098310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your best friend may not know when you last had sex, but it's possible that Facebook does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No One Shows for Impeachment Event in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/09/09/lleftists-d-c-impeach-donald-trump-protests-a-bust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one showed up for protests promoted online for Washington, DC, and other cities to push for the impeachment of President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant NKorea launches two more projectiles after 'advanced missile' warning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-korea-says-willing-resume-152041803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea launched two projectiles toward the sea on Tuesday, South Korea's military said, hours after the North offered to resume nuclear diplomacy with the United States but warned its dealings with Washington may end without new U.S. proposals. The launches and demand for new proposals were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's First Gay Credit Union Gets Green Light...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/america-first-gay-credit-union-170720269.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Do lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people need a bank of their own? Superbia Credit Union is about to find out.Michigan on Monday approved a charter for the new financial institution designed for LGBT customers, clearing the way for online service to begin early in 2020.Superbia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLO Poised to Land First Oscar Nomination for Stripper Performance?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/jennifer-lopez-is-poised-land-her-first-oscar-nom-hustlers-1238125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For her work in Lorene Scafaria's dramedy about New York strippers who team up to con male patrons in order to survive the Great Recession, J-Lo has received some of the best notices of her acting career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Accuses Rivals of Plotting to 'Steal' Israeli Election... </title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/09/netanyahu-accuses-rivals-of-plotting-to-steal-israeli-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - JERUSALEM — Fighting for his political life, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu of Israel on Monday accused opponents of trying to “steal” next week’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Liberals haunted by social media tactics they use against the right...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/460595-liberals-haunted-by-social-media-tactics-they-use-against-the-right</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The people who have made an industry out of destroying ordinary people’s lives over old social media posts and out-of-context comments are very upset that it’s happening to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary challenges show potential cracks in Trump's GOP...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/460585-primary-challenges-show-potential-cracks-in-trumps-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s campaign is moving to block three Republicans challenging him in next year’s primary election, cognizant of the potential threat those challengers represent to Trump’s hold on his vaunted Republican base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD CONTINUES:  Highest August border arrests in more than decade...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190909221852-3iuee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/ (UPDATE 6, PIX):UPDATE 6-U.S. credits Mexico, Central America for sharp drop in border arrests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds probe 8-year-old boy's YOUTUBE channel...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9896654/ryan-toysreview-youtube-channel-probe-ryan-kaji/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POPULAR YouTube channel hosted by an eight-year-old boy is being probed over claims it is “deceiving” kids into buying toys. Schoolboy Ryan Kaji and his parents make £17.3 million ($22 million) a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant NKorea launches two more projectiles after 'advanced missile' warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-north-korea-launches-two-19916742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea fired two projectiles on Tuesday morning from South Pyongan province toward the east, a report citing South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff states</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE FACES 50 PROBES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/09/texas-attorney-general-leads-google-antitrust-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news follows the announcement of a joint state Facebook probe led by the attorney general of New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moody's downgrades FORD to 'junk' status on weak outlook...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/moodys-downgrades-ford-junk-status-weak-outlook-210253793.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moody's downgraded Ford's credit rating to speculative or "junk" status on Monday, citing the company's weak financial outlook as it embarks on an ambitious restructuring. Characterizing the auto giant's current overhaul as "unprecedentedly large and challenging,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST DRAMA:  Weinstein Attacks Paltrow...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/09/gwyneth-paltrow-harvey-weinstein-sexual-harassment-she-said-book-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-new-york-times-1202729541/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the day that Harvey Weinstein’s postponed trial for rape was supposed to have started in New York City, the much accused producer’s team today tried to damn Gwyneth Paltrow in the court of publi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even for Trump, it's been busy stretch of media attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec9e76c9ac9c4c1e985a364f402882e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Even for a president who has made attacks on the media routine, the past few days have seemed turbo-charged. Within five days, President Donald Trump has tweeted a video of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 TEST IN NORTH CAROLINA!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/743fe7db77c543c498e33df29f6c53ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVELOCK, N.C. (AP) — President Donald Trump's rally in North Carolina on Monday will serve as a measure of his clout in trying to elect a Republican to the House in a closely watched special...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK's Johnson to close Parliament as his Brexit plans stall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/600609137bf34bcba826085b085bfcbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British lawmakers demanded Monday that Prime Minister Boris Johnson's government release officials' private correspondence about plans for Brexit, as the government prepared to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany considers 'shadow budget' to circumvent national debt rules...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190909134128-csy5m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-BUDGET/ (UPDATE 1, EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Germany considers 'shadow budget' to circumvent national debt rules - sources</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
