<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>KFC lover finds raw chicken 'HEART' inside bucket...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/3210697/kfc-lover-claims-he-found-a-raw-chicken-heart-inside-his-box-meal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CUSTOMER at KFC claims he found a raw heart among his fried chicken which he had ordered at the fast food chain in Australia. Timothy, 21, said he bought an Original Tenders Box from a Melbourne …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Great Imaginary Willie Nelson Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2018/09/14/willie-nelson-conservative-boycott</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sorry, Fox News and HuffPost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ SWEAT...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/09/15/ted-cruz-says-his-texas-senate-race-is-competitive-because-far-left-has-lost-their-minds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz, R-Texas, was approached at his high-rise campaign headquarters Friday morning by a young volunteer who wanted the incumbent senator to star in his latest Snapchat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kitten clings for life as man awaits rescue...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article218445160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence flooded New Bern, North Carolina where people are being rescued in boats. Robert Simmons Jr. evacuated with a small kitten on his shoulder. He was stranded by floodwaters from the Neuse River.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber to Become U.S. Citizen...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/09/15/justin-bieber-us-citizenship-apply-canadian-dual/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber is applying to become a U.S. Citizen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man lathers up and shaves in his seat on NJ commuter train...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-shown-shaving-aboard-commuter-train</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was caught on video lathering up and giving himself a shave while riding on a New Jersey train.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FAKE' WIND AT WEATHER CHANNEL</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/tanyachen/people-are-cracking-up-at-this-weather-reporter-being</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“And the Oscar goes to...”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: Someone Microwaved McConaughey and Now I Feel Dirty...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2018/09/nothing-good-about-white-boy-rick-especially-not-matthew-mcconaughey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No normal person needs to watch this worthless load of crap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson, Eyes on Downing Street, Sets Political Fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/15/world/europe/uk-boris-johnson.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since leaving Prime Minister Theresa May’s government, Mr. Johnson, who would like her job, has displayed his skill at causing uproars while seeming affable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOODS OF FLORENCE</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2018-09-14-hurricane-tropical-storm-florence-major-record-river-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flooding from Florence will continue into next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAYS OF DOWNPOUR</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Florences-1-100-Year-Storm-Surge-Breaks-All-Time-Records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence was only a Category 1 storm on the Saffir-Simpson wind scale, but the storm’s massive wind field brought a huge storm surge to the coast that broke all-time high-water records as much as 65 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sex once a week can make feel 15 years younger...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7264154/sex-once-week-feel-younger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVING sex at least once a week can help you feel as much as 15 years younger, a study suggests. Over-50s say that over a period of a month, romping at least four times, exercising 16 times and tak…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORENCE WEEKEND</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f0418c00d63048f1b94ee6f8242d387e/Florence,-a-wet-and-unwanted-visitor,-besieges-Carolinas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MYRTLE BEACH, S.C. (AP) — Florence, now a tropical storm, swirled at a near-standstill over the Carolinas on Saturday, dumping non-stop rain over areas already flooded by seawater</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black gov nominees become stars in bid for history...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/black-governor-nominees-become-stars-bid-history-043440074--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It was a raucous scene that could have been backstage at a rock concert: camera flashes, fans clamoring for autographs, scowling bodyguards, reporters hungry for a scoop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKI-MYSTERY: Empty kayak, two phones, missing counter-hacker...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/sep/14/speculation-over-fate-of-missing-dutchman-linked-to-wikileaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arjen Kamphuis’ effects found in the sea but his phones were turned on 1,000 miles away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeklong evacuation of solar observatory still a mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=12125818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did the researchers spot something extraterrestrial?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six gay candidates running in Connecticut -- as Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/six-gay-candidates-running-connecticut-republicans-n909701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vast majority of LGBTQ candidates run as Democrats, but political hopefuls are bucking the trend in Connecticut this election cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother Of Teen Murdered BY MS-13 Killed While Visiting Daughter's Memorial Site...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/09/14/mother-ms-13-victim-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mother of a Long Island teen, who was killed by alleged MS-13 gang members, has died after she was reportedly struck by a vehicle at her daughter’s memorial site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro's huge salary increases force 40% of Venezuelan stores to close...</title>
      <link>http://www.fltimes.com/tns/international/maduro-s-huge-salary-increases-force-percent-of-venezuelan-stores/article_c1492765-34d4-55dc-87bb-ec97b8abe142.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 40 percent of all Venezuelan stores have closed —some of them perhaps permanently —after the government of President Nicolas Maduro increased the minimum salary by nearly 3,500 percent in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Army to Swoop in...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/09/15/drone-army-is-ready-to-swoop-in-for-florence-power-recovery#gs.Lv_drG4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As Hurricane Florence batters the southeastern U.S., a small army of drones is being assembled to quickly help identify and even fix damage caused by the storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Keefe Teases 'Deep State' Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/09/breaking-james-okeefe-teases-next-weeks-hit-deep-state-should-be-worried/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Signs Up Mystery Passenger to Take Rocket Trip Around Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musks-spacex-says-it-has-signed-up-its-first-round-the-moon-tourist-1536898342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s SpaceX announced that it had signed up the first private passenger to fly around the moon. It didn’t provide a timetable or other details about the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls Trump attacks on media 'dangerous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/business-leaders/amazons-bezos-commets-on-trump-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bezos says decision on second headquarters due by end of year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT FLIPS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/14/trump-campaign-chief-paul-manafort-pleads-guilty-to-conspiracy-charges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crimes that Manafort pleads guilty to relate to money earned from consulting work on behalf of pro-Russia politicians in Ukraine, predating his tenure on the Trump campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOTING...</title>
      <link>https://www.wwaytv3.com/2018/09/14/brunswick-county-sheriff-discusses-crime-during-hurricane-florence-four-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wwaytv3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evacuations prompted by Hurricane Florence have left homes and businesses empty and vulnerable and some people are allegedly taking advantage of the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARWOOD:  Economy roaring, but most aren't feeling it...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/13/watch-out-gop-the-economy-is-roaring-but-most-americans-arent-feeling-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The positive news Wall Street savors — robust corporate profits, rising stock prices, surging output growth  deliver the greatest rewards to a relatively modest share of more affluent Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University announces safe space for white students...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Maryland at College Park announced Friday a new diversity support group to create a “safe space” for white students to discuss their feelings about “interactions with racial and ethnic minorities.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like bomb gone off'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/residents-trapped-roofs-vehicles-hurricane-florence-nears-coast/story?id=57818220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First responders are scrambling to rescue residents who didn't heed evacuation orders and are now stranded in their homes, cars and even on rooftops amid rising waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>900,000+ Without Power...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/hurricane-florence-numbers-latest-power-outages-rain-totals/story?id=57819104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence is slamming into the East Coast, knocking out power in North Carolina, dropping torrential rains and inundating several areas with floodwater. Here is a look at the dangerous storm by the numbers: 7: The number of fatalities so far. The first death attributed to Florence was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE, DETAILS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jdICssvaM9s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: http://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Please note that these posts do NOT reflect the official forecasts of the National Hurricane Center, and should not ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statue some call racist removed...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-statue-call-racist-removed-144754464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 19th century statue near San Francisco's City Hall that some said is racist and demeaning to indigenous people was removed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School gets rid of 'homecoming queen' after bullying...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/michigan-school-replaces-homecoming-queen-title-194653044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHELSEA, Mich. (AP) — A Michigan high school has decided to stop crowning homecoming queens amid bullying issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico arrests 'hitman' for trafficking endangered fish...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexico-arrests-hitman-trafficking-endangered-fish-162816949.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico has arrested an alleged drug cartel hitman on charges of trafficking the critically endangered totoaba fish, a species whose swim bladder can fetch up to $20,000 on the black market in China. The suspect, identified as Oscar N, alias "El Parra," was arrested Thursday on charges of leading</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAYS OF DOWNPOUR</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Florences-Grip-No-Relief-North-Carolina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence ground its way along the southern coast of North Carolina on Thursday night, delivering torrential rains, high winds, and a significant storm surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-ex-campaign-chairman-paul-manafort-reaches-deal-to-plead-guilty-1536932667 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort pleaded guilty to two federal crimes and agreed to cooperate with prosecutors, a dramatic turnaround for the former Trump campaign chairman who now becomes a powerful asset for special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cord-Cutters Beware: Streaming TV Prices March Higher...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cord-cutters-beware-streaming-tv-prices-are-marching-higher-1536943821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Streaming services like DirecTV Now and Sling TV have added millions of customers by promising big savings over traditional cable and satellite-TV subscriptions. But prices are going up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican-China Deal Recognizes Communist Appointed Bishops...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-and-vatican-to-sign-landmark-deal-over-bishops-1536929831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China and the Vatican are set to sign a landmark agreement ending a long struggle between Beijing’s Communist rulers and the pope over who controls Catholicism in the world’s most populous country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Catholic Church Breaking...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/jonathan-v-last/vigano-letter-mccarrick-wuerl-and-pope-francis-are-breaking-the-catholic-church</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis, Cardinal Wuerl, Theodore McCarrick, and the crisis of a church divided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen in contact with special counsel...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/09/michael-cohen-mueller</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of Manafort’s plea deal, sources confirm that it is now common knowledge among Cohen’s inner circle that Trump’s former lawyer has been in contact with the special counsel’s office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Hunts Sex Partners to Curb STDs...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2018-09-14/health-workers-in-oregon-attempt-to-stop-a-surge-in-stds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pleads guilty to conspiracy charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/09/14/paul-manafort-plea-deal-muellers-team/1288931002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort, the former chairman of President Donald Trump's campaign, reached an agreement Friday to cooperate with special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation of Russian interference in the 2016 election and pleaded guilty to two felonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis, Cardinals Share Laugh During Scandal Meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7260306/vatican-photo-pope-francis-cardinals-laughing-sex-abuse-scandal-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Vatican has been slammed for posting bizarre images of Pope Francis laughing along with religious leaders at an emergency meeting to discuss the sex scandals which have rocked the Catholic Chur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookshops threatened with legal action over book about Malaysian 'playboy banker'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/14/bookshops-threatened-with-legal-action-jho-low-billion-dollar-whale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free speech campaigners say letters sent to booksellers are attempt to ‘short-circuit legal process’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police scramble to crack down on California's deadly street races...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/14/california-street-racing-los-angeles-movies </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Street racing, spurred on by movies, takes on a second life in the Inland Empire, where opportunities for youngsters are scarce</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrated hunter hired to kill menacing, man-eating tiger...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/14/top-tiger-hunter-called-find-beast-accused-killing-13-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India's most celebrated hunter has been called in for a controversial mission to shoot a man-eating tigress blamed for killing 13 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feinstein Under Fire From Left For Kavanaugh Letter Handling...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article218415520.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Democrats, even some ardent critics, have declined to criticize Feinstein for her handling of a letter with allegations against Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. But 2018 challenger Kevin de León called it “a failure of leadership.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Dorsey: TWITTER So Liberal, Conservative Employees 'Don't Feel Safe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.recode.net/2018/9/14/17857622/twitter-liberal-employees-conservative-trump-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.recode.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don’t think that’s fair or right," Dorsey says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishers Blast TARGET for 'Censoring' Descriptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.publishersweekly.com/pw/by-topic/industry-news/publisher-news/article/77980-publishers-call-out-target-for-censoring-book-descriptions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.publishersweekly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of publishers say Target, on its retail website, is redacting certain keywords from the product descriptions of their books. They say the site has removed words like transgender and queer, as well as the name Hitler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why USA Backs Killer Robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/military/research/a23133118/us-ai-robots-warfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI weapons could soon execute military strikes on their own. Some think that's a bad idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AND THE FLAG WAS STILL THERE...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article218385220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veterans told Richard Neal that leaving his American flag up on Frying Pan Tower off the North Carolina coast through Hurricane Florence was disrespectful. Neal says the resilient flag “represents America.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE says it won't arrest or detain evacuees...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article218334165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During Hurricane Florence, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement will not arrest or detain immigrants in North Carolina and South Carolina who have evacuated their homes or at the emergency shelters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mac Miller's secret last hours -- bizarre theories about rapper death...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/mac-miller-death-conspiracy-theories-13242993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans have come up with a number of theories surrounding the death of the rapper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL employee refuses customer who doesn't speak Spanish...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/hialeah/article218395910.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee of a Taco Bell in Hialeah, FL, refused to take the order of a customer who did not speak Spanish, claiming that no one spoke English at the restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DERSHOWITZ: BIG MUELLER WIN SHOULD ALARM!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/alan-dershowitz-says-manafort-plea-a-big-win-for-mueller-white-house-should-be-alarmed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange cloud formation puzzles Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.kron4.com/news/bay-area/strange-cloud-formation-puzzles-bay-area-1/1444948601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kron4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unusual cloud formation has Bay Area residents puzzled Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cortez Wears $3,500 Outfit For Photo-op With Construction Workers?</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/socialist-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-wears-3500-outfit-for-photo-op-with-construction-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That wealth could have been redistributed better</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient altar reveals Mayan 'Game of Thrones' dynasty...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180914-ancient-altar-reveals-mayan-game-thrones-dynasty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many populations fear big job loss from automation... </title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180913-many-populations-fear-big-job-loss-automation-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar flare?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1017137/national-solar-observatory-sunspot-fbi-solar-flare-new-mexico-NM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE National Solar Observatory shut down has some fearing the sun’s activity is much worse than experts are letting on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Station leak: NASA, Russia tight-lipped over findings...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1017147/nasa-international-space-station-ISS-leak-roscosmos-russia-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA and Russia are remaining tight-lipped on their preliminary findings of what caused the leak in the International Space Station (ISS) in late August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX education board votes to eliminate Hillary Clinton from history curriculum...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/education/2018/09/14/history-curriculum-texas-remembers-alamo-forgets-hillary-clinton-helen-keller</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN — The Alamo defenders are heroes, but Hillary Clinton is not required reading.As part of an effort to streamline the social studies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More evidence of 'drilling'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6167113/More-evidence-drilling-aboard-International-Space-Station-Russia-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traces of drilling have now been discovered not only inside the spacecraft's living compartment, but also 'on the screen of the anti-meteorite shield', Russian space agency sources have claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-foot storm surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6166567/Hurricane-Florence-storm-surge-begins-flooding-hits-North-Carolina.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screaming winds bent trees toward the ground and raindrops flew sideways as Florence's leading edge whipped the Carolina coast on Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-founder Sergey Brin comparing Trump voters to 'fascists'... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6162889/Leaked-Google-conference-video-shows-founder-comparing-Trump-voters-extremists.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google co-founder Sergey Brin can be seen on stage in front of hundreds of employees saying he was 'deeply offended' by Trump's election and that it 'conflicts with many of Google's values.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>121,965,000 Americans on Govt Health Insurance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/121965000-government-health-insurance-522-those-incomes-under-75000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Barack Obama and Vice President Joe Biden at the signing of the Affordable Care Act, March 23, 2010. (Screen Capture)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600,000+ Without Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/hurricane-florence-dle/h_48821602a1d180e47b7f473da1e172f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 620,000 customers in North and South Carolina are now without power. Here are the latest numbers:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA WH LAWYER TO FACE CHARGES?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/14/politics/greg-craig-foreign-agent-registration-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors in New York are weighing criminal charges against former Obama White House counsel Greg Craig as part of an investigation into whether he failed to register as a foreign agent in a probe that is linked to former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort, according to sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE Stock RECORD HIGH After Kaepernick Campaign; Sales boost...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/14/nikes-kaepernick-ad-should-fuel-sales-as-retailer-knows-its-consumer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the campaign prompted a boycott from some consumers who were upset over the use of a polarizing figure like Kaepernick, and the stock initially dropped, Nike's online sales reportedly surged in the days thereafter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Bezos spending $2 billion like to average American... $1,187!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/13/bezos-spending-2-billion-feels-like-what-for-the-average-american.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is what spending looks like when you are Jeff Bezos, the wealthiest man with the highest net worth on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy worries as fire, police recruits asked to detail 'unusual sex acts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/2018/09/13/cincinnati-police-firefighter-recruits-asked-sexual-history/1204906002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cincinnati police, firefighter recruits are asked questions about their sexual history, including their most unusual sex act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake TRIPADVISOR reviews land man in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fake-tripadvisor-reviews-land-italian-man-in-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fake online reviews are a bane for many companies, but this is the first time they've sent someone to jail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years after LEHMAN, another crisis brewing?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/10-years-after-lehman-is-another-crisis-brewing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumers are in better shape regarding their debt, but the prospect of ever-higher federal deficits is worrying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cajun Navy rescues...</title>
      <link>https://www.bradenton.com/news/weather/hurricane/article218356585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bradenton.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the United Cajun Navy start arriving at a staging area in Gaston, SC on Thursday, Sept. 13, 2018. This is one of four staging areas they are setting up to assist in rescues as Hurricane Florence hits the Carolinas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Vowing to Curb Immigration Favored to Win Quebec Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/09/14/party-vowing-to-curb-immigration-favored-to-win-quebec-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A changing of the guard appears to be on the horizon in Quebec.   With less than three weeks to go before the Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flooding Could Cut Off Myrtle Beach...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2018-09-14-south-carolina-impacts-hurricane-florence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence has started to impact South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan firemen jailed after donkey vid mocks Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-venezuela-donkey/venezuelan-firemen-jailed-after-donkey-video-mocking-maduro-rights-groups-idUKKCN1LU2MU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Venezuelan firefighters were detained by military officers this week as susp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ferris wheel spins in wind...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/13JGoody/status/1040540549600690176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Winds at the VB #oceanfront spin the ferris wheel at 15th street. #13StormMode #Florence @13NewsNow @13PhilipT https://t.co/RqFECY0v4K”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas local TV ratings should make rest of NFL nervous... </title>
      <link>https://touchdownwire.usatoday.com/2018/09/13/dallas-low-tv-ratings-local-tv-ratings-nfl-tv-ratings/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;touchdownwire.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dallas market didn’t tune into to their beloved Cowboys and that’s a problem for the entire NFL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE CHINA PROTOTYPE LINKS SEARCHES TO PHONE NUMBERS...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/09/14/google-china-prototype-links-searches-to-phone-numbers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google’s plan for a censored search engine in China also blacklists terms like “Nobel Prize” and “human rights.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://radar.weather.gov/ridge/lite/N0Z/MHX_loop.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radar.weather.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley's Futile Search for 'Perfect Algorithm'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/silicon-valleys-futile-search-for-utopia-via-the-perfect-algorithm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech is new; the lure of false prophets is ancient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Upset As School Holds Active Shooter Drill; Police Fire Blanks Throughout Campus...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/09/12/bethel-park-active-school-shooter-drill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents in the Bethel Park School District are concerned about blanks being used during an active school shooter drill Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Fonda says Moonves ouster 'only the beginning'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/09/14/jane-fonda-says-les-moonves-ouster-is-only-the-beginning/?_ga=2.10438453.1208386760.1536938660-1836769803.1536713031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s a shame he didn’t behave, [but now] it’s come back to get him,” Fonda said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buoy Records 30-Feet Waves...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/09/14/hurricane-florence-landfall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Florence made landfall Friday morning in North Carolina with howling 90 mph winds and terrifying storm surge early Friday, splintering buildings and trapping hundreds of people in high water</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Politicize Wind, Blame Trump for Storms, Predict Mass Death...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-media-politicize-florence-blame-trump-storms-predict-mass-de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is ‘actively making the problem worse’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's killing SEARS? Retirees...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/09/14/news/companies/sears-pension-retirees/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many experts blame Eddie Lampert for the company's misfortune, but he blames what Sears has to pay retirees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Weatherman dramatically braces as civilians casually stroll by...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/weatherman-dramatically-braces-for-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Come on, now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety measures ordered at sinking San Fran tower...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/bendbulletin/article/204a0a6bc2604ef883c72205679f9025/safety-measures-ordered-sinking-san-francisco-tower</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco officials demanded Thursday that managers of a sinking condominium building where a window recently cracked comply with safety measures needed to keep the public safe. Ronald Tom, assistant director of the Department of Building Inspection, said management at Millennium Tower must inspect all units and install a canopy around the perimeter of the 58-story building by Friday afternoon. They also must repair a broken crane to allow engineers to inspect the cracked glass from outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anglican leader faces backlash after big stake exposed...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/anglican-leader-faces-backlash-amazon-zero-hours-contracts-121138955--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archbishop of Canterbury Justin Welby, the spiritual leader of the world's Anglicans, faced accusations of hypocrisy on Friday after it emerged the Church of England holds shares in online retail giant Amazon and employs people on zero-hours contracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORENCE WEEKEND</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8f08c9c8ae648a19dbf21180809e5fd/Florence-rolls-ashore-in-Carolinas,-tears-buildings-apart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, N.C. (AP) — Blowing ashore with howling 90 mph (155 kph) winds, Florence splintered buildings, trapped hundreds of people and swamped entire communities along the Caro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina seizes costly film equipment stolen from Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4c0aaa36810e4d5a8df663884c58eca2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUENOS AIRES, Argentina (AP) — Argentine authorities said Friday that they had seized about $3 million in cameras, lenses and other film equipment stolen in Hollywood and New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosquitoes size of quarter plague Houston...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/weather/quarter-size-mosquitoes-plague-area-ahead-of-heavy-rainfall-/4235028/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSQUITOES SUCK... and with all this rain heading for the Texas Gulf Coast, things might just get even worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>http://www.ssd.noaa.gov/PS/TROP/floaters/06L/imagery/rb-animated.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ssd.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURNS DEADLY...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/09/14/first-deaths-reported-from-hurricane-florence-after-wilmington-home-collapses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florence was downgraded to a tropical storm on Friday after making landfall earlier in the day in North Carolina as a Category 1 hurricane, weather officials said. Meanwhile the first reports of fatalities were emerging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FULL COOPERATION' WITH SPECIAL COUNSEL...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/09/14/paul-manafort-to-plead-guilty-as-part-plea-deal-with-special-counsel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort pleaded guilty in federal court Friday as part of a plea agreement with Special Counsel Robert Mueller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-Year-Old Cat Dies After Shot With BB Gun...</title>
      <link>http://detroit.cbslocal.com/2018/09/14/30-year-old-michigan-cat-dies-after-being-shot-with-bb-gun-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger the cat was shot in the hind leg with a BB gun and was euthanized after being unable to walk.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
