<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NEIGHBORS FEAR FOR SAFETY</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/surfside-condos-neighbors-fear-for-their-safety/ar-AALu6FO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire smolders as hopes dim of finding survivors in the collapsed condo in Miami. And people throughout the area grow frightened of additional collapses and the mayor looks into possible evacuation plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAYOFFS FOR PERMITS?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/27/developers-of-fla-tower-were-accused-of-paying-off-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The developers of the Miami condo tower that collapsed were once accused of paying off local officials to get permits for the site — which needed $15 million in repairs just to bring it to co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Springsteen reopens Broadway...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/26/bruce-springsteen-makes-a-triumphant-emotional-return-to-broadway-jokes-about-arrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Springsteen made an emotional, triumphant return to Broadway tonight at the St. James Theater. His audience included the governor of New Jersey, Phil Murphy, but that didn’t stop Bruce …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 Young Adults Neither Working Nor Studying...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/one-in-five-young-adults-is-neither-working-nor-studying-in-us/ar-AALtulF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost one in five young adults in the U.S. was neither working nor studying in the first quarter as Black and Hispanic youth remain idle at disproportionate rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Probes Leak of Images Showing Health Minister Kissing Aide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-health-department-investigate-leak-081916737.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (Reuters) -Britain's government will investigate how images of former health minister Matt Hancock kissing an aide found their way into the media and forced his resignation, in the latest scandal to hit Prime Minister Boris Johnson's government. The departure put renewed focus on the government over its handling of the COVID-19 pandemic. Britain has one of the highest official coronavirus death tolls in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Shifts 50,000 Troops to China Border in Historic Move...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/india-shifts-50000-troops-to-china-border-in-historic-move</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai's Luxury Home Sales Soar...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dawn-roaring-twenties-seen-dubai-095953169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A record burst of sales in the priciest corners of the global property market may be ushering in a post-pandemic era of exuberance in real estate -- with Dubai among the front-runners.The Middle East business hub is the latest city to light up with what Knight Frank LLP called “a spectacular post-Covid rebound in luxury home sales.” In the first five months of the year, 22 properties worth more than $10 million found a buyer, the most since 2015 and up from a total of 19 last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States hesitant to adopt digital vaccine verification...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-technology-lifestyle-coronavirus-pandemic-business-1c78a2a22e59835286984b5f1ee2df62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customers wanting to wine, dine and unwind to live music at the City Winery's flagship restaurant in New York must show proof of a COVID-19 vaccination to get in. But that's not required at most other dining establishments in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland records hottest day ever... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/heat-waves-health-coronavirus-pandemic-environment-and-nature-790f3c7348cb0b8fa835f259c1e18c14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Intense. Prolonged. Record-breaking. Unprecedented. Abnormal. Dangerous. That’s how the National Weather Service described the historic heat wave that is hitting the Pacific Northwest, pushing daytime temperatures into the triple digits and breaking all-time high temperature records in places where many residents don’t have air conditioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO  MIRACLES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/florida-miami-surfside-condo-building-collapse-02507acd6f14d31ccfe8c42662b76532</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — The death toll from the collapse of a Florida beachfront condo building has risen to nine as search-and-rescue efforts continue, Miami-Dade Mayor Daniella Levine Cava said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  McAfee 'left suicide note in his pocket'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3159316/mcafee-left-suicide-note-before-jail-hanging/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SUICIDE note was reportedly found tucked inside the pocket of tech guru John McAfee’s hanged body, it emerged on Friday.  The letter’s discovery came after the 75-year-old tech guru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 62:  MADONNA IN FISHNETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3165110/madonna-surprise-bar-gig-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUST when we thought all celebs did now was post joyless Instagram shots, the Queen of Pop reminded the young ’uns how it’s done with an impromptu bar show. Madonna – who arrived with boyfriend Ahl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 DEAD, 156 MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article252401258.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescuers have recovered another four bodies in the wreckage of the Champlain Towers condominium collapse, bringing the total to nine dead and 156 still missing since the Surfside building collapsed early Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVEY WEINSTEIN OPERA IN WORKS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/26/a-harvey-weinstein-opera-may-be-coming-to-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hopefully he won’t show his magic flute. An opera about the Manhattan trial of Harvey Weinstein is currently in production in Northern Ireland, and may be coming to New York City, its creator…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE:  HEAT MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_heat.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA to Resume Self-Defense Classes for Airline Crews...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/26/fight-and-flight-t-s-a-to-resume-self-defense-classes-for-airline-crews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration will once again offer self-defense classes to flight attendants and pilots as the airline industry deals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Adulterer in the Room...</title>
      <link>https://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:t6-Rc7XwXMkJ:https://airmail.news/issues/2021-6-26/the-adulterer-in-the-room+&amp;cd=1&amp;hl=en&amp;ct=clnk&amp;gl=us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;webcache.googleusercontent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this the reason he's no longer at the company?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 2 Start-Ups Reaped Billions on Bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/27/how-two-start-ups-reaped-billions-in-fees-on-small-business-relief-loans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though Congress approved billions in aid for small companies to help them keep paying their employees during the pandemic, there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court Rules FACEBOOK Can Be Liable for Sex Trafficking...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/court-rules-facebook-can-be-liable-for-sex-trafficking-on-its-platform-section-230-does-not-create-a-lawless-no-mans-land/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Supreme Court ruled Friday that Facebook can be held liable for any sex trafficking on its platform, despite the protections of Section 230. Facebook’s attorneys had initially argued that under Section 230 of the federal Communications Decency Act, the social media giant could not be held responsible for what a user said or […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSPECTOR ON ROOF BEFORE COLLAPSE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9728761/Emotional-mom-blasts-DeSantis-Miami-condo-rescue-effort-not-moving-fast-enough.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman questioned how 'nobody has emerged dead or alive' from the wreckage of the Champlain Towers South building in Surfside, Miami Beach, in days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As parents forbid covid shots, defiant teens seek ways to get them...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/coronavirus/ct-aud-nw-nyt-teens-covid-shots-defiant-20210626-yoshr7cnz5f6xmpsra66yoznfa-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vaccination of children is crucial to achieving broad immunity to the coronavirus and returning to normal school and work routines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel lawyer accused cops of corruption. Then they accused him of murder...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rebel-lawyer-accused-california-cops-120020873.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modesto defense attorney Frank Carson spent years accusing local police and prosecutors of corruption. One day they accused him of masterminding a sprawling murder and cover-up conspiracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-old gives birth!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15404373/girl-11-gives-birth-britains-youngest-mum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GIRL of 11 has had a baby — and is now believed to be Britain’syoungest ever mum. She became pregnant aged ten before giving birth earlier this month. Mum and tot, delivered after more than 30 we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security robots expand across USA, with few tangible results...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/security-robots-expand-across-u-s-few-tangible-results-n1272421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It would be difficult to introduce a single thing and it causes crime to go down,” one expert said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds for first-ever national rally for D.C. statehood...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/crowds-descend-on-mall-for-first-ever-national-rally-for-dc-statehood/ar-AALtZMv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The event was organized by Black Voters Matter and 50 other civil rights organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight aborts landing after drone infiltrates Tel Aviv airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/delta-flight-forced-to-abort-landing-after-drone-infiltrates-ben-gurion-672177</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where buffalo roam: World's longest wildlife bridge could cross the Mississippi...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jun/27/bison-bridge-wildlife-crossing-mississippi-river</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservationist aims to replace ageing bridge with bison preserve, benefiting environment and spotlighting Indigenous history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon accused of UFO COVER-UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3165390/pentagon-accused-of-coverup-for-top-secret-section-omission/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Pentagon has been accused of cover-up part of the UFO report after a “top-secret” part of the document was left out during its release. The nine-page report that was released on Fri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Barr Speaks: 'All Bullsh*t'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/william-barr-speaks/ar-AALuFs3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the final months of the administration, the doggedly loyal attorney general finally had enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump airs old election grievances in return to stage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-fl-state-wire-ohio-campaign-2016-trump-impeachment-939c98aadd22d09056e9ce5a7c79064f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, Ohio (AP) — Former President Donald Trump reprised his election grievances and baseless claims of fraud as he returned to the rally stage Saturday, holding his first campaign-style event since leaving the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great white shark bites man swimming near San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Great-white-shark-bite-man-swimming-California-16276525.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is in critical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO MIAMI MIRACLES</title>
      <link>https://www.christianitytoday.com/news/2021/june/miami-building-collapse-surfside-church-chaplain-rescue-pra.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.christianitytoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classified UK Ministry of Defense docs found at bus stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-57624942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The papers contain details about UK warship HMS Defender and the British military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt report: UFOs real...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/25/government-report-ufos-are-real-496319</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of 144 encounters with mysterious aircraft, 143 are literally unidentifiable, according to a newly released report to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>143 events can't be explained...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/ufo-report-government-can-t-explain-143-144-mysterious-flying-n1272390</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Defense established the Unidentified Aerial Phenomena Task Force in August to investigate mysterious flying objects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand to reimpose curbs to contain outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210627-thailand-to-reimpose-coronavirus-curbs-to-contain-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thailand to reimpose coronavirus curbs to contain outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READ...</title>
      <link>https://www.dni.gov/files/ODNI/documents/assessments/Prelimary-Assessment-UAP-20210625.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dni.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen reopens Broadway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/27/bruce-springsteen-reopens-broadway-and-opens-up-about-his-dwi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wondrous night was a welcome reminder that Times Square, Broadway theaters and shows are not meant to be shut down. Baby, they are born to run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPO Market Never Been Hotter...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/global-ipo-market-never-hotter-040000004.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Companies are racing to public markets like never before, cashing in on record-high stock prices.An all-time high of almost $350 billion has been raised in initial public offerings in the first six months of this year, according to data compiled by Bloomberg, surpassing the previous peak of $282 billion from the second half of 2020 and enriching entrepreneurs and bankers alike.When the rush for IPOs kicked off last year, stay-at-home technology dominated the scene, seizing on inve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 DEAD, 156  MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9729419/Authorities-identified-four-five-people-confirmed-dead-deadly-Miami.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities identified Antonio Lozano, 83, his wife Gladys Lozano, 79, Manny Lafont, 54 and Stacie Fang, 54, as four of the five people who died in the deadly Miami condo collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENGINEER WARNED IN '18</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/26/engineer-warned-of-major-structural-damage-at-florida-condo-complex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three years before the deadly collapse of the Champlain Towers South condominium complex near Miami, a consultant found alarming evidence of “major</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland records hottest day ever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/heat-waves-fires-wildfires-environment-and-nature-2d15c637c00e15862b592cf0d26638cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Utility workers and wildlife managers across the Pacific Northwest were trying to keep people and animals safe Saturday as a historic heat wave scorched the region, toppling records and sending residents searching for relief.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
