<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN TO REQUIRE PROOF OF SHOT</title>
      <link>https://www.kron4.com/news/bay-area/san-francisco-to-require-proof-of-vaccination-for-some-indoor-activities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kron4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (KRON) — San Francisco will require residents and visitors to prove that they are fully vaccinated against COVID-19 for a number of indoor activities such as visiting restaurant…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Al Qaeda resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/mideast/potential-al-qaeda-resurgence-afghanistan-worries-u-s-officials-n1276614</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gen. Frank McKenzie told NBC News that he does not believe the Taliban will stop Al Qaeda from using Afghanistan to strengthen and rebuild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House cheers empoyer efforts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/canada-business-health-australia-coronavirus-pandemic-460afab866006f92ebd1e3916b024246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Anthony Fauci says Americans can expect to see more children infected with the coronavirus as the highly transmissible delta variant extends its hold across the country. “Quantitatively, you will see more children in the hospital,” the government’s top infectious disease expert said at Thursday’s coronavirus briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel, Morocco to upgrade relations, open embassies...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210812171933-6qhan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-MOROCCO/ (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Israel, Morocco to upgrade relations, open embassies, Israeli FM says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua paper says it can no longer print, blames govt...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210812165931-lomgm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICARAGUA-POLITICS/ (PIX):Nicaragua paper says it can no longer do print editions, blames government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Third Of Pandemic Pet Owners Experiencing Regret...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/12/post-pandemic-pet-regret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent poll of Florida pet owners who had adopted or bought an animal during the pandemic says over 1/3 is experiencing post-pandemic pet regret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mississippi-braces-for-e2-80-98failure-e2-80-99-of-hospital-system-due-to-covid-19-surge-and-lack-of-icu-beds/ar-AANfhef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is averaging nearly 2,700 new covid-19 infections a day in the past week — spiking 54 percent in the past seven days — and a hospital's parking garage is being converted to treat additional ICU patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Hunter Biden tells prostitute Russians stole his laptop...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9881213/Unearthed-video-shows-naked-Hunter-Biden-claiming-Russian-drug-dealers-stole-laptop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: EXPLICIT CONTENT. Hunter Biden claims Russian drug dealers stole another one of his laptops for blackmail while he was close to overdosing in a Vegas hotel room in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: Boosters 'Inevitable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/dr-fauci-inevitably-well-have-to-give-booster-shots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci suggested that coronavirus vaccine booster shots might be inevitable for everyone eventually.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shia LaBeouf eyes comeback -- as Italian Saint?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/global/shia-labeouf-abel-ferrara-film-italian-saint-padre-pio-1235040107/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shia LaBeouf could be making a comeback turn. Legendary director Abel Ferrara has exclusively told Variety that LaBeouf has come on board to play the lead role in his next feature, which centers on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Restaurants Push Back Against Mandate: We're Not Gonna Be Covid Police...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/11/nyc-restaurants-against-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting next week, proof of vaccination will be required citywide for indoor activities such as dining, gyms and concerts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic laid bare America's diabetes crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-laid-bare-americas-100338534.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadly COVID-19 pandemic has exposed a deeper U.S. public-health crisis.For more than a decade, the nation has been losing the battle against diabetes.Here are the stories of diabetes patients who fell victim to the isolation and disruptions the pandemic caused, even if they weren't infected with the coronavirus.Elicia Heaston had a best friend – Kate Herrin.(ELICIA HEASTON): "Kate was my best friend, but really my sister. We met like 26 years ago in high school in our English class, and we just developed a friendship."Long before the pandemic, Herrin was among the millions of Americans struggling to control their diabetes.Then COVID-19 hit.Poor and living alone, Herrin rarely left her apartment.She stopped going in for regular lab tests, and had a harder time than ever securing medical supplies.Her health deteriorated further, until the worst happened.(ELICIA HEASTON): "They found her on the bathroom floor. I heard them radio down that there was an unconscious female on the bathroom floor and I completely lost it. The police had me unlock her phone with the passcode and I unlocked the phone and the last thing she had Googled, what was up on her phone was the signs of a heart attack.”The coroner attributed the heart attack that killed Herrin to complications of type 2 diabetes. Heaston says Herrin was afraid COVID would kill her. Instead, it isolated her, and her diabetes got worse.(ELICIA HEASTON): "It's every day I think about her, every day. There's not one day that since she's passed that I don't think about her."68-year-old John Cupo works as a building systems manager in Las Vegas.He was diagnosed with type 2 diabetes more than a decade ago.Then, in November 2019, he spotted a sore on his left foot. His podiatrist blamed diminished blood circulation due to diabetes and treated the sore.After that, Cupo agreed to visit every other week for checkups.But COVID-19 upended his routine.(JOHN CUPO): "I was too afraid to leave the house to go into a crowded doctor's office or anything like that. So I just stayed home and I was trying to treat it myself, and it just kept getting worse and worse. My foot kept getting worse, so I went to see my new podiatrist, who I had met at the hospital, and he said he needed to amputate my toes. And then my foot ended up … the bone got infected. That's what happened. And the amputation of the toes didn't work because a week later, my foot turned black and I went to the foot doctor and he said I had to have my leg amputated."Cupo had a difficult four-month recovery after the amputation.He has since grown accustomed to his prosthetic, but says he believes he would still have his leg if it weren’t for COVID scaring him to stay home.The ranks of the newly diagnosed type 2 diabetes patients are shifting younger.In part, that’s because more and more Americans are living in “obesogenic” environments where they exercise less, eat more processed foods, and gain excessive weight at an earlier age.The isolation and inactivity imposed by the pandemic compounded many of those risks.At Children’s National Hospital in Washington, D.C., diagnoses of type 2 diabetes among patients 8 to 20 years old nearly tripled in the first year of the pandemic.One of the hospital’s new patients is 15-year-old Adedotun Adebayo.(ADEDOTUN ADEBAYO): "I was a pretty active person before Covid, so when Covid hit and everything shut down and all the gyms were closed and everything, I really didn't do much exercise and I think that's probably one of the factors that contributed to me getting diabetes. Yeah, I gained a lot of weight."In March this year, Adebayo was rushed to the ICU after having passed out at church.(ADEDOTUN ADEBAYO): "I woke up and I was in the hospital like I've seen the movie movies like with the little bed that moves and everything, and I had wires and I had all this beeping stuff around me. And I remember I couldn't, I couldn't talk. I couldn't talk, my speech was very slurred. And I couldn't … I didn't even want to eat. I didn't feel hungry. I just I just kept asking for water." These days, Adebayo says he tries to wake up earlier and eat a better diet.He counts the carbohydrates in his food so he can correctly dose his meal-time insulin injections. He also takes metformin, the first-line drug for type 2 diabetes.Deaths from diabetes surged 17% to more than 100,000 in the U.S. in 2020. That’s according to a Reuters analysis of CDC data.This grim toll is the result of a public-health failure that long predates the pandemic, and it is almost certain to persist after COVID-19 abates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires Calling For Emergency Tax On Billionaires!</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90665399/millionaires-are-calling-for-an-emergency-tax-on-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Groups are urging a one-time tax on the $5.5 trillion in wealth billionaires gained during the pandemic to fund unemployment grants and vaccinate the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINE EFFECTIVENESS SPOOKS SYSTEM</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/vaccine-efficacy-biden-pfizer-moderna-death-infetion-4403be7b-ced7-410e-9c19-67e201f031f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is intensely scrutinizing coronavirus vaccines' effectiveness over time, facing the daunting task of timing booster shots right while still convincing the unvaccinated that getting the jab is worthwhile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUNISHMENT:  Philly Mayor Orders Unvaccinated Workers Wear DOUBLE-Masks...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/08/11/philadelphia-mask-mandate-vaccine-requirements-businesses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia is taking big steps to get the coronavirus pandemic under control once and for all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Warrior mindset' police training proliferated. Then, high-profile deaths put under scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Warrior-mindset-police-training-proliferated-16381887.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ethan Murray was shot five times by a sheriff's deputy on May 4, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: 3 Brothers Die After Passing Out From Fumes In Manure Pit On Farm...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/08/11/ohio-brothers-die-manure-pit-ohio-farm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three brothers who were trapped in a manure pit on their livestock farm after being overcome by fumes have died, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fraternal Order of Police Slams NEWSMAX Host as 'Clown' for Claim About Capitol Riot Officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fraternal-order-police-fanone-newsmax-greg-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fraternal Order of Police condemned Newsmax's Greg Kelly for a weeks-old comment about Capitol riot responder Officer Michael Fanone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executing troops who surrender?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/taliban-may-be-executing-surrendering-afghan-troops-us-embassy-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reported executions are "deeply disturbing &amp; could constitute war crimes," according to the embassy in Kabul, as the Taliban continue to take territory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger, Military Jets Report Seeing UFO Over Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93ymje/passenger-and-military-jets-both-report-seeing-a-ufo-over-eastern-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A July 30 report describes a “bright green flying object” that “flew into a cloud, then disappeared.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herd immunity 'mythical' with delta...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/12/herd-immunity-is-mythical-with-the-covid-delta-variant-experts-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Achieving herd immunity with Covid vaccines when the highly infectious delta variant is spreading is likely to be impossible, leading experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE new 'time crystals' could be breakthrough for long-awaited quantum computers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/google-e2-80-99s-new-e2-80-98time-crystals-e2-80-99-could-be-a-breakthrough-for-long-awaited-quantum-computers/ar-AANeMF0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at Google, Stanford and Princeton say they used Google’s quantum computer to demonstrate a “time crystal.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz associate providing feds intel, docs as probe into congressman continues...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/gaetz-associate-providing-feds-intel-documents-probe-congressman/story?id=79388281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Rep. Matt Gaetz's one-time wingman has been steadily providing investigators with potential evidence that could implicate Gaetz in a federal probe, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents make threats after school board mandates coverings: 'We will find you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tennessee-parents-make-threats-after-school-board-mandates-masks-e2-80-98we-will-find-you-e2-80-99/ar-AANeOB4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As covid-19 cases among Tennessee children surge, some parents are protesting school mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Afghan general takes fight against Taliban to social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210812-young-afghan-general-takes-fight-against-taliban-to-social-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a string of Taliban victories show Afghan government forces in disarray, a young general is advancing his reputation on the battlefield and on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic laid bare America's diabetes crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210812110037-0sv1w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DIABETES/COVID (SPECIAL REPORT):SPECIAL REPORT-How the pandemic laid bare America's diabetes crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police chief says case under review...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-environment-and-nature-police-london-prince-andrew-208d010557b761f96793dab05f405d4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — London's top police official said Thursday that the city's police department is reviewing its files but no opening an investigation of Britain's Prince Andrew, who faces sexual assault allegations in a U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First water cuts in  West supply to hammer Arizona farmers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-science-environment-and-nature-arizona-climate-change-7cf4c472fa64fe57be4b8823c5423fc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CASA GRANDE, Ariz. (AP) — A harvester rumbles through the fields in the early morning light, mowing down rows of corn and chopping up ears, husks and stalks into mulch for feed at a local dairy. The cows won't get their salad next year, at least not from this farm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen basketball player died after collapsing in 97-degree heat. Coaches now face murder charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-teen-basketball-player-died-after-collapsing-in-97-degree-heat-her-coaches-now-face-murder-charges/ar-AANesu2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two years after Imani Bell's death, her basketball coaches have been charged with murder, cruelty to children, involuntary manslaughter and reckless conduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45-year-old Kansas mayor needs pacemaker after long-haul fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-45-year-old-kansas-mayor-needs-a-pacemaker-after-a-long-haul-covid-fight-i-thought-i-was-going-to-beat-it/ar-AANeg4Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The politician is one of millions thought to be suffering from long-haul covid, a lingering condition that leaves some facing heart palpitations, shortness of breath and other health problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says Bezos would be on Pluto by now 'if lobbying and lawyers could get you to orbit'...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-says-jeff-bezos-103330328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the richest people on the planet locked in space race through their companies Blue Origin and SpaceX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis confronts growing resistance...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/567409-desantis-confronts-growing-resistance-over-covid-19-handling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE BEACH, Fla. – Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) is facing growing resistance to his hardline stance against COVID-19 restrictions and mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surf Instructor Killed Children and Claimed QANON Made Him Do It, FBI Says...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/12/surf-instructor-killed-his-children-and-claimed-qanon-made-him-do-it-f-b-i-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California surfing instructor confessed to killing his two children with a spearfishing gun after abducting them, telling investigators that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's Qaddafi Comeback Gambit Sows New Conflict With West...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/putins-qaddafi-comeback-gambit-sows-new-conflict-with-the-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents asked to limit 911 calls...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/covid-surge-prompts-one-florida-county-ask-residents-use-911-n1276561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I can tell you compared to March or July where we were last year to where we are now, this is a lot worse," a Brevard County fire official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Britney Spears to political rivals, Joel Greenberg searched scores of names on confidential database...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/from-britney-spears-to-political-rivals-joel-greenberg-searched-scores-of-names-on-confidential-database/ar-AANcHff?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — During his time as Seminole County’s tax collector, Joel Greenberg used a confidential database to look up the personal information of fellow elected officials, political rivals, county employees, family members and even celebrities — including Britney Spears and Justin Timberlake — newly released records show. The names of hundreds that Greenberg pried into — ranging from U.S. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-UK relations strained as prince refuses to talk to investigators...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/prince-andrew-america-epstein-probes-cooperation-b1900854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears issue over Duke of York could affect wider efforts to collaborate on high-profile legal cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand hopes to relax border controls NEXT YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/zealand-hopes-relax-border-controls-001300967.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand's Jacinda Ardern said Thursday that strict border controls would remain this year but she hoped to cautiously reopen to the rest of the world in 2022 while maintaining the country's virus-free status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines begin to see another drop in travel demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/airlines-begin-to-see-drop-in-travel-demand-as-virus-numbers-rise/ar-AANcGwL?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surge in coronavirus caseloads across the nation is starting to dampen the enthusiasm of leisure travelers, and some airlines are warning of weaker bookings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida covid hospitalizations set another record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/florida-hospitalizations-soar-for-another-day-led-by-broward-county/ar-AANdfzC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the 11th straight day, Florida hospitals set records for the number of COVID patients they are treating, and on Wednesday the state set a new high for daily cases. On Wednesday, Florida hospitals had 15,449 patients a significant jump from just two days earlier when admissions surpassed 14,000 to set a record. The high count reached Wednesday occurred with only 230 of 261 hospitals ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICILY SIZZLES: Nearly 120°, threatens Europe's all-time heat record...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210811-new-heat-record-in-italy-as-lucifer-sweeps-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New heat record in Italy as 'Lucifer' sweeps in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Demands Vax Proof For Stores, Restaurants, Movie Theaters... MORE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/los-angeles-city-requires-vaccination-vaccine-indoors-1234813086/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles City Council voted 13-0 today to have the city attorney prepare an ordinance requiring people to show proof of at least partial vaccination against Covid to enter most public indoor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cz-YKyCmJBg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden asks OPEC to up oil output while limiting U.S. energy production...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/11/joe-biden-asks-opec-oil-output-while-limiting-us-e/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Wednesday made the embarrassing move to call on OPEC and its allies to boost oil production as gas prices continue to climb, underscoring alarms over the U.S. losing its energy independence under President Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge refuses to toss DONINION defamation suits against Giuliani and Lindell...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/11/judge-dominion-defamation-suits-powell-504000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling from the Trump appointee is likely to force depositions by the three allies of the former president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIC TAX COLLECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-set-record-through-july-real-federal-spending</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set a new record for the amount of taxes it collected through the first ten months of fiscal 2021 (October through July), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Tropical storm will approach Florida this weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-fred-forecast-track-us-florida-landfall-impacts/997558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm could falter as it encounters land in the Caribbean but will restrengthen over warm waters setting the stage for 18 inches of rain and 90-mph winds in parts of the Southeast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College professor charged with setting CA fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/11/gary-stephen-maynard-college-professor-charged-wit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A college professor suspected in a series of arson fires has been charged with setting a small blaze in a forest near Northern California’s massive Dixie Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Gov Escapes to Italy as Cases Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.northjersey.com/story/news/coronavirus/2021/08/09/gov-phil-murphy-italy-vacation-nj-delta-variant-cases-rise/5536749001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.northjersey.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NJ has seen a sharp rise in COVID hospitalizations and cases in the last five weeks due to the rapid spread of the highly contagious delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani told agents: OK to 'throw a fake' during political campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/giuliani-told-agents-it-was-okay-to-e2-80-98throw-a-fake-e2-80-99-during-political-campaign/ar-AANcUHm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You’re under no obligation to tell the truth,” Giuliani’s law partner said in defending the former New York mayor’s promise of an October surprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel approves new restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-hits-400-serious-covid-cases-ahead-of-corona-cabinet-meeting-676412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cabinet decided that starting August 18th the Green Pass will apply to everyone over the age of 3, and gatherings will be limited based on the number of participants and their vaccination status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi's Largest Hospital Converting Garage to Covid Ward...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/mississippis-largest-hospital-converting-garage-covid-ward-state-short-icu-beds-1618487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There were ZERO available ICU beds in Mississippi as of early this morning. None," UMMC Dr. LouAnne Woodward said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel officials draft classified report as they near finish of 90-day Covid probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/11/politics/classified-report-covid-origins-under-review-90-day-probe/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intelligence officials are nearing the end of a 90-day investigation into the origins of Covid-19 that was ordered by President Joe Biden, and have drafted a classified report that is now in the preliminary review process, according to three sources familiar with the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Sen. Scott Brown plans to jump back into politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republican-scott-brown-plans-to-jump-back-into-political-arena-8eae7d7c-c937-468d-8777-fc1e4b7a07da.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are two potentially attractive opportunities for Brown in his new home state of New Hampshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraway Planets Don't Seem So Distant Anymore...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/faraway-planets-don-t-seem-so-distant-anymore/ar-AANbGU7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers are stepping up their attempts to unravel the mysteries of exoplanets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden slams Trump for racking up $8 trillion in debt; Vows to tax rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-slams-trump-for-racking-up-8-trillion-in-debt-as-he-vows-democrats-will-pay-for-their-spending-plan-by-taxing-the-rich/ar-AANd9vW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the Senate passed Biden's infrastructure plan, the president said his economic agenda won't be anything like Trump's "unpaid tax cuts."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KABUL SEIZED IN WEEKS?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/11/us-officials-warn-taliban-could-seize-kabul-in-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US officials have warned that the Taliban could seize Kabul in as little as one month amid the American troop withdrawal from Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Pay-for-play scandal behind many MAXIM, PLAYBOY 'covers'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/11/the-pay-for-play-scandal-behind-many-sexy-maxim-playboy-covers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any woman can be a magazine cover girl these days — if she’s willing to pony up the dough. Juliet Amelia, a 45-year-old licensed massage therapist from Florida, looked like the hottest model …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico drug cartel threatens prominent news anchor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/10/americas/mexico-cartel-milenio-azucena-uresti-intl-latam/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A masked man claiming to be the leader of the Jalisco New Generation Cartel threatens to "get" Milenio TV anchor Azucena Uresti for her coverage of the cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICILY SIZZLES: Nearly 120°, threatens Europe's all-time heat record...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/europe-all-time-heat-record-set-sicily-065cef11-fdb7-4aaf-abd5-82b5b8d7a475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The temperature record came in the midst of a regional heat wave that has contributed to wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GANNETT cuts crime coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.poynter.org/reporting-editing/2021/gannett-launches-a-network-wide-push-to-rework-its-crime-coverage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.poynter.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer mugshots, additional context and moving beyond police narratives are just some of the changes its newsrooms are making</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hochul vows not to have 'toxic' workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/11/kathy-hochul-vows-big-difference-from-cuomo-administration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo stunned the state with his resignation. Kathy Hochul, his lieutenant governor, will replace him.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
