<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Coups making comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coup-attemps-countries-around-world-e14f76d2-16b1-43da-8411-6f8fc07cec84.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been 8 coups in the past year, a rate last seen in the 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housework or sleep? Depends when you were born...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-shopping-generations-millennials-generation-x-f83076bc265efff3809700ceaa1b57a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Gen Xer Amy Rottier went shopping for her young children two decades ago, she drove to a mall and browsed for what she needed. Her millennial daughter, Helen, who is studying for a doctorate and doesn't have children, buys anything she needs with a click on her iPad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions of animals slaughtered every year -- just to be wasted...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/22890292/food-waste-meat-dairy-eggs-milk-animal-welfare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The staggering toll of food waste on animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$15 million incentive to wait a week?</title>
      <link>https://www.totalprosports.com/2022/01/29/one-key-detail-from-tom-bradys-contract-explains-why-he-refuses-to-retire-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.totalprosports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read “One Key Detail From Tom Brady’s Contract Explains Why He Refuses To Retire Yet ” and other NFL articles from Total Pro Sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CONTROLS MAY OUTLAST VIRUS</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/30/living-by-the-code-in-china-covid-era-controls-may-outlast-the-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The police had warned Xie Yang, a human rights lawyer, not to go to Shanghai to visit the mother of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The People Lawmakers Hate to Regulate: Themselves...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-people-lawmakers-hate-to-regulate-themselves/ar-AATikqG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing seals off more residential areas, reports 12 cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-coronavirus-pandemic-sports-health-china-d1e60d242db347b2b2335c5244f64793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Beijing officials said Sunday they sealed off several residential communities in the city's northern district after two cases of COVID-19 were found. Residents in the Anzhenli neighborhood in Chaoyang district were sealed off on Saturday, and will not be allowed to leave their compound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  9 dead in Vegas crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/north-las-vegas/9-dead-in-north-las-vegas-crash-involving-speeding-2521066/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 5 dead in North Las Vegas crash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As nonreligious population grows, so do groups offering community...</title>
      <link>https://www.dispatch.com/story/news/2022/01/28/8-greater-columbus-groups-atheists-and-nonbelievers/6581283001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The population of atheists and nonbelievers is growing nationwide. Here are eight local groups that provide a sense of community to religious "nones."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea tests longest-range missile since '17...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-states-seoul-south-korea-north-korea-joint-chiefs-of-staff-37f273d0602f91d392d32b6c0d4002ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea on Sunday fired what appeared to be the most powerful missile it has tested since President Joe Biden took office, as it revives its old playbook in brinkmanship to wrest concessions from Washington and neighbors amid a prolonged stalemate in diplomacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 'hazmat incident' at Ohio hotel pool leaves 7 in critical condition...</title>
      <link>https://www.dispatch.com/story/news/local/2022/01/29/hampton-inn-marysville-ohio-hazmat-situation-puts-several-hospital/9271992002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine people have been taken to area hospitals following a hazmat situation in the pool area of the Hampton Inn in Marysville in Union County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don facing headwinds as he eyes comeback...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trump-facing-legal-political-headwinds-as-he-eyes-comeback-7f3da5e62e169575a27a2c6f2c319414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONROE, Texas (AP) — As he prepared to tee off at one of his Florida golf courses, a fellow player introduced Donald Trump as the “45th president of the United States.” “45th and 47th,” Trump responded matter-of-factly, before hitting his drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same-sex penguins succeed as foster parents in first for zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/jan/29/same-sex-penguins-succeed-as-foster-parents-in-first-for-new-york-zoo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Humboldt penguins, Elmer and Lima, expertly watched over an egg that hatched on New Year’s Day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sealed off: Inside 'closed loop' at Beijing Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220130-sealed-off-inside-the-closed-loop-at-the-beijing-winter-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Beijing Olympics are taking place in a strict "closed loop" with 60,000 competitors, journalists and the Chinese workforce looking after them cut off from local people and tested for Covid-19 eve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek holy men sow vax mistrust: 'Mark of Antichrist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220130-mark-of-the-antichrist-greek-holy-men-sow-vaccine-mistrust</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a remote monastery in northern Greece, an Orthodox abbot delivers a blunt message to dozens of his maskless worshippers: Covid-19 vaccines are "the mark of the Antichrist".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside campaign to pressure Justice Breyer to retire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inside-the-campaign-to-pressure-justice-stephen-breyer-to-retire/ar-AAThso3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superfans trying to save TAB...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/30/business/save-tab-soda/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In October 2020, the moment Trish Priest had been dreading arrived: Tab, the decades-old diet drink, was being killed off by parent company Coca-Cola.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sport, politics and Covid collide...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/jan/30/sport-politics-and-covid-collide-at-the-beijing-winter-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Beijing Games will open on Friday in a country that hopes sport will be the talking point. But political twists or a resurgent virus could leave the event skating on thin ice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia buildup includes blood supplies...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/exclusive-russia-moves-blood-supplies-near-ukraine-adding-us-concern-officials-2022-01-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's military buildup near Ukraine has expanded to include supplies of blood along with other medical materials that would allow it to treat casualties, in yet another key indicator of Moscow's military readiness, three U.S. officials tell Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed camera nightmare coming to America...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10455557/The-speed-camera-nightmare-thats-coming-America.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg's plan to 'promote speed safety cameras' is raising the troubling specter of ubiquitous automated traffic enforcement in the style of the UK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY RETIRES?</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33173652/tom-brady-retiring-22-seasons-seven-super-bowl-wins-new-england-patriots-tampa-bay-buccaneers-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buccaneers quarterback Tom Brady is retiring from football after 22 seasons and seven Super Bowl titles, sources told ESPN's Jeff Darlington and Adam Schefter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges: Nurses made $1.5 million off fake vax cards...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-immunizations-nyc-state-wire-2bab422118ab3e661c32898e2d2de16d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMITYVILLE, N.Y. (AP) — Two nurses on Long Island are accused of forging COVID-19 vaccination cards and pocketing more than $1.5 million from the scheme, prosecutors and police said. Julie DeVuono, the owner of Wild Child Pediatric Healthcare in Amityville, and her employee, Marissa Urraro, are both charged with felony forgery, and DeVuono also is charged with offering a false instrument for filing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest COVID mandates and restrictions in Ottawa...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-justin-trudeau-canada-45778ef0bdca45501411fb21066c46a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA, Ontario (AP) — Thousands of protesters gathered in Canada’s capital on Saturday to protest vaccine mandates, masks and lockdowns. The sounds of honking horns echoed around Ottawa’s downtown core.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Republicans love Trump as they once did?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/do-republicans-love-donald-trump-as-they-once-did/ar-AAThl9S </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Technology Could Reverse Diabetes, IBS, Obesity...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/intestinal-cells-reverse-diseases-ibs-diabetes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A newly developed technology platform has the potential to treat diseases like diabetes, IBS, and obesity by using enteroendocrine (EE) cells found in human intestinal cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron sub-variant  1.5 times more contagious...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/28/the-new-bapoint2-omicron-subvariant-is-already-circulating-in-half-of-us-states.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are already 127 confirmed cases across almost half of the U.S. of a new Covid subvariant that's even more contagious than omicron.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
