<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN:  MUSK IS A TOTAL FRAUD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/21/elon-musk-is-a-total-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One disastrous tweet has finally revealed Elon Musk for what he is: a fraud. Enraged that a British cave diver called his idea to rescue the Thai soccer team for what it was — “a p.r. stunt [with] …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELLS FRIENDS:  HE'S UNFIT TO BE PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/michael-cohen-questions-trumps-fitness-to-be-president-e1ce27b0-414b-4e26-b135-4996687dc06e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things have been heating up since the tape was reported Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic researchers reverse wrinkles, gray hair and balding in mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/20/genetic-researchers-reverse-wrinkles-gray-hair-and/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science has made a mouse look good by reversing age-related wrinkles and hair loss at the genetic level. Humanity could get a similar make-over in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran transient hurled Chihuahua off 7th floor garage, jury says...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article215271300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wakeen Best, a 35-year-old homeless San Francisco woman, was found guilty of burglary and animal cruelty after throwing a Chihuahua seven stories off a parking garage during a car burglary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender Ax Attacker Blames Voices in Head, Demon Possession in Court Defense...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/transgender-ax-attacker-uses-drugs-demon-possession-to-defender-himself-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After vodka, ecstasy, and pot, the suspect heard a voice saying, "kill... and start the rise of hell on earth."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAST:  'Impeach Trump!'</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/movies/2018/07/21/fantastic-beasts-impeach-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The panel for Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald had a few surprises in store for Comic-Con's Hall H on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivers fascist speech in character ...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/johnny-depp-makes-surprise-comic-con-appearance-during-fantastic-beasts-panel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp surprised San Diego Comic-Con audiences in full character from "Fantastic Beasts," emerging after an embarrassing Rolling Stone article</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEPP FREAKOUT AT COMIC-CON...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/fantastic-beasts-new-trailer-arrives-at-comic-con-1128993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depp, dressed in character, delivered a creepy speech as Eddie Redmayne, Jude Law and Ezra Miller (as Super Mario's Toadette) looked on in Hall H.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP Poll:  Americans don't mention 'global warming' as problem...</title>
      <link>http://www.climatedepot.com/2018/07/21/new-gallup-poll-americans-do-not-even-mention-global-warming-as-a-problem-36-problems-cited-but-not-climate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba's new president names cabinet resembling Castro's...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cubas-president-names-cabinet-resembling-castros-175015115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba's new President Miguel Diaz-Canel named his cabinet on Saturday, keeping a majority of ministers from predecessor Raul Castro including in the key posts of defense, interior and foreign relations, signaling continuity rather than change. Diaz-Canel, 58, who replaced Castro in April, announced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Consultants to Get Dragged Into Manafort Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/20/democratic-consultants-to-get-dragged-into-paul-manafort-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Consultants to Get Dragged Into Paul Manafort Trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale sharks bigger than had been thought and can live 130 years, study finds...</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/whale-sharks-are-bigger-than-had-been-thought-and-can/article_71a44a50-96d1-5715-956c-a32ab69fa27b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Whale sharks, the largest of the shark species, can travel the ocean for up to 130 years and can grow as long as 61.7 feet, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba moves toward changes to officially recognize private property, foreign investment...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Cuba-moves-toward-changes-to-officially-recognize-13094090.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI - In communist Cuba, the right to own private property would be enshrined and foreign investment encouraged - and "guaranteed." Where Fidel Castro reigned as a towering 20th-century figure, power would no longer be concentrated in the hands of one ruler. Cuba's legislators are expected to take a major leap this weekend toward adopting those and other changes in the island nation's most significant bid for constitutional reform in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: Ecuador Will Imminently Withdraw Asylum for Assange...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/07/21/ecuador-will-imminently-withdraw-asylum-for-julian-assange-and-hand-him-over-to-the-uk-what-comes-next/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will journalists, due to hatred of Assange, unite behind the Trump DOJ in support of one of the gravest threats to press freedom in years?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tabloid in Middle of Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/21/us/politics/trump-michael-cohen-american-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors believe that American Media Inc. acted more as a political supporter than as a news organization as it helped Michael D. Cohen prevent embarrassing coverage of Donald J. Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked vacations gaining momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/better/pop-culture/why-travel-s-latest-trend-nacation-gaining-momentum-ncna893151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, 4.3 billion dollars was directly spent on nude travel in the state of Florida alone. Psychologists say the trend isn't surprising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation traces from Fukushima nuke disaster found in Californian wine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/718016/fukushima-nuclear-disaster-california-wine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-earning musicians mostly 'heritage artists'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/20/americas-top-earning-musicians-are-mostly-heritage-artists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You rock ’n’ rollers may be getting older — but you’re still shelling out big bucks for your favorite acts. In fact, of America’s 50 top-earning musical artists last year, 29 are considered “herita…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pampered pooch owns 3 sports cars, 175 pairs of sunglasses, 65 outfits...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/pampered-dog-owns-three-sports-12958353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Princess Cleopatra Superchill also feasts on steak for dinner and travels around in a £1,500 pram - so she doesn't get her paws dirty when out and about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare summer nor'easter expected to pound NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/21/rare-summer-noreaster-expected-to-pound-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will see heavy rainfall Saturday night as a rare July nor’easter passes through the tri-state area.​ The heaviest and steadiest rain will fall overnight and most of the city wil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia demands US release 'spy', calls charges false...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russia-demands-us-release-spy-calls-charges-false-155001279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov told his US counterpart Mike Pompeo on Saturday that the arrest of a Russian gun rights enthusiast on espionage charges in the United States was "unacceptable", his ministry said. US prosecutors say Maria Butina, 29, exploited her close links with the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super blood moon apocalypse: Bible prophecy predicts end of world 'days away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/716008/blood-moon-end-of-the-world-july-27-2018-bible-apocalypse-christian-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot human clones: Firm using 3D printers to scan, make replicas of people...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/717872/sex-robot-doll-human-clones-3d-printer-ds-doll-replicas-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midlife crisis myth? Life gets better after 50...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/jul/21/midlife-crisis-myth-life-gets-better-after-50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We don’t peak in middle age, say the experts. So forget about the stereotypes and embrace change</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Military Strides Into Politics, by Ballot or by Force; Warnings of Coup...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/21/world/americas/brazils-election-military.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scores of former officers are running for office. And if the ballot box doesn’t work, some former officials warn of a possible military coup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Dared To Speak Up For ICE -- And Audience Of Libs Ate Her Alive...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/20/ann-kirkpatrick-booed-ice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brutal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Proclaimed Superhero Takes Crime Into Own Hands; Nabs Hundreds Of Alleged Criminals...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/20/stockton-batman-fights-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s a father of two and a local business owner. The latest citizen’s arrest was caught on camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DATA FIRM WITH GOVT CONTRACTS; TRILLION-POST REPOSITORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-probing-how-analytics-firm-shares-public-user-data-1532104502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook said it was suspending analytics firm Crimson Hexagon while it investigates whether the firm’s government contracts violate Facebook policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soon have 'sex' with AMAZON Alexa...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6825412/smart-sex-toy-alexa-lovense-vibrator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON’S Alexa virtual assistant seems to be everywhere these days – and now she’s powering your sex life too. The voice-controlled AI has made its way into the popular Lovense series o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic socialism surging in age of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a1770fd620d94bf58d0ff1035d3e0eea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Last Friday, Maine Democrat Zak Ringelstein wasn't ready to consider himself a formal member of the Democratic Socialists of America, even if he appreciated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget F-35: Tempest Armed with Lasers, Hypersonic Missiles and Swarms...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/forget-f-35-tempest-could-113700344.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But will London pull the trigger?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Iran leader backs suggestion to block Gulf oil exports if own sales stopped...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/iran-nuclear-oil-khamenei/iran-leader-backs-rouhanis-suggestion-iran-to-block-gulf-oil-exports-if-own-sales-stopped-idUKL8N1UH07K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's supreme leader on Saturday backed President Hassan Rouhani's suggestion that Iran may block Gulf oil exports if its own exports are stopped, according to his official website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detention Operators Face Suits Over $1-a-Day Work Programs for Migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/detention-operators-face-suits-over-1-a-day-work-programs-for-migrants-1532170801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private prison companies face legal pressure over work programs at detention centers that pay migrants $1 a day. The companies say the workers are volunteers and the rate was set by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanks Fire on Hamas Post After Infiltration...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-fires-tank-shell-at-hamas-post-after-suspects-cross-gaza-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians flee back into Strip, no reported casualties. Incident is first violence since Hamas announced ceasefire overnight; Israelis return to normal life after latest flareup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captain told passengers NOT to don life jackets?</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2018/07/20/several-members-of-indiana-family-among-those-killed-in-branson-duck-boat-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRANSON, Missouri – Several members of an Indiana family were on a duck boat that capsized in Branson, Missouri, Thursday night, killing 17 people.  The Missouri governor's office confirmed to FOX59 that eleven members of the family, including several children, were aboard the boat and nine of them passed away in the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind closed doors, Guantanamo secret court talks about CIA, torture and rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article214381804.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A McClatchy review of declassified transcripts of Guantánamo’s national security hearings found that, after the public and death-penalty defendants are sent away, what goes on at the war court often involves the CIA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overturning Roe v. Wade would send issue back to states. Then it gets complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/article214820175.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly five decades after the U.S. Supreme Court legalized abortion, a bitter fight looms over President Donald Trump’s nominee for a new Justice and the potential for Roe v. Wade to be overturned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago named 'rat capital' of nation...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/07/20/study-chicago-rat-capital-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study names Chicago the rat capital of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas power use to keep hitting records during heat wave...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/texas-power-keep-hitting-records-during-heat-wave-153305056--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - Homes and businesses in Texas used record amounts of power for a second straight day on Thursday and are expected to use even more in coming days as consumers crank up air conditioners to escape a brutal heat wave, according to the operator of much of the state's power grid. To keep</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
