<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine mayor 'executed alongside husband &amp; son'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5045167/ukraine-mayor-executed-russians-shallow-grave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VILLAGE mayor in Ukraine was kidnapped, executed and dumped in a forest pit along with her husband and son, reports claim. Neighbours said Russian troops occupying Motyzhyn, 30 miles west of Kyiv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Poor Sleep Linked To More Belly Fat...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sleeping-less-more-belly-fat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studies recommend adults sleep 7 to 9 hours a night. However, over one-third of adults living in the United States get less than that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHA ATROCITIES SHOCK WORLD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-kyiv-business-moscow-3a40c029638ffddb289ceba89462c1aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUCHA, Ukraine (AP) — Russia faced a fresh wave of condemnation on Monday after evidence emerged of what appeared to be deliberate killings of civilians in Ukraine. Some Western leaders called for further sanctions in response, even as Moscow continued to press its offensive  in the country's east.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Abortion Underground...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2022/05/roe-v-wade-overturn-abortion-rights/629366/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A covert network of activists is preparing for a post-Roe future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Privately Considers FOXNEWS 'One of Most Destructive Forces' in Nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/joe-biden-privately-considers-fox-news-as-one-of-the-most-destructive-forces-in-the-nation-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An upcoming book says President Joe Biden has been privately making a series of very negative comments about Fox News and their chairman: Rupert Murdoch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massacre tests Europe's 'red lines' on Russian energy...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Bucha-massacre-tests-Europe-s-red-lines-on-17055744.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe is united in its outrage over evidence of alleged Russian atrocities in Ukraine....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mourners rave beside rapper's embalmed body at club...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5045776/goonew-body-propped-nightclub-mourners-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIZARRE footage circulating online appears to show mourners raving alongside the rapper Goonew at his funeral. An event titled The Final Show Goonew was held at Bliss nightclub in Washington DC on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New COVID Variant Most Unpredictable One Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-ba2-covid-variant-sweeping-asia-and-europe-is-the-most-unpredictable-one-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts are baffled as to why the BA.2 COVID variant is running completely rampant in some countries while sparing others with softer blows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Decline Cases Double in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cognitive-decline-cases-double/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research from England finds the number of cases of cognitive decline more than doubled in ten years, increasing the likelihood of dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pills next big abortion battleground...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/abortion-pills-battleground-b5be382d-8ea7-4046-8bd1-ae58ffda702c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the U.S. Supreme Court considers a potential end to Roe v. Wade, "abortion pills" are seen as the next major battleground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA seizes yacht owned by oligarch with close ties to Putin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-war-oligarch-yacht-seized-e8415972392839f818c5505aa93fc8a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALMA DE MALLORCA, Spain (AP) — The U.S. government seized a mega yacht in Spain owned by an oligarch with close ties to the Russian president on Monday, the first in the government’s sanctions enforcement initiative to “seize and freeze” giant boats and other pricey assets of Russian elites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Takes 9.2% Stake in TWITTER After Hinting at Shake-Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/musk-takes-9-2-stake-in-twitter-after-questioning-platform</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk Takes 9.2% Stake in Twitter After Hinting at Shake-Up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing sends in military to help with Shanghai outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-china-shanghai-b14704a20590535969a5687b26f9e200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China has sent more than 10,000 health workers from around the country to Shanghai, including 2,000 from the military, as it struggles to stamp out a rapidly spreading outbreak in its largest city under its zero-COVID strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrors Push Europe Toward New Sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://nz.news.yahoo.com/eu-says-holds-russia-responsible-081840499.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nz.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The European Union said that work is under way on additional sanctions to penalize Russia for what appear to be war crimes in Ukraine, as it condemned the alleged atrocities committed against civilians.Most Read from BloombergA 30-Year-Old Crypto Billionaire Wants to Give His Fortune AwayChina Finds New Virus Subtype as Daily Cases Exceed 13,000Ukraine Update: Kyiv Warns Russia Is Adding Troops in MoldovaUkraine Update: More Talks Possible Even as Bucha Outrage GrowsWhat If Fox Ne</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Election Opens Up as Le Pen Surges...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/04/french-election-opens-up-as-marine-le-pen-surges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — At last, Emmanuel Macron stepped forth. The French president entered a vast arena this weekend, plunged into darkness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flurry of New Laws Move Blue and Red States Further Apart...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/03/flurry-of-new-laws-move-blue-and-red-states-further-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — After the governor of Texas ordered state agencies to investigate parents for child abuse if they provide certain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service paying $30K per month for Malibu mansion to protect Hunter Biden...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/secret-service-paying-30k-month-malibu-mansion-protect/story?id=83821498</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Secret Service detail protecting Hunter Biden has been paying more than $30,000 a month for a swanky Malibu mansion close to Biden's home, sources tell ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Covid Crisis Grows With Cases Surging, New Sub-Variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-covid-crisis-grows-with-cases-surging-new-sub-strains/ar-AAVOX0W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem anxiety grows over Biden's dismal polls...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/3256844-democratic-anxiety-grows-over-bidens-dismal-polls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are growing increasingly worried about President Biden’s standing in the polls seven months out from the midterm elections.   Biden hasn’t seen a boost in his approval ratings a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Claims He's Being  Censored on Trump 'Free-Speech' App...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/roger-stone-claims-hes-being-censored-on-trumps-truth-social</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stone is the most high-profile MAGA character to claim he’s being silenced on the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama set for White House return...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/obama-return-white-house-celebrate-health-care-reform-rcna22762</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first visit since he left office, the former president will appear alongside Biden and Harris to promote the success of the Affordable Care Act, a White House official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Covid Crisis Grows With Cases Surging, New Sub-Variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-covid-crisis-grows-with-cases-surging-new-sub-strains/ar-AAVOX0W?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence of War Crimes as Russians Retreat From Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/horror-mass-killings-ukraine-men-26621558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC IMAGES: As Russian forces withdraw from the areas around the Ukrainian capital of Kyiv, some of the horrors of what they have done are being revealed with bodies being discovered littering the streets of towns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ:  Zelensky  makes surprise Grammys appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10682607/Were-going-keeping-peoples-names-mouths-Trevor-Noah-mocks-Smith-Grammys.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zelensky made a surprise appearance, saying: 'Our musicians wear body armor instead of tuxedos.' He added: 'Fill the silence with your music. Fill it today to tell our story.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Bodies of four people killed in Sacramento bar-fight shooting still lying on street 15 hours later...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10682399/PICTURED-Married-dad-38-man-29-six-killed-Sacramento-bar-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A married father-of-three and much-loved son have been named as two of the six people killed in a mass-shooting outside a Sacramento bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORBAN LANDSLIDE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-viktor-orban-europe-nato-budapest-e29b5d42a86086bb65b413e2b6d1c2bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUDAPEST, Hungary (AP) — Prime Minister Viktor Orban declared victory in Sunday's national elections, claiming a mandate for a fourth term as a partial vote count predicted a strong lead for his right-wing party.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
