<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower Allegations From Inside CA's New Billion Dollar Testing Lab; Swabs Found In Restrooms...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/02/08/whistleblower-allegations-california-covid-testing-lab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lab techs sleeping while processing COVID samples for testing. COVID test swabs found in the restrooms. These are just two of the concerning allegations from whistleblowers about what's happening inside the state’s new billion-dollar COVID testing lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX congressman dies after covid battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/arlington/article249092395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Rep. Ron Wright, known as a staunch conservative and member of the Freedom Caucus, died Sunday after a battle with COVID-19. He was 67.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church Of Scientology Spot Stuns Viewers; 'Dare To Think For Yourself'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/news/super-bowl-scientology-ad-fans-cant-believe-commercial-ran-during-big-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Kansas City Chiefs and the Tampa Bay Buccaneers battled it out on the field for the [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China, Iran to hold joint naval drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/russia-china-and-iran-to-hold-joint-naval-drills-in-indian-ocean-soon-658242</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astrophotographer captures incredible footage of jet photobombing Sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9236207/Photographer-captures-United-Airlines-plane-photobombing-Sun.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California-based astrophotographer has captured 'one-in-a-million' footage of a United Airlines plane photobombing the Sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers blast 'political theater'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-impeachment-40ef81572403c82422464169e67554d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Lawyers for Donald Trump on Monday blasted the impeachment case against him as an act of “political theater” by Democrats, whom they accused of exploiting for their own party’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery disease which 'causes people to throw up blood' kills 'at least 15 victims'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mystery-disease-causes-people-throw-23463535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health official claimed the strange disease emerged in the Chunya district in the Mbeye region of Tanzania and said experts were investigating – but she was later suspended. An outbreak has been ruled out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Capitol on Jan. 6, Vets Fought on Both Sides of Battle...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/08/at-the-capitol-on-jan-6-veterans-fought-on-both-sides-of-an-american-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As Samuel Hahn of the Metropolitan Police Department struggled to hold back rioters storming the Capitol on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish man strikes up 37-year friendship with swan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-turkey-friendships-animals-4f953fb187d21593775156f9e37964c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDIRNE, Turkey (AP) — An unusual friendship between a Turkish man and a swan he rescued has endured for decades. Retired postman Recep Mirzan found Garip, a female swan, 37 years ago in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His Biz Shunned, She Resigned, Everyone Sued: What Became of Trump Election Dead-Enders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/what-became-of-trumps-election-dead-enders-his-biz-is-shunned-she-resigned-and-everyone-is-being-sued</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the current ruin of Trump's hardcore election dead-enders came as a direct result of their decisions to become major players in Trump’s failed endeavor to cling to power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen apologizes to Stormy Daniels for 'needless pain'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/537776-michael-cohen-apologizes-to-stormy-daniels-for-needless-pain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump's onetime fixer and personal attorney Michael Cohen has apologized to adult-film star Stormy Daniels for the pain he says he caused her while working for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracy theories hang over county plans to buy voting machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/conspiracy-theories-hang-over-a-trump-loving-county-e2-80-99s-plans-to-buy-dominion-voting-machines/ar-BB1duGgq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The situation in Stark County is a testament to how viral claims repeatedly debunked by courts and authorities have persisted, hanging over local decision-making and saddling officials with the daunting task of somehow rebuilding public trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As alcohol abuse rises, hospitals see wave of deadly liver disease...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/alcohol-abuse-rises-amid-pandemic-130030403.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UCLA, USC and hospitals nationwide are treating more patients for alcoholic hepatitis, cirrhosis and other conditions amid COVID-19 shutdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Few say democracy working well...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-biden-cabinet-democracy-elections-only-on-ap-403434c2e728e42a955c72a652a59318</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Only a fragment of Americans believe democracy is thriving in the U.S., even as broad majorities agree that representative government is one of the country's bedrock principles,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE IS ON: First of three Mars missions ready to arrive...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/02/08/First-of-three-Mars-missions-ready-to-arrive/9341612466213/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new era of Mars exploration begins Monday with the expected arrival of the United Arab Emirates' Hope spacecraft in vicinity of the Red Planet -- the first of three such arrivals planned for February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unleashed Bezos will shift space venture into hyperdrive...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unleashed-jeff-bezos-seek-shift-120913932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freed from his daily obligations at Amazon.com Inc, Jeff Bezos is expected to turn up the heat on his space venture, Blue Origin, as it faces a pivotal year and fierce competition from Elon Musk's SpaceX, industry sources said. The 57-year-old Bezos, a lifelong space enthusiast and the world's second-richest person behind Musk, said last week he is stepping down as chief executive of the e-commerce company as he looks to focus on personal projects. Blue Origin has fallen far behind SpaceX on orbital transportation, and lost out to SpaceX and United Launch Alliance (ULA) on billions of dollars' worth of U.S. national security launch contracts which begin in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic line judges make Grand Slam debut...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cannot-serious-electronic-line-judges-083755583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The days of tennis players arguing whether balls are in or out could be coming to a close, after the smooth introduction of electronic line judging at the Australian Open on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu walks out on his own corruption trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-e2-80-99s-netanyahu-walks-out-on-his-own-corruption-trial/ar-BB1duCPy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli leader was summoned to court for the second phase of hearings, just weeks before elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Hastens Exit from Israel's Ultra-Orthodox Community...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/08/virus-hastens-exit-from-israels-ultra-orthodox-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — When the coronavirus pandemic swept through Israel, it upended Racheli Ohayon’s life in unexpected ways. The 21-year-old phone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of maskless Tampa fans flood streets, risking superspreader event...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/thousands-of-maskless-tampa-fans-flooded-the-streets-celebrating-the-super-bowl-win-while-risking-a-superspreader-event/ar-BB1duDel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hordes of football fans crammed into bars, clogged up streets and belted chants from their uncovered mouths in Tampa this weekend, defying pleas from public health experts to help stop the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like GAMESTOP, BED BATH &amp; BEYOND reduced to stock meme. But 42,000 people work there...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Like-GameStop-Bed-Bath-amp-Beyond-has-been-15932853.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching short sellers duke it out with Reddit- and Robinhood-inspired buyers over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY SCHOOLS THE CHILDREN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-new-england-patriots-football-7418cec28100392206508c6a1496cb39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — So much of it looked familiar — from the heartfelt rendering of the national anthem, to the silvery, star-studded halftime show, to Tom Brady standing there at the end with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial to open with sense of urgency, speed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-trials-acquittals-40ef81572403c82422464169e67554d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump's historic second impeachment trial is opening this week with a sense of urgency — by Democrats who want to hold the former president accountable for the violent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense team will show clips of Dems urging violence in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/6/trumps-defense-team-will-show-clips-democrats-urgi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s defense at his Senate impeachment trial next week will include videos of Democrats encouraging violence, one of his lawyers said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Commercial Draws Heat...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cure-auto-insurance-draws-heat-for-offensive-super-bowl-spot-casually-joking-about-workplace-harassment-ad-fail-of-the-decade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Super Bowl ad from Cure Auto Insurance is drawing criticism for belittling the seriousness of workplace harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moment of Silence For Covid Victims Booed...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/news/joe-biden-super-bowl-moment-silence-garners-boos-crowd-surprising-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Super Bowl LV is underway, and fans can watch the game for free. Before the big game, President [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY SCHOOLS THE CHILDREN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-football-super-bowl-fbabcae4076a95ad2ba653d72e5a8a10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on Super Bowl 55 (All times EST): ___ 9:05 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder at Yale...</title>
      <link>http://www.newhavenindependent.org/index.php/archives/entry/homicide_in_east_rock/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newhavenindependent.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Updated) A week after his marriage engagement, a 26-year-old Yale forestry graduate student was shot to death Saturday night in the Goatville section of the East Rock neighborhood, the city’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Reporter Aghast at Maskless, Drunk Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/cnn-reporter-aghast-at-maskless-drunk-super-bowl-crowds-in-tampa-i-asked-the-police-what-are-you-doing-about-this/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN reporter Randi Kaye found herself shocked, shocked to find that Super Bowl crowds were drinking in Tampa before the big game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS HAVE HIS BACK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-censures-roger-wicker-trials-05bdcc3475e661077295627bac922ebd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump’s defenders in the Senate on Sunday rallied around the former president before his impeachment trial, dismissing it as a waste of time and arguing that the former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioters' words loom large in President's role in attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/7/trump-supporters-words-capitol-riot-loom-large-ahe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the former president prepared to face his second impeachment trial this week, the words of his supporters, captured in court documents, are looming large as senators try to place blame for the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B.1.1.7  spreading rapidly through USA, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/U-K-coronavirus-variant-spreading-rapidly-15931664.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus variant that shut down much of the United Kingdom is spreading rapidly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Months after contracting covid, some will try anything to regain their sense of smell!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/months-contracting-covid-19-try-130043115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Loss of smell is a common symptom of COVID-19, and about 10% of patients suffer from long-term smell dysfunction. Can the nose be retrained to detect odors correctly?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There is only relentless pursuit of perfection'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/07/tom-brady-intense-pump-up-video-super-bowl-once-more-into-the-fray/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Tom Brady's most cherished traditions in recent years has involved a well-made pump-up video for big games. Super Bowl LV will be no exception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More people choose to die at home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-pandemics-michael-brown-coronavirus-pandemic-nursing-homes-3e51d0fe283d3075fcecf413f8ad8ae3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — Mortuary owner Brian Simmons has been making more trips to homes to pick up bodies to be cremated and embalmed since the pandemic hit. With COVID-19 devastating...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope greets public again with wide distancing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-pandemics-israel-super-bowl-football-6e3df11b3ff68134a02cd597ff4b3054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG — South Africa has suspended plans to inoculate its front-line health care workers with the AstraZeneca vaccine after a small clinical trial suggested that it isn’t effective in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial brings reckoning even if acquittal likely...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-trials-impeachments-trump-impeachment-michael-pence-187a66133bc8932db712d71f6ef714a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — This matters. The outcome may seem preordained in the unprecedented second impeachment trial of Donald Trump.  Democrats prosecuting the former president for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial brings reckoning even if acquittal likely...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/trump-s-trial-brings-a-reckoning-even-if-acquittal-is-likely/article_3c74c449-60a4-576c-9769-45cba3de155a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s second impeachment trial is almost certain to end in acquittal, yet it will deliver a public reckoning for his presidency and influence whether his populist supporters continue to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KC 52.1% CHANCE OF WINNING</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/game/_/gameId/401220403</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get a summary of the Kansas City Chiefs vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers football game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE STREAM</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/superbowl/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the Kansas City Chiefs vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers in Super Bowl LV on February 7, 2021. See the official broadcast live from Raymond James Stadium in Tampa, Florida right here on CBSSports.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/super-bowl-2021-chiefs-vs-buccaneers-live-updates-start-time-kickoff-live-stream-online-odds-spread/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Live coverage of the lead up to Super Bowl LV as Kansas City and Tampa Bay battle for the championship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE SHULTZ DEAD AT 100...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/george-shultz-secretary-state-shaped-175328917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George P. Shultz, who as secretary of State in the 1980s shaped U.S. foreign policy in the closing phase of the Cold War, died Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Shultz dies at 100...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2288159/george-shultz-dead-secretary-state-under-ronald-reagan-100/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER Secretary of state George Shultz has died at the age of 100. He led President Ronald Reagan’s efforts against the Soviet Union during the Cold War. The Hoover Institution, of which Shu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' Skewers 'Former Social Media Influencer'...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/02/06/snl-skewers-joe-biden-and-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Jost mocked Joe Biden's memory lapses and Donald Trump's absence from Twitter during the 'Weekend Update' portion of 'SNL.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest win: In 2020, NFL found ways to play every game...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-football-coronavirus-pandemic-71defaceb1b8c4b12781bc8ae7277801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than the youth of Patrick Mahomes or the agelessness of Tom Brady, the most compelling story surrounding this year’s Super Bowl was that it was happening at all. It took nearly 1...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
