<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Noah's Ark replica faces dilemma of biblical proportions...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/noahs-ark-replica-faces-costly-dilemma-of-biblical-proportions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This ark might need a miracle to get back home. A replica of Noah’s Ark has been stranded in the United Kingdom for a year and a half and his facing $700-a-day fines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms 1st Muslim American federal judge in US history...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/senate-confirms-1st-muslim-american-federal-judge-us/story?id=78206834</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zahid Quraish is the first Muslim American federal judge to be confirmed by the United States Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Detects Suicidal Thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/app-suicide-risk-sound-of-voice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Carol Espy-Wilson says the coordination of someone's speech gestures reflects their mental health status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNGER GAMES:  Zuckerberg goes wild boar hunting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9674091/Zuckerberg-seen-camo-carrying-bow-arrows-Hawaii-danger-hike.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg and his wife Priscilla own property in Hawaii and have plans to expand on it to create a compound-like home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3rd FDA expert resigns over controversial Alzheimer's drug decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/10/third-member-of-fda-expert-committee-resigns-over-controversial-alzheimers-therapy-decision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kesselheim wrote that the approval of Biogen’s Aduhelm “was probably the worst drug approval decision in recent U.S. history.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unanswered 'JEOPARDY!' question: Who's the new host?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-b15ea28c004f905a24c0a8936f7797df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — “Jeopardy!” needed a host, and Lucille Ball had an enthusiastic suggestion for creator Merv Griffin: The smooth-voiced, debonair emcee of the “High Rollers” game show. That was 1984.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory water rules hit Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Santa-Clara-Bay-Area-water-restrictions-drought-16235537.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is sinking into a drought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt for current year hits record $2.1 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-joe-biden-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-00d83a1898855edb9abcde733b97c158</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. budget deficit hit a record $2.06 trillion through the first eight months of this budget year as coronavirus relief programs drove spending to all-time highs. The shortfall this year is 9.7% higher than the $1.88 trillion deficit run up over the same period a year ago, the Treasury Department said Thursday in its monthly budget report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toobin Returns to CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-jeffrey-toobin-returns-to-cnn-to-break-silence-on-moronic-and-indefensible-zoom-masturbation-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN chief legal analyst Jeffrey Toobin has returned to the network following a 8-month absence after being caught masturbating during a Zoom call with his colleagues from the New Yorker. In his return segment to the network, Toobin was confronted by CNN Newsroom anchor Alisyn Camerota — who summarized the events that led to his […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has been 'miserable in therapy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9674023/Jeffrey-Toobin-CNN-months-exposing-Zoom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Toobin was fired from his longtime writing gig at the New Yorker magazine last October after he exposed himself to colleagues during the video call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College linebacker accused of beating man to death over TINDER catfishing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/virginia-tech-linebacker-isimemen-etute-accused-of-fatally-beating-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freshman Virginia Tech linebacker charged with murder told cops he fatally beat a man – breaking every bone in his face – for catfishing him on Tinder, prosecutors said. Isimemen David Etute, 18,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, CLIVE! GELDOF PLANS COVID LIVE AID CONCERT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/live-aid-set-comeback-battle-24293459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE Global gig Live Aid could be set to make a huge comeback to help combat coronavirus, as Sir Bob Geldof has dropped a huge hint that he is making plans for its return</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EA breached -- game source code, tools stolen...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/10/tech/electronic-arts-hack/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers have broken into the systems of Electronic Arts, one of the world's biggest video game publishers, and stolen source code used in company games, a spokesperson confirmed to CNN Business on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penthouse sales sky-high in NYC again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/10/gimme-we-hear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gotham penthouse sky pads are having a moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More kids go down 'deep, dark tunnel.' Docs still can't predict who is at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/10/as-more-kids-get-long-covid-doctors-still-cant-predict-who-is-at-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More children and adolescents are experiencing chronic symptoms after Covid-19 even as the pandemic ebbs in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How primates aid fight against Covid in Louisiana...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610155949-ic1vp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PRIMATES (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-How primates are aiding the fight against COVID-19 in Louisiana</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pursued wives of franchisees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/subways-cofounder-pursued-franchisees-wives-appeared-in-a-shirtless-calendar-and-had-a-secret-adopted-child/ar-AAKUSa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subway's current problems are inextricable from the strategies co-founder Fred DeLuca used to build the chain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu pledges 'peaceful transition of power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/netanyahu-trump-transition-power-election-fraud-1cd7e7c6-6f25-4a26-98d0-f1e0f182e905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu says he's facing "the fraud of the century."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pursued wives of franchisees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/subways-cofounder-pursued-franchisees-wives-appeared-in-a-shirtless-calendar-and-had-a-secret-adopted-child/ar-AAKUSa8?ocid=BingNewsSearch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subway's current problems are inextricable from the strategies co-founder Fred DeLuca used to build the chain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid outbreak among staff at St Ives hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cornwalllive.com/news/cornwall-news/covid-outbreak-among-staff-st-5508053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cornwalllive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just around the corner, preparations are being made for world leaders to arrive in Cornwall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. general: China hiking military capability at 'very serious rate'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610125434-y5oef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CHINA/PENTAGON (URGENT):U.S. general: China hiking military capability at "very serious and sustained rate"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Explains Why So Little on $152 Billion Fortune!</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/06/elon-musk-react-propublica-billionaire-federal-income-tax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He responded to an initial ProPublica query with a lone punctuation mark: “?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DON IN DANGER:  Mueller prosecutor says Manhattan DA may have 'insider' in Trump criminal case...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/mueller-prosecutor-manhattan-district-attorney-insider-trump-criminal-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan prosecutors may have found their "insider" as a grand jury considers whether charges are warranted against former President Donald Trump, according to a top prosecutor in Robert Mueller's special counsel investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laughing Gas Quickly Relieves Depression?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/laughing-gas-treat-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say small doses of laughing gas rapidly improve symptoms of depression in a single session for patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP, UP AND AWAY:  Inflation Fastest Since '08...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/prices-rose-5-percent-in-may-over-the-past-year-as-recovery-continues/ar-AAKUgFq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most recent crop of inflation figures are unlikely to rattle the Biden administration or Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading candidate for NYC mayor --  accused of living in NJ!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/emotional-eric-adams-says-he-lives-in-brooklyn-despite-owning-a-condo-in-fort-lee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Adams acknowledges that he must cross a bridge to get to City Hall from his primary residence, but it's the Brooklyn Bridge, not the George Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK issues dire economic warning for America...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/557743-deutsche-bank-issues-dire-economic-warning-for-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the U.S. economy descends into an inflation spiral like that experienced after World War II, we could be on the brink of excruciating economic pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians find new unity in struggle against Israel...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/palestinians-unity-struggle-against-israel-220512358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israel-Hamas war has helped catalyze a newfound sense of Palestinian solidarity that could mark a new moment in the Middle East, activists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House antitrust panel introducing five anti-Big Tech bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/house-antitrust-panel-expected-introduce-5-anti-big-tech-bills-monopoly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic chairman of the House antitrust panel is expected to introduce five bipartisan bills to rein in Big Tech platforms such as Amazon, Facebook, and Google through new anti-monopoly legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked ISIS gunman went from 'bed to bed' executing workers at Prince Harry's landmine charity...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3053851/gunman-execute-landmine-workers-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARKED ISIS gunman reportedly went “bed to bed” executing workers during the bloody attack on a British landmine charity backed by Prince Harry. Ten people were killed and 16 others wer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Castle where leaders are staying...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/travel/3053553/cornwall-g7-summit-tregenna-castle-inside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORLD leaders have headed to Cornwall this week for the G7 Summit, being hosted in the tiny village of Carbis Bay. Leaders from Canada, France, Germany, Italy, Japan, the UK and the US are to discu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fentanyl seizures skyrocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fentanyl-seizures-texas-mexico-border-immigration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year, fentanyl seizures have jumped 800% in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming heat wave could push Phoenix, Vegas temps to 115&amp;#8457;...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/looming-heat-wave-could-push-phoenix-vegas-temps-to-115-f/960027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters say temperatures will routinely reach well into the triple digits, with one desert location poised to make a run at 125 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Harris gets tough reviews over border on first foreign trip...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/politics/kamala-harris-biden-border-2024/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first six-ish months of Kamala Harris' time as vice president have, generally speaking, gone according to her plan. She's been a consistent messenger for President Joe Biden while learning the possibilities (and limitations) that come with being second-in-command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crosssings continue to soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/u-apprehensions-migrants-crossing-border-100038933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly released data show that migrants were stopped 180,034 times across the southern border in May, nearly eight times the total a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearing mask may go from symbol of responsibility to vulnerability...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wearing-mask-could-sign-caution-120034163.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With California's full economic reopening days away, there remains one question in many people's minds: To mask, or not to mask?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trafficking Charity's Carefully Crafted Public Image Falling Apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qj8j3v/operation-underground-railroad-criminal-investigation-human-trafficking-tim-ballard-jim-caviezel-qanon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators, a staff exodus, and a disastrous appearance at a conspiracy conference have the anti-trafficking charity facing unprecedented pressure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Returns Strict Covid Restrictions to Fight New Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-returns-to-its-strict-covid-restrictions-to-fight-a-new-outbreak/ar-AAKRR89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING — Neighborhoods under strict lockdown. Thousands quarantined. Millions tested in mere days. Overseas arrivals locked up for weeks and sometimes months. China has followed variations of that formula for dealing with the coronavirus for more than a year — and a new outbreak suggests that they could be part of Chinese life for some time to come. China appeared to get the coronavirus under control nearly a year ago. But hundreds of millions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Meeting 'Not About Friendship'...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jackbrewster/2021/06/10/biden-putin-meeting-not-about-friendship-white-house-says-as-cyber-attacks-strain-relations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We want to move to a more stable and more predictable relationship” with Russia, White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just tip of iceberg?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/557688-are-the-recent-cyberattacks-just-the-tip-of-the-iceberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporations are getting better at fending off cyber attacks, but bad actors are also getting better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran sends warships to Atlantic amid Venezuela concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-10b8da94fa9040ec6348a7b7006d879b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — An Iranian destroyer and support vessel are now sailing in the Atlantic Ocean in a rare mission far from the Islamic Republic, Iran's state TV reported on Thursday, without offering the vessels’ final destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food allergies complicate hungry Americans' search for meals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/food-allergies-health-allergies-coronavirus-pandemic-8da1963de9355b4d375f9955265689bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, California (AP) — When Emily Brown, a Kansas City mother, couldn’t find foods that her 2-year-old with multiple food allergies could eat at a local food pantry, she mustered up the courage to ask about gluten-free foods or dairy alternatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supersonic Aircraft Off San Diego Coincided With Mysterious 'Skyquake'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41003/mysterious-skyquake-coincides-with-supersonic-aircraft-tracked-off-san-diego</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are strong indications that a mysterious boom heard in and around San Diego was from a supersonic aircraft on a training mission off the coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrations (and questions) greet US vaccine donation plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-asia-g-7-summit-coronavirus-pandemic-business-8ce6cca4689cce38a81e2cc8a790edb6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE TOWN, South Africa (AP) — Health officials and experts around the world on Thursday welcomed a U.S. plan to donate 500 million more COVID-19 vaccines to developing countries, but the celebrations came with hesitation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huma Abedin, longtime Clinton aide, has book deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-ny-state-wire-huma-abedin-hillary-clinton-entertainment-2aa92ed7007938ba9aebe590c57409ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Huma Abedin, the close aide to Hillary Clinton and estranged wife of disgraced former Rep. Anthony Weiner, has a memoir coming out this fall. Abedin's “Both/And: A Life in Many Worlds” will be released Nov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS: USA image abroad has rebounded...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-canada-europe-government-and-politics-5c93e6c016c59f68f53a7569d361f983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States' image around the world has improved sharply since President Joe Biden took office , according to new surveys conducted in 16 countries, including many long-standing allies of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acropolis now: Greeks outraged at concreting of ancient site...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/10/acropolis-now-greeks-outraged-at-concreting-of-ancient-site</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Installation of new pathway and lift has been criticised by archaeologists and called ‘a scandal’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Homeowners $2 trillion richer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/10/homeowners-got-2-trillion-richer-during-first-three-months-of-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home prices have been soaring, so homeowners have been getting richer, at least on paper. The equity numbers are staggering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang Of Thieves Swarm LOUIS VUITTON Store, Swipe $100K In Handbags...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/09/thieves-steal-louis-vuitton-handbags-purses-palo-alto-stanford-shopping-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a dozen thieves working together swarmed into a Louis Vuitton store in Palo Alto, stealing more than $100,000 in handbags in the second such theft at the Stanford Shopping Center in three weeks, police said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Millions struggle through life with few to trust...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-459178f46ca2c62d6b6ad51517bada81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Karen Glidden's loneliness became unbearable during the coronavirus pandemic . The 72-year-old widow, who suffers from vision loss and diabetes and lives far from any relatives, barely left her house in Champion, Michigan, this past year, for fear of contracting the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL BRANSON BEAT BEZOS?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/15212243/richard-branson-jeff-bezos-space-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT could be a battle of the billionaires to see who can launch themselves into space first as Richard Branson could beat Jeff Bezos. The Amazon CEO announced this week that he and his brother would…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds DOJ pledge on journalist records...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/557683-mystery-surrounds-justices-pledge-on-journalist-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department’s pledge that it will no longer secretly obtain the records of journalists has left a number of unanswered questions about the department’s handling of leak investigations initiated under the Trump-era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have Echo Device? AMAZON May Help Itself to Your Wi-Fi...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2021-06-09/have-an-echo-device-amazon-may-help-itself-to-your-wi-fi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you own an Amazon smart device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is She Being Set Up to Fail?</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2021/06/harris-biden-immigration-voting-rights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president has been assigned to lead on the issues the White House finds particularly challenging. What does this bode for her political future?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era of robot war may be underway unnoticed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610093118-1xf7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPS-DRONES/ (COLUMN, PIX):COLUMN-New era of robot war may be underway unnoticed: Peter Apps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoover Dam reservoir record low...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610085045-9uvq6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DROUGHT/ (PIX, GRAPHIC):Hoover Dam reservoir hits record low, in sign of extreme western U.S. drought</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket on pad, China ready to send 1st crew to space station...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-science-7fa5ef676c9c4725579cf91443bd4564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The rocket that will send the first crew members to live on China's new orbiting space station has been moved onto the launch pad ahead of its planned blastoff next week. The three astronauts plan to spend three months on the space station doing spacewalks, construction and maintenance work and science experiments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new guy? Joe debuts at democracy's most exclusive club...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-canada-europe-g-7-summit-52469dff2d3e135a89c352589e2908de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Angela, Boris, Emmanuel, Justin, Mario, Yoshihide and a relative newcomer: Joe. They’re the board of global democracy’s most exclusive club, and they’re meeting this week after four years of U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattack Forces College to Cancel Classes for Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3aqaa8/hackers-force-iowa-college-to-cancel-classes-for-four-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “cyberattack” is disrupting classes at the Des Moines Area Community College, where the school has cancelled in-person classes for four days and counting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un weight loss could have consequences...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kim-jong-un-appears-to-have-lost-some-weight-e2-80-94-and-that-could-have-geopolitical-consequences/ar-AAKTQVc </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of mysterious fast radio bursts detected in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/world/fast-radio-bursts-chime-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists used the CHIME radio telescope in Canada to detect 535 mysterious fast radio bursts in space over the course of a year. These bursts could be used to map the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador to use energy from volcanoes for bitcoin mining...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/el-salvador-energy-volcanoes-bitcoin-082346002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country’s President tweeted plans to build full bitcoin mining hub powered by geothermal energy from volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery malware steals 26M passwords from 3M PCs...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/06/nameless-malware-collects-1-2tb-of-sensitive-data-and-stashes-it-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Massive trove can be used for ransomware, espionage, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden personal diplomacy to be tested by allies -- and adversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-personal-diplomacy-to-be-tested-by-allies-e2-80-94-and-one-adversary-e2-80-94-on-his-first-trip-abroad/ar-AAKSCHZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden, on his first foreign trip as president, plans to reassert U.S. global leadership and let Russian President Vladimir Putin “know what I want him to know.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pursued CNN reporter records in secret court battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/politics/trump-pursuit-cnn-reporter-records-secret-court-battle/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration battled with CNN for half a year to obtain the email records of a reporter and insisted it all take place under an extraordinary order of secrecy, CNN's lead attorney revealed on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
