<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Charges: Nurses made $1.5 million off fake vax cards...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-immunizations-nyc-state-wire-2bab422118ab3e661c32898e2d2de16d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMITYVILLE, N.Y. (AP) — Two nurses on Long Island are accused of forging COVID-19 vaccination cards and pocketing more than $1.5 million from the scheme, prosecutors and police said. Julie DeVuono, the owner of Wild Child Pediatric Healthcare in Amityville, and her employee, Marissa Urraro, are both charged with felony forgery, and DeVuono also is charged with offering a false instrument for filing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest COVID mandates and restrictions in Ottawa...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-justin-trudeau-canada-45778ef0bdca45501411fb21066c46a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA, Ontario (AP) — Thousands of protesters gathered in Canada’s capital on Saturday to protest vaccine mandates, masks and lockdowns. The sounds of honking horns echoed around Ottawa’s downtown core.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Republicans love Trump as they once did?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/do-republicans-love-donald-trump-as-they-once-did/ar-AAThl9S </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Technology Could Reverse Diabetes, IBS, Obesity...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/intestinal-cells-reverse-diseases-ibs-diabetes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A newly developed technology platform has the potential to treat diseases like diabetes, IBS, and obesity by using enteroendocrine (EE) cells found in human intestinal cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron sub-variant  1.5 times more contagious...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/28/the-new-bapoint2-omicron-subvariant-is-already-circulating-in-half-of-us-states.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are already 127 confirmed cases across almost half of the U.S. of a new Covid subvariant that's even more contagious than omicron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence on invasion debated...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-and-allies-debate-the-intelligence-on-how-quickly-putin-will-order-an-invasion-of-ukraine-e2-80-94-or-whether-he-will-at-all/ar-AATh4pb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says USA plans to pay athletes to 'sabotage' Beijing Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-media-says-us-pays-athletes-disrupt-beijing-games-2022-01-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's foreign ministry and an official newspaper have accused the United States of planning to interfere with and "sabotage" the Beijing Winter Olympics by paying athletes from some countries to make half-hearted efforts in competition and to criticise China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian mother vows to take up gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220129-a-ukrainian-mother-vows-to-take-up-gun-if-russia-invades</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standing in the dining room of her Kyiv flat, mother-of-three Mariana Zhaglo pulls her long rifle out of its khaki case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Olympic bobsled team dealing with COVID 'nightmare'...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/olympics-team-usa-bobsled-dealing-with-covid-19-trouble-per-sources-022756014.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Olympics haven't even started and already Team USA is dealing with COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police attacked in at least 5 states within week. Officers being targeted?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/gma/police-attacked-least-4-us-110120536.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 10 law enforcement officers were shot or killed — most around major cities — in about a week, a byproduct of a national violent crime crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malkovich Like You've Never Seen Him Before...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/see-john-malkovich-transform-into-meryl-streep-che-guevara-albert-einstein-and-more </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ottawa set for 'massive' protest against Canada's vax mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-canada-trucking/ottawa-set-for-massive-protest-against-canadas-vaccine-mandates-idUSKBN2K308U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's capital city of Ottawa is set on Saturday for a "massive" protest against Prime Minister Justin Trudeau's COVID-19 vaccine mandates with the arrival of convoys of hundreds of vehicles from across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer dies after falling, being ignored for 9 hours on busy Paris street...</title>
      <link>https://english.elpais.com/usa/2022-01-28/photographer-rene-robert-freezes-to-death-on-busy-paris-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.elpais.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 84-year-old artist, renowned for his images of flamenco icons such as Paco de Lucía, was left on the sidewalk for hours without anyone coming to his aid after suffering a fall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS, Thriving in Unstable Places, Proves It's Still Threat...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/29/isis-thriving-in-unstable-places-proves-its-still-a-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT, Lebanon — One week after Islamic State fighters attacked a prison in northeastern Syria, where they have held out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump facing legal, political headwinds as he eyes comeback...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elections-texas-florida-donald-trump-united-states-7f3da5e62e169575a27a2c6f2c319414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONROE, Texas (AP) — As he prepared to tee off at one of his Florida golf courses, a fellow player introduced Donald Trump as the “45th president of the United States.” “45th and 47th,” Trump responded matter-of-factly, before hitting his drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas man traveled to DC to kill 'Antichrist' Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-biden-antichrist-assassination-attempt-secret-service-20220129-q4to7j27v5d6tkye5eeh5kzwfi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'There will be a miracle happening at the White House,' the suspect said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions remain over Youngkin's new tipline for 'divisive' practices in schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/questions-remain-over-youngkin-s-new-tipline-for-divisive-practices-in-virginia-schools/ar-AATg4c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS plan to scan face prompts anger in Congress, confusion among taxpayers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/irs-plan-to-scan-your-face-prompts-anger-in-congress-confusion-among-taxpayers/ar-AATco7B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split-screen pandemic: Families resume lives as hospitals overwhelmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/america-e2-80-99s-split-screen-pandemic-many-families-resume-their-lives-even-as-hospitals-are-overwhelmed/ar-AATfRZb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says he will send forces to Eastern Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zacharysmith/2022/01/28/biden-will-send-us-troops-to-eastern-europe-soon-but-not-a-lot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Russian forces mass at the Ukrainian border, 8,500 U.S. troops have been put on heightened alert for possible deployment to Eastern Europe — and President Joe Biden said Friday he’ll send a small number of troops to NATO allies “in the near term.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady retirement imminent?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-brady-retirement-decision-seen-as-imminent-by-those-close-to-qb-who-remain-convinced-hell-call-it-quits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several sources in Brady's inner circle anticipate he'll reveal his plans in the coming days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joni Mitchell removes music from SPOTIFY, joining Neil Young in protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/joni-mitchell-neil-young-spotify-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitchell, who like Young is a California-based songwriter who had much of her success in the 1970s, is the first prominent musician to join Young's effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trucker Vax Rule Brings Polarizing Protest to Canada's Capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trucker-jab-rule-brings-polarizing-protest-to-canada-s-capital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trucker Vaccine Rule Brings Polarizing Protest to Canada’s Capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion of Ukraine could drive up global food prices and spark unrest far from front lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-invasion-of-ukraine-could-drive-up-global-food-prices-and-spark-unrest-far-from-the-front-lines/ar-AATdZZs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady assistant said to be job hunting -- fueling retirement rumors...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/01/28/tom-brady-retiring-assistant-said-to-be-looking-for-a-new-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady’s longtime assistant Ben Rawitz has been talking to other top quarterbacks about work — prompting even more speculation that the star athlete is going to retire. Page Six has been t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New rules put Djokovic at risk of missing French Open...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-novak-djokovic-sports-health-french-open-74b9b748bb0ee88e52c4f4ca59f0a46c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France is tightening its vaccination rules in a way that could put Novak Djokovic at risk of missing the French Open. From Feb. 15, anyone who is not vaccinated against the coronavirus will need to show proof they tested positive for COVID-19 within the previous four months — down from the current six-month window — in order to enter sports venues in France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Targeting Election Lies Mulled by Washington Lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2022-01-28/bill-targeting-election-lies-mulled-by-washington-lawmakers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Gov. Jay Inslee is urging state lawmakers to approve a bill that would make it a crime for elected officials or candidates to knowingly lie about election outcomes if those claims result in violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus-sniffing dogs on tour with METALLICA, BLACK KEYS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/28/covid-sniffing-dogs-living-on-tour-with-metallica-black-keys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But has Snoop Dogg booked them yet? A pack of trained canines are living the rock ’n’ roll life — touring with the likes of Metallica and the Black Keys in an effort to keep the musicians and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Spending Drops With Inflation Hitting 40-Year High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-consumer-spending-drops-inflation-135649366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. inflation-adjusted consumer spending fell last month by the most since February, suggesting that Americans tempered their outlays amid the latest Covid-19 wave and the fastest inflation in nearly 40 years.Most Read from BloombergApple to Rival Square by Turning iPhones Into Payment TerminalsHow a Fox News Interview Threw the Antiwork Subreddit Into ChaosCrypto Secrecy Makes DeFi a Financial Felon’s WonderlandStocks Drop in Roller-Coaster Ride for Wall Street: Markets WrapMega</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists urge athletes to speak out at Beijing Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-sports-beijing-xi-jinping-2020-tokyo-olympics-879330e41869afcc81bfd5473fca56e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Human rights activists issued a call to action against the Beijing Olympics on Friday, imploring athletes and sponsors to speak out against what they call the “genocide games.” Speaking at an online press conference organized by the rights group Human Rights Watch, activists representing Chinese dissidents and the minority Uyghur and Tibetan populations urged international attendants to voice their opposition to China's hosting of the Games, which begin next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia loses million people in historic population fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220128-russia-loses-a-million-people-in-historic-population-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's population declined by more than one million people in 2021, the statistics agency Rosstat reported Friday, a historic drop not seen since the collapse of the Soviet Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are so many San Franciscans moving to Montana?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/sf/article/Data-shows-that-Montana-has-surged-in-popularity-16811723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montana saw the largest pandemic spike in movers from San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China county tells 'leftover' women to marry unemployed men...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/economy/china-economy/article/3165120/china-population-county-sparks-uproar-telling-leftover-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yihuang county in Jiangxi province is offering women a host of sweeteners to encourage them to marry, the latest effort by a local government to address China’s declining birth rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Secretly Bought Spyware, Explored Hacking US Phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/28/world/middleeast/israel-pegasus-spyware.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel used the NSO Group’s software as a tool of diplomacy. The F.B.I. wanted it for domestic surveillance. Then everything soured. Here are highlights of a New York Times Magazine investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for World's Most Powerful Cyberweapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-battle-for-the-world-s-most-powerful-cyberweapon/ar-AATex5P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Adams' war against crime sparks unrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/28/adams-nypd-crime-00002011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA net neutrality law upheld...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-california-telecommunications-jerry-brown-2db073ce6d11c7274fd9c6291d3c411b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court has upheld California’s net neutrality law , rejecting an attempt by telecommunications industry groups to prevent the state from enforcing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside look at how 1 person can control swarm of 130 robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.popsci.com/technology/drone-swarm-control-virtual-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popsci.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usually, one person controls one drone. In this case, virtual reality and artificial intelligence allowed one person to direct a large swarm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Becomes Contagious -- Among Clams...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/contagious-cancer-spreading-clams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contagious cancers, surprisingly, aren't actually unheard of. Scientists have documented these diseases in dogs, Tasmanian devils, and various bivalves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiker falls hundreds of feet to death while taking selfie...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-21-year-old-hiker-fell-hundreds-of-feet-to-his-16812838.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Jacobson, a 21-year-old hiker from Arizona, was high up in the Superstition...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA School Calls Cops on Unvaccinated Teens...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/28/this-l-a-school-called-the-cops-on-unvaccinated-teens-who-showed-up-for-class/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When 15-year-old Ellah Nahum and a few other unvaccinated students showed up at Los Angeles' New West Charter School on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swastikas spray painted on DC's Union Station...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-amtrak-93eb06b8c1b3ee22030314c8993b103b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Vandals spray-painted dozens of swastikas on the outside of Union Station, the central hub for regional train transportation in the nation's capital. The graffiti was discovered Friday, a day after International Holocaust Remembrance Day, with crude Nazi symbols painted on columns across the front of the massive building and several clustered around the escalator entrance to the underground D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide hotline shares data with for-profit spinoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/28/suicide-hotline-silicon-valley-privacy-debates-00002617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disillusionment of a Young Presidential Official...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/the-political-scene/the-disillusionment-of-a-young-biden-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrea Flores’s efforts to roll back Trump’s immigration policies faced opposition inside and outside the White House.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
