<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UF student president faces impeachment threat over Trump Jr. visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/education/2019/11/12/uf-student-president-faces-impeachment-threat-over-trump-jr-visit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A push to oust Student Body President Michael Murphy comes after an email surfaces, suggesting he worked with the Trump campaign to bring a political speech to campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURLEY:  Are Dems building a collapsible impeachment?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/470217-are-democrats-building-a-collapsible-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The constitutional basis to remove a president from office must rest on a solid foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag queen sashays into hearings...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/drag-queen-sashays-trump-impeachment-hearings-n1081261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pissi Myles made an unexpected, and quite noticeable, appearance at Wednesday's impeachment hearings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIGHTS, CAMERA, ACTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/mag-features/adam-schiff-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mild-mannered, vegan congressman from Burbank has become the GOP’s worst nightmare—but is he tough enough to take on the Trump smear machine?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Unions Set to Go to War Over Streaming TV Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/streaming-tvs-ratings-black-box-could-lead-hollywood-guild-war-1254321</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the industry enters a direct-to-consumer era, the dearth of data beyond "self-serving marketing" metrics will play a large role in the 2020 union talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pirates attack ship in Gulf of Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/pirates-attack-ship-in-gulf-of-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican navy says two Italian crew members were wounded in an attack by armed assailants who boarded their ship in the Gulf of Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT:  LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466134-1/impeachment-hearing-william-taylor-george-kent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Intelligence Committee holds its first open hearing of the impeachment inquiry against President Trump. Lawmakers will hear testimony from William Taylor, Acting U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Plan to sacrifice Rudy...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-impeachment-republicans-rudy-giuliani-f192d64d-2bee-4597-8de8-3e0477b988de.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Rudy will be cut loose because he was rogue."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Paying Residents To Catch Feral Cats; $15 Per Feline!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/12/miami-dade-animal-services-will-pay-you-to-help-control-outdoor-cat-population/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Got too many 'community' cats running around in your neighborhood? Now, Miami-Dade County Animal Services could use your help and you could make some money in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: Man Brutally Beaten By Pack of 15 Teens...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/11/12/baltimore-violence-mayor-jack-young-reaction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brutal attack, a shooting outside of a school, and a stabbing next to the Inner Harbor- three violent attacks, and police say what they all have in common is that teenagers are involved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHIFF SHOW</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8a31b8985b14303b71836d85ffd7d0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A “solemn day” or a “show trial”? Americans and the world can decide for themselves as House Democrats let the public in to the impeachment proceedings against President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREAT FLOOD OF VENICE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2e212a874a064ce4af63dc3ffda0258e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE, Italy (AP) — The worst flooding in Venice in more than 50 years prompted calls Wednesday to better protect the historic city from rising sea levels as officials calculated hundreds of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter attacked by gator tells how he was prepared to die in swampy wilderness...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-gator-bite-victim-interview-20191113-kmjirrjhmfbdnoy56otp5vsy34-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A makeshift tourniquet fashioned out of a belt and zip ties saved a hunter's life after he was bitten by an alligator in a swampy wilderness area over the weekend, a trauma surgeon at St. Mary's Medical Center in West Palm Beach said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery objects fall from sky over Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mystery-three-objects-fall-sky-20873143</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three UFOs have been captured in a mysterious video flying above the US city of Las Vegas at night, the conspiracy theorist who took the footage has claimed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regrets I've had a few, says 'MY WAY songwriter...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/regrets-ive-had-few-says-way-songwriter-152418252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He wrote the music for "My Way", one of the world's most popular songs, but Jacques Revaux would like to mention a few of his regrets. For one, "I don't even have a photo with Frank Sinatra," the French songwriter laughed. Fewer still -- not even in France, where the credit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Ginsburg Misses Supreme Court Argument With Illness...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/justice-ginsburg-misses-supreme-court-151618343.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg missed Wednesday’s argument session with what a court spokeswoman said was a stomach virus.Chief Justice John Roberts said from the bench that Ginsburg, 86, was ”indisposed due to illness” but would participate in the two cases based on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters launch flaming arrows at police...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10336052/hong-kong-protesters-flaming-arrows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROTESTERS in Hong Kong fired flaming bows and javelins at riot cops as “murderous” clashes continued overnight. Demonstrators armed with bows and arrows launched their blazing weapons …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Apocalyptic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10335517/venice-flooding-2019-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE has declared a state of emergency after a 1.8-metre flood devastated the tourist hotspot and killed at least two people. Shocking pictures show the historic St Mark’s Basilica under wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentarian Set Out to Expose Monogamy as Sham. Then Fell in Love With Her Subject...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bara-jichova-tyson-set-out-to-expose-monogamy-as-a-sham-then-she-fell-in-love-with-her-subject </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Czech filmmaker Bara Jichova Tyson’s provocative film “Talking About Adultery” condemns what it sees as the restrictive nature of marriage. Then comes an unexpected twist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway Scorches Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-george-conway-kick-off-live-impeachment-coverage-for-msnbc-with-devastating-takedown-of-republicans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney George Conway, husband of senior Trump adviser Kellyanne Conway, kicked off MSNBC's live coverage of the impeachment of President Donald Trump with a devastating takedown of Republicans,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman's eye bursts after using phone too much...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/womans-eye-bursts-after-using-20873392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A blood vessel in the woman's retina exploded after a long session on her phone in China, causing temporary blindness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot gas prices warm up US inflation in October...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hot-gasoline-prices-warm-us-inflation-october-142502242.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flare-up in US fuel prices in October sparked the biggest bump consumer inflation in seven months, but other price gains were more modest, according to new government data Wednesday. The rise in the monthly price index was hotter than expected, bolstering the Federal Reserve's decision to pause</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK app quietly turning on people's cameras...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/11/13/facebook-app-quietly-turning-peoples-cameras-freaking-11088107/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social network assures users the creepy 'bug' has not been filming their intimate moments and uploading them to Zuck's servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lil Peep Doc Tells Familiar Story -- but Doesn't Make Less Sad...</title>
      <link>https://www.theringer.com/movies/2019/11/13/20962535/lil-peep-documentary-everybodys-everything-gustav-ahr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theringer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Everybody’s Everything" is about a promising young musician whose fame only deepened his substance abuse—a tale we’ve seen before, but like his music, Gustav Ahr’s life is well worth remembering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable news showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-13/msnbc-and-fox-news-girding-to-prosecute-and-defend-president-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impeachment inquiry into President Trump has widened a massive divide, nowhere more evident than on cable TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept faces biggest crisis since McCarthy hysteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/State-Department-faces-its-biggest-crisis-since-14831022.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As diplomats prepared to testify publicly at House impeachment hearings, the president of the American Foreign Service Association recalled another perilous era in U.S. history.  That was Sen. Joseph McCarthy's reign of hysteria in the early 1950s about supposed communists in Hollywood and the federal government - especially the State Department.  "I think it's fair to say in the past 70 years, since the McCarthy period, this is the most fraught time and the most difficult time for our members," said Eric Rubin, the president of AFSA, the union representing Foreign Service officers.  During McCarthyism, the Republican from Wisconsin wildly alleged that the State Department was infested with communists and chaired hearings to root them out.  Now, House Democrats are calling on diplomats to help uncover the truth concerning accusations that President Trump invited a foreign government into domestic affairs for his personal political benefit.  This time, unlike in the McCarthy era, Foreign Service officers are not the accused. Video showing William B. Taylor Jr., George Kent and Marie Yovanovitch on Capitol Hill for their closed-door testimony in the Ukraine matter provided images of proud, dedicated federal employees caught up in a political drama they cannot escape.  Taylor and Kent will testify publicly Wednesday, and Yovanovitch on Friday, on Trump's plan to have Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky embarrass Trump's political rival, former vice president Joe Biden, by investigating his son's activities in Ukraine.  This has plunged the diplomats into a legal predicament between the Democratic-controlled House of Representatives and the Republican-controlled White House, and leaves the association in unmapped terrain.  "Our colleagues are finding themselves...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing running 500 concentration camps?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uighur-researchers-china-running-hundreds-more-camps-181157759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uighur activists said Tuesday they have documented nearly 500 camps and prisons run by China to detain members of the ethnic group, alleging that Beijing could be holding far more than the commonly cited figure of one million people. The East Turkistan National Awakening Movement, a Washington-based</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces limits of his power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f43d4e272994e9ca321714c3974eac3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For three years, Donald Trump has unapologetically defied the conventions of the American presidency. On Wednesday, he comes face to face with the limits of his power, confronting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski leaves movie premiere in Paris by side door following protests...</title>
      <link>https://uk.movies.yahoo.com/roman-polanski-leaves-movie-premiere-in-paris-by-side-door-following-protests-130334639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roman Polanski made a swift exit from a back door at the premiere of his new movie in Paris last night, following angry protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy dogs headed to Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/470179-therapy-dogs-slated-to-visit-capitol-hill-today</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cuddly canines are coming to the rescue of stressed-out Capitol Hill staffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Nears Defining Hour as Impeachment Goes Public...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-nears-defining-hour-case-104512848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Balance of Power newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Politics on Twitter and Facebook for more.Congressional Democrats have a tall order ahead.Their challenge, at the start of public impeachment hearings today against President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff on Hook to Make Case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-hearings-open-schiff-090000658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s attempts to pressure Ukraine will be scrutinized in a historic public forum Wednesday as the House opens impeachment hearings that will pit him against Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff, who is tasked with making the case to remove the president from office.Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venetian anger after historic flood devastates city...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/devastation-venice-exceptional-tide-095855792.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venetians woke Wednesday to devastating scenes after the highest tide in 50 years washed through the historic Italian city, beaching gondolas, trashing hotels and sending tourists fleeing through rapidly rising waters. "The city is on its knees," Venice's mayor Luigi Brugnaro said in an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURTAIN-UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/468e0bcb51e74822a1f8cc11627a1c0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The closed doors of the Trump impeachment investigation are swinging wide open. When the gavel strikes at the start of the House hearing on Wednesday morning, America and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong readies for more chaos as violence spreads citywide...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191113012941-iptni</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-PROTESTS/ (PIX, TV):Hong Kong readies for more chaos as violence spreads citywide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pneumonic plague in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/13/two-people-diagnosed-with-pneumonic-plague-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities working to contain outbreak of disease that is worse than bubonic plague</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House laughs off Anonymous book as old news...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/12/white-house-anonymous-book-069684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminally-ill scientist completes transformation into 'world's first cyborg'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/terminally-ill-scientist-completes-transformation-20871943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Peter Scott-Morgan, who suffers from a muscle wasting disease, says he has fully completed his transition into 'Peter 2.0'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Israel-Gaza escalation rages for second day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deadly-israel-gaza-escalation-rages-second-day-113541641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exchanges of fire triggered by Israel's targeted killing of a top militant in Gaza raged for a second day Wednesday and showed little sign of easing, with 22 Palestinians killed. Fresh rocket barrages were fired at Israel, which responded with strikes on what it said were Islamic Jihad militant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to use webcams to create live feed of border wall construction... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/white-house-to-use-webcams-to-create-live-feed-of-border-wall-construction/ar-BBWFlFx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate trial to last 6 WEEKS? </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7678773/Senate-2020-candidates-work-SIX-days-week-Trump-impeachment-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The six senators running for president may find themselves in a time crunch, with President Trump's impeachment trial running six hours a day, for six days a week for six to eight weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel urges EU to seize control of data from US tech titans...</title>
      <link>https://www.afr.com/world/europe/merkel-urges-eu-to-seize-control-of-data-from-us-tech-titans-20191113-p53a5v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The German chancellor said the EU should claim 'digital sovereignty' by developing its own platform to manage data and reduce its reliance on the US-based cloud services run by Amazon, Microsoft and Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aides counseling Trump not to fire Mulvaney...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Mulvaney-says-he-will-no-longer-seek-judge-s-14828841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump has been threatening for weeks to fire acting chief of staff Mick Mulvaney, but senior advisers have counseled him to hold off on such a drastic step amid a high-stakes impeachment probe, according to three people familiar with the discussions.  Trump has expressed particular anger over Mulvaney's performance in an Oct. 17 news conference in which Mulvaney stunned White House aides by saying military aid to Ukraine was withheld to pressure its government to launch investigations that could politically benefit Trump, two of the people said. Later, Mulvaney issued a statement saying the media had misconstrued his televised comments and that "there was absolutely no quid pro quo."  Senior advisers have cautioned Trump that removing Mulvaney at such a sensitive time could be perilous, the people said - both because Mulvaney played an integral role in the decision to freeze the aid, and because of the disruption that would be caused by replacing one of Trump's most senior aides.  "I don't think you'll see him going anywhere until after December," said one Trump adviser, who like others spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private conversations. "But the president was very unhappy with that press conference. That was a very bad day for the president."  White House officials declined to comment Tuesday.  Mulvaney had direct talks with Trump about the president's desire to withhold nearly $400 million in security aid to Ukraine, The Washington Post has reported. At the same time, Trump and other allies were pressuring Ukraine to open an investigation of Democratic rival Joe Biden and of theories about the country's role in the 2016 election, according to congressional testimony in the impeachment inquiry.  Trump's advisers have cited as a cautionary tale the example of national...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary says 'many, many, many people' urging her to run...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/12/hillary-clinton-presidential-run-2020-000325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Threats Increase...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2019/11/as-trump-attacks-death-threats-against-the-whistleblower-and-his-lawyers-increase/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Law enforcement is involved."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Teams invite  Kaepernick to workout...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28067012/teams-invited-colin-kaepernick-workout-saturday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL clubs have been informed that Colin Kaepernick will hold a workout Saturday, although the QB's reps had asked that it could take place on a Tuesday, when more team personnel could attend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Death penalty not fair sentence for jaywalking...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/12/goodwin-trickster-adam-schiff-conjuring-guilt-out-of-thin-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dictionary defines a conjurer as someone who “practices magic arts” and “performs feats of sleight of hand and illusion.” In plain English, people like Adam Schiff. The California Democrat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declares economic 'boom' underway... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/trump-declares-economic-boom-underway-cbo-sounds-slowdown-alarms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump says the economy is "stunning." But congressional analysts see signs of a slowdown - already underway. It will be a big 2020 factor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Puerto Rico's infrastructure failing as federal aid remains on hold...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/policy/report-puerto-ricos-infrastructure-failing-federal-aid-remains-holdrelief-stalls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineers group says hurricane-ravaged island needs up to $23 billion investment over 10 years. The federal government is holding back aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Blocks 'Suspicionless' Searches of Phones, Computers at Borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-privacy/u-s-judge-rules-suspicionless-searches-of-travelers-digital-devices-unconstitutional-idUSKBN1XM2O2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Tuesday ruled that U.S. border agents need "reasonable s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems' lead lawyer known for prosecuting mobsters, swindlers ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-impeachment-lawyer-cut-his-teeth-prosecuting-mobsters-wall-street-cheats/ar-BBWF2p4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists Pursue New Kind of Expose: Uncovering Their Salaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/money/journalists-pursue-new-kind-of-expose-uncovering-their-salaries/ar-BBWF0wC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Blast Trade Aid as Favoring Southern Farmers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/democrats-blast-trump-trade-aid-as-favoring-southern-farmers/ar-BBWECQf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Sued for Censoring Posts Naming Whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-sued-censoring-posts-naming-211503373.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc. was accused in a lawsuit of censorship by a user who says the company hasn’t explained to him why it deleted three of his posts that named “the alleged Ukraine whistle-blower” who kicked off the presidential impeachment inquiry.Connecticut law school student Cameron Atkinson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURTAIN-UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/77645ee9804c4056a9a6e42e64cb755a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The closed doors of the Trump impeachment investigation are swinging wide open. When the gavel strikes at the start of the House hearing Wednesday morning, America and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHIFF: Impeachable Offenses Include 'Bribery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/12/778380499/rep-adam-schiff-trumps-potentially-impeachable-offenses-include-bribery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Intelligence Committee chairman said bribery is a "breach of the public trust in a way where you're offering official acts for some personal or political reason, not in the nation's interest."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approving marijuana sales leads to increases in crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/lake-county-news-sun/opinion/ct-lns-talk-of-county-st-1115-20191111-o3qksl5l4bhbbij3rfld4dfi7m-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk of the County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC scrambles to find leaker...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/12/abc-scrambles-to-figure-out-identity-of-amy-robach-leaker-who-goes-by-ignotus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC bigwigs are going potty to find the identity of the leaker behind the Amy Robach tape — after the alleged source posted a letter online slamming the network under the name “Ignotus,&amp;#8221…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURTAIN-UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a74ed5bfddba4c93918ec3aa5349ceb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The public impeachment inquiry hearings set to begin Wednesday will pit a Democratic attorney who built his reputation as a federal mob and securities fraud prosecutor against a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows families of Sandy Hook shooting victims to sue gunmaker...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8755008e727a4a1b804cdf5cf03ab620</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court said Tuesday that a survivor and relatives of victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting can pursue their lawsuit against the maker of the rifle used...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball coach told kid to slide. Then he got sued...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/slide-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Considered Firing Intel Inspector General...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-has-considered-firing-intelligence-community-inspector-general/ar-BBWEW5B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-ASTROS pitcher: Team stole signs with camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28066522/ex-astros-pitcher-mike-fiers-team-stole-signs-camera</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Astros pitcher Mike Fiers told The Athletic that the team used a camera in center field to help steal signs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Meat' -- Made From Air!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/air-protein-launches-air-based-meat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No, this is not a joke. Air Protein is making air-based meat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff's top inquisitor is ex-MSNBC personality...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/10/04/adam-schiff-tapped-former-msnbc-contributor-to-question-key-ukraine-envoy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President rails on Fed, notes negative rates: 'Give me some of that money'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/12/trump-rails-on-fed-says-market-and-economy-would-be-doing-even-better-without-powell-mistakes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump complained that foreign countries have negative interest rates. "Give me some of that money. I want some of that money," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAVAGE: DECADES OF DARKNESS, EVEN IF TRUMP WINS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/11/11/exclusive-michael-savage-raw-and-unfiltered-on-trump-beethoven-and-the-future-of-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with Breitbart News, conservative radio legend Michael Savage tackles a wide variety of today’s political issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 25% of infections in Canada resistant to drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50383332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 25% infections in the country are resistant to drugs and the figure is rising, scientists warn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Christmas Comes Early' as ABC Turns Journalists Into Promoters...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2019/11/12/christmas-comes-early-abc-whores-out-news-division-disney-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next time you hear liberals in the media talk about undue influence of corporate entities or the dominance of powerful voices, think of Good Morning America on Tuesday. The “news” program devoted almost 17 minutes to shilling for the new Disney+ streaming service. Disney, of course, owns ABC and the journalists on the network sounded more like PR talking points come to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: TRUMP MUST GO</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/ann-coulter-gives-up-daca-kids-can-stay-trump-must-go/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Braces for Violent Night; Pounded By 200+ Rockets...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Explosions-at-house-of-Islamic-Jihads-Abu-al-Ata-Palestinian-report-607579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IDF reinforced its troops and prepared for multiple possible situations. Shelters in Ashkelon were opened and school was canceled as a "severe security event." Ashdod is in a state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat-shaming: Passenger loses airline miles over fat pet swap...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cat-shaming-russian-loses-airline-miles-over-fat-155447186.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's Aeroflot on Tuesday stripped a passenger of his air miles after he boasted online of sneaking his overweight cat on board by switching him for a slimmer cat during check-in. Traveller Mikhail Galin wrote in a Facebook post last week that his cat Viktor was judged too fat to be taken into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Homeless man hurls bucket of hot diarrhea at woman near Hollywood Walk of Fame...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/12/homeless-man-hurls-bucket-of-diarrhea-at-woman-near-hollywood-walk-of-fame/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A homeless man dumped a bucket of “hot” diarrhea on a Los Angeles woman near the Hollywood Walk of Fame — an unprovoked attack that’s left her with PTSD,  she said this…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy TX Millennial Spending Fortune Trying To Live To 120...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/11/11/texan-spending-fortune-hours-trying-live-120-years-old/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ari Rastegar goes to bed in special clothing on a temperature-regulated bed. He also wears a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hospital Delays Plan To End Life Support For TX Infant...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/11/10/cook-childrens-hospital-delays-plan-to-end-life-support-for-tinslee-lewis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook Children's Hospital in Fort Worth has stopped plans to end life support for 9-month-old Tinslee Lewis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German intel agencies open new spy school in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bd54c90fd83f40bf9ee7f8c58300b8f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A room full of grey suits, strict instructions only to photograph the audience from behind and — of course — a medley of James Bond tunes to lighten the mood. Germany's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe Mandates Labels for Jewish Products...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/world/food-israeli-west-bank-settlements-must-carry-special-labels-european-court-rules-psagot-wine-1.493035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows families of Sandy Hook shooting victims to sue gunmaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/12/778487920/supreme-court-allows-sandy-hook-families-case-against-remington-to-proceed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gun-maker had appealed to the highest federal court after the Connecticut Supreme Court allowed the lawsuit over the 2012 school massacre in Newtown, Conn., to go forward in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In private speech, Bolton says some of Trump's policy decisions guided by personal interest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/private-speech-bolton-suggests-some-trump-s-foreign-policy-decisions-n1080651</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former national security director was especially critical of the president's handling of Turkey, according to multiple sources present for his remarks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
