<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Marine commander sacked over LGBT slur...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/08/30/26-meu-battalion-commander-fired-during-deployment-over-equal-opportunity-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2/6 commander was abruptly fired in May in the middle of a deployment with the 26 MEU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan braces for 'very strong' typhoon...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/japan-braces-very-strong-typhoon-065230096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typhoon Jebi, packing winds of up to 252 kilometres (156 miles) an hour, is expected to make landfall on the country's main island on Tuesday, according to Japan's Meteorological Agency. "Maintaining its very strong power, the typhoon is forecast to approach western and eastern Japan,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's 'Silk Road' project runs into debt jam...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinas-silk-road-project-runs-debt-jam-042500476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's massive and expanding "Belt and Road" trade infrastructure project is running into speed bumps as some countries begin to grumble about being buried under Chinese debt. First announced in 2013 by President Xi Jinping, the initiative also known as the "new Silk Road" envisions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem Surprise Album 'Epic Fail'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/why-eminem-s-surprise-album-kamikaze-is-an-epic-fail-1139101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record is the work of an aging artist trying, and failing, to remain relevant by acting out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Winter Storm Warning of Season Issued in USA...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2018-09-01-first-winter-storm-warning-of-season-in-us-issued-alaska</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be the beginning of meteorological fall, but winter is right around the corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health officials, worried about outbreak, investigate HIV cluster in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/homeless/health-officials-investigating-cluster-of-hiv-infections-in-north-seattle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diagnoses are among 19 HIV cases reported so far this year among heterosexuals in King County. For all of last year, that number was seven, according to the health agency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEOS: Obama, Bush, Meghan McCain Take Shots at Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-obama-bush-meghan-mccain-swipe-at-trump-during-john-mccain-funeral-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a race'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2018/09/01/race-cruz-allies-will-spend-plenty-put-brakes-betokeep-texas-senate-seat-red</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON--With Beto O'Rourke fighting Ted Cruz to a draw in polls and topping him in cash, and his party itching to nab a Senate seat and end...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High School Football Team Cancels Season After Outscored 102-0 In First Two Games...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/08/29/healdsburg-high-football-team-calls-it-quits-after-crushing-shutout-losses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a pair of lopsided losses to start off the year, the Healdsburg High School football team has decided to turn in its uniforms and cancel the rest of the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caught in political echo chamber? Listening to opposition can make partisanship worse...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-twitter-partisan-politics-20180831-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Living in a political echo chamber where you only encounter the views of people who agree with you is hardly conducive to a healthy democracy. But it turns out that broadening our horizons by listening to opposing points of view on Twitter only makes the problem worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Insult to public GOOGLE isn't sending CEO to Senate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/01/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-declines-invite-to-testify-in-senate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's decision to ignore the Senate Select Committee on Intelligence's invitation to have CEO Sundar Pichai testify on Russian election meddling is an insult to the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens to exclude Canada from new NAFTA...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-threatens-exclude-canada-nafta-deal-161717125.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump on Saturday threatened to exclude Canada from a new NAFTA agreement after negotiations to rewrite the pact ended without an agreement the night before. "There is no political necessity to keep Canada in the new NAFTA deal. If we don't make a fair deal for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARETHA'S TOO!</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/video/vicious-anti-trump-diatribes-mar-aretha-franklins-memorial-service-orange-apparition-leech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;Continuing a sickening Democratic tradition of politicizing public memorial services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BASH AT MCCAIN FUNERAL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6c3b8c91dfc34f42868eb2ccb09b675a/McCain-tributes-echo-with-criticism-of-Trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — John McCain's daughter opened his memorial service by posing her father's legacy as a direct challenge to President Donald Trump, setting a tone that echoed the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man: The Orb...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/burningman/article/Bjarke-Ingels-Jakob-Lange-the-ORB-Burning-Man-13197472.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some are calling it a giant bulb of garlic. Others say it's the world's biggest disco ball. But really, the official name of the 100-foot-diameter reflective sphere is "the ORB."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Festival adds security but won't fence off fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/life/arts/burning-man/2018/08/31/burning-man-adding-volunteer-security-around-fires/1171094002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after a man died after running into the flames of the Man burn, organizers say they won't add fencing around large fires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Giant cage protests tech ties with ICE...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/404630-activists-protest-palantirs-ice-contract-at-burning-man</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers hope to catch the attention of tech workers who often flock to the Nevada festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BASH AT MCCAIN FUNERAL</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/09/01/obama-bush-to-pay-tribute-to-john-mccain-at-washington-national-cathedral-memorial-service.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan McCain took a number of thinly-veiled swipes at President Trump on Saturday in a eulogy for her father John McCain -- who sparred with Trump on a number of occasions before his death last week of brain cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC CRAZY: Woman smashes bus window, hits man with car...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2018/08/video-woman-smashes-greyhound-bus-window-rams-driver-in-dc/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic video released by D.C. police shows a woman smashing the windows of a Greyhound bus with a car jack, and then ramming and attempting to run down the bus driver in an apparent act of road rage…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Impeachment talk has perils for both parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Impeachment-talk-has-perils-for-both-parties-13198900.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent convictions of President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort and his longtime lawyer Michael Cohen have pushed talk of a possible impeachment proceeding to a new level. Right now, it's potentially tricky territory for both parties. A new Washington Post-ABC News poll finds that 49 percent of all Americans say Congress should initiate impeachment proceedings, while 46 percent are opposed. Among registered voters, it's the opposite - 46 percent in favor and 49 percent opposed. Those are higher numbers in support than in other recent polls. Three in 4 Democrats now favor a start to impeachment, while 4 in 5 Republicans do not. Fifty-seven percent of women say yes; 44 percent of men say no.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ FIGHT OF HIS LIFE?</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/beto-o-rourke-dreams-of-one-texas-ted-cruz-sees-another-clearly-/17809047/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONGVIEW, Texas — Beto O’Rourke was racing left again, insisting he knew what he was doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BASH AT MCCAIN FUNERAL</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/01/thousands-arrive-in-dc-to-bid-farewell-to-john-mccain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan McCain tore into an absent President Trump at a memorial service for her father, Arizona Sen. John McCain, in Washington on Saturday. “We gather here to mourn the passing of American greatne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone:  All I'm guilty of is backing Trump...</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/news/us_politics/2018/09/roger_stone_tells_herald_the_only_thing_i_m_guilty_of_is_supporting_donald</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A steamed Roger Stone, in the special counsel’s crosshairs, said he counted 79 media inquiries peppering his cellphone all day in anticipation of an indictment that never materialized.“The only thing I’m guilty of is supporting Donald Trump for president and being effective against Hillary Clinton,” Stone told the Herald last night as he confirmed Robert Mueller didn’t come knocking.Stone said Mueller is being merciless in his dogged pursuit of a scalp for Russia’s meddling in the 2016 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARETHA'S TOO!</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/404645-stevie-wonder-takes-swipe-at-trump-during-aretha-franklin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stevie Wonder on Friday took a swipe at President Trump during a speech at Aretha Franklin's funeral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI to 'bring dead back to life' with human replicas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/726877/AI-bring-dead-back-life-human-replicas-3D-technology-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police reports detail O'Rourke's '98 drunken-driving arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/police-reports-detail-orourkes-98-drunken-driving-arrest-145042700--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Police documents reveal previously unreported details about a decades-old drunken-driving arrest of Democratic Senate candidate Beto O'Rourke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida's Democratic gubernatorial candidate under attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/floridas-democratic-gubernatorial-candidate-under-attack-123123793--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Gillum is picking up endorsements, money and plenty of national attention in the aftermath of his suprising upset victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aretha funeral bishop apologizes for 'groping' Grande...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180901-aretha-franklin-funeral-bishop-apologizes-groping-grande</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary helped up steps...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-two-people-help-hillary-up-stairs-at-aretha-franklin-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton still needs help with stairs. The Clintons were in Detroit today for Aretha Franklin’s funeral, and after viewing the open casket, the two made their way to different parts of the stage. As Hillary approached the stairs, two people grabbed each of her arms to help her ascend the handful of steps. Watch: …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First ever trials on microdosing LSD to begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/sep/01/first-ever-trials-on-the-effects-of-microdosing-lsd-set-to-begin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Silicon Valley they say taking tiny amounts of the hallucinogenic drug increases creativity and productivity, but is it all in the mind?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan McCain Unloads on President at Father's Funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/09/awful-meghan-mccain-takes-cheap-shot-at-president-trump-at-fathers-funeral-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to Kill?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-09-01/there-plan-south-africa-take-white-farms-and-kill-white-farmers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott Of IN-N-OUT Backfires Spectacularly...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-31/california-liberals-draw-line-refuse-boycott-n-out-after-democratic-official-goes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica white farmers warn as more land grabs loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/31/white-farmers-warn-new-zimbabwe-calls-grow-land-expropriation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any aspiring farmer would envy Nick Serfontein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth set for big freeze? Sun blank...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1010638/cold-weather-forecast-big-freeze-solar-minimum-maximum-space-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE sun has been void of sunspots for more than half of the year asm scientists believe the Earth could be in for a huge cold snap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's leaked 'off-record' comments complicate deal...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trumps-leaked-off-record-comments-complicate-trade-deal/story?id=57528243</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As efforts stalled Friday to persuade Canada to sign onto a rewrite of the North American Free Trade Agreement, President Donald Trump blasted “dishonest reporting” for complicating a potential deal after off-the-record comments he made during an interview with Bloomberg leaked into the Canadian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside terrifying world of modern exorcisms...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/inside-terrifying-world-modern-exorcisms-13172802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new BBC documentary looks at the popularity of exorcisms in Buenos Aires with Padre Manuel Acuna who has performed thousands of the religious rituals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From popsicles to tweets: How US-Canada trade talks stalled...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/popsicles-trump-tweets-us-canada-trade-talks-stalled-134355560.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was about 10:30 pm when Chrystia Freeland emerged from a meeting with Robert Lighthizer, saying she had but a few words with the US Trade Representative. Ever concerned about reporters -- her former job -- Freeland had even taken care that afternoon to bring popsicles to the two dozen journalists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pepper spray discharges during flight to Hawaii, 15 treated...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/15-aboard-hawaii-flight-treated-pepper-spray-goes-002751836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — A can of pepper spray went off inside a plane headed from Oakland, California, to Maui on Friday, requiring emergency help for several people aboard, Hawaiian Airlines said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi plot to turn Qatar into island with huge canal...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1011376/saudi-arabia-qatar-canal-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SENIOR Saudi official today appeared to confirm local media reports the kingdom is considering digging a canal to separate the Qatari peninsula from the mainland and turn it into an island, amid a year-long dispute between the neighbours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpatriotic...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180901-neil-armstrong-film-accused-being-unpatriotic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport Installs First Unmanned Control Tower...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/08/31/unmanned-airport-control-tower-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A one-of-a-kind virtual air traffic control tower was recently installed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENICE GOES GAGA!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6119393/Venice-Film-Festival-Lady-Gaga-Irina-Shayk-stun-Star-Born-screening.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer, 32, continued to pull out all the stops as she headed to the screening with her co-star's partner Irina Shayk for her film A Star Is Born at the 75th annual Venice Film Festival on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Self-Driving Car in Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/2018/08/31/apple-discloses-minor-crash-involving-self-driving-test-vehicle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. disclosed in a filing with the California Department of Motor Vehicles that one of its autonomous test vehicles was involved in a crash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day Sees Americans Grilling More Steaks on Strong Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/31/americans-are-grilling-more-steaks-for-labor-day-as-economy-hums#gs.YgWPfLw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans Are Grilling More Steaks for Labor Day With the Economy Humming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry over 'FIRST MAN' Signals Controversial Award Season...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/31/-first-man-outcry-portends-controversial-award-season-for-films#gs.=QOU_Lk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not even September yet, and likely Oscar contenders are already stirring up controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women cheer as man-free music festival kicks off...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.se/20180901/women-cheer-as-swedish-man-free-music-festival-opens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.se&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matilda Hagerman laughs with her friends as she queues at a man-free music festival, which kicked off in Sweden  on Friday in protest against a wave of sexual assaults at festivals in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Safe zone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/01/world/europe/sweden-statement-festival-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Statement festival in Gothenburg was conceived as a protest against a wave of sexual assaults and harassment at other concerts across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PLANS MASSIVE RALLY FOR CRUZ IN TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2018/08/31/ted-cruz-beto-orourke-donald-trump-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No details have been announced, but Trump tweeted the news on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first sex robot movie hits screens...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/726800/sex-robot-porn-lumidolls-private-movie-film-future-sofia-curly-dorian-del-isla</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
