<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Elite Claim Homeless Bad for Environment...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jul/11/san-francisco-navigation-center-shelter-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort to block construction of a new shelter comes as city’s homeless population surges to more than 8,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's longest deepfake!</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2019/07/the-lion-king-review-2019-1202157153/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfolding like the world's longest and least convincing deepfake, the new "Lion King" fatally misunderstands what once made Disney special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In first, A.I. beats pros in six-player poker...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190711-ai-program-beats-pros-six-player-poker-first</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI program beats pros in six-player poker -- a first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW 27,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/11/stock-market-fed-chief-signals-a-rate-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow rallied after testimony by Fed Chair Jerome Powell that signaled a rate cut is coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miley Cyrus Says Won't Have Children Due to 'Climate Change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/07/11/miley-cyrus-wont-reproduce-until-shes-confident-her-kid-can-live-on-an-earth-with-fish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop star turned Planned Parenthood activist Miley Cyrus is vowing not to reproduce until she is confident her offspring can "live on an earth with fish in the water." (Fact check: fish currently exist in bodies of water all over the planet).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran 'to ramp up production' at secret nuke bunker built under mountain...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9490505/iran-nuclear-production-secret-bunker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN is preparing to ramp up production at a secret nuclear site built under a MOUNTAIN to protect it from US attack, it’s been claimed. Tehran’s nuke scientists are ready to massively …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House 'Social Media Summit' nearly descends into brawl...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/11/trumps-social-media-summit-nearly-descends-into-brawl-in-rose-garden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a fracas at the White House! President Trump’s Social Media Summit on Thursday almost descended into a brawl when Sebastian Gorka got into a brief shouting match with a White House rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK follows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-follows-france-as-it-unveils-new-tax-on-google-and-other-tech-giants-134558528.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May seeks to carve a legacy with a new law to make companies like Google, Facebook and Amazon "pay their fair share."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  AMAZON Pays $0 in Federal Taxes on $11.2 Billion Profits...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2019/02/14/amazon-doesnt-pay-federal-taxes-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, which has a trillion dollar valuation, won't pay federal taxes for the second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGTV Hosts Slapped With Chicago-Wide Suspensions for Multiple Building Code Violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hgtv-windy-city-rehab-code-violations-alison-victoria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Season 2 of HGTV's "Windy City Rehab" is "currently in production," an HGTV rep tells TheWrap, despite the City of Chicago suspending host Alison Victoria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cortez wants to ax Homeland Security; Some conservatives didn't want it... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ocasio-Cortez-wants-to-ax-Homeland-Security-some-14089173.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although some activists have urged the government to abolish its immigration enforcement arm, Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y., came out in favor of eradicating the entire Department of Homeland Security, which is tasked with protecting the country.  The department's creation after the terrorist attacks of Sept. 11, 2001, significantly threatened American civil liberties, Ocasio-Cortez said Tuesday on the WNYC podcast "New Yorker Radio Hour." She said she wanted to get rid of Homeland Security, the formation of which she called an "egregious mistake."  "People sounded the alarm back then, that these agencies are extrajudicial, that they lack effective oversight, and it is baked into the core foundational structure of these agencies," she told The New Yorker's editor, David Remnick.  Conservative political figures immediately castigated the congresswoman's proposal.  "Moronic, stupid, naive and dumb," former White House Deputy Chief of Staff Karl Rove said on Fox News.  "Absolute irresponsibility," Rep. Liz Cheney, R-Wy., told reporters, according to the Washington Examiner.  The usefulness of the Department of Homeland Security, however, wasn't always lauded on the right. President George W. Bush's administration initially had "zero interest" in creating a new department to protect against terrorism, The Washington Post previously reported. Vice President Dick Cheney, Liz Cheney's father, thought it would needlessly increase the size of government. (Rove served in that administration.)  "Creating a Cabinet post doesn't solve the problem," White House spokesman Ari Fleischer said in March 2002, according to The Post.  Some members of Congress worried that the White House was concealing the department's true cost to avoid alienating Republicans who opposed the growth of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House frustration over moon mission delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/shakeup-at-nasa-as-space-agency-scrambles-to-meet-trump-moon-mandate/ar-AAE9aUe?li=BBUPk4T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO ORDERS MORE 'EUPHORIA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/euphoria-renewed-second-season-at-hbo-1219147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The eight-episode drama will return for more on the premium cable network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vows to restore world order...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/blasting-trump-biden-pledges-global-summit-democracy-193839763.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denouncing President Donald Trump as an affront to American values, Democratic candidate Joe Biden vowed Thursday that if elected he would hold a summit aimed at halting a backslide in global democracy. "The world sees Trump for what he is: insincere, ill-informed and impulsive -- and sometimes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CANNOT PUMP OUR WAY OUT'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190711180137-6jyrj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flooding risks rise with the Mississippi River at it highest level in 70 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation leak '100,000 times normal level' from Russian nuke sub wreck...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/radiation-leak-russian-nuclear-sub</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have identified a radiation leak on the wreck of a Russian nuclear submarine that sank in Arctic waters in 1989.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDERAL SPENDING SMASHES RECORDS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/3355970000000-federal-spending-sets-record-through-june-deficit-hits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Win McNamee)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3257e93ce6474e72bc2bcc2ac3ea4b16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabies alert issued...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/07/11/rabies-alert-issued-at-walt-disney-world-resort/1704265001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's Department of Health issued a rabies alert for Disney World's Epcot Center after two employees were scratched by a rabid cat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORECAST: HURRICANE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/tropical-storm-barry-headed-gulf-coast-could-drop-20-inches-n1028836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The town of Grand Isle, Louisiana, south of New Orleans, ordered a mandatory evacuation of residents Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS to stop selling newspapers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/11/starbucks-will-stop-selling-newspapers-in-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to read the paper at Starbucks, you’ll have to start bringing your own. The Seattle-based coffee giant, beginning Sept. 1, will no longer sell The New York Times, The Wall Street Journa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Downturn? Smaller Crowds, Shorter Lines...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/11/smaller-crowds-shorter-lines-reported-at-disneyland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disneyland visitors are noticing something a little unusual at the popular theme park — wait times for many rides are less than 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA police chief vows to erase homeless people's warrants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ecd49deadf4b4b16a30beaabdb900465</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techno pioneer Mills says electro music now 'too middle class'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190711-techno-pioneer-mills-says-electro-music-now-middle-class</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Techno pioneer Mills says electro music now 'too middle class'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of murders threaten Cape Town's tourist mecca image...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/cape-town-drug-gangs-violence-warzone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When most Americans think of Cape Town, South Africa, they probably think of it as a mecca for tourists. But there’s a side to the city that is becoming more of a frightening reality – murder, much of it gang-related.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama goes to Hollywood; Rents $23M 'Shark House'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-7236537/Michelle-Obama-rents-stunning-23-million-Hollywood-Hills-home-open-air-shark-tank.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former First Lady is believed to have rented a spectacular new property in Hollywood Hills on Monday and Tuesday. The home has been dubbed the Shark House due to its open-air aquarium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers turning to factory jobs to get by...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/school-day-assembly-line-night-how-teachers-south-carolina-make-n1026381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in the state, which ranks among the worst for education in the country, recently approved a raise for teachers. Advocates say it’s not enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans priest leaves Catholic church to become woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7238011/Basingstoke-Transgender-priest-leaves-Catholic-church-woman.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alisha Cacace, 37, of Basingstoke, felt she was in the wrong body for as long as she can remember. A year ago she began hormone therapy and says she's never been happier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital fires 23 workers in case of excessive doses, deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/37e3f64408b04099b65657d0a7b4b44d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intruders jump fence at U.S. nuclear reactor that uses bomb-grade fuel...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190711185145-uffxv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-NUCLEARPOWER/SECURITY (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Intruders jump fence at U.S. nuclear reactor that uses bomb-grade fuel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR CANADA flight diverted to Honolulu due to 'severe' turbulence...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2019/07/11/air-canada-flight-diverted-honolulu-due-severe-turbulence-multiple-injuries-reported/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline officials said at least 25 people suffered minor injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes may be key to spotting dementia...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1662990/scientists-could-have-a-better-way-to-spot-early-signs-of-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our sight could be a window into our brain health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 passengers with head, neck injuries...</title>
      <link>https://montreal.ctvnews.ca/air-canada-flight-makes-emergency-landing-with-multiple-injuries-1.4504071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;montreal.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden promises to end 'forever wars' as president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fcd9b36a5f0542c5b0a9688f38338e2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimp returned to zoo after recovering from depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.khon2.com/news/international/skopje-zoos-chimp-returns-after-recovering-from-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khon2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SKOPJE, North Macedonia (AP) — Koko the chimpanzee, once a star in Skopje’s zoo, has returned home after spending 10 years in the Netherlands recovering from depression, the zoo says. Koko wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Offers Plan to Decriminalize immigration violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/elizabeth-warren-offers-plan-to-decriminalize-migration-probe-trump-abuse-1.1285853</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed chairman warns of 'unthinkable' harm if debt ceiling isn't raised...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/452609-fed-chairman-warns-of-unthinkable-harm-if-debt-ceiling-isnt-raised</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell said Thursday that the global economy could suffer “unthinkable” damage if the White House and Congress fail to raise the federal debt limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Sheriff Deputy Arrested After Planting Drugs on Innocent People...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/07/11/florida-sheriff-deputy-arrested-after-planting-drugs-on-innocent-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reason uncovered body camera footage of the officer lying about a roadside field test for drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300,000 ILLEGAL KIDS TO FLOOD PUBLIC SCHOOLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/illegal-immigrant-population-to-surge-10-this-year-flood-schools</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The continued surge of Latin American illegal immigrants at the U.S.-Mexico border will lead to hundreds of thousands being released into the country, increasing the already massive population of migrants by some 10%, according to a new analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone owners could be spied on through microphone controlled by Watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9483739/apple-watch-walkie-talkie-iphone-spy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE has disabled a major feature on the Apple Watch after learning it could be used to spy on iPhone owners. The Walkie-Talkie app – which has now been switched off – could remotely listen in to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of all American adults in FBI's facial-recognition database...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/07/ice-and-ever-widening-surveillance-dragnet/158308/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICE agents have used facial-recognition technology on state driver’s-license photos, turning a public database into a de facto criminal database.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most obese states...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-the-no-1-most-obese-state-in-america-2019-07-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sad individual and societal costs of the obesity epidemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rails against 'Fake News' in new tirade, warns media industry will fold when he leaves office...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-rails-against-fake-news-in-bizarre-tirade-warns-industry-will-fold-when-he-leaves-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump teed off on the news media in a bizarre Twitter rant Thursday morning ahead of a big social media summit at the White House slated for later in the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24" of rain?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/tropical-storm-barry-forms-over-gulf-expected-to-make-landfall-as-a-hurricane/70008788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORTEZ CORNERED:  Rips Pelosi for 'singling out newly elected women of color' ...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/852117/alexandria-ocasiocortez-rips-nancy-pelosi-singling-newly-elected-women-color</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) has made enemies of a few more Democratic newcomers. In an interview with The New York Times published Saturday, Pelosi pushed back against Reps. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), Ilhan Ohmar (D-Minn.), Ayanna Pressley (D-Mass.), and Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) for their opposition to a largely bipartisan border spending bill, referring to them just "four people." Now, Ocasio-Cortez has suggested there's a racial motivation to Pelosi's words. Pelosi has often rejected the will of progressive newcomers, and in an interview with The Washington Post published Wednesday, Ocasio-Cortez said she "understood" that was "to protect more moderate members." But this "persistent singling out" has become "just outright disrespectful .â€‰.â€‰. the explicit singling out of newly elected women of color," Ocasio-Cortez added. Ocasio-Cortez's comment comes after she and her self-described "squad" pushed for amendments to a Republican-led bill that directed emergency funding to the border, received some compromises, and still voted against it. The bill still passed because despite having "their public whatever and their Twitter world," the freshmen representatives are just "four people and thatâ€™s how many votes they got," Pelosi told The New York Times. Pelosi also reportedly told a closed-door meeting Wednesday that Democrats can't just "tweet about our members and expect us to think that that is just okay," per the Post. Yet as Politico Playbook describes it, Pelosi's words weren't meant as an insult. To Pelosi, "if you are one person who controls 20 votes, you're powerful," and everyone else is just a "normal member," Politico writes. Those supposedly offensive comments, as Politico puts it, are simply "a reflection of a reality under which [Pelosi] operates." Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, allies planning naval escort for Gulf tankers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-plans-form-military-coalition-091802902.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US says it is planning to create an international military coalition to safeguard strategic waters off Iran and Yemen, after several attacks on tankers in the Gulf it blamed on Tehran. Under the plan, Washington would provide command ships and lead surveillance efforts, while enlisted allies would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France passes law taxing digital giants in defiance of Trump anger... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-passes-law-taxing-digital-giants-defiance-us-101353240.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's parliament on Thursday passed a law making it the first major economy to impose a tax on digital giants, defying a probe ordered by an angry US President Donald Trump that could trigger reprisal tariffs. The legislation -- dubbed the GAFA tax in an acronym for Google, Apple, Facebook and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Migrants from India crossing TX border...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-migrants-from-india-another-with-recent-gastric-bypass-surgery-line-up-after-illegally-crossing-tx-border/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The steady flow of illegal immigrants strolling into the United States from Mexico continues unabated, with large groups including migrants with recent gastric bypass surgery, pregnant women a week away from their due date, and scores of very young children sent on treacherous journey alone. KGBT’s Sydney Hernandez offered several updates on the immigration situation …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman knifed boyfriend because he was too tired to have sex...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/florida/things-got-slashy-305628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her boyfriend said he was too tired to have sex, a Florida Woman allegedly grabbed a kitchen knife and slashed him multiple times on the arm and shoulder, according to a criminal complaint. The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball history made: Inside debut of robot umpires...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2019/07/11/mlb-trackman-system-makes-history-calls-balls-and-strikes-pro-game/1702431001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TrackMan radar system debuted during the Atlantic League all-star game, calling balls and strikes for the first time in pro baseball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMMY ROBINSON JAILED AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9483610/tommy-robinson-sentenced-contempt-trial-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURIOUS Tommy Robinson supporters attacked a BBC film crew and hurled smoke bombs in riots after the EDL founder was jailed for nine months today. Robinson called for protests after he was found to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>363-foot projection of rocket will be flashed on Washington Monument to celebrate Apollo 11 anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-363-foot-projection-of-a-rocket-will-be-flashed-14088032.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A 363-foot projection of a rocket will be flashed on one side of the Washington Monument next week to commemorate the 50th anniversary of the Apollo moon landing.  The Smithsonian National Air and Space Museum is sponsoring a series of events to honor the Apollo 11 mission of July 20, 1969. The mission, which launched astronauts Buzz Aldrin, Neil Armstrong and Michael Collins from Earth on a Saturn V rocket, culminated with Aldrin and Armstrong successfully landing on the moon.  Part of the commemoration includes "Apollo 50 Festival" live performances, exhibits and speakers. The events will take place July 18-20 on the Mall.  As part of the celebration, the image of a 363-foot Saturn V rocket will be projected on the east side of the Washington Monument.  There will also be a free show that will have "archival footage to re-create the launch of Apollo 11 and tell the story of the first moon landing," according to Smithsonian officials. The show will also have a "re-creation of the famous Kennedy Space Center countdown clock."  Viewers can see the show from areas on the Mall in front of the Smithsonian Castle.  The event is being sponsored by the Air and Space Museum along with the Department of the Interior and will be produced by 59 Productions, which has handled the opening ceremony of the London 2012 Olympic Games and other high-profile events.  In a statement, Interior Secretary David Bernhardt said: "Almost 50 years ago, the Apollo 11 mission captivated the world as two American astronauts were the first to step foot on the moon, forever changing space exploration."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERE COMES BARRY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/111452.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI investigating tattooed deputy gangs in LA County Sheriff's Dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-fbi-investigating-sheriff-20190711-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities are examining whether the Banditos, an inked deputy group, have committed illegal acts, sources tell The Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS OUTSIDE OF COURTHOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7235869/Dozens-Tommy-Robinson-supporters-gather-outside-Old-Bailey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former English Defence League (EDL) founder, whose real name is Stephen Yaxley-Lennon, was found to have committed contempt of court following a two-day hearing at the Old Bailey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORECAST: HURRICANE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a30cb02802024409a6a94e5a51da7c93?utm_source=PushNotification</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Man Who Gets Bitten By Sharks -- On Purpose...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-man-who-is-intentionally-bitten-by-sharks-fear-is-a-funny-thing </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeremiah Sullivan has been studying sharks for over forty years, and on July 17, the world will see him get bitten by a shark (several times) on NatGeo—all in the name of research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW U.S. TECH GIANTS HELPING TO BUILD BEIJING SURVEILLANCE STATE...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/07/11/china-surveillance-google-ibm-semptian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nonprofit led by Google and IBM executives is working with Semptian, whose technology is monitoring the internet activity of 200 million people in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Fearless dog chases bear from yard...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/pets-animals/video-shows-dog-scaring-off-backyard-bear-in-new-jersey/5387530/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey man is promising his neighbor's dog a steak dinner after the pooch scared off a bear in his backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New generation of political exiles leave Bolsonaro's Brazil 'to stay alive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jul/11/brazil-political-exiles-bolsonaro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politicians, academics and writers have fled a climate of death threats and hostility reminiscent of the military dictatorship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Trump to announce executive action on census citizenship question... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-to-announce-executive-action-on-census-citizenship-question-today-2019-07-11-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president announced a White House Rose Garden press conference on the topic for Thursday afternoon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENTLEY Car of Future So Luxurious, It's Self-Chauffeured...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bentley-s-car-of-the-future-is-so-luxurious-it-s-self-chauffeured-1.1285180</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President lashes out on TWITTER ahead of social media 'summit'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6bffba9456e5419190a5478117b30607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Of Teens Storm Philly WAWA, Throw Ice At Customers, Ransack Store...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/07/10/group-10-teenagers-throw-ice-customres-philadelphia-wawa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It happened at the Wawa on the 500 block of South 2nd Street around 3:45 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Tops Projections in Broad Advance...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-core-consumer-inflation-tops-123002157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A key measure of U.S. consumer prices rose more than forecast in June, potentially complicating the Federal Reserve’s assessment of inflation as policy makers weigh an interest-rate cut as soon as this month.The core consumer price index, which excludes food and energy, rose 0.3% from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank God it's Thursday: Four-day work-week some want to bring to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Thank-God-it-s-Thursday-the-four-day-work-week-14087572.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The women at the Belgian nonprofit Femma decided quickly how to spend their new free time. Onetook up Spanish classes. Another studied flamenco dance. A senior manager revived her interest in art crafts.  Four years ago, the feminist advocacy organization polled its 60,000 female members on their biggest frustrations. The results were remarkably consistent, regardless of age: The women wanted more free time. Between work and their disproportionate share of the household and child-care responsibilities, the women reported having little time for themselves.  So as a one-year experiment starting in January, Femma implemented a 30-hour workweek for its approximately 60-person staff, which effectively means most take their Fridays off. The employees are being closely followed through December by Free University of Brussels researchers, who are studying the impact of more leisure time on both the women and their children.  "Our colleagues are very happy with this new situation; they're experiencing a lot more freedom," said Eva Brumagne, the director of the Belgian nonprofit, who has started a book club focused on modern literature. "They have a much more balanced life, new hobbies and are spending more time with their children. People are saying their lives have slowed down."  Femma's experiment comes as part of a new push across much of Europe to reduce working hours, including through a four-day workweek. For much of this decade, the idea of a four-day week has been primarily championed by industry executives in certain business niches - like those in software development or sales - as a way to boost employee morale and hourly productivity.  But over the past several years, particularly in Europe, trade unions, leftist organizations and some academics have increasingly called for a far broader, economy-wide transition to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ridgecrest quakes caused damage to earth's crust seen from satellite...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-earthquake-visible-space-20190711-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA released images that showing damage from the 6.4 and 7.1 magnitude earthquakes that struck Southern California as seen from space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel sits through anthems after shaking spells...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190711-merkel-sits-through-anthems-after-shaking-spells</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel sits through anthems after shaking spells</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE ADMITS LISTENING TO SMART SPEAKER RECORDINGS...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/google-admits-listening-smart-speaker-105207882.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech giant said it listened to a small number of interactions with its Google Assistant to train the software and improve its responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190711094254-vuo9x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-GULFMEXICO/:Storm likely to churn into hurricane, looms on U.S. Gulf coast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Toxic' stew...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/healthcare_hospitals/article_4d7097ea-a340-11e9-adc3-53715c9eee61.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a day like Wednesday, when the New Orleans area was pounded with as much as seven inches of rain in less than three hours, it may seem like the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Vets Say Iraq, Afghanistan Wars Weren't Worth It...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/07/10/most-veterans-say-iraq-afghanistan-wars-werent-worth-it-pew-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of vets taking part in a new study says that the cost of the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan outweigh any successes .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson jailed for nine months...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/791215/tommy-robinson-at-old-bailey-with-katie-hopkins-sentencing-latest-update-court-case-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEVEE DANGER NEW ORLEANS...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5736a388e0f040a3bfd2a4b7890b407b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-07-10-gulf-coast-barry-preps-louisiana-mississippi-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how Mississippi, Louisiana and Texas are preparing for the impacts of this tropical system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deportation raids Sunday?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/452555-deportation-raids-to-begin-sunday-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) agents will launch massive raids on Sunday targeting undocumented immigrants scheduled for deportation, The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans fret over nightmare scenario for Senate primaries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/452535-gop-frets-over-nightmare-scenario-for-senate-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are facing an early headache of nightmare primary fights as they plot to keep control of the Senate.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
