<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mummy of 3,000-year-old woman found 'perfectly' preserved inside coffin in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/mummy-3000-year-old-woman-13639066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ancient coffin was one of two discovered in El-Asasef, Luxor, on the bank of the River Nile, by Egyptian authorities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS BURNS</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1049731/France-protests-paris-riots-police-emmanuel-macron-latest-france-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEAR gas and water cannons have been fired by riot police in France amid a desperate struggle to control violent protests of more than 30,000 residents angry at President Emmanuel Macron over rising fuel prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON'S BEATINGS! BLACK FRIDAY BRAWLS...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/seasons-beatings-men-brawl-in-walmart-aisle-during-black-friday-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Black Friday, and you know what that means: People trading in their dignity for discounted toys and paper towels. Two men brawled in the aisle of a Walmart on Thanksgiving evening. It’s not clear what the tussle was over, but women jumped in and cursed them out. Watch (NSFW): ﻿ Others wrestled TVs as …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUEL TAX REBELLION</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181124101720-ghrrs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PROTESTS/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-French police fire tear gas at fuel price protesters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Deal reached to make asylum seekers wait outside USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-united-states-mexico-asylum-20181124-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has won the support of Mexico's government for a plan to remake U.S. border policy by requiring asylum seekers to wait in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Deal reached to make asylum seekers wait outside USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/deal-with-mexico-paves-way-for-asylum-overhaul-at-us-border/2018/11/24/87b9570a-ef74-11e8-9236-bb94154151d2_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump administration has won support of leftist president-elect Andrés Manuel López Obrador, who takes office Dec. 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for civil war...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d3033b920af449b594e66b51890b517b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French police fired tear gas and water cannons to disperse violent demonstrators in Paris on Saturday, as thousands gathered in the capital and beyond and staged road blockades to vent anger against rising fuel taxes. Thousands of police were deployed nationwide to contain the eighth day of deadly demonstrations that started as protests against tax but morphed into a rebuke of President Emmanuel Macron and the perceived elitism of France's ruling class. Two people have been killed since Nov. 17 in protest-related tragedies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sex doll spa...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/744254/sex-doll-spa-galmato-haven-repairs-realdoll-reggie-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREISAND: If only we could be the way we were...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6410531/Barbra-Streisand-76-felt-compelled-write-album-protest-songs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barbra Streisand mourned the death of her beloved curly-haired Coton de Tulear Samantha 18 months ago ‘as if it were a child’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez, freshmen look to shape party...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ocasio-Cortez-Democratic-freshmen-look-to-shape-13418215.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has rapidly emerged as the de facto leader of a historic class of House Democrats whose diversity and ties to the progressive left will shape the party as it targets President Donald Trump and works to clarify its message ahead of the 2020 elections. Incoming members have quickly exerted their influence on Capitol Hill since the midterm elections, with progressives bolstering Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi's, D-Calif., bid for speaker by declining to endorse an opposition movement led by centrist Democrats. Yet while Rep.-elect Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Every human spawned from single couple 200,000 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6424407/Every-person-spawned-single-pair-adults-living-200-000-years-ago-scientists-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists from the Rockefeller University and the University of Basel surveyed genetic 'bar codes' of five million animals and deduced that we sprang from a single pair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil records worst annual deforestation for decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/24/brazil-records-worst-annual-deforestation-for-a-decade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 8,000sq kms lost in the year to July amid alarm new president Jair Bolsonaro will make situation worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man covered in face tattoos arrested 54th TIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6424339/Cincinnati-man-charged-kidnapping-woman-arrested-53-times-violent-offenses.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Mann, 35, of Cincinnati wanted a payout of $100 before allowing a woman to go free, according to prosecutors, adding a 54th arrest to his lengthy rap sheet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Warns Brexit Plan Akin to Titanic Heading Toward Doom...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/johnson-warns-brexit-plan-akin-to-titanic-heading-toward-doom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Warns Brexit Plan Akin to Titanic Heading Toward Doom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$86,000 Reward For Snitching On Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-23/china-offers-86000-reward-snitching-porn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSISSIPPI RUNOFF: Dems target another Senate seat in Deep South...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/417930-dems-target-another-senate-seat-in-deep-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are aggressively targeting another Senate seat in the Deep South in next Tuesday’s runoff election after scoring a major win in Alabama last year, as embattled Sen. Cindy Hyde-Smith (R) stumbles in deep-red Mississippi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffes prefer to dine with friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.myscience.org/news/wire/just_like_us_giraffes_prefer_to_dine_with_friends-2018-bristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.myscience.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence on Champs Elysees...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/24/french-gilets-jaunes-protests-turn-violent-on-the-streets-of-paris </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clashes broke out between crowds and police on the Champs Élysées in the second weekend of demonstrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Third Of People Find Texting Daily Source Of Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-texting-source-daily-stress-third-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In its earliest days, texting was a simple way to shoot a short message to someone in a jiff. But with photos, videos, emojis, gifs, and countless other bells and whistles causing so many of us to keep our heads buried in our devices constantly, text messaging has become a way of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Saudi prince says CIA cannot be trusted on Khashoggi conclusion...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi/senior-saudi-prince-says-cia-cannot-be-trusted-on-khashoggi-conclusion-idUSKCN1NT0G5 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Saudi prince cast doubt upon the reported CIA finding that Saudi Crown ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Macron must resign'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/tear-gas-fired-at-furious-protesters-in-france-11561900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a second week of demonstrations, thousands are protesting against the steep rise in diesel prices brought in by the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Rouhani calls for Muslims to unite against USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-usa-rouhani/irans-rouhani-calls-for-muslims-to-unite-against-united-states-idUSKCN1NT080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani called on Muslims worldwide on Saturday to unit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian mission tasked with verifying American moon landings real...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1966a07c5a63419fb825ed7a92cec8de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The head of Russia's Roscosmos space agency has said that a proposed Russian mission to the moon will be tasked with verifying that the American moon landings were real. "We have set this objective to fly and verify whether they've been there or not," said Dmitry Rogozin in a video posted Saturday on Twitter. Rogozin was responding to a question about whether or not NASA actually landed on the moon nearly 50 years ago. He appeared to be joking, as he smirked and shrugged while answering. But conspiracies surrounding NASA's moon missions are common in Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Are Killing People. How Worried Should We Be?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/robots-are-killing-people-how-worried-should-we-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new HBO doc ‘The Truth About Killer Robots,’ premiering Nov. 26, casts a critical eye on our increasing dependence on technology—and the ramifications, moral and otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Leaking Oil Everywhere and Making Dangerous Mess...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/venezuela-is-leaking-oil-everywhere-and-making-a-dangerous-mess</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela Is Leaking Oil Everywhere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mortgage deal offers massive six times income...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/money/2018/nov/24/mortgage-deal-income-darlington-clydesdale </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darlington launches loan aimed at professionals in wake of Clydesdale’s ‘monster’ offer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass riots turn Paris into warzone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7817676/police-bombarded-with-fireworks-fight-back-with-tear-gas-as-mass-riots-turn-paris-into-warzone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNDREDS of protesters filled the streets of Paris as they clashed with police during marches against rising fuel prices. Water cannons and rounds of teargas were used by riot cops against thousand…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt 'global warming' report warns of worsening disasters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9732784135c4f4a8963daff79e2583e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As California's catastrophic wildfires recede and people rebuild after two hurricanes, a massive new federal report warns that these types of disasters are worsening in the United States because of global warming. The White House report quietly issued Friday also frequently contradicts President Donald Trump. The National Climate Assessment was written long before the deadly fires in California this month and before Hurricanes Florence and Michael raked the East Coast and Florida. It says warming-charged extremes "have already become more frequent, intense, widespread or of long duration." The report notes the last few years have smashed U.S. records for damaging weather, costing nearly $400 billion since 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INHUMANE CONDITIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/may/31/amazon-accused-of-treating-uk-warehouse-staff-like-robots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambulances called out 600 times in three years but online retailer denies GMB’s claims of unsafe working conditions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undocumented man arrested after leaving sanctuary to meet with immigration officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article222024860.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An undocumented man who has been living in a Durham church out of ICE’s reach is briefly leaving the church for an appointment with U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services, risking possible arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUMAN SCANNER:  He alerted people to the Thousand Oaks shooting, then warned of the California fires that came next...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-alerted-people-to-the-thousand-oaks-shooting-then-warned-of-the-california-fires-that-came-next/ar-BBQ1fGo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems won 47% of votes -- in Texas!</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2018/11/23/texas-democrats-won-47-votes-congressional-races-13-36-seats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Texas Republicans collected half the votes statewide in congressional races this month. ­But even after Democrats flipped two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAREHOUSE WALKOUTS</title>
      <link>https://www.techspot.com/news/77553-amazon-european-warehouse-employees-walking-out-black-friday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techspot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's European warehouse workers are going on strike to protest Black Friday and the company's alleged mistreatment of its employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey says Trump turning a 'blind eye' to Khashoggi murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkey-says-trump-turning-blind-eye-khashoggi-murder-102725202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey on Friday said US President Donald Trump intended to turn a "blind eye" to Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi's murder after he said it would not affect Washington's ties with Riyadh. Trump's backing of Saudi Arabia, his key ally against Iran, comes despite global outrage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi dismisses sexual harassment reports as 'baseless'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saudi-dismisses-sexual-harassment-reports-baseless-145626406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia dismissed Friday as "baseless" reports that detained activists, including women, faced sexual harassment and torture during interrogation. "These recent reports by Amnesty International and Human Rights Watch are baseless," the kingdom said in a statement. The activists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ:  Trump Expresses Dissatisfaction With Treasury Secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-expresses-dissatisfaction-with-treasury-secretary-1543006250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is expressing dissatisfaction with Treasury Secretary Mnuchin, blaming him for the appointment of a Fed chairman who has been raising interest rates, a move Mr. Trump worries will jeopardize economic gains ahead of 2020, people familiar with the matter said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Posted a Bad YELP Review. Then Her Nightmare Began...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/she-posted-a-bad-yelp-review-then-her-nightmare-began</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bachelorette slammed a wine bar on Yelp—and faced a campaign of cyberbullying and sexual insults. And she's not the only online reviewer to face harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks post worst Thanksgiving week decline since 2011...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/23/stock-markets-dow-set-for-losses-as-trading-resumes-for-half-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Friday as some of the most popular technology shares were under pressure once again, while a steep drop in oil prices also weighed on equities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top House Dem vows 'deep dive' into Kingdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/23/adam-schiff-house-dems-will-investigate-trump-financial-ties-to-saudis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are a whole set of potential financial conflicts of interest and emoluments problems that Congress will need to get to the bottom of," Schiff said in a Washington Post interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabid otter spooks Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/article222023765.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Department of Health found a seventh rabid raccoon in Kendall so the alert is now back on and extended to Jan. 19. A rabid otter that bit someone in the Palmetto Bay area leads to alert there, also.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million moved into Muslim homes to monitor, spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/china-uighur-muslim-people-move-homes-xinjiang-china-religion-a8648561.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Badboy Bieber now wants to be more like Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/married-man-justin-bieber-says-wants-more-jesus-212655809.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber marked his first Thanksgiving as a married man, saying that "love isn't always easy" but adding he was trying, like Jesus Christ, to be more patient and selfless. The Canadian pop singer, 24, who married model Hailey Baldwin in a hush-hush civil ceremony in September, told</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime menaces migrants as Tijuana declares crisis...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/crime-menaces-migrants-mexico-border-tijuana-declares-crisis-001725567.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 4,600 migrants from the bedraggled caravans whose advance has angered U.S. President Donald Trump are camped out with blankets and little food in an overcrowded stadium in Tijuana, whose mayor has declared a "humanitarian crisis." Trump has sent troops to the U.S.-Mexico border, authorized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi in plea negotiations with Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/83a7e797f6eb48399bbe9530e4bce9a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. (AP) — A conservative writer and associate of Trump confidant Roger Stone said Friday that he is in plea talks with special counsel Robert Mueller's team. Jerome Corsi told The Associated Press he has been negotiating a potential plea but declined to comment further. He said on a YouTube show earlier this month that he expected to be charged with lying to federal investigators, though he said at the time that he was innocent of wrongdoing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney first duty in DC? Flexing fundraising muscle...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/23/mitt-romney-senate-republicans-fundraising-pac-1012658</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator-elect Mitt Romney is already collecting chits, hosting a donor event Tuesday evening in Washington for his Believe in America PAC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to Judge ALL Behavior: Untrustworthy 'unable to move single step'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-21/beijing-to-judge-every-resident-based-on-behavior-by-end-of-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police new crime-fighting tactic: Ramming into 'moped bandits'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/london-police-ramming-into-thieves-on-mopeds-in-new-tactic-to-lower-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London police say their tough tactic of ramming violent “thieves” off their moped as they flee has helped bring down crime in the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewelry store robbers with gun thwarted by sword-swinging owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/jewelry-store-robbery-thwarted-by-sword-wielding-owners-1.4189022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University paid scholarship money for students to STAY at football games!</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2018/11/23/college-football-one-big-ten-school-paid-students-stay-games/2081646002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maryland students won $28,000 in scholarships for staying at home football games this season. The Big Ten school wants to increase attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Swedes implant chips into body, govt scrambles to figure out societal impact...</title>
      <link>https://business.financialpost.com/news/economy/swedens-push-to-get-rid-of-cash-has-some-saying-not-so-fast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;business.financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 4,000 Swedes have gone the microchip route as cash use fades and the government scrambles to figure out the effects on society and the economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets, Horses, Bribes: How Venezuelan Official Became Billionaire as Country Crumbled...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/jets-horses-and-bribes-how-a-venezuelan-official-became-a-billionaire-as-his-country-crumbled/18015844/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador — The opulent lifestyle of the Andrade family was as spectacular as the economic collapse of the country it left behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family peacock runs away with wild turkey flock...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcax.com/content/news/Vermont-peacock-on-the-run-with-wild-turkeys-501092271.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some ruffled feathers in southern Vermont on this Thanksgiving. A woman says her bird is missing but it's not a turkey. It's a peacock! We sent our Ike Bendavid down to Springfield to see if the bird came home for the holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owners who feed cats vegan diet could face prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/23/pet-owners-feed-cats-vegan-diet-could-face-prosecution/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The RSPCA has warned cat owners they could be prosecuted for feeding their pets vegan food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronaut 'serious harm' risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7810782/international-space-station-mysterious-space-bugs-astronauts-risk-harm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE International Space Station is infested with mysterious space bugs that may be leaving astronauts at risk of ‘serious harm’, according to a new study. Scientists discovered a thriving ecosystem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of frozen turtles wash ashore on Cape Cod...</title>
      <link>https://www.capecodtimes.com/news/20181122/dozens-of-dead-turtles-wash-ashore-on-cape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capecodtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLFLEET — Low temperatures and high winds killed most of the more than 80 turtles that washed ashore Thursday morning in Brewster, Orleans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmer crushed to death by dog driving forklift...</title>
      <link>https://www.bristolpost.co.uk/news/local-news/derek-mead-death-dog-truck-2251769</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bristolpost.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr Mead left his pet Jack Russell in the cab of the truck to open a gate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infectious bugs infest International Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/23/the-international-space-station-is-infested-with-mysterious-and-potentially-dangerous-space-bugs-8165994/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The orbiting space base is home to a thriving ecosystem of horrible little 'infectious organisms'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious tunnels discovered in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/mysterious-tunnels-discovered-in-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More evidence has emerged of a mysterious network of tunnels beneath the historic neighborhood of Ybor City in Tampa, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola in Congo now infecting newborns...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/ebola-in-congo-now-infecting-newborn-babies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization says a worrying number of the newest Ebola cases amid Congo's ongoing outbreak are in patients not usually known to catch the disease: babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugh Hefner dumped casket of sex tapes into sea...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/23/hugh-hefner-dumped-casket-of-sex-tapes-into-the-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He feared that his most famous and secret conquests would be exposed…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin report: Climate change intensifying...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/23/climate-change-intensifying-economy-impacted-federal-report-finds/2093291002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Administration released a major report on climate change Friday, one that emphasizes the dire threat that human-caused global warming poses to the U.S. and its citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Loses Millions MORE Subscribers...</title>
      <link>https://www.outkickthecoverage.com/espn-loses-two-million-more-subscribers-in-fiscal-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkickthecoverage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yesterday Disney announced in its yearly 10K filing that ESPN lost another two million subscribers in fiscal year 2018.  ESPN now has 86 million subscribers, down from over 100 million subscribers in 2011.  Now the positive for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt asks Supremes to hear trans military case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6fed8608b434a4395ba4d3ef3cf784f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration is asking the Supreme Court to fast-track cases on the president's decision to prevent certain transgender people from serving in the military. The administration asked the court on Friday to take up three cases on the issue. Lower courts had blocked the administration from implementing the policy. A three-judge panel of the 9th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals heard arguments in one of the cases in October but hasn't ruled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARRIORS Star Steph Curry Involved In Multi-Car Crash...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/11/23/stephen-curry-involved-in-multi-vehicle-crash-in-oakland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Golden State Warriors' star point guard Stephen Curry was involved in a multiple vehicle collision on Highway 24 in Oakland on Friday morning, according to the California Highway Patrol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIANSA chief Hayden hospitalized after stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/politics/michael-hayden-stroke/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Hayden, a former director of the CIA and National Security Agency, suffered a stroke earlier this week, his family said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro taps philosopher for Education Minister job...</title>
      <link>http://en.mercopress.com/2018/11/23/bolsonaro-picks-army-philosopher-for-education-minister-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.mercopress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's president-elect Jair Bolsonaro, Thursday announced he has chosen Colombian-born philosopher Ricardo Vélez Rodríguez as his future Education Minister.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Humans NOT cause of mass animal extinctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/11/23/humans-didnt-cause-animal-extinctions-africa-science-study-says/2090400002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In research published in the journal Science, authors say extinctions of mammal communities in Africa occurred before evidence of human hunting.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
