<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Tried to Take Down These Hackers. They're Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-pentagon-tried-to-take-down-these-hackers-theyre-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Cyber Command and Microsoft, among others, launched operations on the eve of the election meant to hobble a Russian-speaking hacking group. But it’s rising again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUCKER 'TENSION' WITH FOXNEWS EXECS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/11/media/tucker-carlson-fox-news/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson is furious with Fox News executives for not vigorously defending him amid his evidence-free claims that the National Security Agency spied on him in a conspiracy to destroy his TV show, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald's lawyers might be penalized over Michigan election case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-government-and-politics-elections-michigan-e45f806062edd8a7ba81cefd8f3f2638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — A federal judge is considering whether to order financial penalties or other sanctions against some of former President Donald Trump's lawyers who signed onto a lawsuit last year challenging Michigan's election results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRANSON BACK FROM SPACE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-technology-science-spacex-richard-branson-37fd721264b1421f8a1223ee5e5626e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRUTH OR CONSEQUENCES, N.M. (AP) — Swashbuckling billionaire Richard Branson hurtled into space aboard his own winged rocket ship Sunday, bringing astro-tourism a step closer to reality and beating out his exceedingly richer rival Jeff Bezos .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: WHAT TUCKER IS DOING IN FAKE LOG CABIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/07/tucker-carlson-today-americana-fake-log-cabin/619411/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fox host has a new daytime show, and he’s using it to poison the meaning of patriotism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marriage to robots 'normal by end of century'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3263535/married-robots-normal-end-of-century/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GETTING married to a robot will be considered normal by the end of the century, an expert claims. Dr David Levy argues sex and relationships with androids could even be common in the next 30 years.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bright lights 'swarm' ISS on live feed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/bright-lights-swarm-iss-live-24510859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of the International Space Station (ISS) being surrounded by bright objects has sparked conspiracy theories that there are aliens or UFOs flying around in space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking 'gut microbiome' -- massive significance to health...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/jul/11/unlocking-the-gut-microbiome-and-its-massive-significance-to-our-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are only just discovering the enormous impact of our gut health. Rebecca Seal reveals how it could hold the key to everything from tackling obesity to overcoming anxiety and boosting immunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few options for Biden as vaccination pace hits wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/12/biden-boosting-vaccination-rates-499047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is now strategizing over how to manage a nation with 68 percent of the population at least partially vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engagement ring sales soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/10/business/engagement-ring-sales/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As wedding aisles open up, more Americans are getting down on one knee and popping the question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Wall St Sees Blowout Profits Ahead...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/12/wall-street-sees-blowout-profits-ahead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Optimism blooms in earnings season After closing the books on the second quarter, executives are the most positive they have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. highest in months...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/troubling-spike-l-county-sees-183730756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. County has recorded more than 3,000 new coronavirus cases in three days, as viral transmission increases among unvaccinated people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER to discuss booster...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-a8beda2708e148f5e887a434553da845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pfizer says it plans to meet with top U.S. health officials Monday to discuss the drugmaker’s request for federal authorization of a third dose of its COVID-19 vaccine as President Joe Biden’s chief medical adviser acknowledged that "it is entirely conceivable, maybe likely” that booster shots will be needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: California and other parts of West broil and burn...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arizona-california-wildfires-ap-top-news-us-news-6b4bd2147d7185049405c176979e0615</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters working in searing heat struggled to contain the largest wildfire in California this year while state power operators urged people to conserve energy after a huge wildfire in neighboring Oregon disrupted the flow of electricity from three major transmission lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red tide leaves 15 tons of dead fish on Tampa Bay shore; Experts warn more destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/another-e2-80-98red-tide-e2-80-99-left-15-tons-of-dead-fish-on-tampa-bay-e2-80-99s-shore-and-experts-warn-of-more-destruction/ar-AAM3583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A red tide is responsible for dead fish continuing to wash up on the shores of St. Petersburg, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrations in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/562487-demonstrations-break-out-in-miami-as-protestors-march-against-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people joined together in Miami, Fla., on Sunday to protest in solidarity with the Cubans who are speaking out against their government amid food shortages and high prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brewing battle over tax hikes to test Dem unity...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/562463-brewing-battle-over-tax-hikes-to-test-democratic-unity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An emerging proposal from the White House and Senate Democratic leaders to pay for President Biden’s infrastructure agenda is setting the stage for a major battle in Congress that will test the support of moderates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida, Land of Gleaming Condos, Frets After Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/12/florida-the-land-of-gleaming-condos-frets-after-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. — Modern Florida was built on condos like Champlain Towers South. “A new lifestyle is evolving in Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Defeat, England Black Soccer Players Face Racist Outburst...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/12/after-defeat-englands-black-soccer-players-face-a-racist-outburst/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — England wrapped its arms around its national soccer team the morning after its history-making run ended in heartbreaking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Games In CA, FL Linked To Test Massive 'Kill Web'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41472/war-games-in-california-and-florida-linked-to-test-massive-kill-web-and-autonomous-drone-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Test pilot explains how the Air Force linked two major developmental exercises that included cutting-edge long-range targeting and autonomous drones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avocado farmers take up arms as Mexico violence spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210712-avocado-farmers-take-up-arms-as-mexico-violence-spikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avocado farmers take up arms as Mexico violence spikes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother found home in Norfolk gang. Then they shot her in face, left her for dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/a-mother-found-a-home-in-a-norfolk-gang-then-they-shot-her-in-the/article_d12d543c-25c3-57ac-ab11-d7e1f5332cf0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. — Shot in the face, stabbed in the head and nearly drowned with bleach, Brianna Arrington had been dying for about nine hours by the time someone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro wages Trumpian campaign to sow doubts about voting...</title>
      <link>https://tylerpaper.com/ap/international/bolsonaro-wages-trumpian-campaign-to-sow-doubts-about-voting/article_1d54e698-a7f5-59b9-9c57-854965ccdb3f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tylerpaper.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil’s election is 15 months away, but President Jair Bolsonaro warns almost daily of cheating, chicanery and hacking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Lawyer Makes Moves to Represent Britney Spears...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/11/prominent-lawyer-makes-moves-to-represent-britney-spears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prominent Hollywood lawyer has had discussions in recent days with Britney Spears about representing her in her conservatorship battle,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds suspected mastermind of Haiti presidential assassination plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mystery-surrounds-suspected-mastermind-of-haiti-presidential-assassination-plot/ar-AAM36z1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People dumped pets into lakes, officials say. Now football-size goldfish taking over...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/people-dumped-their-pets-into-lakes-officials-say-now-football-size-goldfish-are-taking-over/ar-AAM2q5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldfish are an invasive species that can damage habitats, and their presence appears to be a growing problem in waterways across the United States and around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlottesville takes down more statues; Offensive to Native Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/charlottesville-takes-down-two-more-statues-deemed-offensive-to-native-americans-in-weekend-of-removals/ar-AAM262c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city previously removed a statue of Robert E. Lee that was the focal point of a deadly 2017 rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demand end of dictatorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article252713788.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an unprecedented display of anger and frustration, thousands of people took to the streets Sunday in cities and towns across Cuba, including Havana, to call for the end of the decades-old dictatorship and demand food and vaccines, as shortages of basic necessities have reached crisis proportions and COVID-19 cases have soared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans Denounce 'Misery' in Biggest Protests in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/11/cubans-denounce-misery-in-biggest-protests-in-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Shouting “Freedom” and other anti-government slogans, hundreds of Cubans took to the streets in cities around the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs complicate effort to recover...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-caribbean-coronavirus-pandemic-united-nations-haiti-f1ebc8a7adb5d295c69ad89fce484b99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — Gangs in Haiti have long been financed by powerful politicians and their allies — and many Haitians fear those backers may be losing control of the increasingly powerful armed groups who have driven thousands of people from their homes as they battle over territory, kill civilians and raid warehouses of food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA building solar-powered neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/tesla-launches-initiative-to-build-first-solar-neighborhood-in-austin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The initiative, provisionally named SunHouse at Easton Park, will be the first Tesla Solar neighborhood and the nation’s most sustainable residential community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McGregor breaks silence after being stretchered out of with broken leg...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3262291/conor-mcgregor-dustin-poirier-ufc-264-you-need-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONOR MCcGREGOR insists UFC “needs people like me” as he vowed to fight on despite breaking his leg in defeat to Dustin Poirier. The Irish superstar has now lost three of his last four …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLIONARE TOUCHES THE HEAVENS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3251842/virgin-galactic-space-launch-richard-branson-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIR Richard Branson’s Virgin Galactic space launch has won his battle to become with Elon Musk to become the first billionaire in space. The rocket ship launched the 70-year-old and his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS ON THE CROISETTE:  CANNES JEWEL THIEF ROBS ACTRESS' HOTEL ROOM...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/jodie-turner-smith-cannes-jewelry-theft-1235017019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jodie Turner-Smith was a victim of jewelry theft Friday in Cannes, a local source tells Variety. On Sunday afternoon in France, Turner-Smith — who attended the festival for the premiere of he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNORES FOR PENN?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/flag-day-sean-penn-cannes-dylan-penn-1235016789/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not to be outdone by Matt Damon, Sean Penn looked like he was about to cry at the Saturday night premiere of “Flag Day.” The drama earned a four-minute standing ovation broken up by remarks from Pe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Releases Pro-Vaccine Single Sparking Anger From Fans...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/07/10/juvenile-releases-pro-vaccine-single-vax-that-thang-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juvenile turned his hit song "Back That Thang Up" into a pro-vaccine anthem called "Vax That Thang Up," sparking backlash from fans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panetta calls for vaccine mandate in military...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/562401-panetta-calls-on-biden-to-mandate-covid-19-vaccines-for-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Defense Secretary Leon Panetta said that President Biden should require all military members to get the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP NEXT: BEZOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/richard-branson-virgin-galactic-test-flight-4accdc24-ef49-43f6-9614-80829c418ff0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic hopes to open up full commercial operations next year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
