<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BARRACK: Commercial Mortgages on Brink of Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/real-estate-billionaire-barrack-says-230309693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Real estate investor Tom Barrack said the U.S. commercial-mortgage market is on the brink of collapse and predicted a “domino effect” of catastrophic economic consequences if banks and government don’t take prompt action to keep borrowers from defaulting.Barrack, chairman and chief executive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss of Smell Highlights Unusual Marker...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/lost-sense-of-smell-may-be-peculiar-clue-to-coronavirus-infection/articleshow/74767666.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several patients who have had symptoms consistent with coronavirus, but who have not been tested or are still awaiting results, described losing senses of smell and taste, even though their noses were clear and not congested. The loss occurred regardless of how sick they got, or whether they were congested. Using nasal drops or sprays did not help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing blunders crippled US response as coronavirus spread...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c335958b1f8f6a37b19b421bc7759722</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A series of missteps at the nation's top public health agency caused a critical shortage of reliable laboratory tests for the coronavirus, hobbling the federal response as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Olympics to be postponed...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/olympics/2020/03/23/olympics-2020-ioc-member-tokyo-games-postponed-dick-pound-coronavirus/2899848001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran IOC member Dick Pound told USA TODAY Sports that "postponement has been decided" for the 2020 Olympics, and that it won't start July 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors, Nurses 'Truly Scared To Come To Work' For First Time Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-doctors-nurses-medical-supply-shortages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a shortage of personal protective equipment, some have resorted to using bandanas to cover their faces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy records smaller increase in virus cases for 2nd day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0a69c921eb603e6a85fd5c2c490d66a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italy has recorded a smaller day-to-day increase in new coronavirus cases for the second straight day, officials said Monday while cautioning it was too soon to know if the worst is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS LOCKS DOWN UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11238253/boris-johnson-coronavirus-lockdown-fines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson tonight drastically locked down Britain in the most desperate bid yet to halt the coronavirus spread. In a massive ramping of government restrictions, the PM ordered the whole country…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spit On, Yelled At, Attacked: Chinese-Americans Fear for Safety...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/spit-on-yelled-at-attacked-chinese-americans-fear-for-their-safety/ar-BB11AEg5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz calls on President to address medical supply shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Sen-Cruz-calls-on-Trump-to-address-medical-15151571.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruz joins many Democrats, and some Republicans, in urging Trump to use war powers and compel American manufacturers to make more medical supplies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen details relationship with Soon-Yi in new memoir...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/23/woody-allen-details-relationship-with-soon-yi-in-new-memoir-couldnt-keep-our-hands-off-each-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen also blasted his ex-girlfriend Mia Farrow for her “Ahab-like quest” to destroy him with sex abuse allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite hackers target WHO as cyberattacks spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-who-hack-exclusive-idUSKBN21A3BN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elite hackers tried to break into the World Health Organization earlier this mon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard arrives at JAVITS to build first of 4 emergency hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8144037/National-Guard-arrives-Javits-Center-Manhattan-build-FOUR-emergency-hospitals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of National Guard troops arrived at the Jacob Javits Center in Manhattan on Monday to begin setting up four temporary hospital units inside the sprawling 1.3 million-sq-ft convention center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana Gov says his state has fastest growing cases in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8143211/Louisiana-Gov-says-state-fastest-growing-coronavirus-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana Governor John Bel Edwards said on Sunday that Louisiana had seen the highest initial growth rate of confirmed cases globally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Finally Available In LA, But Only To High-Risk Groups...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/03/23/coronavirus-testing-finally-available-to-city-of-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The testing is limited to only certain at-risk groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Correspondent Has 'Suspected Case'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/03/23/white-house-correspondent-suspected-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Correspondents' Association President Jonathan Karl informed the press corps Monday that &amp;quot;one of our colleagues has a suspected case of&amp;quot; coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Says Beijing's Virus Lies Just Fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/twitter-says-beijings-coronavirus-lies-are-just-fine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese officials have spread disinformation about the origin of the coronavirus, including blaming its creation on the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Convention Planners Look at Contingency Options...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/23/us/politics/democratic-convention-milwaukee-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus crisis has created uncertainty about whether the gathering, scheduled for mid-July in Milwaukee, can still take place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS BLOCK RESCUE FOR SECOND DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/congress-phase-3-stimulus-negotiations-fail-ab006a3c-fe77-4a3a-9a39-79cf9709c622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions flared on the Senate floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals trying to figure out how to ration ventilators...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/hospitals-figure-ration-ventilators/story?id=69748177</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with more critically ill COVID-19 patients than equipment to treat them, New York’s hospitals are mapping out how they can ration care and equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women face childbirth alone...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Family/imagined-women-face-childbirth-partners-amid-coronavirus-outbreak/story?id=69712411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the coronavirus outbreak and changing hospital policies, women face giving birth alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strip club forced to close, so dancers now do delivery...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/coronavirus/2020/03/portland-strip-club-forced-to-close-so-dancers-now-do-delivery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portland finds a way. Close down her strip clubs, and dancers will do delivery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong appeared to have under control, then it let guard down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/23/asia/hong-kong-coronavirus-quarantine-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the sudden surge in cases in Hong Kong shows, quarantines and social distancing must continue well beyond the initial wave of cases, if another round of infections is to be avoided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan Still Finding Symptom-Free Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-03-23/wuhan-still-finding-symptom-free-virus-cases-caixin-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Producer Begs Closing Of 30 ROCK For Health Reasons...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/msnbc-senior-segment-producer-close-30-rockefeller-center-health-scare-coronavirus-1202890215/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editors’ Note: With full acknowledgment of the big-picture implications of a pandemic that has already claimed thousands of lives, cratered global economies and closed international borders, Deadli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions growing in White House... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/tensions-brewing-inside-white-house-over-economic-consequences-coronavirus-response-n1166671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health officials have pushed the White House to urge Americans to stay at home in an effort to blunt the spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic 'accelerating', WHO warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/coronavirus-live-updates-pandemic-is-accelerating-who-warns/ar-BB11z4C6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Can't Jump In Front of the Microphone and Push Him Down'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/dr-fauci-vents-on-trumps-false-coronavirus-statements-i-cant-jump-in-front-of-the-microphone-and-push-him-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci established himself over the last few weeks as a leading member of the White House's anti-coronavirus task force, but in a new interview, he outlined multiple points of disagree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven earthquakes rattle Oklahoma in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article241429526.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 60 Italian priests have died... </title>
      <link>https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/at-least-60-italian-priests-have-died-after-contracting-coronavirus-78399</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholicnewsagency.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past week alone, more than 3,000 people have died in Italy after contracting the coronavirus. Among the dead, there have been at least 60 priests this month, according to local sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Slams Trump 'Failure'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/489014-biden-trumps-failure-of-planning-and-preparation-worsened-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden on Monday accused President Trump of dithering in the early days of the coronavirus, saying that a “failure of planning and preparation” by the White House has worsened the health and economic crises the nation face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients lying on floor at overrun Madrid hospital...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/23/coronavirus-patients-spotted-lying-on-floor-at-overrun-madrid-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilling scenes have emerged from hospitals in Madrid, Spain, that have been overrun by coronavirus patients — showing some sprawled out over the floor. The Severo Ochoa de Leganes Hospital has bee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS USE DRONES FOR LOCKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/california-police-to-use-chinese-made-patrol-drones-with-night-vision-cameras-during-coronavirus-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California police department is planning on using drones equipped with cameras and loudspeakers to monitor a coronavirus shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI AND TRUMP CLASH</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/opinion/article/I-know-but-what-do-you-want-me-to-do-Fauci-s-15150393.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci's interview with Science magazine began on an inauspicious note. Asked how he's doing right now, Fauci said he was "exhausted" but "good."  "I mean, I'm not, to my knowledge, coronavirus-infected," he said, before adding with a laugh: "To my knowledge, I haven't been fired."  The half-joke was a sign of things to come. What followed were several exchanges that should help people take stock of President Donald Trump's response to the coronavirus. Repeatedly, Fauci tacitly and even openly admitted that comments made by the commander in chief are not true and are not in line with what the nation's leading infectious disease expert is advising.  In short, it's precisely what the critical coverage of Trump has been saying for weeks, but that Trump's many and ardent defenders have applied blinders on themselves to ignore.  The interviewer, Jon Cohen, asked whether Fauci would acknowledge that Trump says things he disagrees with, and Fauci seemed to grant the premise - albeit diplomatically. Fauci maintained that, "I don't disagree on the substance" - with "on the substance" being the key phrase - but then added: "It is expressed in a way that I would not express it, because it could lead to some misunderstanding about what the facts are about a given subject."  If we're going to distill that down, he's essentially saying the president is confusing people - at the bare minimum. The exchange highlights the mixed messages the country has been getting in recent days, in particular, about the promise of certain drugs to treat coronavirus. While Fauci has warned that evidence of the drugs' effectiveness is "anecdotal" and that there is no "magic drug" to treat coronavirus, Trump said Friday that he "disagreed" with Fauci, at least in part, and has repeatedly hailed a malaria drug in particular as a possible...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump weighs easing stay-at-home advice to curb economic rout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-says-coronavirus-cure-cannot-be-worse-than-the-problem-itself/ar-BB11zYyS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED PUMPS ALL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/23/fed-announces-a-slew-of-new-programs-to-help-markets-including-open-ended-asset-purchases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve launched a barrage of programs aimed at helping markets function more efficiently amid the coronavirus crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Spring Breakers Begin Testing Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-florida-spring-break-test-positive-covid-19-college-students-not-social-distancing-university-of-tampa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This comes after spring-breakers in Florida​ were criticized for ignoring social distancing guidelines and packing beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York coronavirus cases surge 38% overnight to 20,875...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/23/coronavirus-cases-top-20000-in-new-york-state-with-12000-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grim toll also includes 157 deaths in the Empire State, Cuomo said — representing more than a third of the 463 deaths nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5 BILLION STAY HOME...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d1ddda5b644a9cdd6b844a196377b88e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The hunt for masks, ventilators and other medical supplies consumed the U.S. and Europe, as more than 1.5 billion people — one-fifth of the world's population — were urged or ordered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK internet capacity could be RATIONED to prioritize 'critical' apps and websites...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/11232963/uk-internet-rationed-prioritise-apps-websites-traffic-speeds/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN’S internet capacity could be “rationed” to prioritise critical apps and websites, experts have told The Sun. It comes as networks and apps reveal how the coronavirus crisi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There's a lot we don't know': Researchers look at how coronavirus turns body against itself and kills...</title>
      <link>https://www.theeagle.com/news/national/there-s-a-lot-we-don-t-know-uw-researchers/article_4791b57c-6058-5913-85e6-4fbb72d00156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — Last Tuesday, a scientist working in a secure upper-floor laboratory in the University of Washington Medical Center’s South Lake Union campus cracked open a vial containing one of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Tests hard to get -- unless you have money, fame and right doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/coronavirus-tests-hard-to-get-unless-you-have-money-fame/article_07a0c9c0-c71f-59e8-b919-aa6f00b0507f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — As people across the country were unable to get tested for COVID-19, a Santa Monica, Calif., pediatrician emailed the parents of his patients with a pricey but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar husband hospitalized with coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/amy-klobuchar-husband-coronavirus-60e1f49d-9852-4d50-990d-432af8cc165a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She said she has not seen him for two weeks — and will not be tested or self-quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump weighs easing stay-at-home advice to curb economic rout...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200323135136-fho7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRUMP (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Trump aims to decide economic course on coronavirus at end of 15-day plan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Database Exposes 200 Million Americans' Personal Info...</title>
      <link>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/a-mysterious-database-exposed-200-million-americans-personal-info</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tomshardware.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And we have no idea who it belonged to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon General: 'This week it's going to get bad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/surgeon-general-has-coronavirus-warning-week-it-s-going-get-n1166421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disease is spreading, the surgeon general said, because many people are not following the guidance to stay at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen dies day after testing positive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/23/british-teen-dies-one-day-after-testing-positive-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teenager aged just 18 has died in the UK — one day after testing positive for COVID-19, according to officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hiker survives 200-foot fall during Mount Washington descent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae0b5db8f7db5eaa434e80739e25fbd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRETTON WOODS, N.H. (AP) — A hiker descending Mount Washington who fell about 200 feet (60.9 meters) and got hurt was rescued with the help of the Cog Railway train that takes visitors up and down...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen memoir released...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6e7f6ad6a0daf117ec54c765bdf838b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Woody Allen's memoir, dropped by its original publisher after widespread criticism, has found a new home, The Associated Press has learned. The 400-page book, still called...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What do you want me to do?': Fauci's strikingly honest review of Trump response...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/03/i-m-going-keep-pushing-anthony-fauci-tries-make-white-house-listen-facts-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The infectious disease researcher has become America’s most trusted coronavirus expert</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far more people in USA have coronavirus than think...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Far-more-people-in-the-U-S-have-the-coronavirus-15150191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an infectious disease epidemiologist who's worked on pandemics for two decades, I've talked in recent days to journalists and health officials around the United States and from halfway around the world about how to stop the coronavirus. They all have the same questions: How many tests do we need? How should we use tests? For each case we know about, how many more cases are out there? What's the best way to find undiagnosed cases? Should we do "active case finding," which involves testing everyone who is mildly ill, then isolating known cases and quarantining and isolating their contacts? Instead - or in addition - should we implement intense social distancing, close schools and take other similar measures?  Everyone asks the same important, interrelated questions. In one respect, the answer is the same for all of them: We must vastly expand our testing capacity. No country has controlled transmission effectively without massive testing capacity. The United States currently has a sliver of the capacity we need, which is only a tiny fraction of that available in other countries. South Korea has performed over 320,000 tests - almost one for every 150 people. That is 30 times the testing per capita that we have done in the United States. Exceptional teams are racing to solve testing bottlenecks at local and state levels (Massachusetts is just one example), filling the vacuum left by the complete absence of federal leadership. Regulatory and technical hurdles accounted for early delays. Now that we're past those, several shortages are getting in the way. We don't have enough protective equipment for testers, nor swabs for sampling or reagents to extract genetic material from the virus. We don't have enough physical test kits, or enough human power to run large-scale testing. The result is that we have no idea how many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrifying images show patients lying on floor of packed hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8142013/Horrifying-images-coronavirus-patients-lying-floor-packed-Madrid-hospital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scenes were reportedly recorded at the Infanta Leonor Hospital and the Severo Ochoa de Leganes Hospital in the Spanish capital Madrid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATION RAGE: Couple Throws Fit At Supermarket Over Not Being Able To Buy 552 Cans Of Soda...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/2020/03/23/coronavirus-mountain-dew-kroger-couple-552-cans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Kentucky couple reportedly tried to buy as many Mountain Dew cans at a Louisville Kroger earlier [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People in China Need Green Light From App to Move Around Country...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-china-green-light-alibaba-091822087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- To get permission to leave China’s coronavirus epicenter and return to his job in Hong Kong, a Chinese banker needed two things: a letter from his company and a green health code from Alipay.The man, who gave his name only as Clarence because of privacy concerns, secured the necessary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump appears to waffle on shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/502a3b1afb9c5d1bc14e6af77d112207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Top Trump administration officials and congressional leaders struggled Monday to finalize a nearly $2 trillion economic rescue package as the coronavirus crisis deepened, even as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon General: 'This week it's going to get bad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/video/us-surgeon-general-jerome-adams-on-coronavirus-this-week-it-s-going-to-get-bad-81091141801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Jerome Adams, the U.S. surgeon general, tells TODAY that “we need to come together as a nation” to fight the coronavirus outbreak but “a lot of people think this can’t happen to them.” He urges Americans to stay at home despite an overnight tweet from President Trump saying “we cannot let the cure be worse than the problem,” saying we all need to act as if we already have the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking video shows how far coughs can travel through air...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/coronavirus-shocking-video-shows-how-21738511</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists from Bauhaus University in Weimar have revealed exactly what happens when we cough, and why it's wise to stay home even if you don’t think you have the virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service employee sick...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/488963-secret-service-employee-tests-positive-for-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Secret Service employee has tested positive for the coronavirus, the agency said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beautiful World Beside the Broken One...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/23/the-beautiful-world-beside-the-broken-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE — A two-week bout with flu turned me into a person I didn’t recognize — a hopeless, coughing, exhausted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm 26. It Sent Me to Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/23/im-26-coronavirus-sent-me-to-the-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m 26. I don’t have any prior autoimmune or respiratory conditions. I work out six times a week, and abstain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Just Called to Say... the Phone Call Is Back...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/22/i-just-called-to-say-the-phone-call-is-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other night my friend Margot called. It’s not unusual for me to hear from Margot — we’ve been friends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am constitutional lawyer. I see govt using Covid-19 to take away rights'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/op-ed/483758-coronavirus-constitutional-rights-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do we really think “it can’t happen here” in America? Could we quarantine the constitution? Are we doing it already?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS DELAYED A YEAR?</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/off-whos-saying-over-tokyo-olympics-postponement-081022956--oly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the deadly coronavirus spreads around the globe, doubts grow over whether the Tokyo 2020 Olympics will go ahead as scheduled from July 24 to August 9. -- International Olympic Committee president Thomas Bach, announcing on Sunday that a postponement was under consideration. &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t think</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA orders first shutdown of website over coronavirus fraud...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-orders-first-shutdown-website-over-coronavirus-fraud-023738032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Department of Justice announced Sunday it had shut down a website claiming to sell a coronavirus vaccine, in its first act of federal enforcement against fraud in connection with the pandemic. Lawsuits had been filed against the site coronavirusmedicalkit.com, which claimed to sell vaccines for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On call with Trump officials, police chief pleads: 'Stop testing NBA players, start testing first responders'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/call-trump-officials-police-chief-pleads-stop-testing/story?id=69739541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the International Association of Chiefs of Police pleaded Friday with Trump administration officials for help dealing with the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington to pick which companies survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/03/22/bailout-coronavirus-congress-crisis-142961</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with the biggest economic bailout ever, a lot of firms won't make it through the coronavirus crisis. How should Congress handle the triage?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Gov. Pritzker mocks Trump's efforts...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/22/wild-west-states-pritzker-says-141580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“All I can say is get to work or get out of the way.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Tread Lightly as Pandemic Spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-tread-lightly-as-pandemic-spreads/ar-BB11yiwv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWSON: Please can our politicians stop calling this a war. It's nothing like it... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-8141097/DOMINIC-LAWSON-politicians-stop-calling-war-like-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOMINIC LAWSON: As so often in her 68-year reign, the Queen gets it right. In her statement to the country on meeting the challenge of the coronavirus, she did not once use the word 'war'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus reveals financial irresponsibility of Americans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/488906-coronavirus-reveals-financial-irresponsibility-of-americans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This national crisis reminds us to save for the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS DELAYED A YEAR?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ioc-admits-postponing-olympics-option-cancellation-not-agenda-211002862--oly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The International Olympic Committee said Sunday that postponing the 2020 Olympics is one of its options as the world grapples with the coronavirus pandemic, but that cancellation of the Tokyo showpiece was "not on the agenda". The IOC has faced strong pressure to push back the Games, scheduled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisis can't bridge partisan divide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-coronavirus-crisis-cant-bridge-191231600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is so politically polarized that even views of the coronavirus pandemic split along party lines, polls show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ hosts 10-hour INSTAGRAM party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dont-stop-music-dj-hosts-10-hour-instagram-230426818.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus has upended daily lives, with thousands of deaths around the world. Celebrity DJ D-Nice has begun hosting virtual dance parties on his Instagram Live channel in an effort to lift spirits as people self-isolate over coronavirus concerns. Many of his A-list friends -- including Rihanna</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress May Allow Fed to Purchase Longer-Term Corporate Debt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/congress-may-allow-fed-purchase-153000316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Congress is likely to pass legislation Monday clearing the way for more emergency action from the Federal Reserve, following already unprecedented steps from the central bank to keep credit markets liquid.Though details were unclear, lawmakers and Trump adminstration officials on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia steps up efforts as second wave of infections strikes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asia-steps-virus-efforts-second-wave-infections-strikes-065250439.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Australia's Bondi Beach to the streets of New Delhi, authorities across Asia have ramped up efforts to stem the spread of the deadly novel coronavirus amid fears of a second wave of infections in places where outbreaks had appeared under control. Tighter travel restrictions were imposed in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic prompts rare questioning of Thai monarchy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200322230729-bnkdg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/THAILAND-MONARCHY (PIX):Coronavirus pandemic prompts rare questioning of Thai monarchy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi King imposes curfew...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200322224027-pflg0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SAUDI (URGENT):Saudi King Salman imposes curfew to curb coronavirus spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO: 80% WILL GET VIRUS; NINE MONTH CRISIS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/574277/new-york-cuomo-slams-groups-crisis-could-last-nine-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York Governor Andrew Cuomo has warned that 80% of New York state’s population could become infected with the coronavirus and said the crisis could last as long as nine months. Cuomo’s sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says 'no need' to postpone November vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-says-e2-80-98no-need-e2-80-99-to-postpone-november-vote-over-virus/ar-BB11yfHo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tylenol, soup and internet can treat most symptoms of COVID-19 [whether you have it or not]...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/tylenol-soup-and-the-internet-can-treat-most-symptoms-of-covid-19-whether-you-have-it-or-not/ar-BB11yfoQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Rate May Soar to 30%... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/us-jobless-rate-may-soar-to-30-25-fed-e2-80-99s-bullard-says/ar-BB11y3ER</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ gov. vows to 'take action' against people who don't stay home...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gov-murphy-vows-action-to-enforce-nj-stay-at-home-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy expressed anger Sunday at reports of people in New Jersey ignoring his stay-at-home order and warned “We're going to take action."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Govt uses Bluetooth to track exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/singapore-coronavirus-big-brother-bd7cec2b-eb47-4b49-a337-f4f4ecff57f2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore is tracing the coronavirus in ways that are simultaneously impressive and terrifying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna calls virus the great equalizer in bathtub video...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/22/madonna-calls-coronavirus-the-great-equalizer-in-bizarre-bathtub-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 61-year-old singer preaches to her fans from her tub, surrounded by candles and wearing nothing but jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Nobel laureate predicts a quicker recovery: 'We're going to be fine'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-nobel-laureate-predicts-quicker-210318391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nobel laureate predicted China's recovery weeks before it happened. Analyzing the numbers, he sees a much brighter global outcome than many experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela prohibits company layoffs and suspends credit collections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200323001838-oqzqs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VENEZUELA:Venezuela prohibits company layoffs and suspends credit collections over coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS ON THE BRINK</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/team-canada-says-wont-participate-020548863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The COC and CPC urgently call on the International Olympic Committee (IOC), and the International Paralympic Committee (IPC) and the World Health Organization (WHO) to postpone the Games for one year and we offer them our full support in helping navigate all the complexities that rescheduling the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel in quarantine... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f71e89eacd7cc6f84b81991c03e82c31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German Chancellor Angela Merkel has gone into quarantine after being informed that a doctor who administered a vaccine to her has tested positive for the new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen.  Rand Paul Tests Positive... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c3db22a242e9577126052dece8285d2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. Rand Paul of Kentucky has tested positive for the novel coronavirus, becoming the first case of COVID-19 in the Senate and raising fears about the further transmission of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Public places stand abandoned...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af7b4e94c6c0b86f6d35f4c79be99cf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are places meant for people. New York’s Grand Central Terminal — a common metaphor for “busy” in much of the English-speaking world — dotted with only scattered commuters. The Grand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC trying to keep crowds from cherry blossoms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5720c07cc92db122d5f2e147c02b1063</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As signature cherry blossom trees go through peak bloom in the nation's capital, officials in the District of Columbia are resorting to mass street closures to keep large crowds...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
