<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The controversial sale of 'Big John,' world's largest Triceratops...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/the-controversial-sale-of-big-john-the-worlds-largest-triceratops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fossil's $7.7-million sale has some experts worried that ancient bones' rising prices will put more scientifically valuable fossils out of reach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol rioter gets asylum in Belarus; Paraded on state TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10178457/Capitol-rioter-wanted-FBI-attacking-cops-gets-asylum-Belarus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evan Neumann, 48, gave a sit-down interview with Belarusian state run television on Sunday describing how he fled the United States as he faces charges for his alleged role in the Capitol riots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joy at JFK as first flights arrive from UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10176609/Miles-long-traffic-delay-greets-drivers-trying-Mexico-travel-restrictions-end.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BA Flight 001 carrying 331 passengers and Virgin Atlantic Flight VS3 carrying another 350 arrived shortly after 11am at Terminals 4 and 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists tweak brains to cause illness, gaining psychosomatic insights...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-scientists-tweak-brains-to-cause-illness-gaining-psychosomatic-insights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After making mice sick using their neurons alone, researchers at the Technion believe they may have laid foundations for brain-based cures to inflammation in humans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin says Hollywood should hire cops to inspect on-set firearms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/alec-baldwin-says-hollywood-should-hire-police-officers-to-vet-prop-guns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin took to social media Monday to urge Hollywood to hire police officers on all film and television sets that utilize guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNFIT NATION: 2 In 5 Exhausted -- After Walking Up Flight Of Stairs!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/exhausted-walking-up-stairs-exercise-pain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of respondents feel like exercising would be a lot of work and 47 percent dread post-workout soreness or aches and pains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative thinkers, ideologues announce creation of 'fiercely independent' college

...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/politics/article/University-of-Austin-college-Bari-Weiss-16602677.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative-led university says it is dedicated to 'the fearless pursuit of truth'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feral Hogs Run Wild Across Texas; 'Catastrophic'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/11/05/feral-hogs-presence-growing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The animals seem to have the run of North Texas and in search of nutrient rich grubs, it's no surprise that they've behaving like pigs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Israel activists publish information of Israeli security officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/anti-israel-activists-publish-information-of-israeli-security-officials-684388</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group, known as Justice for Palestine, began publishing the information of a number of officials from the Mossad, IDF and Shin Bet, in mid-October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVENATION Hit With Restraining Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/livenation-restraining-order-astroworld-1254721/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cristian Guzman’s lawyer asked the court to prevent the concert promoter from “damaging” or “modifying” “any evidence of negligence” at the scene</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon mocks senator's penis...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/tesla-stock-elon-musk-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk asked Twitter users whether he should sell 10% of his stake in the company. They said yes. Was it all a farce? Probably.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investment firm will need permission to hire white men...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/one-of-worlds-largest-investment-firms-will-need-permission-to-hire-white-men</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaders at one of the largest investment firms in the world will need to ask permission to hire white men as it rolls out a diversity hiring initiative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Thieves Ransack Apartments In NYC Building Ravaged By Deadly Fire...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/07/bronx-high-rise-fire-mott-haven-mitchel-houses-aiden-hayward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neighbors in the Bronx were just starting to pick up the pieces after last week's a fatal fire in their 20-story building, when they became victims once again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Admin Amassing Millions of Records on Gun Owners...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/biden-admin-amassing-millions-of-records-on-u-s-gun-owners-amid-new-crackdown-on-firearms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration in just the past year alone stockpiled the records of more than 54 million U.S. gun owners and is poised to drastically alter gun regulations to ensure that information on Americans who own firearms ultimately ends up in the federal government's hands, according to internal Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (ATF) documents obtained by the Washington Free Beacon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Trump threatened to leave Republican party!</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/trump-told-rnc-chair-leaving-gop-create-party/story?id=80979889</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his new book, "Betrayal: The Final Act of the Trump Show," ABC News' Jonathan Karl writes that Donald Trump decided to leave the Republican Party before backing down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman stabbed cousin when he asked her to return borrowed sex toy...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/assault/kentucky-stabbing-275901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dispute over a borrowed sex toy ended with a Kentucky woman stabbing her male cousin with a kitchen knife, according to cops who arrested the alleged assailant on multiple criminal charges. Police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS FEST CANCELLED...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/music/news/travis-scott-refund-all-astroworld-tickets-buyers-day-n-las-vegas-headline-canceled-1235107124/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travis Scott will not perform at this weekend’s Day N Vegas Festival, Variety has confirmed. The headlining appearance at Las Vegas Festival Grounds was scheduled for Saturday, Nov. 13, less …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Sweden's experiment worked...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/11/how-sweden-swerved-covid-disaster/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death toll here is lower than nations with draconian restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They will not come in': Mounting standoff over migrants on Poland and Belarus border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98they-will-not-come-in-e2-80-99-mounting-standoff-over-migrants-on-poland-and-belarus-border/ar-AAQrQAC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European nations are accusing Belarus of weaponizing refugees in its disputes with the E.U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor tackles armed man during church service...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/580518-pastor-tackles-armed-man-during-church-service</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Nashville, Tenn., said a pastor tackled an armed man who threatened parishioners during church service,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico army stands between gangs, enforcing turf divisions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-mexico-caribbean-army-drug-cartels-5b165c95f2d1c276fbccd688d1ee12a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AGUILILLA, Mexico (AP) — In western Mexico a small squad of soldiers with about a half-dozen trucks and sandbag emplacements stands guard on a rural highway. In one direction, almost within earshot, one drug cartel operates a roadblock extorting farmers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol rioter applies for asylum in Belarus, says local media...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/europe/capitol-rioter-asylum-belarus/2021/11/08/fbc4eb14-4093-11ec-9404-50a28a88b9cd_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neumann was presented by local media as someone who was persecuted for questioning election results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS: BACK OFF, LEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.ladbible.com/entertainment/celebrity-jeff-bezos-responds-to-viral-leonardo-dicaprio-footage-20211108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ladbible.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of Jeff Bezos' partner Lauren Sánchez meeting Leonardo DiCaprio recently went viral</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO Says USA Should Take Warning From Europe COVID Resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-europe-cases-surge-deaths-vaccination-vaccine-hesitancy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a 4th wave floods hospitals in some parts of the continent, a top WHO official urges the U.S. to bring back restrictions at the 1st sign of an uptick: "The earlier, the stricter, the better."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used car prices shock...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/used-car-market-prices-dbea46f6-f8b3-42fe-b972-ece6c0f96de1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The industry’s key index of used vehicle prices jumped another 9.2% over the span of just a month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lorde Edge' Name Change Sparks Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/elon-musk-lorde-edge-name-change-meaning-twitter-dogecoin-1646910</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The term was trending on Twitter on Monday morning as users wondered if it was a reference to the Dogecoin cryptocurrency, which the SpaceX CEO often tweets about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell spent decades chasing power. Now he heeds Trump, who mocks him and wants him gone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mitch-mcconnell-spent-decades-chasing-power-now-he-heeds-trump-who-mocks-him-and-wants-him-gone/ar-AAQrPuf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his 16th year as the Senate’s top Republican, McConnell is increasingly playing the role of a conflicted and compromised booster of Trump’s interests — not a leader with his own vision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Organic-Food Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/11/15/the-great-organic-food-fraud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no way to confirm that a crop was grown organically. Randy Constant exploited our trust in the labels—and made a fortune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART using fully driverless trucks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/08/walmart-is-using-fully-driverless-trucks-to-ramp-up-its-online-grocery-business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Taking the driver out is the holy grail of this technology," Gatik CEO Gautam Narang, who founded the autonomous trucking company in 2017, told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Third of millennials identify as gay or trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/nearly-one-in-three-millennials-identifies-as-lgbt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 30% of millennials in the United States identify as gay or transgender, according to a recent study conducted by Arizona Christian University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Self-Driving update made cars go haywire. It may be excuse regulators needed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/tesla-e2-80-99s-recent-full-self-driving-update-made-cars-go-haywire-it-may-be-the-excuse-regulators-needed/ar-AAQrSoM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration previously asked Tesla for increased transparency around updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell's Inadvertent Loophole Helping America Get High...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2021-11-08/high-thc-pot-gummies-are-getting-a-boost-from-mitch-mcconnell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAPPER WAS WARNED BEFORE TOOK STAGE...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/07/houston-officials-worried-about-crowd-control-before-travis-scott-took-the-stage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON — Concert organizers and Houston city officials knew that the crowd at a music festival planned by Travis Scott,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Newspaper cutting back on print, training readers to use iPads...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/this-newspaper-is-cutting-back-on-print-and-training-readers-to-use-ipads-instead-will-it-work/ar-AAQpFWV </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS Union Vote Sets Up Watershed Moment for Labor...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/starbucks-union-vote-sets-watershed-175940803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. workers have authorized strikes in a wide swath of industries and quit jobs in record numbers but could soon pull off an even more audacious coup: Winning a unionization vote at one of the country’s signature non-union firms, Starbucks.Most Read from BloombergWhere Did All the Public Bathrooms Go?What It Means to Design a Space for ‘Care’COP26 Protests: Inflatable Cows, Megaphones and a RainbowThe Rising Pacific Forces a Native Village to Move. Who Will Pay?‘Airbnb Queen’ Say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Morrison sued over COVID criticism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-health-9811c0204c3913f4f9ac846acb61e918</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Northern Ireland’s health minister is suing Van Morrison after the singer called him “very dangerous” for his handling of coronavirus restrictions. The Belfast-born singer opposes restrictions to curb the spread of the virus, and has released several songs criticizing lockdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto World Hits $3 Trillion Market Cap as Ether, Bitcoin Gain...</title>
      <link>https://www.moneyweb.co.za/moneyweb-crypto/bitcoin/crypto-world-hits-3trn-market-cap-as-ether-bitcoin-gain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moneyweb.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of 7:38 a.m. in London, the overall market cap of cryptocurrencies hit $3.01 trillion, according to CoinGecko pricing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Australian footballer 'scared' to play in Qatar...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211108-gay-australian-footballer-scared-to-play-in-qatar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian footballer Josh Cavallo, who came out as gay last month, has revealed he would be scared to play at the upcoming World Cup in Qatar because of the country's criminalisation of homosexualit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyachts enjoy pandemic tailwind as rich seek zen at sea...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211108095820-ay5ap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEISURE-SAILING/RECOVERY (PIX, TV):Superyachts enjoy pandemic tailwind as rich seek zen at sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Heating Bills Loom as Next Inflation Threat...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/08/winter-heating-bills-loom-as-the-next-inflation-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With consumers already dealing with the fastest price increases in decades, another unwelcome uptick is on the horizon: a widely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleaze claims roiling UK govt put Boris under pressure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-london-boris-johnson-lobbying-scotland-7aff81421e6301d1194193ae4df4687f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson wants to talk about climate change. But his opponents want to focus on sleaze. As a United Nations climate summit aimed at staving off catastrophic global warming enters its final week in Glasgow, Scotland, host leader Johnson is facing a barrage of criticism in London over his attempts to change the system that oversees lawmakers’ standards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension rises in Iraq after failed bid to assassinate PM...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-iran-elections-iraq-28fe31151ed74ca6f7ef313793765824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) — The failed assassination attempt against Iraq’s prime minister at his residence on Sunday has ratcheted up tensions following last month’s parliamentary elections, in which the Iran-backed militias were the biggest losers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER votes Musk should sell 10% of TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/twitter-votes-elon-musk-sell-211909106.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has spoken -- after Elon Musk polled his more than 62 million followers on whether he should sell 10 percent of his Tesla shares, by Sunday a majority had voted "yes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Not credible'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/bomb-threats-reported-at-multiple-ivy-league-schools-officials-say/ar-AAQqxAo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cornell, Columbia and Brown universities warned students to evacuate campus buildings on Sunday after reports of bombs on campus, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could long covid unlock clues to chronic fatigue and other poorly understood conditions?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/could-long-covid-unlock-clues-to-chronic-fatigue-and-other-poorly-understood-conditions/ar-AAQpN0d?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As millions of people nationwide suffer from long-haul covid, patient advocates are cautiously hopeful that new research may unlock clues to other conditions that appear to crop up after infections, including chronic fatigue syndrome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA finally reopening borders after 20 months...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-finally-reopening-borders-20-150009885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States reopens its land and air borders Monday to foreign visitors fully vaccinated against Covid-19, ending 20 months of restrictions on travel from around the globe that separated families, hobbled tourism and strained diplomatic ties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Scott Hit With First Lawsuit After Festival of Death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-astroworld-lawsuits-land-travis-004125843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There is no excuse for the events that unfolded," says a Texas attorney suing rappers Travis Scott and Drake as well as Live Nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients went into hospital for care. After testing positive there, some never came out...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/hospital-acquired-covid-nosocomial-cases-data-analysis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 21% of patients diagnosed with covid during a hospital stay died, according to data analyzed for KHN. In-hospital rates of spread varied widely and patients had no way of checking them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive mafia trial sees nearly 100 gangsters convicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4019282/massive-mafia-trial-100-gangsters-convicted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Italian court has convicted nearly 100 mobsters in the biggest mafia trial in decades. Defendants from the powerful and feared ‘Ndrangheta group — including a boss’s right-hand man and the head …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Scott Hit With First Lawsuit After Festival of Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/travis-scott-live-nation-astroworld-lawsuit-1254537/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They consciously ignored the extreme risks of harm to concertgoers and, in some cases, actively encouraged and fomented dangerous behaviors,” lawyers for one attendee claim</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $30 billion woman: Megadonor Miriam Adelson leaps back into politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/07/miriam-adelson-megadonor-back-in-politics-519912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adelson is taking her first political meetings since her husband Sheldon died, seeing possible 2024 candidates and a key Senate contender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradshaw Slams Aaron Rodgers for Vaccine Fake...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/fox-sports-terry-bradshaw-destroys-aaron-rodgers-for-lying-about-vax-status-learn-how-to-be-honest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Fox Sports NFL analyst Terry Bradshaw is lashing out at Green Bay Packers quarterback Aaron Rodgers for having lied about taking a Covid-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XI FOR LIFE?</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/xi-set-to-unveil-new-doctrine-that-could-let-him-rule-for-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  APPROVAL PLUNGES TO 38%...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/11/07/biden-approval-falls-38-midterms-loom-usa-today-suffolk-poll/6320098001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A USA TODAY/Suffolk University Poll shows Biden's support cratered among the independent voters who delivered his win over Donald Trump a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/politics/video-and-photos-bidens-go-for-stroll-along-delaware-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden and first lady Jill Biden arrived at the beach around 4:10 p.m. and stayed for about 40 minutes, according to a White House press pool report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSILE TARGETS IN DESERT</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/11/07/china-builds-missile-targets-shaped-like-u-s-aircraft-carrier-destroyers-in-remote-desert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese military has built targets in the shape of an American aircraft carrier and other U.S. warships in the Taklamakan desert as part of a new target range complex, according to photos provided to USNI News by satellite imagery company Maxar. The full-scale outline of a U.S. carrier and at least two Arleigh Burke-class destroyers …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
