<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'culture of violence' alleged by LAPD SWAT whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/inside-the-culture-of-violence-alleged-by-lapd-swat-whistleblower/article_7ad66c68-e790-506f-b1dd-e1069f3fc7e5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — After assessing the hilly terrain around a Sunland house where a homeless man had holed up one morning in May 2017, the Los Angeles Police Department's heavily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden VP race highly fluid days before expected pick...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/510936-biden-vp-race-is-highly-fluid-days-before-expected-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before Joe Biden is set to announce his running mate, Democrats including confidants of the former vice president say the race is fluid, with different candidates gaining or losing momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, losing grip on GOP, wields less influence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-losing-grip-gop-wields-110037157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than three months before election day, President Trump is losing his iron grip on congressional Republicans and is facing pushback on multiple fronts, from delaying the election to false claims about mail-in voting leading to widespread fraud, that show his weakened status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Wistful Age, Farmers Find New Angle: Chore TV...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/07/in-a-wistful-age-farmers-find-a-new-angle-chore-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEACHAM, Vt. — The sweet smell of hay rose off the earth on a recent evening, as Morgan Gold strode</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to U.S. Visitors: Please Don't Sneak Across Border...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/07/canada-to-u-s-visitors-please-dont-sneak-across-the-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was packing for my road trip from Colorado to Alberta, Canada, when the text came in from a gentleman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Trump Blew Up More Than Just TIKTOK and WECHAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2020-08-07/trump-s-bans-on-tiktok-wechat-could-hit-u-s-tech-giants-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackout hits large area of NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/07/power-outage-hits-large-area-of-manhattan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A widespread power outage left about 130,000 customers in darkness across a large area of Upper Manhattan early Friday, a Con Edison spokesman said. Three networks in the utility’s transmissi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border agents unearth 'most sophisticated smuggling tunnel in history'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e759e3542d183822decd8979d341a814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — An incomplete tunnel found stretching from Arizona to Mexico appears to be “the most sophisticated tunnel in U.S. history," authorities said. The tunnel intended for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House candidate selling anti-China face masks. Asian Americans say they incite racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-GOP-House-candidate-in-Va-is-selling-15465262.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a selfie by Virginia Del. Mark Cole that first caught Sookyung Oh's eye.  Cole, R-Fredericksburg, tweeted an image showing off a bright red face mask he said he'd purchased from the congressional campaign of Del. Nick Freitas, R-Culpeper.  "COVID-19, 'MADE IN CHINA," it read.  Oh, who is Virginia director of the National Korean American Service &amp; Education Consortium Action Fund, said that she and other Asian American community leaders were "shocked" to find the masks for sale as campaign merchandise.  "He's literally financing his campaign with a tactic that has been shown to exacerbate anti-Asian racism," Oh said of Freitas, a libertarian-leaning Republican who is running against first-term Democratic Rep. Abigail Spanberger in central Virginia's largely rural 7th district.  In an open letter issued this week, the NAKASEC Action Fund called on Freitas's campaign to stop selling the "Made in China" face masks, saying the merchandise is another example of anti-China political rhetoric that has put Asian Americans at risk of discrimination during the coronavirus pandemic.  Some of the rhetoric has come from President Donald Trump, who routinely refers to the deadly virus as the "China virus" and has also outraged his critics by calling it the "Kung flu."  A number of Asian American community organizers and two Asian American lawmakers from Virginia, Dels. Sam Rasoul, D-Roanoke, and Kathy Tran, D-Springfield, signed onto the statement.  "Blaming China for the COVID-19 crisis in the United States has led to a sharp increase of racially motivated attacks and discrimination against people of Chinese descent and others perceived to be of Chinese descent," the statement said, citing incidents in which Asian Americans have been spit on, cursed at or assaulted.  "Nick...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TIGHTENING?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-campaign-chief-sees-bounce-after-virus-briefings-revived/ar-BB17F6rm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain denies suffering second virus wave as cases mount ...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-08-spain-denies-virus-cases-mount.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's health ministry on Thursday denied that the country is facing a second wave of COVID-19 infections, despite a spike in cases of the virus in recent days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins switches to virtual fall semester...</title>
      <link>https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/08/06/university-moves-undergraduate-instruction-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hub.jhu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students urged to stay home due to resurgence of COVID-19; JHU increasing financial aid and other supports to offset pandemic's burden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye admits he wants President reelected in interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1268485/kanye-west-campaign-president-joe-biden-trump-reelection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West has apparently admitted to running a spoiler campaign to take away votes from Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden. In an interview with Forbes via text message, the rapper claimed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools begin opening, parents on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Virus-keeps-spreading-as-schools-begin-to-open-15465493.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Miss. - Even before President Donald Trump admonished his top coronavirus adviser for saying the country was entering a "new phase" of widespread infection, patients at Mississippi's only Level 1 trauma hospital were already on a wait for ICU beds.  "Our ICUs have been full for weeks," Dr. LouAnn Woodward, a vice chancellor at the University of Mississippi Medical Center in Jackson said Thursday. "It's a very acute issue we're facing here."  Mississippi, now experiencing the country's highest rate of positive tests, is emblematic of the pandemic's new reality. The virus is no longer principally an urban problem: It is present throughout every state, and those infected often don't know it, leading to what top public health officials call "inherent community spread."  This has proved true for Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine, a Republican, who learned he was positive for covid-19, the disease caused by the novel coronavirus, when he was tested Thursday morning in advance of a planned meeting with Trump. Trump went ahead with his visit to a Whirlpool plant; DeWine, the second governor known to have contracted the virus, went into self-isolation.  The situation in Mississippi is unfolding as well in other largely rural parts of the country, including in Alabama, South Carolina and California's Central Valley, places where so much viral material is circulating that when people get infected, many are unsure when or how it happened - so the outbreaks cannot be easily traced and contained.  State health officials in Alabama, for instance, say they are starting to see the impact of a mask mandate imposed two weeks ago. But some worry the dramatic spread might be attributable to people giving up on testing, as results can take days or weeks to come back.  "My fear is if we don't see...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GREED, ABUSE AND BRAZEN ILLEGALITY'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/new-york-attorney-general-letitia-james-files-lawsuit-dissolve-nra-n1236009</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James said last year that an investigation of the NRA was underway, part of her campaign promise to dig into the group's not-for-profit status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities go to extremes... </title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/cities-go-to-extremes-with-coronavirus-quarantine-crackdowns-checkpoints-power-shutoffs-steep-fines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the daily number of coronavirus cases in the United States still hovering at about 50,000 and American deaths from the disease approaching 160,000, cities across the country are taking increasingly severe measures to force the curve of the outbreak downward -- including power shutoffs, fines and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model forecasts 300,000 US covid deaths by Dec 1...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806221829-76we1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-University of Washington forecasts 300,000 U.S. COVID-19 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine 'checkpoint' opens at NYC's Penn Station...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806190446-nql9u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NEW YORK-QUARANTINE (TV, PIX):Quarantine 'checkpoint' opens at New York City's Penn Station to enforce travel rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance Standoff Over 'Smart' Streetlights...</title>
      <link>https://myfintale.com/business/in-san-diego-smart-streetlights-spark-surveillance-reform/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;myfintale.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this article A homicide detective looked up from the scene of a fatal shooting in San Diego’s Gaslamp District in August 2018 and saw [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge nixes Trump bid to delay suit from woman alleging rape...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/judge-nixes-trump-bid-delay-230247652.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York judge knocked down President Donald Trump&amp;#39;s bid to delay a lawsuit from a woman who accused him of rape, ruling in a decision released Thursday that the presidency doesn&amp;#39;t shield him from the case. Pointing to a recent U.S. Supreme Court ruling that the president isn&amp;#39;t immune</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In devastated Beirut, French leader offers comfort and a hug...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fdfa749a9ef0c29ed875c7dd63916e81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — It was one of the most powerful moments of Emmanuel Macron’s lightning visit to devastated Beirut: confronted by a distraught woman in a sea of enraged residents, the French leader...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W. Bush pays tribute to immigrants in new book...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f731fda15d2f91dcbdca160bc6be2b89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A new book by former President George W. Bush will highlight an issue which now sets him apart from many of his fellow Republicans — immigration. Crown announced Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims Biden opposes God...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a3c57cdcf8e44755d15930b29c660e36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — President Donald Trump billed his trip to Ohio Thursday as a chance to promote economic recovery, but he quickly pivoted to a deeply personal attack on Joe Biden, even questioning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress urges Postal Service to undo changes slowing mail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a291ebc31c5638aa5a9adafc2ff2b430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Lawmakers from both parties are calling on the U.S. Postal Service to immediately reverse operational changes that are causing delays in deliveries across the country just as big...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boomerang?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/20bd8464759422fd2df7100488f6be7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Kanye West's unlikely White House bid is getting help qualifying for presidential ballots in key states from Republicans around the country, fueling suspicions he's being pushed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misery Ranking Will Show USA Getting Worse Versus Rest of World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/misery-ranking-will-show-us-getting-worse-versus-rest-of-world/ar-BB17DrwR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: Daughter claims mom Kellyanne had her 'ARRESTED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12334875/claudia-conway-donald-trump-idiot-twitter-lawyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLAUDIA Conway claimed that her mom Kellyanne had her “arrested” in a TikTok video after she said that she “needs a lawyer.” One viewer claimed that the teenager went live o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Zuckerberg Fortune Surpasses $100 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2020/08/06/news/facebook-founder-mark-zuckerbergs-fortune-surpasses-100b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capturing rescue in Beirut...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-lebanon-security-blast-survivor-wider-idUSKCN25232S?taid=5f2c78b1df732d0001466633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When he first felt the ground shaking, Reuters photographer Mohamed Azakir thought Beirut had been struck by an earthquake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign aide admits killing Arkansas Senator...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8601615/Campaign-aide-admits-killing-Arkansas-Senator-Linda-Collins.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Lynn O'Donnell, 49, pleaded guilty on Thursday to first-degree murder and abuse of a corpse in the June 2019 death of former Arkansas Senator Linda Collins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Port worker found alive at sea 30 hours after explosion...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/06/beirut-port-worker-found-alive-at-sea-30-hours-after-explosion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bloodied Amin al-Zahed was admitted to the Rafic Hariri University Hospital after being pulled out of the Mediterranean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside San Fran restaurant's 'quarantine bubble'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/hashiri-quarantine-bubble-igloo-patio-dining-covid-15464405.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As restaurateurs continue to seek creative solutions to serve their clientele during the pandemic, a first-of-its-kind outdoor dining experience has made its way to downtown San Francisco.  Three seven-foot-tall translucent domes dotted the pavement of the Mint Plaza in SoMa on Wednesday evening, where a handful of customers at Sushi Hashiri were escorted inside to enjoy a meal -- and a rather unusual patio seating arrangement.  Intrigued by restaurants in Amsterdam and Japan that had implemented similar greenhouse-style structures, manager Ken Matsuura decided to test out the concept at his own restaurant.  "We hadn't seen any other Bay Area restaurants doing it, so why not be the first?" he told SFGATE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens arrested after jumping Mar-a-Lago wall with 'mini AK-47', loaded magazine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8597613/Police-3-teens-inadvertently-jump-wall-Mar-Lago.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three teenagers fleeing police while carrying a semiautomatic gun in a backpack jumped a wall at President Donald Trump's Mar-a-Lago resort, but probably didn't know that's where they were.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada allowing terminally ill patients to use psychedelic mushrooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/06/world/canada-psychedelic-mushrooms-cancer-therapy-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian government will allow four patients with incurable cancer to receive psilocybin therapy, which uses the drug found in the so-called "magic mushrooms" or "shrooms," to ease their end-of-life distress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commission rejects request for 4th face-off...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/06/commission-rejects-trump-request-for-4th-presidential-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Commission on Presidential Debates on Thursday rejected President Trump’s request that it schedule a fourth presidential debate. Trump attorney and former New York Mayor Rudy Giuliani req…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew's alleged 'puppet fetish' revealed...</title>
      <link>https://knewz.com/prince-andrew-victim-puppet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knewz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York faces fresh allegations in newly released court documents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE shines in pandemic with $2 trillion value on horizon...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/apple-shines-pandemic-trillion-horizon-72217125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early in 2020, Apple appeared to be caught in a horrible bind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope appoints 6 women to top roles on Vatican council in progressive step...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/06/pope-appoints-six-women-to-top-roles-on-vatican-council-in-progressive-step</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Labour minister Ruth Kelly is among the women who will oversee Vatican finances and address its cashflow problems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCUNIVERSAL TV Shake-Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/nbcuniversal-tv-shake-up-nbcs-paul-telegdy-frances-berwick-oversee-networks-1306249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conglomerate is searching for an executive to oversee a new entertainment programming unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA lifts advice to avoid all foreign travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200806-us-lifts-advice-to-avoid-all-foreign-travel-due-to-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US lifts advice to avoid all foreign travel due to pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Giving Patients $1,250 Stipend To Stay Home After Diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/08/05/alameda-county-offering-1250-stipend-to-help-covid-19-patients-during-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alameda County hopes to slow the spread of COVID-19 by helping families that face a sudden financial crisis when a test comes back positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs understand praise -- the same way people do...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2020/08/dogs-praise-brains-human-language/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogs can't speak, but their brains respond to spoken words, suggesting human language has deep evolutionary roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In CA, 57% seeking benefits lost jobs for 2nd time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/06/in-california-57percent-filing-for-unemployment-lost-their-jobs-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of workers who recently applied for unemployment benefits in California were doing so because their jobs or hours were cut again, hinting at the nation's unstable economic recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance Standoff Over 'Smart' Streetlights...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-06/a-surveillance-standoff-over-smart-streetlights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea planning for contact-free future...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20200803-south-korea-contact-free-untact-society-after-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital technology has helped South Koreans cope with the pandemic. But the elderly have been left behind in the new contact-free era</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raphael's face reconstructed to solve tomb mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200806-raphael-s-face-reconstructed-to-solve-tomb-mystery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raphael's face reconstructed to solve tomb mystery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Saudi intel official accuses MBS in lawsuit of ordering torture, assassination...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/former-saudi-intelligence-official-files-complaint-against-mohammed-bin-salman-in-u-s-district-court-over-alleged-assassination-plot-on-american-soil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Saudi minister of state and intelligence official has filed an explosive lawsuit against Mohammed bin Salman (MBS), Crown Prince of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, alleging that he “orchestrated an ongoing multi-year conspiracy by a Saudi government-sanctioned ‘death squad’ to torture and assassinate” the ex-intel officer on both U.S. and Canadian soil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems demand U.S. Postal Service reverse rules slowing delivery...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-targets-Nevada-mail-voting-in-lawsuit-even-15461535.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Democratic leaders on Capitol Hill told negotiators for President Donald Trump on Wednesday that preserving funding for the U.S. Postal Service and removing new rules that have slowed delivery times are essential ingredients of a new coronavirus relief bill in a year when millions of Americans plan to vote by mail.  "Elections are sacred," Senate Minority Leader Charles Schumer, D-N.Y., told reporters after a meeting with Postmaster General Louis DeJoy. "To do cutbacks when ballots, all ballots, have to be counted - we can't say, 'Oh, we'll get 94 percent of them.' It's insufficient."  Schumer said he and House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., told DeJoy, along with Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin and White House Chief of Staff Mark Meadows, that their demands regarding the Postal Service are necessary to striking a deal on a broader relief bill that may also include new unemployment benefits and a payroll tax cut.  "It was a heated discussion," Schumer said, adding that the demand is a "sine qua non for us. We told that to the postmaster."  DeJoy declined to take questions as he left the Capitol. Meadows suggested that Schumer is looking at the Postal Service as a "fall guy" to blame if ballots are delayed.  "I don't know that it's the postmaster general's position to assure him what's going to happen with the elections," he said.  "It's not a post office problem," Meadows added. "It's a secretary of state problem in each state."  That contradicted a statement from Trump earlier Wednesday, when the president said that part of his opposition to mail balloting is that the USPS is ill prepared to handle it.  "I'm sure the post office doesn't have enough time," Trump said in the Oval Office during a meeting with Arizona Gov. Doug Ducey, a Republican. "Millions of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study links physical stress to cognitive decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.safetyandhealthmagazine.com/articles/20159-study-links-physical-stress-on-the-job-to-cognitive-decline-memory-loss-later-in-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.safetyandhealthmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fort Collins, CO â€” Physically demanding work may lead to poor memory and faster aging of the brain among older adults, results of a recent study led by researchers from Colorado State University show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT expands TIKTOK takeover ambitions to entire global business...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-tiktok-microsoft/microsoft-expands-tiktok-takeover-ambitions-to-entire-global-business-ft-idUSKCN2522BD?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft Corp is chasing a deal to buy all of TikTok's global business, the Financial Times reported on Thursday, citing five people with knowledge of the talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  HE CAN'T DO THAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/pelosi-on-trump-idea-to-accept-gop-nomination-on-white-house-lawn-it-wont-happen-he-cant-do-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi put her foot down on President Donald Trump's thoughts about holding his Republican National Convention acceptance speech from the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OHIO GOV. TESTS POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/open/2020/08/ohio-gov-mike-dewine-tests-positive-for-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine announced Thursday he has tested positive for COVID-19, the disease caused by the new coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE FOR RENT:  PLANNED RNC CONVENTION SPEECH FROM SOUTH LAWN IGNITES CONTROVERSY...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Democrats-and-Republicans-push-back-on-Trump-s-15462379.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Local and national leaders pushed back Wednesday against President Donald Trump's desire to deliver his convention acceptance speech from the White House, warning that the event could bring protests and novel coronavirus spread to the nation's capital while violating historic norms that separate political activity from the seat of presidential power.  House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., predicted that a political convention gathering at the White House "won't happen," for legal and ethical reasons, while District of Columbia Mayor Muriel Bowser, a Democrat, said she did not plan to offer "any exemptions" for the event from a recent health order that restricts the movement of nonessential visitors to the city from 27 states with elevated rates of the virus.  Members of the District Council expressed alarm about the idea, and on Capitol Hill, some Republicans also voiced concern. Sen. John Cornyn of Texas called it "problematic," Sen. John Thune of South Dakota questioned the legality of political events at the White House, and Sen. Ron Johnson of Wisconsin suggested that other plans should be made.  "Probably not allowed," he said. "Probably shouldn't do it."  The pushback came as Trump indicated publicly for the first time that he preferred speaking from the White House at the end of four nights of convention programming, from Aug. 24-27, that will be a mix of live speeches from around the country and prerecorded video. In an interview Wednesday on "Fox and Friends," he described the White House as a "beautiful setting" that is "greatly representative of our nation" where the logistics would be easy and inexpensive to arrange.  A Republican involved in the planning said it was highly likely that Trump's speech would be delivered at the White House, perhaps on the South Lawn, but various locations were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SAYS LEGAL...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/510785-trump-dismisses-legal-questions-on-gop-nomination-speech-at-white</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday dismissed legal questions surrounding potential plans to deliver his GOP nomination acceptance speech from the White House, emphasizing that the federal Hatch Act does not apply to the pr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Already worried about next pandemic wave...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/06/dr-fauci-already-worried-about-next-coronavirus-pandemic-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, raised the specter during Politico’s “Pulse Check” podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat On For Omar Week Before Primary...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/08/05/1-week-before-primary-rhetoric-heats-up-between-rep-ilhan-omar-challenger-antone-melton-meaux/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Congresswoman Ilhan Omar and her leading opponent, Antone Melton-Meaux, held dueling news conferences Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GREED, ABUSE AND BRAZEN ILLEGALITY'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/056b7845ad1a35a68a4bf837329d9f6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s attorney general sued the National Rifle Association on Thursday, seeking to put the powerful gun advocacy organization out of business over allegations that high-ranking executives...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Man broke into bank, only stole hand sanitizer...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/bank-heist-sanitizer-674910</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 6--In what may be the least lucrative heist ever, a convicted felon broke into an Iowa bank early Tuesday and escaped with only hand sanitizer, according to a criminal complaint. Mark Gray, 39</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LYFT RIDE TO HELL:  Passenger rips down covid partition and chokes out driver...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1265297/drunk-lyft-passenger-choke-driver-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HORRIFYING moment a “drunk” Lyft passenger ripped down a plastic partition and choked the drive while the car was moving was caught on camera. Travis Smith, 36, was charged with bat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Gov't Spending to Eclipse All-Time Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cio-briefing/2020/08/annual-government-spending-approaches-historic-territory/167474/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Driven heavily by the Defense Department, contract spending across government will exceed $600 billion in fiscal 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TISH TAKES ON NRA</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806144855-coo0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-NEW YORK/ATTORNEY GENERAL (PIX, TV):New York seeks to break up National Rifle Association, alleging financial mismanagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Mayor Says City Will Shut Off Water And Power At Homes That Throw Large Parties...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/los-angeles-coronavirus-garcetti-shut-off-water-large-parties-1203005621/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti on Wednesday announced the city was taking action against those who throw large parties. He called recent gatherings of mostly young people in the Hollywood Hills an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer diagnoses plummet in pandemic; Experts fear could mean worse disease later...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/cancer-diagnoses-plummet-during-covid-19-and-experts-fear-that-could-mean-worse-disease-later/article_f1b61230-faa8-58e1-b029-693833e2b341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diagnoses of six common cancer types dropped in the early months of the coronavirus pandemic, as routine screenings were postponed by health systems and patients avoided going to the doctor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shia LaBeouf in 'brownface'? Role raises question of who gets to adopt whose culture...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/shia-labeouf-brownface-cholo-role-140016611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director David Ayer says Shia LaBeouf plays a white guy who adopts Mexican American barrio culture in &amp;quot;The Tax Collector.&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s sort of how he grew up too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU files 400 cases versus president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/81f61e7d5c381b707bd21efc9a704e93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The day after Donald Trump’s election in November 2016, the American Civil Liberties Union posted a message to him on its website: “See you in court.” As president, Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grammy-winning music producer DETAIL arrested on sexual assault charges...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/music-producer-detail-arrested-on-sexual-assault-charges/6356834/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detail, whose real name is Noel Christopher Fisher, won a Grammy for producing Beyonce's hit "Drunk in Love."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHE DIES TOMORROW' review: On mortality, mass psychosis, and how we live today...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/culture/2020/8/5/21352779/she-dies-tomorrow-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two new films — She Dies Tomorrow and Strasbourg 1518 — cut through our fantasies about life and loneliness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TISH SET FOR 'MAJOR ANNOUNCEMENT'</title>
      <link>https://www.syracuse.com/state/2020/08/ny-ag-letitia-james-to-make-major-announcement-after-deutsche-bank-turns-over-trump-finances.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.syracuse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has frequently called it "presidential harassment" and a "witch hunt."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE DANGER:  TRUMP BANK SUBPOENAED</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-bank-was-subpoenaed-by-n-y-prosecutors-in-criminal-inquiry/ar-BB17Ca5m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeping loved ones from visiting patients making them sicker...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/article/Keeping-loved-ones-from-visiting-our-coronavirus-15463298.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly six months into the coronavirus pandemic, an emptiness lingers at the bedsides of our patients in hospitals wards and intensive care units. Though some hospitals are trying out limited visitation policies, most are not, leaving too many of our patients without loved ones at their side. The trauma to families, while difficult to measure, is immense, and the absence of loved ones is making things worse for patients and their medical care teams. It's as if we have fallen back in time.  ICUs of the 1990s were not inviting to families. We imposed uncompromising and paternalistic limits on visitation with patients. There was no sharing of power, or even knowledge. A patient's family was often viewed as preoccupied by minor concerns that paled in comparison to the physician's definitive vision of what was important. That period, in retrospect, was defined by a kind of testimonial injustice - a prevailing prejudice that deflated the authority of family and consolidated power solely within the medical team. Are we repeating that same injustice now?  What the virus that causes covid-19 brought - along with fear, contagion and uncertainty - is epistemic exclusion, which is to say that families are excluded from essential moments of their loved one's illness, recovery and dying process that would allow understanding and healing. There is simply no way the family, excluded from the bedside during a novel pandemic, can share the knowledge the team possesses. The best tools and patterns of communication on our digital devices are never going to be enough to allow someone to truly know what's going on in the hospital. And without families, care teams are missing essential knowledge about the patient. We are handicapping each other.  Take, for example, Fred Reyes, an ICU patient who, like so many others we've seen, is Hispanic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How American West became 'billionaire wilderness' and home to most unequal part of country...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/billionaire-wilderness-author-inequality-teton-county-wyoming-2020-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Author Justin Farrell explains how Teton County turned into a billionaire wilderness, and what that means — not just for Wyoming, but for America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey's Lira Hits Record Low as Interventions Fail to Stem Drop...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lira-sinks-toward-record-interventions-094819526.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Turkey’s lira tumbled to its lowest level against the dollar as interventions by state banks failed to keep a lid on the currency’s depreciation.At the root of the strains are concerns about the level of Turkey’s reserves and an aggressive monetary easing cycle that’s fueled an outflow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence blasts Chief Justice Roberts as 'disappointment to conservatives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/06/pence-john-roberts-disappointment-to-conservatives-392202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president’s criticism comes after Roberts sided with the Supreme Court’s Democratic appointees on several occasions in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birx warns of uptick in 9 cities...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/510817-birx-warns-of-uptick-in-coronavirus-cases-in-9-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House coronavirus task force coordinator Deborah Birx is warning of an uptick in coronavirus cases in nine new U.S. cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyeing big China box office, Hollywood bows to censorship...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eyeing-big-china-box-office-hollywood-bows-censorship-175542306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lure of the massive Chinese market has led Hollywood to readily self-censor its films to please Beijing, according to a new report by Pen America, an anti-censorship group. Screenwriters, producers and directors in the huge US film industry are changing scripts, deleting scenes and altering other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'REVOLUTION'</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806111709-kph72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON-SECURITY/BLAST-MACRON-TOUR (PIX, TV):'Revolution': Angry crowds in Beirut urge Macron to help bring change</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween canceled? Costumers, candy makers, theme parks face scary realities...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/halloween-canceled-costumers-candy-makers-120041059.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knott's Scary Farm is canceled because of the COVID-19 pandemic, as are other California theme parks' Halloween events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBANON ON THE BRINK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d10149b5d5f3e0e837edd6d5a8e0d8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Lebanese officials targeted in the investigation of the massive blast that tore through Beirut sought to shift blame for the presence of explosives at the city’s port, and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loneliness cured with pill?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2020/aug/06/loneliness-cure-pill-research-scientists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chronic loneliness has little to do with being alone, experts say – could a pharmaceutical treatment help lonely people form meaningful relationships?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne enters Australia's toughest virus lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200806-melbourne-enters-australia-s-toughest-virus-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melbourne enters Australia's toughest virus lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport of Future Will Have No Check-In, Security Lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-airport-of-the-future-will-have-no-check-in-security-lines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Airport of the Future Will Have No Check-In OrÂ Security Lines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Love is not tourism,' says couple separated for 6 months...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806101236-8gqsi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BI-NATIONAL COUPLES (TV):'Love is not tourism,' says couple separated for 6 months by coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't stand so close: Singapore trials automated drones to check...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200806100805-ys1ly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore implements the use of drones to enforce social distancing measures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Brace for Thousands to Attend Sturgis Motorcycle Rally...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/06/boxed-into-a-corner-residents-brace-for-thousands-to-attend-motorcycle-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of the year, Sturgis, S.D., is a relatively quiet city of 7,000 residents tucked beside a 1.2 million-acre</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
