<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mom bathes toddler in bleach to keep alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/06/21/mom-bathes-toddler-rare-skin-disorder-bleach-keep-him-alive/718328002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mom from Washington state bathes her 1-year-old son with harlequin ichthyosis in bleach twice a week, because she wants him to defy the odds. Alicia Barber is hopeful she won't need to use the toxic chemical forever. She's searching for other options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter Of DC Public Schools Teachers Unlicensed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Approximately-1000-DC-Public-Schools-Teachers-Are-Unlicensed-486076271.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 1,000 D.C. Public Schools teachers do not have a D.C. teaching license, according to a yearlong investigation by the News4 I-Team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rips Obama's 'Inhumane' Treatment Of Migrant Kids...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/trump-calls-out-obama-for-inhumane-treatment-of-migrant-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'They were treating them terribly'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: THE PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/photos-obama-immigration-detention-facilities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negligent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury sneakers: High style and booming market...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/luxury-sneakers-high-style-booming-market-033449512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian, aged 10, has 20 pairs of high-end sneakers in his closet at his home in the suburbs of New York. Maxance, who just turned 14, asked his parents for an $800 pair of Adidas shoes for his birthday. The world is also one in which luxury sneakers -- often limited-edition collaborations between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas paid Gaza family to claim baby killed by Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/hamas-paid-family-to-say-baby-killed-by-tear-gas-says-gaza-terror-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mahmoud Omar, arrested by Israel for terror-related offenses, tells interrogators his relatives lied: 8-month-old Layla actually died from fatal blood condition that runs in family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hispanics on pace to outnumber whites in Texas by 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/demographics/2018/06/21/texas-may-not-become-mostly-latino-soon-experts-thought</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas got a little older and a little more diverse last year, data released Thursday from the U.S. Census Bureau shows.The state’s median age...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLINE SHOPPERS FACE RECKONING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/21/supreme-court-rules-that-states-can-force-online-shoppers-to-pay-sales-tax.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court overturned a 1992 precedent barring states from requiring businesses with no "physical presence" in that state to collect sales taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE LOVED A KITTEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Koko-the-beloved-gorilla-who-knew-sign-language-13013823.php#photo-2701745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Koko, the beloved gorilla who shocked the world with her mastery of sign language and ability to communicate with humans, died in her sleep at the age of 46.         The western lowland gorilla, born on July 4, 1971 at the San Francisco Zoo, spent the bulk of her extraordinary life at the Gorilla Foundation in Woodside. Her full name, Hanabi-ko, is Japanese for "Fireworks Child."         When Koko was just a year old, her doctor, Francine "Penny" Patterson, decided to teach her a few basic signs including, food, drink and more. Patterson would speak the words as she signed them, according to the Gorilla Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous gorilla Koko who could do sign language dead at 46...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/21/koko-gorilla-famed-for-using-sign-language-and-crying-over-pet-kitten-dead-at-46/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Koko, the thoughtful gorilla who captivated the world through her ability to use sign language and revealed an empathetic side to great apes, has died. She was 46. The western lowland gorilla passe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Media Face Class-Action Lawsuit over SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER labels?</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/47-groups-weighing-splc-lawsuit-warn-editors-ceos-you-are-complicit-in-hate-group-defamation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will journalists face a class-action lawsuit?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Pastor Shoots, Kills Gun-Wielding Carjacker In WALMART Parking Lot...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/06/20/pastor-kills-gun-wielding-carjacker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An armed off-duty paramedic is being hailed as a hero after he shot and killed a shooting suspect at a Washington state Walmart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALLOW INTERNET SALES TAX!</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/norquist-statement-south-dakota-v-wayfair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES DEAL BLOW TO AMAZON EMPIRE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/332abb7455cb4b60b2effc0852ff3c89/High-Court:-Online-shoppers-can-be-forced-to-pay-sales-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court says states can force online shoppers to pay sales tax.        The 5-4 ruling Thursday is a win for states, who said they were losing ou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smuggler abandons 6-year-old in Arizona desert...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/smuggler-abandons-6-year-old-in-blazing-desert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 6-year-old Costa Rican boy was rescued by U.S. Border Patrol agents after he was abandoned on a border road in Arizona on Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: People Freak Out On Trump's Detention Centers -- They're Actually Obama's!</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/trump-obama-detention-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheDC's Justin Caruso and Amber Athey are on it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's crumbling subway system falling in on itself...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/subway-station-ceiling-tile-crumbles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Borough Hall subway station in Brooklyn is more than 100 years old and is known to have water problems. That issue led to a ceiling collapse on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI counterspies under fire after disclosures of politicization...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/issues/ig-report-highlights-fbi-counterspy-failings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disclosures by the Justice Department inspector general of political bias among FBI agents is focusing new attention on problems within the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Internal Memo Reveals the ACLU Wavering on Free Speech...</title>
      <link>http://reason.com/blog/2018/06/21/aclu-leaked-memo-free-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our defense of speech may have a greater or lesser harmful impact on the equality and justice work to which we are also committed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES DEAL BOW TO AMAZON</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/332abb7455cb4b60b2effc0852ff3c89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court says states can force online shoppers to pay sales tax.        The 5-4 ruling Thursday is a win for states, who said they were losing ou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  New mosquito-borne virus jumps from animals to humans... </title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/health/first-human-case-of-virus-spread-by-mosquitoes-reported-in-north-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s mosquito season&amp;nbsp;and it’s almost impossible to avoid being bitten.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pot users feel MORE pain...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5869259/Marijuana-users-feel-pain-study-debunks-theory-cannabis-numbs-discomfort.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the Swedish Medical Center, Colorado, found that after an injury, cannabis users required higher painkiller doses than non-users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'blinding laser weapon' attacks on US pilots spread to Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/711099/china-news-laser-united-states-air-force-pacific-djibouti-africa-beijing-world-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Erdogan seeks new term with greater powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkeys-erdogan-seeks-term-greater-powers-082436562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Since he took office in 2003, President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has given a name to each stage in his consolidation of power in Turkey. First he called himself the apprentice; then the journeyman; and latterly the master. Now, he says a new five-year term would elevate him to the role</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rats break into ATM, munch through $18,000 in cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rats-break-atm-munch-18-000-cash-132945441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian police on Thursday said rats nibbled through more than a million rupees of banknotes after busting into a cash machine in the country's northeast. The rodent heist in Assam state was only detected by bank officials after locals complained that the ATM was faulty and had stopped dispensing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: Possible I'll be indicted...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/393422-stone-its-possible-ill-be-indicted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone said Thursday that it's possible he'll be indicted by special counsel Robert Mueller. “I acknowledge it is a possibility," Stone said in an interview on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge-porn bill dies after 11th-hour campaign by GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/21/new-yorks-revenge-porn-bill-dies-after-11th-hour-campaign-by-google/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s revenge-porn bill died early Thursday morning after the Senate adjourned for the year and took no action in the wake of an 11th-hour campaign by Google against the legislation. The propo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHT HELL: Terrified passengers vomit as cabin fills with mist...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/travel/articles/977606/viral-video-AirAsia-India-air-conditioning-passengers-vomit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALARMING footage has captured the moment airline passengers in India started vomiting as they were blasted with clouds of mist from the air conditioning in an attempt to force them out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Burger Built by Robot About to Hit Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/21/the-world-s-first-robotic-burger-is-ready-to-hit-the-bay-area</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The First Burger Built by a Robot Is About to Hit the Bay Area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTEL CEO resigns after consensual relationship with employee...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/intel-ceo-brian-krzanich-resigns-after-violating-company-policy-1529586884 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intel Corp. Chief Executive Brian Krzanich resigned Thursday after the company determined he violated company policies during a past, consensual relationship with an Intel employee. .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG HITS AGAIN...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5318229/donald-trump-border-separation-policy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gambit reflects a President uncomfortable with ideals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese worker punished for starting lunch three minutes early...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/21/japanese-worker-punished-for-starting-lunch-three-minutes-early</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Managers called TV news conference and bowed in apology at employee’s ‘deeply regrettable’ actions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Claims Fall for Fourth Consecutive Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-jobless-claims-fall-for-fourth-consecutive-week-1529584802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing applications for new unemployment benefits fell for the fourth straight week in mid-June, signaling continued strength in the labor market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting suspect arrested in death of XXXTentacion...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/21/xxxtentacion-murder-arrest-cops-police-mom-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;XXXTentacion's alleged murderer is in police custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe hits road to boost Dem govs -- and self...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/21/mcauliffe-democratic-governors-2020-661140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Virginia governor has thrown himself into 2018 campaigning, gathering potential chits if he runs for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eureka! Giant Oil Find Set to Bring Guyana Startling Riches?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/eureka-giant-oil-find-set-to-bring-guyana-startling-riches-maybe-1529578800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Exxon Mobil-led consortium has begun offshore drilling after recently discovering at least 3.2 billion barrels of light crude in Guyanese waters. That makes the tiny South American nation a top global energy frontier, but not everyone is convinced of a bonanza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash Is King: One-Month Treasury Bills Compete With S&amp;P Payouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/21/cash-is-king-one-month-treasury-bills-compete-with-s-p-payouts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now You Can Gorge Guilt-Free: 1-Month Bill Yield on Par With S&amp;P</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury sneakers: High style and booming market...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180621-luxury-sneakers-high-style-booming-market </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face scans for travelers at Florida airport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eade4e6efbf442328b0e1eefabd98f05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Florida's busiest airport is becoming the first in the nation to require a face scan of passengers on all arriving and departing international flights, includ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' spin-off movies to be put 'on hold' after 'SOLO' flop...</title>
      <link>http://collider.com/star-wars-spinoffs-on-hold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;collider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the disappointing launch of 'Solo: A Star Wars Story', Lucasfilm has put plans for more 'A Star Wars Story' spinoffs on hold and is instead focusing on 'Episode IX' and crafting a new trilogy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETANYAHU WIFE INDICTED FOR FRAUD...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Sara-Netanyahu-indicted-for-fraud-560550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charges follow collapse of plea bargain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans of yoga therapy have yet to win over doctors...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-06-fans-yoga-therapy-doctors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yoga practitioners often tout the unique health benefits of the ancient discipline—from relieving stress and pain to improving vascular health—but most doctors remain sceptical in the absence of hard proof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAA: Record 47 million to travel for July 4th...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/record-47-million-expected-travel-u-july-fourth-040522114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. travelers will hit the roads, rails and airports in record numbers this Fourth of July holiday, despite higher gasoline prices, the nation's largest automotive advocacy group said on Thursday. Some 46.9 million Americans will travel 50 miles (80 km) over the upcoming July Fourth holiday, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home of China's dog meat festival defiant amid outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/home-chinas-dog-meat-festival-defiant-amid-outcry-082555551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Joyce Zhou and Christian Shepherd YULIN, China (Reuters) - Residents of China's southern city of Yulin defended eating dog meat to celebrate the summer solstice on Thursday, as animal rights activists seek new ways to pressure organizers to cancel the annual festival. The ten-day event, dubbed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homes Prices Least Affordable in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/21/u-s-homes-prices-least-affordable-in-almost-a-decade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Homes Prices Least Affordable in Almost a Decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaped lion shot dead at zoo following evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-planckendael-zoo-belgium-evacuated-12757452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We'll be bringing you the very latest updates, pictures and video on this breaking news story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threshold for harmful chemicals in drinking water lower than thought...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/threshold-harmful-chemicals-drinking-water-lower-thought-study/story?id=56029597</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study caused a controversy after reports the government delayed its release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous gorilla Koko who could do sign language dead at 46...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/21/famous-gorilla-koko-sign-language-died-age-46-7648488/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rest in Peace, Koko.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta mayor signs order blocking city jail from accepting new detainees...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/393340-atlanta-mayor-signs-order-blocking-city-jail-from-accepting-new-ice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta Mayor Keisha Lance Bottoms (D) signed an executive order Wednesday blocking the city jail from accepting any new detainees from Im</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Janet Jackson reveals 'intense' battle with depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/janet-jackson-reveals-intense-battle-depression-163947832.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Janet Jackson has revealed that she suffered an "intense" battle with depression, which she linked to a childhood inferiority complex and societal racism and sexism. In an essay in the latest issue of Essence, a magazine geared toward African American women, the 52-year-old pop superstar said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration fears fuel crisis in Western politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/immigration-fears-fuel-crisis-western-politics-014823922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One issue now dominates political debate within the major Western democracies, and that one issue could now divide the West upon itself: migration. Donald Trump is trying to ride a tide of anti-immigration feeling to a victory for his Republican supporters in the US mid-term elections in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Rare FERRARI May Fetch Record $45 Million at Auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/20/a-rare-ferrari-250-gto-may-fetch-record-45-million-at-auction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Rare Ferrari 250 GTO May Fetch Record $45 Million at Auction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 4,000 episodes, halt for Jerry Springer's show...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/4-000-episodes-halt-jerry-springers-show-203235591.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Somehow it doesn't seem right for Jerry Springer to exit quietly. Instead, it was announced with no fanfare this week that he will stop making new episodes of his memorably raucous talk show, and neither Springer nor his bosses will talk about it. Producers said "there is a possibility"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'FACEBOOK taking everything': Rising rents drive out Silicon Valley families...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jun/20/facebook-silicon-valley-housing-crisis-families-pushed-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Property companies advertising their proximity to Facebook’s campus are giving low-income residents a choice: pay a huge rent increase or move out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIMBAUGH: Media 'going to get somebody killed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rushlimbaugh.com/daily/2018/06/20/the-media-is-going-to-get-somebody-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rushlimbaugh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSH: The Democrats now more than ever are rabid, unhinged. They're becoming zombie-like. If you don't believe me, jump on Twitter for a few minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SIGNS EXECUTIVE ORDER TO STOP SEPARATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1dafadd6fee4447cadd4a0179553026e/In-reversal,-Trump-orders-halt-to-his-family-separation-rule</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Bowing to pressure from anxious allies, President Donald Trump abruptly reversed himself Wednesday and signed an executive order halting his administration's pol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIMBAUGH: Media 'going to get somebody killed'...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/06/limbaugh-media-going-to-get-somebody-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump calls the coalition of mainstream news outlets in America “fake news” and they respond by investigating him, casting doubt on his word, integrity and plans, report all sorts of allegations – even those that are “salacious” and unsupported like in the “dossier” that started the Russia investigation. In short, there’s never been a […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Border Patrol searches its buses, GREYHOUND pulled into immigration uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/business/article/As-Border-Patrol-searches-its-buses-Greyhound-is-13011177.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was a 12-year Miami resident originally from Trinidad, taken off a Greyhound bus in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, by U.S. Border Patrol agents in January. She was a 60-something Jamaican national who had just met her granddaughter for the first time, whose Greyhound was stopped by Border Patrol. She was arrested and turned over to Immigration and Customs Enforcement. And on the other side of the country, they were an undocumented father and son riding a Greyhound from Seattle to Montana when agents came aboard and asked, "Are you illegal?" "Do you have your documents?" The son, a DACA recipient traveling without his papers, was held for a few hours. The father was sent to a detention center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI warns of sex assaults on planes...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/travel/2018/06/fbi-warns-about-sexual-assaults-on-airline-flights/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE LONGEST DAY</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5868021/Hello-sunshine-Thousands-flock-Stonehenge-solstice-summer-officially-arrives.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up to 25,000 people are expected to attend the 2018 summer solstice at Stonehenge in Wiltshire, to mark the beginning of the summer. It is believed Stonehenge solstices are thousands of years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biblical prophecy claims Rapture coming... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/711049/end-of-world-rapture-june-21-2018-summer-solstice-earth-bible-apocalypse-jesus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration protesters clash with each other in AZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/phoenix/2018/06/20/phoenix-protesters-disagree-message-against-trump-immigration-policy/719212002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shows Dulce Juarez trying to share her opinions about the separation of immigrant families and being abruptly cut off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're Keeping Families Together, But Border Going To Be Just as Tough'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-we-are-keeping-families-together-border-going-be-just</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I signed an executive order — ‘</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCOLDS MEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-media-they-dont-bring-cameras-interview-angel-moms-who</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The media never talks about the American victims of illegal immigration’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RALLY WILD!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/85d1a0cc773e4122a6078f349dc53e61/The-Latest:-Trump-rails-against-FBI-probe-of-Clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DULUTH, Minn. (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump's rally in Minnesota (all times local):        8 p.m.        President Donald Trump is railing against the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS burned by social-justice appeasement as growth stalls, stock plunges...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/20/starbucks-burned-social-justice-appeasement-growth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks may have appeased progressives with its social-justice workshops and open-bathroom policy, but such moves have failed to caffeinate the company’s bottom line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heckler ejected...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5866937/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the protesters at the Duluth rally on Wednesday held up a picture of Trump with Epstein, who was jailed for 13 months in 2008 for soliciting prostitution from a 14-year-old girl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with trying to have sex with auto tailpipe...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/kansas-man-charged-for-tailpipe-tryst-762953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 20--A Kansas man was charged today with lewd and lascivious behavior for his repeated attempts to have sex with the tailpipe of a parked automobile, according to court records. Ryan Malek, 23,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboard tells liberals: Keep driving 'until you have left our great state of Texas'...</title>
      <link>http://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/06/20/snap-your-neck-liberals-billboard-goes-viral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A billboard in Texas has gone viral with a message for folks of a particular political persuasion and now the person who posted the image online - and the billboard company - are receiving threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Activist Who Protested Homeland Security Sec. at Resturant -- Works For DOJ!</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/20/socialist-activist-kirstjen-nielsen-doj/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working for the Trump administration to own ... Trump?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania Calls Secret Service After Actor Threatens To Kidnap Barron...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/20/melania-calls-secret-service-after-actor-peter-fonda-threatens-to-kidnap-barron-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'USSS has been notified'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear kills hiker. Mauls search party member days later...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/wildlife/2018/06/20/anchorage-police-responding-to-bear-mauling-in-eagle-river/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Soltis’ body was found in the same area -- near where Hiland Road ends -- that a brown bear attacked a member of a search party looking for Soltis on Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHILLIES fan shot by hot dog cannon hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://mlb.nbcsports.com/2018/06/20/phillies-fan-injured-after-being-shot-by-phillie-phanatics-hot-dog-cannon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mlb.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Phillies fan was hit in the face by a hot dog shot out of the Phillie Phanatic’s hot dog cannon during Monday’s game against the Cardinals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhunt Underway For PA Man Accused Of Threatening To Kill President...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/06/20/manhunt-for-pennsylvania-man-accused-of-threatening-to-kill-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Marshals are searching for a Central Pennsylvania man accused of threatening President Trump and other officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stealth Sheets' Hide From Drones, Infrared Cams...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-5867469/The-stealth-sheets-hide-soldiers-vehicles-infrared-cameras.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of researchers have developed a device that can make soldiers and vehicles disappear. Called the 'stealth sheet,' it's a paper-thin device that can obscure objects from a drone's camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to Propose Merging Education, Labor Depts...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-house-to-propose-merging-education-labor-departments-1529533148</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House plans to propose merging the Departments of Labor and Education as part of a broader reorganization of the federal government, according to a person with knowledge of the proposal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birds Singing Same Song For A Millenium...</title>
      <link>https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/06/swamp-sparrow-bird-sings-same-song-animals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American swamp sparrow’s amazing ability to pass down its song perfectly is an example of handing down a cultural tradition, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Chiefs: U.S. Cannot Win Global Cyber Wars...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/national-security/defense-chiefs-u-s-cannot-win-global-cyber-wars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOD warns in a new organizational document that the U.S. cannot win the global battle over cyber security due the overwhelming complexity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER Publisher Subpoena In Cohen Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/publisher-of-national-enquirer-subpoenaed-in-michael-cohen-probe-1529529151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities have subpoenaed the publisher of the National Enquirer for records related to its $150,000 payment to a former Playboy model for her story alleging an affair with Donald Trump, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Northern California, Rent Disputes Turn Deadly...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/california/articles/2018-06-20/northern-california-landlord-charged-with-shooting-tenant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Naked lady dies of hypothermia... After trapped in closet 'mistook' for bathroom for days... Broke pipe, clawed walls...</title>
      <link>https://www.walesonline.co.uk/news/wales-news/sporty-fit-healthy-mum-who-14808581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.walesonline.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Mary Isherwood's family said they were 'absolutely devastated' by her tragic death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stonehenge builders used Pythagoras' theorem -- 2,000 years before he was born...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/06/20/stonehenge-builders-used-pythagoras-theorem-2000-years-greek/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The builders of Britain&amp;rsquo;s ancient stone circles like Stonehenge were using Pythagoras' theorem 2,000 years before the Greek philosopher was born, experts have claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algeria turns off internet to stop exam cheating...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/algeria-has-done-away-with-internet-to-stop-students-from-cheating-1870727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Algeria went offline on Wednesday for the start of high school diploma exams, the first in a series of internet blackouts to stop students cheating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau picks Oct. date for marijuana legalization...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4285946/marijuana-legal-date-october-17-canada-trudeau-confirms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational marijuana will officially become legal in Canada on Oct. 17, 2018, the prime minister announced on Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA steps up protection from asteroids, comets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-stepping-earths-protection-asteroids-comets-193810541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The U.S. government is stepping up efforts to protect the planet from incoming asteroids that could wipe out entire regions or even continents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Archbishop of DC Removed After Sex Abuse Allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/20/politics/theodore-mccarrick-washington-abuse-allegation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cardinal Theodore McCarrick, who led the Archdiocese of Washington and was a political force in the nation's capital, said on Wednesday that he has been removed from public ministry by the Vatican because of a decades-old allegation of sexual abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX AGREES TO HIGHER DISNEY BID...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fox-disney-announce-new-deal-1529496937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney raised its offer to purchase most of 21st Century Fox to more than $70 billion in cash and stock, topping an unsolicited offer from rival Comcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Hugh Hefner's 26-year-old son save PLAYBOY?</title>
      <link>http://nationalpost.com/news/world/we-should-not-apologize-for-sex-can-hugh-hefners-26-year-old-son-save-an-ailing-playboy-empire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Hugh’s death at 91, Cooper Hefner has stepped up as the creative mind of the sprawling 65-year-old brand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beer may lack fizz in Europe amid carbon dioxide shortage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3e238478e4d24430bf05b8e8ccb08730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — No beer at this time of year?        A British trade group says there's a shortage of carbon dioxide in Northern Europe, sparking fears that drinks may lack f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man crushed to death by coffin at mother's funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/06/20/indonesian-man-crushed-coffin-mother-funeral/717591002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indonesian man was crushed to death by his mother's casket at her funeral on Friday on the island of Sulawesi, according to police.  Pallbearers at the funeral were carrying the casket up a bamboo ladder onto a lakkian  when the ladder slipped and the coffin landed on Samen Kondorura, 40.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURGER KING rescinds offer for women impregnated by World Cup players...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2018/06/20/burger-king-russian-world-cup-pregnancy-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burger King says it’s sorry for offering a lifetime supply of Whoppers to Russian women who get pregnant from World Cup players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman may have served ex-lover's remains at BBQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2018/06/20/serial-killer-kelly-cochran-bbq-michigan/716988002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alleged serial killer fed the remains of her lover at a neighborhood barbecue before turning around and killing her husband two years later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE CRITICIZES...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-pope-criticises-trump-administration-policy-migrant-family-092151372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has criticised the Trump administration's policy of separating migrant families at the Mexican border, saying populism is not the answer to the world's immigration problems. Speaking to Reuters, the Pope said he supported recent statements by U.S. Catholic bishops who called the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SO SORRY...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/politics/abc-news-apologizes-banner-falsely-claims-paul-manafort-killed-five-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News issued an apology Wednesday after a banner during a live report claimed that former Trump aide Paul Manafort had copped to killing five people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Falsely Reports Manafort Guilty of Manslaughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chyron-malfunction-abc-apologizes-for-graphic-declaring-manafort-pleaded-guilty-to-manslaughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
