<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MACRON SOUS PRESSION!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/18/europe/france-coronavirus-measures-third-wave-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France will impose new coronavirus restrictions in 16 areas around the country, including the greater Paris and Nice areas, the country's prime minister announced Thursday in an attempt to contain a third wave of Covid-19 sweeping the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKDOWN CONFUSION, FRUSTRATION IN PARIS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210320120353-l64be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEATH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE (TV, PIX):Parts of France enter lockdown amid confusion and frustration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare at Sea for World's Most Essential Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/virus-nightmare-sea-world-most-044242374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaisal Bhati“We were out of sight and out of mind,” says Second Officer Jaisal Bhati. “Everybody forgot about us (and) everyone turned a blind eye.” Behind the scenes of the coronavirus pandemic, an invisible workforce of about one million seafarers has continued to toil on bulk carriers, oil tankers, fishing vessels, cruise ships, and more. These people have crisscrossed the world, many working seven-day weeks with no holidays or even sick days delivering medicines, grain, coal, fuel—and now vaccines. “They wanted our services but they did not want us.”Even in normal circumstances, weathering the perilous seas with limited personnel is a tough, dangerous job. A regular cargo ship might be crewed by only 20 people, each with designated duties—a ship at sea, like a plane in the air, requires constant attention so one cannot simply “down tools” and leave it unattended without risking catastrophe. On top of their daily tasks, each seafarer has emergency responsibilities for fire, health, defense, come what may. There are no separate firemen, doctors, or policemen on board. It’s just the crew, where every worker is essential and any delay is unthinkable.And while many industries ground to a standstill as a result of the coronavirus, the global shipping industry did not. As the health crisis spread, the International Transport Workers' Federation (ITF) agreed to allow two month-long contract extensions for seafarers in March and April and a “final implementation period” in May 2020 to avoid a disruption in international trade and make time for crew changes to happen as borders and airports started to close down. But companies and flag states took that show of grace and ran with it. The International Maritime Organization (IMO) estimated in December that as many as “400,000 seafarers remain on board commercial vessels, unable to be repatriated and past the expiry of their contracts.”Bhati was one of them. He found himself sheltering in place at the onset of the pandemic like so many across the globe—except that his place was a ship. He was due to return home at the end of last March after a five-month contract, but the worldwide COVID-19 lockdown beat him by two weeks—shutting down all the checkpoints that would have taken Bhati back home to India.Many seafarers have now been on board for as long as 18 months, stranded in their workplaces having been refused repatriation, and barred from shore leave because of domestic regulations intended to curb the spread of the virus. That’s far longer than the internationally recognized limit in Regulation 2.4 (Entitlement to Leave) of the Maritime Labor Convention (MLC), ratified by 97 countries representing 91% of the global shipping industry as of 2019, which states that seafarers are not permitted to work longer than 11 consecutive months and has simply been ignored. c/o Jaisal Bhati Like truckers and grocers, seafarers have shown up and done thankless work day in, day out, to keep society running. The difference is that many of them haven’t been allowed home. Some ships owned by smaller businesses have been completely abandoned by their owners and ghosted by their flag states—the country where a vessel is registered and whose regulations it follows. In other cases, fatigue has undoubtedly contributed to disaster: in July, the Panama-flagged, Japanese-owned bulk carrier Wakashio ran aground on a coral reef on the Mauritian coast, spilling toxic fuel oil into the ocean. It turns out that ship was understaffed and at least three of the 20 crew were on extended contracts.These nightmarish conditions are perhaps the inevitable result of the international nature of the maritime industry with its port states, flag states, owner states, and labor-exporting states built to endlessly shift blame.Owners are responsible for taking care of their sailors and it is their obligation to navigate government bureaucracy and cover all the expenses incurred to make repatriation happen. But much of that process is dependent on cooperation from governments. Despite working across international ports, seafarers are required to have visas in order to set foot on foreign soil and thus have access to airports. Even in cases of sickness, seafarers have been denied entry because of a lack of visa. A Russian seafarer suffered a stroke on board and was denied immediate medical attention in Indonesia due to COVID-19 restrictions. In Uruguay, a Peruvian seafarer died on a Portuguese-flagged fishing ship after showing symptoms of COVID-19 on board for 30 days. He was never brought in for treatment.Practically, it’s simply impossible to apply for visas in every single country where ports exist, so seafarers normally apply for the ones that correspond to the countries on their ship’s route. But the pandemic completely turned this upside down when governments began to close down airports and borders, canceling viable routes home in the process. Meanwhile, embassies closed down, making it impossible for seafarers to obtain last-minute visas in remaining ports. Some governments even refused to grant “key worker” status to seafarers which would have given them special visa exemptions. Granting this status is a top priority for organizations like the ITF and IMO.“Sadly, we’ve seen an incredible inflexibility from some governments, many of whom just don’t understand our industry, and don’t want to,” says ITF Seafarers’ and Inland Navigation Section Coordinator Fabrizio Barcellona. “These governments refuse to accept that the globalized trade system that they rely on to get people their toothpaste, their shampoo, food and medical supplies, relies on these people who have been treated like a rubber band, stretched to the absolute limit and about to snap.”They’ve Been Trapped on Navy Ships for Months. Now One Has Died by Suicide.Making matters even more difficult, a mandatory 14-day quarantine period put in place by governments to stop the spread of the virus demands perfectly choreographed crew changes to avoid delays that could force owners to pay expensive fees to keep their ships in port. One extra day could cost as much as $100,000—an amount most owners aren’t willing to shell out. Instead, many crewmembers waiting eagerly to disembark at open ports have had their hopes dashed when there were not quarantined crews ready to relieve them.“When it comes to money and human life, this whole industry prefers money, over human sacrifice. Not just the industries, the countries,” says Bhati. “When it comes to trade, forget people.”But those people are remembered as a threat to be kept at bay, with some governments rejecting entry to ships seeking medical attention for COVID-19 cases while other governments have refused to take back their own countrymen.Barcellona says: “In instances where ships have attempted to change crew, seafarers have been blamed for spreading the virus and their ability to come ashore blocked. This is despite seafarers’ fundamental human right to go home at the completion of their contracts. To compel someone to work beyond the period they agreed to work is absolutely a matter of forced labor—it is modern slavery.”Unsurprisingly, morale has collapsed under these conditions. An ITF survey of 1,434 seafarers taken in December and shared exclusively with The Daily Beast showed that one third of of respondents had unmet medical needs while more than four-fifths said their mental health and wellbeing had been negatively affected by the new conditions.“It was all kinds of bad. Emotionally bogged down. Couldn’t go out,” says Bhati. “Newborn child—cannot meet them. Parents passed away—could not reach them. It was really bad, it’s still bad.”In some cases on board, companies refused to give disability, or even sickness allowance, arguing that illnesses caught while seafarers are at sea aren’t “work-related illnesses.” Many times illnesses are blamed on the seafarers’ smoking habits, eating habits, or hygiene.Jessie Braverman, a member of the Pacific Coast Coalition for Seafarers, described a number of concerning issues flagged by crews during the height of the coronavirus pandemic. Some ships, sparsely crewed and with crew members unable to leave, weren’t getting enough food or clean drinking water. Seafarers complained meals were tight because food provision orders weren't made. Pacific Coast Coalition for Seafarers A Facebook post in October described a situation where seafarers were forced to eat “seaweed for breakfast and bacon from 2017” and use “water coming from an old rusted water converter.” There was another case, Braverman told The Daily Beast, where “the only thing they had to eat were onions.” That was on top of the wage theft and abuse on board that goes on largely unreported, as problems that existed before the pandemic were only further exacerbated by it. Seafarers were eating bacon from 2017 and improperly stored fish. Pacific Coast Coalition for Seafarers Her particular chapter focuses on educating the local population (in her case, Portland, Oregon) on the issues happening right in their ports, but it is also part of a greater coalition that works in tandem with unions on the West Coast and advocacy organizations around the world. While they report these abuses to unions and local inspectors, there just aren’t enough of them to inspect every ship that comes in and out of port at a regular basis and even then, most seafarers are afraid to go on the record about ship abuses for fear of losing their jobs. Volunteers from the Pacific Coast Coalition for Seafarers deliver care packages to seafarers. Justin Katigbak Being on the open seas also meant intermittent internet access. Seafarers on ships without cell service or internet connections relied on ports (or the goodwill of their ship companies) to be able to communicate with maritime organizations for any sort of relief, let alone their families. Those left without the blessing of reliable internet often missed huge milestones, tragedies in the community, and in the case of a pandemic, even letting their own families know that they wouldn’t be coming home as planned.Prior to the pandemic, Braverman had visited a ship that imported cars and felt like a “floating parking garage.” She noted how the crew lived in small rooms, with limited amounts of food. “It’s definitely not cozy,” she said. “It seems really hard from my perspective—you’re literally living and sleeping at your workplace, on this really dangerous ship.”Cruise ship crews, similarly confined to cramped living spaces, found that proper social-distancing was impossible as the coronavirus spread. While passengers were allowed off the ship and made to quarantine according to the coastal state’s medical standards, oftentimes, crews were not held to the same health standards. They were left to deal with a virus with minimal medical knowledge, and if they had not obtained the correct visa, were usually not even allowed to step off the ship to seek medical attention.Pastor Marsh Drege, an ordained minister of the Evangelical Lutheran Church, is one of many members of faith who serves in “maritime ministry.” Rooted in centuries-old stereotypical views of sailors as violent, bad-mouthing, impulsive, sinful people, maritime ministry grew with the intent of proselytizing and spreading the Christian (or Catholic) religion. Today, that’s no longer the main purpose of maritime ministry—as port chaplains in North America sign memoranda vowing not to proselytize—but their influence and presence has remained on the gangway.“We are concerned with spirituality, but we work equally with Muslims, Jews, Christians” and others, says Drege, explaining that their main goal is to tend to the functional and individual needs of seafarers. “Our chaplains, our maritime ministers, are there to listen and counsel and pray with them.”Now, the usual anxieties of seafarers have been made exponentially worse by the uncertainty of the pandemic. Though many felt compelled to work at the beginning of the pandemic as their form of service for the world’s greater good, the lack of transparency concerning their future on board left many distraught. While disappearances and deaths at sea often go unreported, a spate of suicides among seafarers—including six cruise workers in the month of May—demonstrates the fatal effects of a depressed and hopeless crew amid an unending crisis. Just recently, an Indian seafarer trapped aboard MSC’s bulker Anastasia off the coast of China attempted suicide after languishing on board eight months past his original contract’s expiration, and his most recent pleas to return home were refused.“I've personally had people call me from all over the world, all times of day, just wanting to talk,” Drege says. “It has really increased during the pandemic… I talked to a seafarer almost every day in August, because they were in the Middle East, and they couldn’t get off the ship. They couldn’t go anywhere. They were basically prisoners.” Pastor Marsh Drege with a seafarer at the “Seafarers International House Relocated” c/o Marsh Drege Faith-based organizations like the Seafarers International House have long worked closely with unions and advocacy groups to bring help to seafarers and when the coronavirus drastically limited the number of people interacting at ports, chaplains were often the one line of relief, bringing whatever practical items were needed to the gangway.“Seafarers will contact [our chaplains], usually through WhatsApp, and will ask them to pick up something at a store, or they will order things on the internet to the chaplain’s home,” Drege explains. “One of our chaplains has spent $20,000 a month on just buying things, that he is just trusting the seafarers will reimburse him.”He recalls asking one chaplain: “‘Do you ever get stiffed?” and being told “Never. It’s never happened.” That, says Drege, “really shows the trust and the relationships that happen between our chaplains and our seafarers.”The reality of the pandemic has not only pushed Drege to find ways to support seafarers but also has helped him appreciate their situation, he said: “I’ve developed more empathy for what seafarers go through all the time—isolation, and loneliness. We all have been on lockdown, we all know now what that’s like.”While one might assume that special consideration would be given to seafarers, since they, you know, deliver basically every imaginable thing that we need in order to live our lives, they’ve been almost completely ignored even for the most basic of needs. All the while, the entities tasked with enforcing regulations and protecting seafarers did next to nothing.“Flag states and port states are not actually stepping up,” says Natasha Brown, the IMO’s acting head of media and communications.One key issue is the notorious “flag of convenience” system. It’s a business practice originating from the Prohibition era in the United States, where American-owned ships registered to Panama served alcohol to American patrons on American coasts, claiming that they need only abide by the Panamanian rule of law. Though Prohibition ended, flying a flag of convenience didn’t. Instead of bypassing a ban on alcohol, it turned out that bypassing labor laws, tax requirements, and environmental codes was too lucrative to give up.The benefits are great for flag states too. It is a steady source of income for poorer nations, giving them an “in” with wealthy corporate fleet owners. A 2014 report by UNCTAD reveals that 73 percent of the world’s fleet is “foreign flagged,” meaning the ship’s flag does not match the owner’s. Today, as many as 60 percent of ships fly flags in countries where there are no nationality or residency requirements for registration, called open registries. The practice, in effect, gives extraordinary power to shipowners, who dangle their fleet’s registration in exchange for more lax, agreeable regulation.“Part of the problem is that the ‘Flags’ popular with shipowners do not have the political or economic influence to lobby on behalf of the ships registered to them, or the workers aboard,” says ITF Maritime Coordinator Jacqueline Smith. “Major Flag states generate substantial profits from their registers, but don’t have the strength or enforcement mechanisms required to do their job when violations occur.”While people like Bhati had their fates in the hands of neglectful governments and inconvenienced ship companies, flag states like Panama and Liberia had no issue allowing contract extensions—despite the expressed cap of continuous labor on board at 11 months—to anywhere as long as 14 to 17 months, spurring outrage from trade unions and advocacy organizations. The ITF maintains that “Flags of Convenience have been granting shipowners unsafe and unsustainable exemptions from important international regulations in the name of COVID-19.”“Many Flags of Convenience have shown their true colors during this pandemic by putting the profits they make from shipowners ahead of the lives of seafarers and their human rights,” says Smith.Port states aren’t innocent either. Every country has jurisdiction over its own docks and their Port State Control is responsible for enforcing maritime regulations and detaining ships that have clearly violated them. Inspections not only cover the technical aspects of a ship—whether the engine is operating correctly, the fuel is up to environmental standards—but are supposed to interrogate the quality of life on the ship and the working conditions of seafarers.“If every country in the world did this, there would be no issues with overdue seafarers,” Bhati asserts.But port states, hesitant to spend resources, do the paperwork, or take responsibility for correcting the violations perpetrated on board, instead disregarded the injustices happening in their ports. Their inaction sent a message loud and clear to many seafarers that owners and states wouldn’t be held accountable. The onus of pursuing justice on board is once again placed on seafarers, who operate at a severe disadvantage compared to their employers, and threaten their own livelihoods when they speak out.Seafarers work under a contract-based system where good, steady salaries mean there are always more workers available than jobs despite the tough lifestyle and inherent dangers that come with the work and where the large labor pool makes it easy for employers to maintain blacklists. Those are technically illegal, but as the current crisis has highlighted, the maritime industry is notoriously bad at enforcing its own rules. Few international seafarers belong to unions (though they may sail on unionized ships) and many are afraid of the consequences of speaking out—that they’ll be cut off from their source of income and replaced by another sailor eager for work and willing to stay quiet.“Contract-based employment means that no one has to give you an explanation of why you haven’t been picked for a new contract,” says Barcellona. “It’s very hard to prove you’ve been blacklisted for speaking up on an issue like health and safety, or for demanding the shipowner conduct a crew change. How do you prove the reason you didn’t get a new contract is because of what you did under the last contract?” Seafarers at the dock of the Port of NJ/NY with Christmas at Sea satchels. Port Chaplain Luisito Destreza This issue is especially prevalent in such countries as the Philippines, Indonesia, China, India, Ukraine, and Russia, which supply most of the world’s crews. There’s an unspoken but distinct racial and economic hierarchy within the industry, in which sailors from Western regions like the U.S. or Scandinavia are most represented in higher level positions and protected by unions. Contracts usually run around four months for captains and higher-ranking officers, six months for mid-level officers and nine months or longer for ordinary and able-bodied seamen.For Filipinos especially, seafaring jobs averaging $1,000 a month, one of the lowest rates for any nationality, pay much more than most local work provides. With about 250,000 Filipinos working the seas on any given day, they are the largest nationality employed in the industry, making up about 20 percent of the world’s seafarers. They also make up the highest proportion of sailors who are not ranked as officers, and thus, easily replaceable.In the Philippines, they call it “contractualization.” It’s just another aspect of the Philippine government’s cheap labor program started by the late dictator Ferdinand Marcos, and continued by every regime, until now, with Rodrigo Duterte, which has sent Filipinos to every corner of the globe trained as nurses, domestic helpers, and sailors. But the underlying issue of this program is the inherent disposability of the labor, thus putting the rights of workers, and the security of their employment in perpetual jeopardy.“Filipino [sailors] are afraid to lose their jobs,” says Edwin Dela Cruz, president of the International Seafarers Action Center. “They are always contractual. Every time they go home, they are not sure that they will be rehired next time. It’s a buyer’s market.”Filipino cruise workers were some of the hardest hit by the COVID-19 pandemic, and among the first cases outside of China. They were often forced to continue working despite coronavirus protocols, while passengers were quarantined and had access to medical attention. But the fear of speaking out and losing their jobs largely outweighed the potentially deadly consequences of working under problematic conditions. Dela Cruz and his organization have lobbied the Philippine Congress to end contractualization with legislation called the “Magna Carta of Filipino Seafarers,” but he acknowledged that recognizing the rights of poor Filipino workers against wealthy corporate interests is an uphill battle.Bhati, on the other hand, was monumentally lucky. Eventually, after four extra months on board, he and his crewmates were replaced by a new crew and flown back to India on special charter flights last July. He felt grateful towards his employer for doing the right thing but he knows that most people were not shown the same treatment. What angers him most is the fact that protections for seafarers already exist—at least on paper.“You have all the legislation, who will implement it?” he asks. “It’s a joke. They always find a way through it, or find a way to override it. They don’t have it in their hearts to implement it because of the money.”Bhati is understandably frustrated with unions like the ITF: “Unions are pro-owners, pro-managers, they’re not pro-seafarers. The ITF, if you’re under contract, under a union, it's the union’s job to protect its people, seafarers, their job is for these times. These are the times we need them…Their response was pathetic.”As part of a lengthy statement, Barcellona called anger at shipowners for closed borders and scarce flights and anger at the ITF for lack of action “anger misdirected” and said that “much of the ITF’s most important work will not always be visible to our critics, or to seafarers themselves,” emphasizing how difficult their mission is.“The ITF and our seafarer union affiliates have done an extraordinary job through this pandemic to fight for seafarers and their rights,” Barcellona states. “Together, our team has used the few resources we have, to expose employers who have refused to perform crew changes, and to pressure governments to take action. We have pushed back on employers who tried to cut health and safety corners. We have stopped countries from further undermining safe maximum time limits on board. We have helped thousands of seafarers to come ashore and go home to their families.”Many, like Bhati, ask why ITF didn’t simply call for a strike?Barcellona claimed that striking was “neither supported by seafarers, nor conducive to pressuring the actual decision-makers we needed to influence” and in an “incredibly precarious industry” would have career-ending repercussions for the seafarers who engaged in such a risk.“In striking, seafarers would have also put themselves in a legally dangerous situation, since many countries have strict rules regarding strikes with severe penalties payable by seafarers themselves. To complicate matters, seafarers would have had to be mindful of the several jurisdictions that often apply before taking action.”In the end, every recourse and form of relief for seafarers has been at the whim of shipowners and governments, always with extreme and adverse risk on the part of the seafarers. But many have shown extreme bravery in standing up for themselves and their fellow sailors.Yurii Babii is a 23-year-old electro-technical officer from Ukraine, who has been sailing on ships since he was 21. After the first two months of extensions, Babii decided to put his foot down on what looked like the beginning of a never-ending cycle that would see his time on board extended far beyond his original contract. Babii told The Daily Beast what he told his superiors: “I will not perform my duties; I will be like a passenger on the vessel.”He acknowledged that his particular skill set and youth (or some could argue, naïveté) gave him confidence to speak out for himself that others couldn’t afford, certain he would find work again. But he also argued that there is swift action that can be done to help individual seafarers if they know how to push the right buttons. Babii recalls sending letters to the IMO and to one of the headquarters of his former ship’s company, MSC, in Odessa. Yurii Babii on right c/o Yurii Babii He said: “If you will not help me, new letters will be in your office.” After two months later, Babii made it off his ship.There are many stories like that of Babii and Bhati, individuals advocating publicly for better treatment for all seafarers—but in a workforce of over one million there are even more untold stories of seafarers working under extreme pressure and living without access to the resources and protections they need to call out abuses against them. Still, these seafarers rise against the tide of injustice, banding together the way they must at sea.When one Filipino seafarer died at sea after a lack of medical attention, his crewmates testified in front of the Philippine Congress about their adversity, confirming that it is often the laborers themselves who put their livelihoods on the line to see progress.“The government is doing nothing. The shipowners are doing nothing. The manning agents do not even know the problems of their own crew,” Dela Cruz tells me. “It’s seafarers themselves, and advocates, working to help each other and helping themselves.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian national pleads guilty in plot to steal TESLA secrets for extortion...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-national-pleads-guilty-plot-172100810.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian national admitted in federal court this week that he tried to recruit a Tesla employee to install a malicious software into the company’s computer network with the goal of extorting the electric car giant. Egor Igorevich Kriuchkov, 27, repeatedly tried to persuade an employee at Tesla’s electric battery plant in Nevada to participate in the hacking scheme, offering to pay the worker ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark reports two cases of serious illness, including death, after vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-denmark/denmark-reports-two-cases-of-serious-illness-including-one-death-after-astrazeneca-shot-idUSKBN2BC0A4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark said on Saturday that one person had died and another fell seriously ill with blood clots and cerebral haemorrhage after receiving the AstraZeneca COVID-19 vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry gives advice to grieving children in new book...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/princess-diana-paris-royalty-coronavirus-pandemic-prince-harry-fe343120b70c7c0893ff3f883e891dcf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain’s Prince Harry has written the forward for a new book aimed at the children of frontline workers who died in the COVID-19 pandemic, sharing the pain he suffered as a boy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eco-Friendly People Back To Wasteful Ways During Pandemic To Avoid Risk Of Exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eco-friendly-single-use-plastics-water-bottles-environment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;97 percent have access to reusable products, but 67 percent of them are turning to single-use items to limit COVID exposure risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE securing hotel rooms to hold growing number of families...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ice-hotel-rooms-border-migrant-families-7682092b-952c-428e-ae3b-f8b2d4072c0a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has awarded an $86 million contract for hotel rooms to house migrant families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Horror house': Raid at Connecticut estate reveals dozens of dead goats...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/20/raid-of-ritzy-connecticut-estate-reveals-dozens-of-dead-goats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A run-down estate in a ritzy Connecticut town devolved into a “horror house” littered with the decomposing corpses of dozens of goats. The grisly discovery was made March 10 by state De…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobs in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14400392/anti-lockdown-protesters-clash-police-london/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-lockdown protesters clashed with cops in London today after police warned they could be arrested if they gathered. Hundreds of maskless demonstrators marched through the capital to rally again…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands demonstrate in Switzerland...</title>
      <link>https://www.swissinfo.ch/eng/thousands-demonstrate-against-covid-19-restrictions/46465314</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.swissinfo.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people have protested in the north-western Swiss town of Liestal against restrictions introduced to curb the Covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS FOR FIRST SUSTAINABLE CITY ON MARS UNVEILED...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/living/2021/03/19/plans-for-the-first-sustainable-city-on-mars-unveiled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vertical city has homes, offices and green spaces and construction is due to start in 2054.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany: Police clash with protesters against virus measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/berlin-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-99b7100d7c223654a31c878a6f7375aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Protesters in Germany clashed with police Saturday over coronavirus measures, with officers using water cannons, pepper spray and batons against people trying to break through police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans anxious about return to normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/20/why-some-are-averse-to-return-to-normal-post-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a year into the coronavirus pandemic, some people have fallen in love with their 'Covid caves'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexual Anguish Familiar Thorn for Faith Community...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/20/sexual-anguish-of-atlanta-suspect-is-familiar-thorn-for-evangelicals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Brad Onishi heard that the man accused of a rampage at three Atlanta-area spas told detectives that he had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden on his heels amid migrant surge at Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-immigration-united-states-1efbf1f357a5210d2433b48820b9aa54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Somehow, they didn’t see it coming. Within weeks of Inauguration Day on Jan. 20, the Biden administration had reversed many of the most maligned Trump-era immigration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NATO Scientist With Security Clearance Busted Spying for Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/top-nato-scientist-security-clearance-073352843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaanus Lensment / Ekspress Meedia (Estonia)TALLINN, Estonia—Chinese military intelligence recruited an Estonian national working at a NATO research institution focused on maritime and submarine research, The Daily Beast has learned.The spy, Tarmo Kõuts, renowned in the Estonian scientific community for his research, was convicted last week and sentenced to three years in prison. The Baltic country’s intelligence services had warned for years of the growing Chinese threat, but the conviction was the first of its kind. So far, Estonia’s counterintelligence service, known domestically by its acronym KAPO, has been praised for its success in catching spies recruited and run by Russia.According to Aleksander Toots, the deputy director of KAPO and Tallinn’s top counterintelligence official, Kõuts was recruited in 2018 by China’s Intelligence Bureau of the Joint Staff Department of the Central Military Commission—as Beijing’s military intelligence agency is known—along with an alleged accomplice who is yet to be tried in court. Both were arrested on September 9, 2020, with no publicity or discussion of the case in the Estonian media.Kõuts pleaded guilty to conducting intelligence activities against the Republic of Estonia on behalf of a foreign state. The charges were one stop short of treason. He was sentenced to three years in prison.Kõuts was recruited on Chinese territory, said Toots, who spoke exclusively with The Daily Beast and Estonia’s Delfi newspaper: “He was motivated by traditional human weaknesses, such as money and need of recognition.”Toots added that Kõuts received cash payments from his Chinese handlers as well as paid trips to various Asian countries, with luxury accommodations and dinners at Michelin star restaurants. The intelligence operatives handling him were operating under cover of a think tank. Inna Ombler, the prosecutor handling the case confirmed that Kõuts earned €17,000 -- a little over $20,000 -- for his espionage, which the Estonian government has since seized from him.Kõuts, who earned his doctorate in environmental physics in 1999, had worked for years at Tallinn Technical University’s Maritime Institute where he specialized in geophysics and operational oceanography. His research led to marine scientists successfully predicting a damaging winter storm with rapidly rising sea levels in Estonia in 2005. Kõuts was also part of a scientific research group that was awarded the Estonian National Science Prize in 2002 for finding the best location for a seaport on the island of Saaremaa. Although officially designed to accept cruise ships, the port needed to be able to host NATO vessels.From 2006, Kõuts became directly involved in the national defense sector. He was named a member of the Estonian Ministry of Defense’s Scientific Committee, which oversees the country’s military research and development initiatives. As part of that secondment he also became a member of the Scientific Committee of the NATO Undersea Research Center based in La Spezia, Italy and even served, from 2018 to 2020, as the vice president of that organization, which is now known as the Centre for Maritime Research and Experimentation (CMRE). According to its website, the CMRE “conducts relevant, state-of-the-art scientific research in ocean science, modelling and simulation, acoustics and other disciplines.”Kõuts’s public Facebook account shows he checked-in at Lerici, Italy— from La Spezia—in April 2018, the year of his recruitment by China. His role at the NATO center gave Kõuts direct access to Estonia’s and NATO’s confidential military intelligence. At the time of his arrest, he had a state secret permit as well as NATO security clearance dating back fourteen years. In the three years Kõuts worked for Chinese military intelligence, confined his espionage to observations and anecdotes about his top-level work but did not, according to Toots, yet pass on any confidential military information.“That he had such security clearances was one of the reasons we decided to put a stop to his collaboration [with the Chinese] so early,” Toots said. It might have saved him from a much stricter sentence that would have followed if he’d been charged with treason, which he would have been if Kõuts had passed on state or NATO secrets.Indeed, the biggest espionage breach NATO ever had was an Estonian one, just four years after the Baltic state joined the military alliance. In 2008, KAPO arrested Herman Simm, the head of the Ministry of Defense’s Security Department. Simm’s job was to coordinate the protection of state secrets, issue security clearances and act as a liaison between the Estonian Ministry of Defense and NATO. He’d been working for Russia’s foreign intelligence service, the SVR, for the entirety of his tenure. Simm was sentenced to twelve and a half years imprisonment and he additionally needed to pay €1.3 million—$1.8 million in today’s dollar value—in damages. He was released from prison on Christmas 2019.Since that scandal, Estonia has become one of the foremost Russian spy-catchers. “I'm continually amazed,” Toomas Henrik Ilves, Estonia’s former president, said. “We must be the only country the Kremlin seems to be interested in since we're the only ones catching all their agents. What makes us so special?”Unlike other NATO members, this Baltic country has a tendency to name and shame those it captures. It also rarely trades spies for its own captured assets. A much publicized exception to this rule was the case of Eston Kohver, a KAPO officer who was captured in 2014 by the FSB, Russia’s domestic security service, on the Estonian side of the Estonian-Russian border while conducting an operation to interdict cross-border smuggling. Kohver was traded, Bridge of Spies-style, in 2015 for Aleksei Dressen, a Russian agent the FSB recruited from within KAPO’s own ranks years earlier.Aleksander Toots oversaw both counterintelligence investigations that led to Simm’s and Dressen’s arrests. And despite his pedigree in snaring agents from Estonia’s next-door neighbor and former occupying power, Toots now sees a rising threat from farther east.Over the last three years, KAPO and Välisluureamet, Estonia’s foreign intelligence service, have raised the alarm about the rising threat of Chinese espionage. Last year Välisluureamet warned that Estonians who traveled to China were susceptible to influence operations and recruitment. “To this end, Chinese special services may use various methods and pretexts, such as establishing first contact or job offers over the internet. At home, Chinese special services can operate almost risk-free,” Välisluureamet explained in their annual security environment assessment. Politicians, public servants and scientists who hold political or defense-related clearances were named as possible recruitment targets.KAPO added that it first detected an increase in the interest of Chinese intelligence services after Estonia joined the EU and NATO in 2004 but lately that interest had intensified. The Chinese, Estonian counterintelligence concluded, are particularly interested in “decisions on global issues, be it the Arctic, climate or trade.”Tarmo Kõuts’ recruitment fits that category exactly, as his scientific research concentrated heavily on the maritime impact of climate change and some of his scholarly papers focused squarely on the Arctic region.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say goodbye to $30 plane tickets. Era of dirt-cheap flights ending...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/20/say-goodbye-to-30-plane-tickets-the-era-of-dirt-cheap-flights-is-ending.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airfare and some hotel rates are on the rise as cooped up Americans rush to vacation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Parties Back. Vaccines Optional...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sex-parties-are-back-vaccines-are-optional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As sex parties resume, expect hand sanitizer and temperature checks at the door. As one partygoer says, “No one wants to be the person who ruins the party by causing an outbreak.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Chaotic situation': Puerto Ricans indignant at tourists breaking mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/chaotic-situation-puerto-ricans-indignant-tourists-breaking-covid-mandates-n1261588</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts and residents worry that tourists’ unwillingness to follow Covid-19 measures could reverse the island's successful efforts at containing the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Believe Possible To Become Immortal...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/researchers-believe-its-possible-to-become-immortal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infowars: There's a War on for your Mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot skeleton unveiled in step towards dolls walking 'unaided'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/incredible-ai-sex-robot-skeleton-23763883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RealDoll representative promised that the company is getting ever closer to developing a sex robot that can walk unaided as well as conducting conversations with their owner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods 'did nothing to prevent crash'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9383587/Tiger-Woods-crash-investigation-suggests-golfer-prevent-collision.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New details have emerged in the ongoing Tiger Woods crash investigation revealing the golfer may have done 'nothing to prevent' the collision after he lost control of his car while speeding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury car thieves making killing on streets. In many cases, you're helping...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/luxury-car-thieves-making-killing-111500410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They creep into upscale South Florida neighborhoods on the hunt for Range Rovers, Lamborghinis, and Ferraris. They look for the telltale sign of an unlocked car: unfolded side view mirrors. On a good day — more often than you’d think — they find the car’s key fob inside. And with a simple push of a button, the luxurious car is gone. The scenario has repeated itself over and over recently, as ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Wicked betrayal'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210319165140-h4kd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRIME-GEORGIA/SPAS (PIX, TV):Atlanta shooting suspect's church decries killings as 'wicked betrayal'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summers Says USA Facing Worst Macroeconomic Policy in 40 Years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/summers-says-u-facing-worst-114227209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Former U.S. Treasury Secretary Lawrence Summers warned that the U.S. is suffering from the “least responsible” macroeconomic policy in the last 40 years, pointing the finger at both Democrats and Republicans for creating “enormous” risks.The fiscal-policy outlook has dimmed, the Covid recovery will stoke demand pressure, and the Federal Reserve has “stuck to its guns” for no rate cuts for years while expanding its balance sheet, he said in an interview with David Westin for Bloomberg Television’s “Wall Street Week” “What was kindling, is now igniting.”“I think these are the least responsible fiscal macroeconomic policy we’ve have had for the last 40 years,” he said. “I think it’s fundamentally driven by intransigence on the Democratic left and intransigence and the completely irresponsible behavior in the whole of the Republican Party.”Summers, a top official in the past two Democratic administrations, has emerged as one of the leading critics among Democrat-leaning economists of President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion pandemic plan. Summers warned in the interview the U.S. was facing a “pretty dramatic fiscal-monetary collision.”He said there is a 1/3-chance that inflation will accelerate in the coming years and the U.S. could be face stagflation. He also saw a 1/3-chance of no inflation because the Fed would hit the breaks hard and push the economy near recession. The final possiblity is that there Fed and Treasury will get rapid growth without inflation.“But there are more risks at this moment that macroeconomic policy will cause grave risks than I can remember,” he said.Administration officials have pushed back against the critique, saying the Biden bill aims to provide relief to those in need and won’t overheat an economy still suffering from high unemployment. Fed officials have broadly echoed that view -- flagging the risk of delivering too little fiscal support, and signaling they have no intention of tightening monetary policy anytime soon.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout from riot, virus leaves toxic mood on Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-ap-top-news-coronavirus-pandemic-7153ffc196f746883f57d4d407d38cf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The mood is so bad at the U.S. Capitol that a Democratic congressman recently let an elevator pass him by rather than ride with Republican colleagues who voted against certifying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you should spend more time barefoot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/health/is-it-safe-to-work-out-barefoot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learn about barefoot lifestyle pros and cons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unruly Spring Breakers Force Popular Miami Hotel Restaurant To Temporarily Close...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/19/unruly-spring-breakers-force-popular-clevelander-hotel-restaurant-to-temporarily-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dangerous situation has caused the popular Clevelander Hotel restaurant to shut its doors in Miami Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Was Fast: Blowups With ChinaRussia in Biden's First 60 Days...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/20/that-was-fast-blowups-with-china-and-russia-in-bidens-first-60-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Sixty days into his administration, President Biden got a taste this week of what the next four years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic trauma haunts health workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/why-put-life-line-pandemic-181700979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar. 15—Brittany Bankhead-­Kendall, 34, was a newly minted surgeon when the COVID-19 pandemic began. At first, like thousands of other health care professionals, she worked tirelessly in crisis mode. But by last fall, she was experiencing random and repeated physiological symptoms, including a racing heart and dimmed vision. She diagnosed herself as suffering from post-traumatic stress ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 posing as TINDER dates charged in 'organized attack'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/3-posing-tinder-dates-charged-220000289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Two 18-year-olds “terrorized” two men looking for a Tinder date hook up who instead were attacked from behind, beaten, kidnapped and robbed in Chicago's Kenwood neighborhood earlier this week, prosecutors said Friday. Jahziah McDonald and Jeremiyah Mannie were denied bail Friday by Cook County Judge Arthur Willis during a hearing audio streamed live on YouTube. The suspects, both of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man indicted for using GRINDR to find men for kill and eat...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvertiser.com/story/news/crime/2021/03/19/man-charged-hate-crime-used-grindr-hunting-ground-documents-say/4756378001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chance Seneca is accused of using dating app Grindr used as “hunting grounds,” lured a man to a home where he planned on killing him, according to court documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Atlanta gunman was patient at evangelical treatment center within mile of first targeted spa...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Accused-Atlanta-gunman-was-a-patient-at-16039343.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA - The first spa targeted in the Atlanta-area killings this week was in an area...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could set pattern for sustained partisan war...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/03/19/effort-to-expel-marjorie-taylor-greene-could-set-pattern-for-sustained-partisan-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort to expel Marjorie Taylor Greene from the House could set the stage for extended partisan war in the chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 Cubans in limbo as visa backlog grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/what-is-happening-is-inhumane-100000-cubans-in-limbo-as-us-visa-backlog-grows/ar-BB1eIFHa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — When María Sulay López arrived in the United States in 2014, she assumed her son in Cuba would quickly get a visa to join her. But almost seven years later, the breast cancer patient still doesn’t know when they will be together. As she gasped for breath from an oxygen tank, a result of a permanent tracheotomy, López said she can no longer work and just wants a solution. “I’ve been ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio closes beaches, Bolsonaro frets over vitamin D...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rio-closes-beaches-bid-contain-144643955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio de Janeiro closed its famed beaches Friday in a bid to contain a surge of Covid-19, a move criticized by anti-lockdown President Jair Bolsonaro, who said sun-deprived citizens risked a lack of vitamin D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Gavin Newsom's fateful decision to lockdown California...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-gavin-newsoms-fateful-decision-120012117.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom's March 19, 2020, stay-at-home order was applauded when California was hit less hard by COVID-19 than other parts of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icelandic volcano erupts, lighting up night sky near Reykjavik...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/icelandic-volcano-erupts-lights-night-231325099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A volcano erupted just 40 kilometres (25 miles) from Iceland's capital Reykjavik on Friday, with red lava spewing out of the ground and a crimson glow lighting up the night sky as a no-fly zone was established in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As a 9-year-old, she was saved at sea. Thirty-five years later, she reunited with her rescuers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/9-old-she-saved-sea-130011425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 20 hours in the Pacific Ocean, Desireé Rodriguez was the only one in her family left alive. She had almost given up. Then two fishermen spotted her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setbacks risk another summer travel washout...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210319211628-r8efi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AIRLINES (UPDATE 1, ANALYSIS, PIX):ANALYSIS-Europe's COVID-19 setbacks risk another summer travel washout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANA DEL REY 'MASTERPIECE' WITH 'CHEMTRAILS OVER COUNTRY CLUB'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/03/18/lana-del-rey-delivers-a-pop-masterpiece-with-hit-laden-hypnotic-new-chemtrails-over-the-country-club</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know you’re in for something unusual in 2021 when an album’s title track starts with this couplet: “I’m on the run with you, my sweet love There’s nothing wrong co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE:  Current Cuomo aide makes sex harassment allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Cuomo-faces-new-allegation-of-misbehavior-by-16039850.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another employee of New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, a Democrat, went public Friday with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE BLOB:  MASSIVE JELLYFISH WASHES UP ON MYRTLE BEACH...</title>
      <link>https://www.myrtlebeachonline.com/news/state/south-carolina/article250027144.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.myrtlebeachonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Has no one seen a 50’s horror movie ever? This is how it starts.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany weighs longer lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/germany-weighs-longer-covid-lockdown-amid-exponential-rise/a-56924921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Health Minister Jens Spahn has said that rising infections mean it may be impossible to ease restrictions in the coming weeks. Experts now warn that the rise in cases is "clearly exponential."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most of media totally ignored Biden's Air Force One stumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9381755/Major-media-outlets-shrug-Bidens-stumbles-AF1-steps.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Friday afternoon, the homepages of MSNBC, CBS News, Washington Post, Los Angeles Times and New York Times had no mention of Biden's stumbling incident earlier in the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates says he'll fly a lot less, eat more synthetic meat to fight climate change...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/19/bill-gates-says-hell-fly-less-to-fight-climate-change.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates said Friday in an Ask Me Anything session on Reddit that he aims to cut his carbon consumption by flying less and eating synthetic meat more often.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Current Cuomo aide makes sex harassment allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/19/current-cuomo-aide-accuses-governor-of-sexual-harassment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A current aide to Gov. Andrew Cuomo accused him of trying to cover up the allegation that he groped one of her colleagues — while also sharing her own disturbing interactions with her boss, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asylum' signs welcome those crossing illegally in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/19/asylum-signs-welcome-migrants-who-cross-illegally-in-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Texas — A few hundred feet from the murky, green waters of the Rio Grande River, a handwritten sign tucked inside a plastic Department of Homeland Security property sleeve is duct ta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces New Claims of Sex Harassment From Current Aide...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/19/cuomo-faces-new-claims-of-sexual-harassment-from-current-aide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. — He called her and her co-worker “mingle mamas.” He inquired about her lack of a wedding ring,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mar-a-Lago partially closed due to outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-coronavirus-pandemic-mar-a-lago-32a7a9694c1f738eef6af6d3fc6e5aa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former President Donald Trump's Palm Beach club has been partially closed because of a COVID outbreak. That’s according to several people familiar with the situation,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
