<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NFL star threatens to quit if he can't wear old helmet...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27356491/sources-ab-says-no-football-old-helmet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raiders receiver Antonio Brown has threatened to not play football if the NFL will not allow him to wear the same helmet he has worn throughout his career, even though it is no longer approved, sources told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Drunk flight attendant slurs safety speech, passes out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnd.com/news/state/illinois/article233658102.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson lost 40 pounds through starvation in jail...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/tommy-robinson-40-pounds-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vigilantes, mob justice grow as violence mounts in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/29eefa28f74c43358eb2df99ad1c5a8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Vigilante attacks and mob justice appeared to be on the rise in Mexico this week as violence mounted, more than two dozen bodies appeared along roadsides and the government...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How madam lured girls into depraved world...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article233704797.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED FLAGS OVER RED FLAG...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf77af0e76664973b45fcf1547f91580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said Friday he believes he has influence to rally Republicans around stronger federal background check laws as Congress and the White House work on a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security 'incidents' force soccer standouts to miss season opener...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/09/football/arsenal-mesut-ozil-sead-kolasinac-security-intl-gbr/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Arsenal football club players will not travel with the team to play against Newcastle United on Sunday, after the club withdrew them over security concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROUNDUP labels warning of cancer won't be permitted, EPA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/roundup-labels-trump-administration-says-it-wont-approve-glyphosate-warning-labels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The EPA said California's warnings that Roundup's glyphosate is known to cause cancer represent "false labeling"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport occupied; Security tightened...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/transport/article/3022074/security-increased-hong-kong-international-airport-ahead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands expected to join the peaceful sit-in against the extradition bill, which could last until Sunday. Passengers told to arrive early as airport introduces extra ID and ticket checks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI can't hack Dayton shooter's phone...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/09/fbi-cant-hack-into-dayton-shooter-connor-betts-phone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is having trouble unlocking Dayton mass murderer Connor Betts’ primary smartphone — and it may take years before they crack it. Agency officials said during a congressional hearing th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poop less for cleaner planet, says Brazil's president...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/poop-less-cleaner-planet-says-brazils-president-195014136.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro suggested Friday that people "poop every other day" as a way to save the environment, after he came under fire for a surge in deforestation of the Amazon since he came to power. Bolsonaro has been criticized for a rapid acceleration in deforestation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug shortages forcing hospitals to ration treatments...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/drug-shortages-forcing-hospitals-to-ration-treatments-2019-08-09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shortage of a drug used to treat immune disorders is forcing U.S. hospitals to suspend treatment for some patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairground Ride in Cathedral Draws Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-norfolk-49292493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fairground ride is put in a cathedral's nave to allow people to stand close to its medieval roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 million Muslims on hajj pilgrimage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/more-two-million-muslims-hajj-pilgrimage-191252277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two million Muslims began the annual hajj Friday under sweltering conditions, as the Saudi hosts sought to deter politicisation of the pilgrimage against a backdrop of simmering Gulf tensions. The hajj, one of the world's largest annual religious gatherings, is one of the five pillars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe Poised to Put Warning Labels on Jewish-Made Products...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/europe-poised-to-put-warning-labels-on-jewish-made-products/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union is poised to mandate that Israeli products made in contested territories carry consumer warning labels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7342169/Prince-Andrew-exposed-Teen-sex-slave-alleges-pair-intimate-Ghislaine-Maxwells-London-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Roberts, whose defamation case against Epstein's alleged madame Ghislaine Maxwell is the source of these unsealed documents, provides a photo of herself with Prince Andrew and Maxwell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Senator, Governor, Hedge Fund Manager, Professor...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/09/jeffrey-epsteins-alleged-sex-slave-reveals-the-men-she-claims-she-was-forced-to-sleep-with/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein’s alleged teenage “sex slave” claims she was ordered to sleep with powerful men — including a former US senator, the former governor of New Mexico, a prominent hed…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDOWS Malware Records Victim's Desktop -- When Viewing Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/windows-malware-strain-records-users-on-adult-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Varenyky trojan records videos of users navigating adult sites. Currently targeting only French users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest frogs so strong they build their own ponds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/09/africa/goliath-frog-intl-scli-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research shows that Goliath frogs -- the world's largest frog species -- build ponds for their eggs and tadpoles, pushing rocks more than half of their body weight in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Trans Reality TV Star Found Hanged in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/miriam-rivera-dead-dies-reality-tv-first-trans-star-1203297832/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miriam Rivera, the world’s first transgender reality television star, died Feb. 5 in Mexico under mysterious circumstances. She was 38. Though Rivera died several months ago, the news emerged…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge power cut brings UK to its knees with trains halted and traffic signals off...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9691385/power-cut-uk-trains-tubes-power-lights-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HUGE power cut has hit the UK, with trains, tubes and traffic lights cutting out across the country. Britain was plunged into darkness at rush hour with large parts of London, the South East, Liv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsealed Documents Name Powerful Men in Epstein Sex Ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-unsealed-documents-name-powerful-men-in-sex-ring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In newly unsealed documents, Virginia Giuffre claims that Jeffrey Epstein and Ghislaine Maxwell trafficked her to politicians, princes, and a high-flying financier, among others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sides with Kim criticism of US-SKorea war games... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-sides-kim-criticism-us-skorea-war-games-154612612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump told reporters Friday he agreed with Kim Jong Un's opposition to US-South Korea war games, after receiving what he was a new letter from the North Korean leader. "I got a very beautiful letter from Kim Jong Un yesterday," Trump said. "He wasn't happy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartel Shoots at Border Patrol Agents On Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/08/09/gulf-cartel-shoots-at-u-s-border-patrol-agents-on-rio-grande/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gulf Cartel gunmen fired what are believed to be AK-47s or similar weapons at U.S. Border Patrol agents on the Rio Grande.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA reauthorizes use of cyanide bombs to kill wild animals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/09/epa-reauthorizes-use-of-cyanide-bombs-to-kill-wild-animals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has reauthorized the use of controversial traps dubbed “cyanide bombs” to kill coyotes, foxes and other animals across the US. The Environmental Protection Agency announced…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  APPROVAL 42%...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/262694/latest-trump-job-approval-rating.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gallup's latest update finds President Donald Trump's job approval rating at 42%, about where it has been since May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas ready to debut their first film...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/8/hollywood-regulars-obamas-ready-to-debut-their-fir/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama and Michelle Obama, who signed an exclusive production deal with Netflix some 15 months ago, are now readying their first release, a documentary titled “American Factory,” which debuts Aug. 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun activists warn could lose their votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/gun-rights-supporters-say-trump-could-lose-their-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than a week before calling for more gun control laws, President Trump invited boos at a massive Ohio campaign rally, warning 17,000 supporters that if Democrats reclaim power, “there is no Second Amendment.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To keep Texas county red, Republican says time to become politically intolerant...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/sns-tns-bc-texas-gop-intolerance-20190809-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas There's a new political battle cry in Tarrant County, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missle test gone wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1163716/Russia-latest-news-Putin-military-explosion-nuclear-missile-radiation-leak-world-war-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN naval base is on a mysterious month-long lockdown after an accidental missile explosion at the base was linked to a sudden radiation spike in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armie Hammer calls out MARVEL exec Trump contributions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/456834-armie-hammer-calls-out-marvel-chairmans-trump-contributions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armie Hammer on Friday called out one of the most powerful men in entertainment over his politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER explosion...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/russia/201908091076515014-new-explosion-hits-military-facility-in-russias-south-five-injured/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, a fire erupted at a military depot located near the Siberian city of Achinsk, which caused multiple explosions and left 12 people injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDIDATE FATIGUE IN IOWA</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/too-many-candidates-iowans-tired-051716837.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jake Poorman is exhausted. Iowans treasure the national attention that shines on them every four years when presidential candidates descend on the state, whose caucuses mark the beginning of an election year. The concern isn't limited to Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man reports Glock stolen during weekend-long orgy at home...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/gun-stolen-during-weekend-gathering-274938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 8--In the midst of a weekend-long orgy, a 9mm handgun was stolen from the host's bedroom, according to Florida police who are not confident in catching the thief since guests at the gathering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sleep loss 'breathalyzer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7338853/Scientists-identify-way-spot-brain-impaired-lack-shut-eye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study from the NASA Ames Research Center in California says that tracking eye-movements were significantly impaired from people who didn't get enough sleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME FOR A BREAK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/955b8436cd084f58a42ff96ee78330ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Hoarding Food, Gold In Anticipation Of Global Collapse?</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/is-china-hoarding-food-gold-and-other-commodities-in-anticipation-of-a-global-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does China believe that we are on the verge of a major global crisis?  The communist Chinese government has always been very big into planning, and it appears that they have decided that now is the time to hoard food, gold and other commodities.  Of course in recent days the fact that China is compl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside TACO BELL hotel in Palm Springs...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/food/story/2019-08-08/taco-bell-hotel-palm-springs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We got a room at the Taco Bell hotel in Palm Springs. This is our story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 YEARS OF PUTIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/after-20-years-is-vladimir-putins-untouchable-image-crumbling/a-49953706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During Vladimir Putin's two decades in power, polls have often shown Russians blame their government rather than their president for their problems. Amidst a new wave of domestic tension, that could be changing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Alligator Eats Woman's 100-Pound Dog...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/08/08/florida-woman-alligator-ate-her-dog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman says an alligator ate her 100-pound dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Asks Clerk For 'Anything That Would Kill 200 People'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/08/08/florida-man-walmart-employee-anything-kill-200-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida man ran into some trouble with police on Thursday, after he reportedly asked a Walmart clerk for "anything that would kill 200 people."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
