<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>US-Japan trade deal 'done in principle'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/25/us-japan-trade-deal-g7-1474461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abe said the agreement followed “a series of intensive negotiations.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houses Of Worship Find New Life After Congregations Dwindle...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/08/24/753256634/houses-of-worship-find-new-life-after-congregations-downsize</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the percentage of Americans who belong to a church, mosque or synagogue declines, congregations are selling their buildings. Some of those former houses of worship are finding new life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran foreign minister makes surprise visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ac47e26e6d2c4f8e8546460d6780b4f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIARRITZ, France (AP) — The Latest on the Group of Seven leaders' summit (all times local): 4:15 p.m. A senior French official says France invited Iran's foreign minister to the venue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-7 cracks emerge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f19d28009bc94db387ac238dffa27348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIARRITZ, France (AP) — The first fissures emerged among G-7 leaders on Sunday over how to deal with Iran, as U.S. President Donald Trump denied he had signed on to an agreement on giving France a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police draw guns as protesters chase them...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/51e60b361c4a467caa4e73bf9a60372e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — The Latest on Hong Kong protests (all times local): 9:35 p.m. Hong Kong police officers have pulled their guns and reportedly shot a warning shot after they were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans' love of hiking has driven elk to the brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/aug/25/hiking-elk-driven-to-brink-colorado-vail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trail use near Vail, Colorado, has more than doubled since 2009. It’s had a devastating impact on a herd of elk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Biggest holy s*** moment in sports in while'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/sports/nfl/dallas-cowboys/article234357587.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mooch attends Biden fundraiser in Hamptons...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/2019/08/the-mooch-attended-biden-fundraiser-in-the-hamptons-because-trump-has-lost-his-mind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House press secretary Anthony Scaramucci attended a fundraiser for former Vice President Joe Biden on Saturday. CBS News reporter Ben Mitchell posted a photo of Scaramucci at the event, and subsequently interviewed “The Mooch.” Scaramucci said he was still a registered Republican, but added that Trump “has lost his mind.” Spotted at a […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of neighbors diagnosed with brain tumors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dozens-who-lived-in-same-neighborhood-diagnosed-with-brain-tumors/ar-AAGhbtr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia fires 2 missiles from nuke subs in Arctic Ocean...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/24/europe/russia-test-fires-ballistic-missiles/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The missiles launch took place from two nuclear-powered submarines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Walsh announces Republican challenge for president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/458720-joe-walsh-announces-republican-challenge-to-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Joe Walsh (R-Ill.) on Sunday announced he would mount a primary challenge to President Trump.The conservative radio host made the announcement on ABC's "This Week."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Reunited With Lost Cat -- 11 Years Later!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/23/new-york-cat-returns-home-11-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was found wandering, seemingly living in plain sight, just a few miles from his Dutchess County home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals judge found shot dead behind home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/25/stephen-goss-appeals-judge-found-shot-dead-behind-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An appeals judge in Georgia was found Saturday shot dead behind his Albany home, but officials do not believe it was a homicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong police use water cannon in latest clashes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-police-water-cannon-latest-clashes-113026680.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong police fired water cannon towards protesters for the first time on Sunday in a significant escalation of clashes that have rocked the city for the past three months. The financial hub has been gripped by street demonstrations that were initially against a proposed extradition bill to China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: More Dangerous Than WMDs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/08/amazon-fires-show-limits-sovereignty/596779/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person shouldn’t have the power to set policies that doom the rest of humanity’s shot at mitigating rising temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid restrictions to end at UK airports because of new technology...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/security-upgrades-in-uk-airports-will-mean-no-more-unpacking-liquids-11793561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The upgrades should mean the end of the 100ml limit on liquids, but the new technology will not be introduced straight away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea's tests new 'super-large' multiple rocket launcher...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aea805efb3f842c38680b523018263bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Sunday leader Kim Jong Un supervised the test-firing of a "newly developed super-large multiple rocket launcher," another demonstration of its expanding...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: LA deputy confesses to fabricating sniper shooting...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/lancaster-deputy-confessed-to-fabricating-sniper-shooting-authorities-say/5491304/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles Sheriff's Department deputy who was reported shot in Lancaster this week made up the incident, authorities announced during a rare Saturday night news conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters, Protestors Clash At Straight Pride Event In CA...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/24/approximately-200-people-gather-at-straight-pride-event-in-modesto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 200 people gathered, including protestors, at a Straight Pride event this afternoon in Modesto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUT OF LUCK:  Colts QB  to retire after latest injury; 'Mentally worn down'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27456682/luck-informs-colts-retiring-source-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Luck has informed the Indianapolis Colts that he is retiring from the NFL, a source told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Foley reinvented!</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-mark-foley-post-scandal-trump-republican-20190823-lsaesyt5yrfiba4afvyjh2lcz4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Foley had a stunning downfall, resigning from Congress in 2006 over sexually laced Internet messages to teens. In 2019, he's being honored by the Republican Party and he's a supporter of President Donald Trump. And despite $1 million in his congressional campaign account, he downplays suggestions of a comeback attempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change in politics with more black voters in Deep South...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/08/12/a-change-in-politics-with-more-black-voters-in-the-deep-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third dengue fever case confirmed in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article234329597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRETS OF PRINCE ANDREW'S SIX DAYS WITH EPSTEIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7391369/Prince-Andrew-spent-six-days-Jeffrey-Epsteins-home-two-years-convicted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York stayed over a period of six days with shamed financier Jeffrey Epstein in 2010. This was two years after the businessman was convicted of having sex with a child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Stephanopolous went to lavish party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7391265/Woody-Allen-pictured-leaving-Jeffrey-Epsteins-mansion-lavish-party-royals-honor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial film director, 83, and his wife Soon-Yi, 48, attended the New York party. They left Epstein's house midway through Prince Andrew's visit, at 11.30am on December 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea's Kim Guides Test Fire of New Rocket Launcher...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-korea-kim-guides-test-230203645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- North Korea’s Kim Jong Un guided a test fire of a newly developed super-large multiple rocket launcher on Saturday, setting the stage for one of the busiest weekends for missile firings since talks began with U.S. President Donald Trump more than a year ago.The test firing comes after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson's Long Journey From Trump Hater to Best Friend...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boris-johnsons-long-journey-trump-135221894.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In December 2015, Boris Johnson joked that he wouldn’t go to some parts of New York because of the risk of meeting Donald Trump, a man of "stupefying ignorance."How times change.Johnson was London’s popular mayor, Trump a presidential outsider attacking the U.K. capital on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asserts He Can Force U.S. Companies to Leave China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be18b8619cde4658a418dda4f416968a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIARRITZ, France (AP) — President Donald Trump is threatening to use the emergency authority granted by a powerful but obscure federal law to make good on his tweeted "order" to U.S. businesses to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican reporter found dead with stab wounds amid escalating violence...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190824235434-e4b38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/:Mexican reporter found dead with stab wounds amid escalating violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete making faith-based appeal to voters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf10ec40db0b407f85a45edd1f261819</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KEOKUK, Iowa (AP) — The question was about climate change. The answer soon turned to the Bible. And Pete Buttigieg knew the verses. "There's a lot about the stewardship of creation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple injured by lightening strike at PGA championship in Atlanta...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4de295e646a740ce9013af0fe1c279e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Six people were injured Saturday when lightning struck a 60-foot pine at the Tour Championship where they were taking cover from rain and showered them with debris, Atlanta police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/refresh/AL052019_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/205313_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Dorian forms over the Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/forecasters-tracking-tropical-disturbance-as-it-moves-closer-to-florida/70009155 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Issues Sanctions on Top Trump Admin Officials...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-issues-sanctions-on-top-trump-admin-officials-sen-cruz/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian lawmakers are preparing to issue a salvo of sanctions on top Trump administration figures and their supporters in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple injured by lightening strike at PGA championship in Atlanta...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbs46.com/news/multiple-injured-by-lightening-strike-at-pga-championship-in-atlanta/article_9e71de20-c6b7-11e9-a6c4-83037e826fe0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbs46.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST LAKE, Ga. (CBS46) -- Multiple people were struck by lighting at East Lake Gold Club on Sunday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic storm clouds hovering over Trump and global leaders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/052e7f4497f14e319ed67cef9f9332cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIARRITZ, France (AP) — Under the threatening clouds of a global economic slowdown, President Donald Trump is confronting the consequences of his preference to go it alone, with low expectations...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antibiotic-resistant Salmonella strain confirmed as 'superbugs' continue to worry experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/08/24/antibiotic-resistant-salmonella-strain-found-cdc-worries-scientists/2093599001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strain of Salmonella found in beef and soft cheeses in the United States and Mexico has been found resistant to antibiotics, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squabbles erupt...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g7-summit/squabbles-erupt-as-g7-leaders-arrive-for-summit-in-france-idUSKCN1VD2MM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Squabbles erupted among G7 nations on Saturday even before their leaders had gat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUX ON THE SEAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/geffen-yacht-celebrities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why we can’t stop thinking about Katy Perry, Orlando Bloom, and Oprah on David Geffen’s yacht.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Williamson: We have bit of a 'mad King George' in charge...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/458683-marianne-williamson-on-trump-we-have-a-little-bit-of-a-mad-king-george-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House hopeful and author Marianne Williamson likened President Trump to King George, the monarch from whom the U.S. declared independence, and hammered his trade policies as responsible for market instability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical disturbance brewing near Florida; Hurricane may target Caribbean...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/A-tropical-disturbance-is-brewing-near-Florida-14375757.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the mid-September peak of Atlantic hurricane season draws nearer, the tropics are heating up. A disturbance off the Florida coast is likely to become a tropical depression or storm in the coming days as it heads north but remains offshore.  Meanwhile, a second disturbance tracking toward the Caribbean was declared a tropical depression Saturday morning and is forecast to become a hurricane.  Should these tropical weather systems earn names, they will be called Dorian and Erin.  And it probably won't be long until there are others to keep an eye on.  The National Hurricane Center currently gives the system near Florida a 70 percent chance of developing into a tropical depression or tropical storm over the next 48 hours and a 90 percent chance in the next five days.  In its Saturday morning discussion, the Hurricane Center wrote that the disturbance is unlikely to strengthen Saturday given its proximity to land. But that's not the end of it.  "Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual development once the low moves off the east-central coast of Florida over the western Atlantic by Sunday," they wrote.  The main risks from the disturbance at present are rain related. Parts of South Florida could see downpours into Sunday. Some isolated flooding could result, although the most widespread torrential rain seems likely to stay offshore.  Computer models insist that whatever forms from this disturbance will not strike the United States. But as it is likely to parallel the coast between the U.S. and Bermuda, high waves, rip currents, and even some coastal flooding are possible along much of the Eastern Seaboard early next week.  What may become a more threatening system down the line is the tropical depression slowly marching toward the Caribbean Sea. This system is now...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
President 'hereby' orders U.S. business out of China. Can he do that?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Trump-hereby-orders-U-S-business-out-of-China-14374432.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's extraordinary edict demanding U.S. companies move out of China - delivered in a series of angry tweets Friday - left industries of every stripe scrambling to understand how seriously to take the order, and how the White House might enforce it.  Businesses from retail to electronics to home goods, many already under pressure from a months-long U.S.-China trade war, were contacting their industry associations for guidance and awaiting more substantive announcements from the White House.  "I'm trying to keep my cool and not get worried and upset, but it's becoming hard," said Margaret Raible, founder of Lite Gear Bags, a luggage maker based in Vallejo, California.  She has a meeting next week with an industry colleague to discuss moving more of her manufacturing from China to India or South Africa, she said. "I don't know how much faster I can move or how much more urgency I can have," she said.  Late Friday night, as he arrived in France for the G7, Trump suggested on Twitter he would be looking to the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, signed into law in 1977, to follow up on his demand.  Trump does not have the authority to "duly order" companies to leave China, according to Jennifer Hillman, a Georgetown University law professor and trade expert at the Council on Foreign Relations.  But under the law he cited, Trump can prevent future transfers of funds to China, she said. First, he would have to make "a lawful declaration that a national emergency exists," she said.  Congress could terminate the declaration if it wishes, she said.  "Moreover, even if all this happened, it would not provide authority over all of the U.S. investments that have already been made in China," Hillman said.  Other trade experts said Trump does have powerful tools...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll 'clones' demand soars as customers order models of friends' girlfriends...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/sex-doll-clones-demand-soars-18992206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bizarre sex doll trend has taken off this year. Punters are asking for models that resemble their friend's partners</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wags and weeds: Invasive plants meet match in detection dogs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b57bc5e73f0648be9c0f822c9c220cdd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TUXEDO, N.Y. (AP) — In brushy terrain where a botanical interloper evades detection by the human eye, count on Dia to sniff it out. Dia is a spunky Labrador retriever trained to track down a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic mushrooms for better health? Psychedelic drugs having moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/24/magic-mushrooms-gain-popularity-following-decriminalization-efforts/1999501001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proponents say psychedelics from magic mushrooms hold mental health benefits, but doctors remain cautious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant sheep being bred in lab to fight human brain disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/aug/24/mutant-sheep-may-help-cure-batten-disease-roslin-institute-genetic-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roslin Institute scientists create a flock to mimic human gene that causes Batten disorder</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Police Photoshopped His Mug Shot for Lineup. He's Not Only One...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/24/us/police-photoshop-tattoos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When witness descriptions made no mention of a suspect’s facial tattoos, the police airbrushed them away for an identification lineup. The practice goes beyond one case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEFFEN YACHT SNAPS BECOME TOP STATUS IN MEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/how-david-geffens-yacht-photos-became-a-status-thing-hollywood-1233154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A voyage on Rising Sun is summer’s "most coveted" vacation for A-listers with Oprah Winfrey, Chris Rock, Steven Spielberg, Leonardo DiCaprio and even Jeff Bezos popping up on the mogul’s Instagram feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The robots are coming for your job, too...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/24/politics/economy-us-workforce-automation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The robots. They're coming for your jobs. But what is very much up for debate in the imaginations of economists and Hollywood producers is whether the future will look like "The Terminator" or "The Jetsons."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'China not paying for it': Tariff hike hits beer brewers to book publishers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/24/china-is-not-paying-for-it-trumps-tariffs-hit-beer-brewers-and-book-publishers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American small and medium-size companies that rely on China are scrambling to adjust their business plans in response to the escalating trade war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of new fires in Brazil as Amazon outrage grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hundreds-fires-brazil-amazon-outrage-grows-141009002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of new fires are raging in the Amazon rainforest in northern Brazil, official data showed Saturday, amid growing international pressure on President Jair Bolsonaro to put out the worst blazes in years. Official figures show 78,383 forest fires were recorded in Brazil so far this year, the highest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haley-Pence rivalry heats up as GOP weighs post-Trump future...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/24/haley-pence-rivalry-post-trump-1474377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interviews with top Republicans reveal they're watching each other warily ahead of a potential 2024 showdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST CRIME IN SPACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7390353/NASA-investigates-claims-astronaut-accessed-spouses-bank-account-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decorated astronaut Anne McClain (far left and far right) is accused of accessing estranged wife Summer Worden's (in black) bank account as part of a campaign to gain custody of her son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIARRITZ BRACED!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7389913/Trump-opens-G7-slap-leaders-calling-friends-part.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump threw shade at some of America's closest partners on Friday evening, mere hours before he'd see them in Biarritz at the Group of Seven summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: APPLE Contractors Listening to 1000 Siri Customer Recordings a Day...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201908241076625393-each-apple-contractor-listening-1000-siri-customer-recordings-day/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contractors hired by Apple reportedly listened to more than 1,000 Siri recordings per shift containing private information of the company’s customers, before Apple suspended the internal project.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
