<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>At his New Jersey golf club, Trump finds supportive audience...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/16c9d20d2286da893fa5317c98df68a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEDMINSTER, N.J. (AP) — They hustled down the stairs, the rain dabbing their polo shirts and golf attire, as they dashed inside the clubhouse, drinks in their hands and masks missing from their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES 'Blatantly Sexist' Headline Comparing to 'THE BACHELOR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/la-times-sexist-headline-comparing-biden-campaign-to-the-bachelor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Times came under fire after giving a "blatantly sexist" headline comparing Joe Biden's campaign to "The Bachelor"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'threat' against former Saudi spy in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/politics/article-former-saudi-intelligence-chief-faces-new-death-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saad Aljabri has been living in exile in Toronto since 2017</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida cases trend higher again...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/coronavirus/fl-ne-florida-coronavirus-deaths-cases-saturday-august-8-20200808-dm7hljll55ej3bmzajp6f4ndjq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been three consecutive days of increases in both COVID-19 cases and fatalities, though the totals are not close to Florida's record highs set last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A lost summer: How President fell short in confronting virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-lost-summer-How-Trump-fell-short-in-15469703.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As the White House chief of staff, Mark Meadows is responsible for coordinating the vast executive branch, including its coronavirus response. But in closed-door meetings, he has revealed his skepticism of the two physicians guiding the anti-pandemic effort, Deborah Birx and Anthony Fauci, routinely questioning their expertise, according to senior administration officials and other people briefed on the internal discussions.  Meadows no longer holds a daily 8 a.m. meeting that includes health professionals to discuss the raging pandemic. Instead, aides said, he huddles in the mornings with a half-dozen politically oriented aides - and when the virus comes up, their focus is more on how to convince the public that President Donald Trump has the crisis under control, rather than on methodically planning ways to contain it.  During coronavirus meetings, Meadows has repeatedly questioned the scientific consensus that wearing masks helps contain the spread of the novel coronavirus, officials said. He has regularly raised with Fauci and others a range of issues on which he thinks Fauci has been wrong, and he personally monitors the infectious-disease expert's media appearances. When he catches Fauci sounding out of sync with Trump, the chief of staff admonishes the doctor to "stay on message," officials said - and he has impressed upon Fauci, Birx and other public health professionals that they should not opine on restrictions or make policy in the media.  In an interview Saturday, Meadows said he has been appropriately skeptical of information presented to him but disputed that he is anti-science.  "My comments to all of our doctors is that they need to stick with the science, comment on the science and do not become media commentators and opine on what may or may not happen," he said. "I've been consistent from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive actions to curb voting by mail?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/08/trump-wants-to-cut-mail-in-voting-the-republican-machine-is-helping-him-392428</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s campaign and the Republican Party have taken to the courts dozens to challenge voting rules. Trump's aides are pondering possible executive actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris makes masks mandatory...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/paris-makes-masks-mandatory-as-virus-toll-crosses-722000/ar-BB17Jwjn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attempts to wrest tax and spending powers from Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-attempts-to-wrest-tax-and-spending-powers-from-congress-with-new-executive-actions/ar-BB17JjQI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bourbon Street to Food Banks, Signs of Slow Recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/from-bourbon-street-to-food-banks-signs-of-a-slow-us-recovery/ar-BB17J5da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces legal challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trumps-stimulus-orders-dont-seem-to-be-feasible-or-legal-experts-say-2020-08-08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump’s executive order and memorandum to stimulate the economy don’t seem to be feasible or legal, experts said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  Republican satisfaction with state of America has plummeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/republican-satisfaction-with-the-state-of-america-has-plummeted-2020-08-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall American satisfaction is the lowest it’s been in almost a decade, Gallup reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 DAYS UNTIL FIRST DEBATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/columns/eric-zorn/ct-column-biden-trump-senility-trap-20200808-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is setting a very low bar for &amp;quot;Sleepy Joe&amp;quot; to jump over in debates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC businessman has record of success, but he's drawing fire as new postmaster general...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/politics-government/article244724002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTA BACK AT HOTSPOT?</title>
      <link>https://waok.radio.com/articles/news/coronavirus-task-force-s-dr-birx-concerned-about-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;waok.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus Task Force’s Dr. Birx ‘concerned’ about COVID-19 numbers in Atlanta</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's up and who's down...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/511131-biden-edges-closer-to-vp-pick-heres-whos-up-and-whos-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is expected to choose his running mate this weekend, after a months-long search that began with several dozen options and has been narrowed down to a select few, confidants say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA parties head for Hollywood Hills as mayor vows crackdown... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/la-parties-head-hollywood-hills-013929200.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Los Angeles nightclubs closed, party promoters have turned to mansions in the Hollywood Hills to throw lavish, raucous and sometimes deadly gatherings that have enraged neighbors and local officials. Starting this weekend, Mayor Eric Garcetti has granted emergency powers to utility workers to cut</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-hit Italy cautiously embraces new normal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hard-hit-italy-cautiously-embraces-173918524.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy has eased out of its strict coronavirus lockdown and has returned to a semblance of normality without -- so far -- a major, secondary flare-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data failures add to California struggle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-data-failures-add-californias-130000353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials still scrambling to fix a database tracking coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Dodd, Insider From Biden's Past, Helping Him Pick His Future...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/08/bidens-v-p-search-chris-dodd-a-d-c-insider-helping-pick-the-democratic-running-mate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. knew how to flatter an old friend. He had been sitting in the Oval</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jailed on felony for Slurpee battery on 7-ELEVEN worker...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/slurpee-battery-arrest-716953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 8--A Florida Man was jailed yesterday on a felony Slurpee battery charge, records show. Investigators allege that Brian Duffy, 40, last month doused a 7-Eleven employee with the frozen treat d</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allows some unemployment pay, defers payroll tax...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/555a34baec6ce9ee9b532799fca58bc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEDMINSTER, N.J. (AP) — Seizing the power of his podium and his pen, President Donald Trump on Saturday bypassed the nation's lawmakers as he claimed the authority to defer payroll taxes and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% have no symptoms. Might they be key to ending?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/40-of-people-with-coronavirus-have-no-symptoms-15469295.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When researcher Monica Gandhi began digging deeper into outbreaks of the novel coronavirus, she was struck by the extraordinarily high number of infected people who had no symptoms.  A Boston homeless shelter had 147 infected residents, but 88% had no symptoms even though they shared their living space. A Tyson Foods poultry plant in Springdale, Ark., had 481 infections, and 95% were asymptomatic. Prisons in Arkansas, North Carolina, Ohio and Virginia counted 3,277 infected people, but 96% were asymptomatic.  During its seven-month global rampage, the coronavirus has claimed more than 700,000 lives. But Gandhi began to think the bigger mystery might be why it has left so many more practically unscathed.  What was it about these asymptomatic people, who lived or worked so closely to others who fell severely ill, she wondered, that protected them? Did the "dose" of their viral exposure make a difference? Was it genetics? Or might some people already have partial resistance to the virus, contrary to our initial understanding?  Efforts to understand the diversity in the illness are finally beginning to yield results, raising hope that the knowledge will help accelerate development of vaccines and therapies - or possibly even create new pathways toward herd immunity in which enough of the population develops a mild version of the virus that they block further spread and the pandemic ends.  "A high rate of asymptomatic infection is a good thing," said Gandhi, an infectious-disease specialist at the University of California at San Francisco. "It's a good thing for the individual and a good thing for society."  The coronavirus has left numerous clues - the uneven transmission in different parts of the world, the mostly mild impact on children. Perhaps most tantalizing is the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman: Actual national debt is $30 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/buck-actual-national-debt-30-trillion-theres-no-conversation-dc-about-paying-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This troubles me greatly, but all I see is more spending' with 'no conversation in Washington D.C. about how to pay this money back,’ Rep. Buck says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrators take control of govt buildings in Beirut amid violent protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/beirut-braces-for-protests-as-grief-over-blast-turns-to-fury-resign-or-hang/2020/08/08/5c050e3e-d8e2-11ea-a788-2ce86ce81129_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators storm the Foreign Ministry amid deep anger in a country already reeling from economic collapse and chronic corruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK fate was shaped by 'knockdown, drag-out' Oval Office brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/TikTok-s-fate-was-shaped-by-knockdown-drag-out-15469209.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Last week, as leaders in Silicon Valley, China and Washington raced to seal the fate of one of the world's fastest-growing social media companies, a shouting match broke out in the Oval Office between two of President Donald Trump's top advisers.  In front of Trump, trade adviser Peter Navarro and other aides, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin began arguing that the Chinese-owned video-sharing service TikTok should be sold to a U.S. company. Mnuchin had talked several times to Microsoft's senior leaders and was confident that he had rallied support within the administration for a sale to the tech giant on national security grounds.  Navarro pushed back, demanding an outright ban of TikTok, while accusing Mnuchin of being soft on China, the people said, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discuss private discussions freely. The treasury secretary appeared taken aback, they said.  The ensuing argument - which was described by one of the people as a "knockdown, drag-out" brawl - was preceded by months of backroom dealings among investors, lobbyists and executives. Many of these stakeholders long understood the critical nature of establishing close connections with key figures in the Trump administration.  But over the past few weeks, they also were reminded of the unpredictable and precarious nature of business dealings under a Trump-led government - and how the winner of a heated debate in front of the president could help decide the fate of a multibillion-dollar deal that may reshape the technology business landscape for years to come.  Over the past two weeks, TikTok's future has been publicly tossed about, first as it appeared that the president would agree to a sale, then that he would ban it outright, then that he would allow a sale again - but only if a fee were paid to the U.S. Treasury.  Behind...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Data Shows 207,000 'Excess Deaths' During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/cdc-data-shows-207000-excess-deaths-during-coronavirus-pandemic-far-eclipsing-160000-confirmed-death-count/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a New York Times analysis of data from the Centers for Disease Control, there have been 207,000 excess deaths in the United States during the coronavirus pandemic, much higher than the current total of 161,000 confirmed deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump path to winning runs through small Rust Belt towns - like one near Biden hometown...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/politics/pennsylvania/carbondale-pennsylvania-trump-biden-2020-election-20200808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Trump rebounds from a slide in the polls to win Pennsylvania again, it will be partly thanks to smaller cities like Carbondale scattered all across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia pastor has potential to take Senate seat away from warring Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Georgia-pastor-has-potential-to-take-Senate-seat-15469097.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats have longed for the day when once ruby-red Georgia would be ready to transform into a diverse urban-suburban stronghold in their column.  Joe Biden's presidential campaign has made it a top target. Republicans and their allies have already reserved $30 million in ad spending to defend Sen. David Perdue, a Republican, from a surprisingly strong challenge.  But the GOP fear of a perfect storm has always involved the second Georgia Senate race, an odd special election with five potentially strong contenders thrown together on the initial November ballot, including appointed Sen. Kelly Loeffler, a Republican, and the Rev. Raphael Warnock, a Democrat.  A confluence of events has created a moment for Warnock's campaign that, if he can seize it, could turn into a political disaster for Republicans and a boon for Democrats.  Warnock, as senior pastor of Ebenezer Baptist Church, just oversaw the nationally televised funeral of John Lewis, the congressman and civil rights icon whose stature brought three presidents to Warnock's pulpit for eulogies.  His bid to become Georgia's first Black U.S. senator had already begun to find its footing after the death of George Floyd in Minneapolis and the ensuing police brutality protests. And on Tuesday, as the WNBA launched its pandemic-delayed season, many players adorned "VOTE WARNOCK" warm-up shirts before games, including those on the Atlanta Dream.  That's the team Loeffler owns, a protest to the senator's public opposition to basketball players embracing the Black Lives Matter movement.  Now Warnock gets to test something that he highlighted when he launched his long-shot campaign on Jan. 30, touting his rise from one of 12 children growing up in the Savannah projects to running the church the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. used as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Execute them'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200808-execute-them-lebanon-protesters-demand-revenge-after-blast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Execute them': Lebanon protesters demand revenge after blast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly 'Romeo and Juliet' risk COVID-19 for one final embrace...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/08/elderly-florida-couple-braved-covid-19-for-one-final-embrace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was love in the time of COVID-19 for a 90-year-old Florida man who died Saturday after he insisted on visiting his beloved wife who had caught the virus. Sam Reck died of coronavirus-related com…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over deadly explosion...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/08/clashes-erupt-in-beirut-at-blast-protest-as-lebanons-anger-boils-over/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT, Lebanon — Clashes between demonstrators and security forces broke out near Lebanon’s Parliament on Saturday at a protest fueled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Dodd, an Insider From Biden's Past, Is Helping Him Pick His Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/08/us/politics/biden-vp-chris-dodd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Biden works to win over progressive voters, he has empowered a Washington uber-veteran long trailed by allegations of personal and financial indiscretion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VP PICK DOWN TO WIRE</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/08/how-the-final-stretch-of-bidens-vp-search-is-playing-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been an abnormal, increasingly contentious process, but the wait is finally almost over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: No Wrist Corsages, Please...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/08/opinion/sunday/biden-vice-president-geraldine-ferraro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Has America grown since 1984, or will the knives still be out for Biden’s running mate?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From levitation to super-strength: Exorcist on why 1973 classic is 'real'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/levitation-super-strength-christian-exorcist-22462051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Exorcist Reverend Bill Bean tells Daily Star Online about the chilling ways demonic possession presents itself and claims he has seen cases of levitation and superhuman strength</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dire outlook for movie theaters as covid resurges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/08/dire-outlook-for-cinemas-as-coronavirus-resurges-in-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American studios have had to make tough decisions about film releases due to resurgences of coronavirus cases in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebs' gratuitous apologies make Black Lives Matter all about them...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/08/celebrities-gratuitous-apologies-make-blm-all-about-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arson, looting and rioting have died down, but we’re still a long way from cultural normalcy in the US of A. (That A is for antagonism). One strange new feature of the culture is the abject, I-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Pesticides, Pathogens Ruled Out as Cause for Mass Elephant Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/botswana-rules-out-pesticides-and-pathogens-as-cause-for-elephant-deaths/ar-BB17Hg7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complaints Allege People Tricked Into Signing Kanye Nomination Paperwork...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/politics/2020/08/07/group-accuses-lawyer-working-trump-and-west-campaigns-simultaneously/3318242001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney for Trump's re-election campaign submitted West's papers, and some wonder if the two are working together to siphon Biden votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Broker Turns to New Zealand as New York Luxury Market Wilts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/star-broker-turns-to-new-zealand-as-new-york-luxury-market-wilts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Broker Turns to New Zealand as New York Luxury Market Wilts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bourbon Street to Food Banks, Signs of Slow Recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/from-bourbon-street-to-food-banks-signs-of-a-slow-u-s-recovery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Bourbon Street to Food Banks, Signs of a Slow U.S. Recovery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: QUASH QANON...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/qanon-is-running-amok-and-the-time-has-come-for-interventions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QAnon Is Running Amok, and the Time Has Come for Interventions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela jails two U.S. ex-soldiers for 20 years after failed incursion...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200808122442-5a38w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/:Venezuela court jails two U.S. ex-soldiers for 20 years after failed incursion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics say watching Shia LaBeouf new film like having face dragged across asphalt...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/the-tax-collector-film-reviews-shia-labeouf-a9660906.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short on Money, Cities Around World Try Making Own...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-07/a-depression-era-idea-gets-a-new-look-local-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible 'external interference' in blast; Israel swift to deny...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807150756-2a2hg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON-SECURITY/BLAST (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Lebanon sees possible 'external interference' in port blast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saint-Tropez resort makes masks mandatory outdoors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d94752dd1bc0be5fddf17baf3aeac860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAINT-TROPEZ, France (AP) — The glamorous French Riviera resort of Saint-Tropez is requiring face masks outdoors starting Saturday, threatening to sober the mood in a place renowned for high-end,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is France helping Lebanon, or trying to reconquer it?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8eab366aa599b101eb2aad10f9e6528d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — It was almost as if Emmanuel Macron forgot that Lebanon is no longer a French protectorate. Visiting explosion-ravaged Beirut this week, France’s leader comforted distraught...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
