<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>5G signal could jam satellites that help with weather forecasting...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/04/5g-mobile-networks-threat-to-world-weather-forecasting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New mobile system to be launched this year ‘will put lives at risk’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short shrift for Napoleon complex as it turns out he was quite nice...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/05/04/short-shrift-napoleon-complex-turns-quite-nice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychoanalyst Alfred Adler was inspired by Napoleon Bonaparte when he diagnosed a syndrome in the last century in which men overcompensate for their short stature through aggressive behaviour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Warns Dems: Stay in Center; Trump May Contest Election Results...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pelosi-warns-democrats-stay-in-the-center-or-trump-may-contest-election-results/ar-AAATyaD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Gaza targets in response to heavy rocket fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/89aa1c66a136495d906a7ad123503547</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Palestinian militants in the Gaza Strip fired scores of rockets into southern Israel on Saturday, wounding at least two Israeli civilians and triggering retaliatory...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump attacks social media companies after FACEBOOK bans...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4d9c8e4e4211410c87807f6cf0f5f57a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STERLING, Virginia (AP) — President Donald Trump criticized social media companies after Facebook banned a number of extremist figures, declaring that he was "monitoring and watching,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final minutes of miracle plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/05/04/florida-plane-crash-survivor-landing-guantanamo-bay-cuba/1100290001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plane that greeted 143 passengers and crew at Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, was four hours late and lackedÂ air-conditioning. It got terrifyingly worse at the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army investigating soldier's alleged ties to neo-Nazi group...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/442126-army-investigating-soldier-for-alleged-leadership-role-in-neo-nazi-group</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army is investigating after a soldier has been accused of holding a leadership position in a neo-Nazi group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says Kim Won't Break Promise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-04/south-korea-says-n-korea-fired-short-range-missile-joongang</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/03/trump-hails-unbelievable-economy-amid-historic-jobs-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business is booming in the US, as a record number of Americans are getting back to work. The nation’s economy got another rave review on Friday as the latest April jobs report showed businesses add…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Faces Anti-Gay Hecklers in Dallas...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5583265/pete-butigieg-anti-gay-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate Beto O’Rourke defended Buttigieg on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo da Vinci never finished Mona Lisa because 'injured arm fainting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/05/04/leonardo-da-vinci-never-finished-mona-lisa-injured-arm-fainting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leonardo da Vinci left the Mona Lisa unfinished because he gravely injured his arm while fainting, a new study argues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Warns Dems: Stay in Center; Trump May Contest Election Results...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/04/us/politics/nancy-pelosi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speaker’s “coldblooded” plan for defeating President Trump, who she worries would challenge a slim Democratic victory in 2020, focuses on moderate voters and avoiding a protracted impeachment bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA robots 'blurring line' between life and machine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/776563/dash-dan-robot-machine-life-cornell-university-science-robotics-engineering-ethics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' Projected to Eclipse 'AVATAR' as Highest-Grossing Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-03/-endgame-projected-to-eclipse-avatar-as-highest-grossing-film</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilians film barrage...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/HenMazzig/status/1124670998144536576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“WATCH THIS VIDEO. Sound on.  That’s what it’s like for Israeli civilians in the south, millions of people, that are under barrage of rockets from #Gaza by #Hamas and #IslamicJihad for the last 7 hours nonstop #IsraelUnderFire https://t.co/rzyLvkuDD4”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gray whales starving to death in Pacific -- scientists want to know why...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/gray-whales-starving-to-death-in-the-pacific-and-scientists-want-to-know-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty-one dead gray whales have been spotted along the West Coast since January, the most for this time of year since 2000, when 86 whales died. So far, scientists say, most of the 21 dead whales that turned up on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems give Barr final warning before contempt proceedings...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/house-democrats-give-ag-barr-final-warning-before-contempt-proceedings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Chairman Jerry Nadler has threatened AG William Barr with contempt of Congress if he does not hand over the full Mueller report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Department of Defense studying military options for Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article230001069.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coaster dares you to take 245-foot straight dive into abyss...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/yukon-striker-roller-coaster-opens-canada/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Yukon Striker, the world's tallest dive coaster, opens in Canada's Wonderland amusement park. The highlight: A 245-foot straight drop into the gaping maw of an underwater tunnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Top Internet User Taps 'Fake News' Busters for Elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-04/world-s-top-internet-user-taps-fake-news-busters-for-elections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Thomas moment may be now, some experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fbb07af9d5254aecbbab9422faf405ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Clarence Thomas has been a Supreme Court justice for nearly three decades. It may finally be his moment. Many Americans know Thomas largely from his bruising 1991...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's increasing influence in Cuba stirs ghost of Cold War...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russias-increasing-influence-cuba-stirs-ghost-cold-war-063958227.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is stirring the ghosts of Cuba's Cold War past as it looks to re-establish its influence in the Communist-run island nation, although this time analysts say Moscow has no intention of bankrolling Havana. Whereas once the Soviet Union and Cuba were linked by an ideological bond, now pragmatism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer asteroid flattens New York in simulation exercise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/killer-asteroid-flattens-york-simulation-exercise-020055474.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After devastating the French Riviera in 2013, destroying Dhaka in 2015 and saving Tokyo in 2017, an international asteroid impact simulation ended Friday with its latest disaster -- New York in ruins. The exercise has become a regular event among the international community of "planetary defense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA: I'M PUNISHED FOR TURNING 60...</title>
      <link>https://home.bt.com/news/showbiz-news/madonna-on-ageism-in-the-music-industry-im-punished-for-turning-60-11364359726202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;home.bt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pop star also said there are no living role models for her, because she is so unique.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza-Israel hostilities flare with rocket attacks, air strikes...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190504103335-wr8m9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Gaza-Israel hostilities flare with rocket attacks, air strikes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING 737 slides into Florida river with 136 on board, no fatalities...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190504025946-r4z0w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AIRPLANE/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Boeing 737 slides into Florida river with 136 on board, no fatalities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires new missile as tensions flare with West...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9001709/north-korea-fires-a-new-missile-as-tensions-flare-with-the-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korea has fired a new short-range missile today as simmering tensions with the West have once again started heating up. The weapon was fired in the direction of the East Sea at around 9am loc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  Biden leads Dem primary field by 30 points...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442037-poll-biden-leads-dem-primary-field-by-30-points</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden holds a 30-point lead over Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Durant best in world? No longer in LeBron shadow...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Kevin-Durant-was-derided-for-taking-easy-path-13817756.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as a shy teenager, Kevin Durant expressed himself about one thing: his disdain for the nickname Durantula. He was a 19-year-old rookie phenom with the Seattle SuperSonics when people started to use the pun for fun, and he wasn't having it.  "Call me KD," he said then and still repeats now. "Just KD is fine."  Twelve years ago, Durant didn't seem to have many opinions. His life revolved around the gym and video games, and on most other matters, he went with the flow. But he was adamant about how you referred to him. He refused to let Durantula crawl into the NBA vernacular. He didn't want to let the obsession with his impossibly long arms and legs turn him into a thing. He wanted to be a person, an extraordinary one but still a person.  He lives by the introduction line on his Twitter handle, which he wrote 10 years ago: "IM ME, I DO ME, AND I CHILL."  Just KD is fine. Nothing else. So far in this postseason, Durant is playing some of the best basketball in his life, which is quite a statement considering his Hall of Fame resume: 10-time all-star, four-time scoring champion, two-time Finals MVP, one-time regular season MVP.  This is the platform Durant always wanted, even though he won't admit it. He's not in the shadow of LeBron James, who is home for the playoffs. More people love Steph Curry because he's a rather regular-sized dude and can make shots from the equator, but in these playoffs, Durant is the undisputed driving force on the Golden State Warriors. He's not riding their championship coattails, and in fact, that has always been true in his three seasons in the Bay Area. But during this run, he is carrying them more than usual, and finally you should be seeing him as a necessity and not the greatest luxury in NBA history. Unless you're some stubborn knucklehead clinging to outdated perceptions, Durant...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCARTHY: Irked by bad press, Mueller signed leaked letter...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/05/the-big-lie-that-barr-lied/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney general’s testimony was clearly accurate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China putting Muslims in 'concentration camps,' U.S. says...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-china-concentrationcamps/china-putting-minority-muslims-in-concentration-camps-u-s-says-idUKKCN1S925F?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States accused China on Friday of putting well more than a million mi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver to decriminalize 'magic' mushrooms?</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/US/2019/05/03/Denver-voters-might-decriminalize-magic-mushrooms/2891556821811/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An initiative to decriminalize "magic mushrooms" will appear on municipal ballots in Denver on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anyone Ever Seen Cocaine?' Archives of Sanders Long-Lost TV Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/05/03/bernie-sanders-burlington-tv-show-video-2020-226761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a forgotten trove of videotapes reveals about the man who rewrote America’s political script.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beekeepers hit hard by sophisticated hive heists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2019/05/bee-thieves-cost-beekeepers-thousands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In sophisticated night heists, thieves are stealing thousands of bees. Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Dispatches Goats to Prevent Wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-03/california-dispatches-goats-to-eat-brush-prevent-wildfires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
