<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Russia says gave only few mins warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-says-us-gave-only-a-few-minutes-e2-80-99-warning-before-strike-in-syria/ar-BB1e2YGL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The notice came too late to “deconflict” the situation, Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of covid bankruptcies has begun...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/the-wave-of-covid-bankruptcies-has-begun/ar-BB1e2NdQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts warn that because bankruptcies lag other signals of economic distress, a mountain of filings may be to come. New data show what industries might be most at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late for jab: 88-year-old caught going 119 mph...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210226-late-for-my-jab-88-year-old-caught-going-191-km-h-in-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late for my jab: 88-year-old caught going 191 km/h in France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With new podcast, sex work comes out of shadows...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210226133553-243ib/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The podcast, 'A Sex Worker's Guide to the Galaxy', offers guests in the industry a stage to share their experiences free of sanction and in their own words</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopper whips off THONG and wears as mask after supermarket refuses to serve her...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2411562/shopper-thong-wears-as-covid-facemask-supermarket/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a shopper whipped off her thong in the middle of a supermarket and donned it as a face covering after being refused service. The viral clip shows the female customer rem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID cases, deaths starting to RISE again...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/969094/covid19-cases-deaths-are-starting-rise-again-how-worried-should</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two weeks, COVID-19 cases and deaths have dropped steadily from the alarmingly high peak of America's third wave of the pandemic. Vaccination rates are rising, new vaccines and millions more doses of approved ones are coming online soon, and deaths have dropped dramatically in places where significant numbers of people have been inoculated, especially nursing homes. But 'this is not a time to relax,' President Biden said Thursday as he celebrated the country's 50 million's vaccination. 'We must keep washing our hands, stay socially distanced, and for God's sake — for God's sake — wear a mask.' It turns out, a fourth wave of the pandemic already appears to be building. But the news is not all so encouraging. Most worrisome, the number of new cases has stopped declining over the past week. It's true in the U.S.: pic.twitter.com/CmOUFzLgDb — David Leonhardt (@DLeonhardt) February 25, 2021 Cases have leveled out worldwide, too. 'The most likely explanation is the more contagious variants of the virus, like the B.1.1.7 variant, which was first detected in Britain,' David Leonhardt writes at The New York Times. Business Insider's Jim Edwards points out that the uptick in cases and deaths could be statistical noise, but notes that worrisome new variants have also popped up in California and New York.  Big question: Are the new fast-moving variants (UK, CA, and NY) moving faster than the vaccines? — Jim Edwards (@Jim_Edwards) February 26, 2021 'Taking into account the counterbalancing rises in both vaccinations and variants, along with the high likelihood that people will stop taking precautions, a fourth wave is highly likely this spring,' Apoorva Mandavilli reports at the Times, citing a majority of 21 experts interviewed on the pandemic. 'But they stressed that it is not an inevitable surge, if government officials and individuals maintain precautions for a few more weeks,' and 'COVID-19 deaths will most likely never rise quite as precipitously as in the past.' 'The good news,' Mandavilli writes, is that 'despite the uncertainties, the experts predict that the last surge will subside in the United States sometime in the early summer. If the Biden administration can keep its promise to immunize every American adult by the end of the summer, the variants should be no match for the vaccines. ... For now, every one of us can help by continuing to be careful for just a few more months, until the curve permanently flattens.' Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Lane Teases 'BIRDCAGE' Sequel...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/nathan-lane-teases-birdcage-sequel-095038732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getty ImagesIf fans of The Birdcage ever actually get a sequel, we will have Nathan Lane’s newfound love of podcasts to thank.With a lot of extra time on his hands staying at home over the past year, Lane decided to check out a 2018 episode of the podcast Beyond the Box Set in which the two British hosts pitch sequels that “nobody asked for” for films they love. It was titled “The Birdcage: Starina Rides Again.”“So, I’ve got nothing to do, I listened to it,” he says in this preview of next week’s 100th episode of The Last Laugh podcast. The first idea they threw out there was “not good” in his opinion, but as he listened to their second pitch he started thinking to himself, “Gee, this is really good, I’d like to see this movie.”With both director Mike Nichols and his co-star Robin Williams gone, Lane had always thought that “you can’t really revisit” the classic comedy film, which was released 25 years ago next week. “But what this guy came up with, I thought, wow, it’s a way to honor Robin and go off on another adventure with my character and [Hank Azaria’s] Agador Spartacus going to Guatemala,” he explains. “It’s a really smart, clever, funny pitch.”“So, I said to my manager, listen to this,” Lane continues. “He takes it to MGM. MGM likes it. So they’re optioning it and they’re going to try to team with a streamer and see if it can actually happen! And this is all because of a podcast.”Then, all of a sudden, he realized, “Maybe someone should mention this to Hank Azaria.” Lane called up the actor to see what he thought and Azaria told him something along the lines of, “I can’t possibly play the part again. People would go crazy. I have one word for you: Apu.’”Before Azaria’s breakthrough film performance as Agador Spartacus, he had already made a name for himself voicing several characters on The Simpsons, including Kwik-E-Mart owner Apu.After comedian Hari Kondabolu released his documentary The Problem With Apu in 2017, which highlighted the racist implications of having a white actor play that stereotypically Indian character, Azaria ultimately decided to stop playing the role. He recently told The New York Times, “Once I realized that that was the way this character was thought of, I just didn’t want to participate in it anymore. It just didn’t feel right.”Why MAGA-Mocking Comedian Blaire Erskine Makes Liberals So MadFor the actor to then step back into the role of a Guatemalan “house boy” in a sequel to The Birdcage would inevitably open him up to another round of justified criticism. According to Lane, Azaria said, “I loved playing it, I would love to do it again, but it’s just not appropriate now. And you should get a Latin actor.”“So then, again, I thought, ‘Oh well, maybe that’s the end of that,’” Lane says. “And then I thought, ‘Gee, this idea is so good, if you could find a great Latin actor or comedian, it could maybe still work.’ It’s now 25 years later, we’re all older looking. Maybe Agador looks a little different.”When I suggest that the story could center on Albert and Agador’s son somehow, Lane gets excited. “‘The Birdcage 2: Son of Agador!’” he imagines. Then he deflates again, adding, “Anyway look, I don’t know if it’ll ever happen.”Of course, this conversation about who is “allowed” to portray which parts also extends to the debate surrounding straight actors playing gay roles. That public conversation was recently reignited amid the release of the new film Supernova, starring straight actors Stanley Tucci and Colin Firth as an aging couple, and HBO Max’s It’s a Sin, in which all of the lead gay roles are played by gay performers.Lane was notably the only gay actor in the main cast of The Birdcage, even though he did not come out publicly until he started promoting it—more on that in our full interview next week—but he says he does not believe gay roles “have to be played” by gay actors.“Do I think maybe something special might come from it? Perhaps,” he says. “You have to take into consideration the world we’re living in right now. And on some level you can’t really fight it. Sometimes there’s a point and sometimes it seems ridiculous.”As someone who has been able to play plenty of straight roles over the past quarter-century, he thinks there has to be some room for actors to take on characters that are unlike themselves.“I certainly get it. But to say it has to be this—I mean, to a certain degree, it’s like, well, does this mean Meryl Streep is out of business because she can’t do another accent ever again?” Lane adds. He imagines the accusatory mob shouting, “She’s not Polish!”“What about acting?” he asks. “This is a part of acting, to take on different personalities, a totally different character than you. So, I don’t know. Obviously, I think it’s a healthy discussion, but I think it can be taken to an extreme and I get nostalgic for just being able to act.”Subscribe to The Last Laugh podcast now to hear our full conversation with Nathan Lane about the 25th anniversary of ‘The Birdcage,’ including stories about Mike Nichols, Robin Williams, Gene Hackman, Oprah Winfrey and a lot more when it drops next Tuesday, March 2nd.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Golden Calf' Wheeled Into Gathering...</title>
      <link>https://www.towleroad.com/2021/02/golden-calf-trump-statue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.towleroad.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of Trump's keynote speech at the CPAC conference this weekend, two staffers wheeled in a massive golden statue of the insurrectionist former president, and everyone was thinking about the idol created by Israelities when Moses went up to Mt. Sinai.Wrote one Twitter user with more following suit: 'Republicans wheel in the golden calf as they prepare to wander the electoral desert for 40 years.'https://twitter.com/WesClarkjr/status/1365170881039798274?s=20https://twitter.com/CKourouklis/status/1365163554958020613?s=20https://twitter.com/AynRandPaulRyan/status/1365158774952972291?s=20https://twitter.com/JoyAnnReid/status/1365166137718226944?s=20https://twitter.com/mmpadellan/status/1365180643446059008?s=20https://twitter.com/TheRaDR/status/1365142286854742016?s=20https://twitter.com/CaptNostradamus/status/1365166357071937537?s=20https://twitter.com/Goss30Goss/status/1365148754890883072?s=20https://twitter.com/DavMicRot/status/1365168538718248961?s=20https://twitter.com/JLCauvin/status/1365267970419793921?s=20</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Hazards Grow as Americans Churn Out More Garbage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/local-hazards-grow-as-americans-churn-out-more-garbage/ar-BB1e2nyI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasing waste, full landfills and shuttered recycling programs mean more cities are paying to send their trash out-of-state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians Escape NKorea on Hand-Pushed Railcar...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/26/russians-escape-north-korea-on-a-hand-pushed-railcar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW — North Korea sealed its borders more than a year ago because of the pandemic, grounding flights and shutting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte Gainsbourg says Serge would struggle with today's censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210226-charlotte-gainsbourg-says-serge-would-struggle-with-today-s-censorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlotte Gainsbourg says Serge would struggle with today's censorship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris eyes three-week Covid-19 lockdown in bid to then 'reopen everything'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210226-paris-eyes-three-week-covid-19-lockdown-in-bid-to-then-reopen-everything</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Paris is considering proposing a three-week lockdown in a bid to “reopen everything” in the City of Lights afterwards, the deputy mayor said Thursday, calling the current nighttime curfew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant kills zookeeper with blow from trunk...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spain-elephants-371f33e9420a25ef72c60d783dd5070f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Authorities in Spain’s northern Cantabria region are investigating how an elephant killed a worker at a local zoo. The Cantabrian regional government says 44-year-old Joaquín...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy warships in Mideast hit by outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bahrain-dubai-united-arab-emirates-persian-gulf-tensions-coronavirus-pandemic-706500afe1fe80156ca40eb481b02176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Two U.S. Navy warships operating in the Mideast have been struck by coronavirus outbreaks, authorities said Friday, with both returning to port in Bahrain....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling sperm counts 'threaten human survival', expert warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/falling-sperm-counts-threaten-human-survival-expert-warns/ar-BB1e2cc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Falling sperm counts and changes to sexual development are “threatening human survival” and leading to a fertility crisis, a leading epidemiologist has warned. Writing in a new book, Shanna Swan, an environmental and reproductive epidemiologist at Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai in New York, warns that the impending fertility crisis poses a global threat comparable to that of the climate crisis. “The current state of reproductive affairs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob boss Peter Gotti dies in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/breaking-mob-boss-who-headed-23569073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Gotti was sentenced to prison in 2004 – he had bid for an early release last year, however it was denied. The 81-year-old had suffered from heart problems and dementia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan's district attorney acquires eight years of Trump's tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-s-tax-returns-have-been-turned-over-to-15979089.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - The Manhattan District Attorney's Office has taken possession of former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Al-Qaeda now as dangerous as under Bin Laden...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2404228/al-qaeda-dangerous-osama-bin-laden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AL-QAEDA are set to become as dangerous as they were during the 9/11 attacks twenty years ago, an expert has claimed.  The terror cult has gained a ruthless new leader dubbed “the Sword of Rev…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Union target...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/25/capitol-police-national-guard-help-early-471579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting chief Yogananda Pittman also says she pulled her precedessor's phone records to verify his recollection of the chaos of Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOYOTA building 'smart city' with self-driving cars, robots and AI homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/toyota-starts-building-smart-city-23568764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toyota has started constructing the smart city, dubbed "Woven City." It will be a full sustainable city with buildings made of wood to minimise carbon footprint and self driving cars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo finds his brand tarnished amid multiple crises...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Cuomo-once-touted-as-the-gold-standard-finds-15980734.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus pandemic ravaged the country last year, New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Litmus test at CPAC...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/conservative-gathering-just-one-litmus-235554631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP officials disagree intensely over the party's future. But no sign of debate will be visible when conservatives gather this weekend for CPAC's festival of Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden orders Syria airstrike after rocket attacks against US forces...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210225224858-6eitm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SYRIA/STRIKE (UPDATE 1, EXCLUSIVE):EXCLUSIVE-U.S. carries out airstrike against Iranian-backed militia target in Syria, officials say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil death toll tops 250,000, virus still running rampant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brazil-rio-de-janeiro-coronavirus-pandemic-jair-bolsonaro-coronavirus-vaccine-3b6231bb42559755a76e07db823c6e7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Brazil’s COVID-19 death toll, which surpassed 250,000 on Thursday, is the world’s second-highest for the same reason its second wave has yet to fade: Prevention was never...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shockingly real Tom Cruise deepfakes invade TIKTOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/shockingly-real-tom-cruise-deepfakes-are-invading-tiktok</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Be afraid. Be very afraid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDENTS GO MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Schools-work-overtime-to-find-students-gone-15980557.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT - Kenneth Chapman Sr. was hopeful as he navigated a hulking Detroit Public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel freezes vaccine gifts scheme amid legal uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/israel-s-gantz-demands-halt-to-illegal-vaccine-gifts-01614276306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel has halted its plan to distribute surplus coronavirus vaccines as authorities examine whether it was in Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's authority to order the move, the justice ministry said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAGA BOW-WOW:  Singer's dogs stolen in Hollywood shooting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lady-gagas-dog-walker-shot-170329434.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was hospitalized Wednesday after being shot while walking pop star Lady Gaga's French bulldogs in Hollywood. Two of the dogs were abducted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden orders Syria airstrike after rocket attacks against US forces...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210225235631-9xial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SYRIA/STRIKE (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-U.S. carries out airstrikes against Iranian-backed militia facilities in Syria- Pentagon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAND PAUL TAKES ON TRANS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7vgv7/a-gop-senator-just-compared-trans-health-care-to-genital-mutilation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kentucky Sen. Rand Paul used the Senate confirmation hearing for Dr. Rachel Levine to falsely compare gender-affirming treatment for kids to genital mutilation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald prepares to bask in 'conservative' movement he changed...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-prepares-to-bask-in-the-conservative-15980475.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. - The Conservative Political Action Conference has grappled with Republican...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male worker sues female boss who told him to 'man up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/male-worker-sues-female-boss-23566068 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge found Daniel Price has an 'arguable case' for sex bias after alleging 'extreme discrimination against males' at a laboratory where he was told to 'go away' during 'girls-only' conversations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids return [part time] to school...</title>
      <link>https://www.wenatcheeworld.com/news/coronavirus/back-at-school-pandemic-continues-but-life-goes-on-at-wenatchee-and-eastmont-highs/article_b9d7ae06-762e-11eb-abef-bbb60008f62a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wenatcheeworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WENATCHEE — You can’t see them smiling beneath the masks, but students at Wenatchee and Eastmont high schools are glad to be back in school, even if it’s only part-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  NYTIMES says it needs culture change...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/newspapers-us-news-tom-cotton-workplace-culture-1dbd01abdffb9c05001ede64dcb68f5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The New York Times says it needs a culture change to become a better place to work, particularly for people of color. The newspaper told its employees in a report Wednesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Massive 'Pipeline' in Cosmic Web Connecting Universe...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkd4nn/scientists-discover-massive-pipeline-in-the-cosmic-web-connecting-the-universe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study reveals “by far the best evidence” for the elusive cosmic filaments that supercharge ancient galaxies with cold gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief of staff at center of controversy over White House budget pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-s-chief-of-staff-at-center-of-controversy-over-white-house-budget-pick/ar-BB1e1ezv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Chief of Staff Ron Klain has been second-guessed by some Biden allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jab May Create 'Terminator' Antibody Response In People Who Have Had Virus...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/02/25/vaccine-create-terminator-type-antibody-response-people-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS4 Medical Editor Dr. Dave Hnida shared his advice about the new questions being raised concerning whether or not people who've had COVID-19 need two doses of the vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked man carrying Bible shot while knocking on doors in FL...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/florida/2021/02/25/naked-man-carrying-bible-shot-outside-florida-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say a naked man who was knocking on doors at a South Florida apartment complex was shot by someone who then called 911 to turn himself in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OXFORD virus lab hacked by cyber gang...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210225190914-joyrc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-CYBER (URGENT):Oxford University COVID-19 laboratory hacked by cyber gang -Telegraph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/02/25/lady-gaga-dog-walker-french-bulldogs-stolen-video-surveillance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We've obtained video of the horrifying shooting of Lady Gaga's dog walker and abduction of her dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailed Putin critic Navalny moved, probably to prison camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/jailed-putin-critic-navalny-moved-probably-to-prison-camp-660250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept presses fight against Omarosa...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/19/biden-justice-department-omarosa-470143</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new brief takes an aggressive stance against outspoken Trump critic Omarosa Manigault Newman in a financial disclosure flap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everything Has Been Criminalized,' Says Justice Gorsuch...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/25/everything-has-been-criminalized-says-neil-gorsuch-as-he-pushes-for-stronger-fourth-amendment-protections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The justice weighs in during oral arguments in Lange v. California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Cuba's economy worsens, desperate rafters risk lives at sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/i-cant-buy-food-as-cubas-economy-worsens-desperate-rafters-risk-their-lives-at-sea/ar-BB1e0CqL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feb. 25—Marisol Monteagudo's son gave her a kiss goodbye as he headed out the door to spend a night out with friends in Cuba's Isla de la Juventud. What he didn't tell her: That instead of grabbing a drink or watching a movie, they were planning to board a flimsy raft en route to Mexico. That was three months ago. She hasn't heard from him since. "Only a mother can understand this pain," ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Potato Head goes gender neutral...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mr-potato-head-goes-gender-neutral-d3c178f2b9b0c424ed814657be41a9d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Mr. Potato Head is no longer a mister. Hasbro, the company that makes the potato-shaped plastic toy, is giving the spud a gender neutral new name: Potato Head. The change...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: No 'final decision' on participation in Olympics in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-olympics-2022-usa/white-house-has-not-made-final-decision-on-participation-in-olympics-in-china-idUSKBN2AP2JV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has not made a final decision on participation in the Winter Olympics in Beijing, a spokeswoman said on Thursday, as Republican lawmakers call for the United States to boycott the Games in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops will be giving doses in Philly, Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/02/25/troops-will-be-giving-vaccines-in-philadelphia-florida-in-coming-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of troops have been deployed across the country to vaccinate in cities hardest-hit by COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK 'Supreme Court' to receive new powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/facebook-supreme-court-thomas-hughes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oversight Board is expected to be able to review whether content still online breaks the tech giant’s community standards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police chief warns extremists 'want to blow up Capitol'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/capitol-law-enforcement-heads-detail-intelligence-failures-leading-jan-6-n1258829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acting chief said members of militia groups want to "kill as many members as possible" in an attack during Biden's upcoming address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65,640 Minutes! Painfully Long Wait Times On MA Vaccine Website...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/25/massachusetts-covid-vaccine-vaxfinder-ma-gov-website-appointments-waiting-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of new vaccine appointments became available Thursday as a new website waiting room was launched, but the waits were agonizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticket to ride: Passports divide world...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210225-ticket-to-ride-vaccine-passports-divide-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ticket to ride: Vaccine passports divide world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France, Germany brace for ANOTHER lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14156386/merkel-germany-lockdown-oxford-jab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE and Germany are now both braced for further Covid lockdowns after they shunned the Oxford vaccine. It comes as a German virologist today revealed the country was sitting on a whopping 1.2 mi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCartney Plans $100 Memoir Told Through Lyrics and Memorabilia...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/02/24/paul-mccartney-plans-memoir-told-through-two-volumes-of-lyrics-with-memorabilia-as-holiday-gift-box</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul McCartney been busy through the pandemic, that’s for sure. First he released the much praised “McCartney III” and it was his first real number 1 album in 31 years. Now he&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince approved killing of Khashoggi, U.S. intelligence report concludes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/new-public-report-blame-saudi-crown-prince-2018-killing-jamal-n1258800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The release will mark a new chapter in U.S.-Saudi relations and a clear break from Trump's policy of equivocating about the Saudi state's role in the brutal murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly NYC woman murdered with machete...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-78-found-slashed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police responding to reports of an unconscious person found a 78-year-old woman dead in her bedroom in Queens with a slash to her head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems hesitant to move on taxes increases amid pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/540427-democrats-hesitant-to-move-on-taxes-amid-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden declared during the campaign that he would repeal the Trump tax cuts on “day one,” but after more than a month in office, some key Democratic lawmakers say they are reluctant to raise taxes during an economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyday chemicals threatening future of human fertility...</title>
      <link>https://futurehuman.medium.com/humans-may-not-be-able-to-reproduce-naturally-much-longer-scientist-warns-bd3b9dbbf859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurehuman.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyday chemicals are threatening the future of human fertility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks fall as yields continue to climb; GAMESTOP surges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/game-stop-surges-eaef3fd5ff0a536a8ada4a4f7afce4d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks were mostly lower in the early going Thursday as the recent theme of the market — rising bond yields and falling prices of technology companies — continued to weigh on trading....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$500,000 Offered For Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/02/25/lada-gaga-bull-dogs-stolen-dog-walker-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga's dogs were targeted by thieves Wednesday night ... thieves who shot her dog walker and stole 2 of her French Bulldogs ... law enforcement sources tell TMZ, and we're told Gaga is offering $500,000 for the return of her dogs, "no questions asked."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene blasted for attacking colleague's trans child...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Marjorie-Taylor-Greene-blasted-for-attacking-15978706.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - After a contentious debate on the Equality Act, which would extend civil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA declining to hand over any more info...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39441/faa-releases-statement-on-airliners-encounter-with-unidentified-object-over-new-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Airlines Airbus A320 was buzzed by a mysterious "cylindrical object" at high speed as it traveled from Cincinnati to Phoenix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI 'aware'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/fbi-american-airlines-ufo-new-mexico-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is "aware of" an American Airlines pilot’s report of an apparent UFO seen soaring over Northeast New Mexico earlier this week – but stopped short of confirming whether an investigation is underway, Fox News learned Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANHATTAN DA GETS TRUMP TAXES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/25/politics/trump-taxes-mazars-vance/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cy Vance obtained the records Monday after the Supreme Court denied Trump's last-ditch attempts to keep them private</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZILLOW Price Estimates Now Cash Offers in Homebuying Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-02-25/zillow-s-price-estimates-are-now-cash-offers-in-homebuying-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Zillow Group Inc. has titillated homeowners, prospective buyers and the voyeuristic public by estimating the value of tens of millions of U.S. homes and publishing the results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene criticized for 'cruel' response to Democrat's trans flag...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/540457-marjorie-taylor-greene-criticized-for-cruel-response-to-democrats-trans-flag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) drew bipartisan condemnation for putting up a poster stating “There are TWO genders” in response to a trans pride flag installed outside the neighboring office of Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel adopts law allowing names of unvaccinated to be shared...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-adopts-law-allowing-names-153232886.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's parliament passed a law Wednesday allowing the government to share the identities of people not vaccinated against the coronavirus with other authorities, raising privacy concerns for those opting out of inoculation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rarely seen Van Gogh painting exhibited ahead of auction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/paris-amsterdam-france-140675d55c8f1f3d8e64145ee39b5831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A rare painting by Dutch impressionist master Vincent van Gogh of a street scene in the Parisian neighborhood of Montmartre will be publicly displayed for the first time before its...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
