<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE BANS NICK FUENTES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/youtube-bans-popular-conservative-commentator-nick-fuentes-for-hate-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comes after Conservative Inc. called for his de-platforming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juror 1261 in Roger Stone's case: Was justice undone?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/483210-juror-1261-in-roger-stones-case-was-justice-undone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is serious question as to whether the conviction itself should be reevaluated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like Something Out Of Book Of Exodus': Locust Armies Devouring Farms In  30 Seconds...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/like-something-out-of-the-book-of-exodus-locust-armies-are-devouring-entire-farms-in-kenya-in-as-little-as-30-seconds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Locust armies numbering in the billions are absolutely ravaging large portions of eastern Africa and vast stretches of the Middle East.  We are being told that these locust armies "are unprecedented in size and scope", which means that we have never seen anything like this before.  And as you will s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nimitz Navy crew 'ordered to stay quiet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/third-navy-crew-saw-2004-21491602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nimitz UFO encounter in November 2004 is one of the most famous sightings in history. Now, a previously-unknown witness has come forward to say he saw it "form" in front of his Navy craft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem rivals sharpen attacks as Bloomberg rises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/483185-democratic-rivals-sharpen-attacks-as-bloomberg-rises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House hopefuls are unloading on Mike Bloomberg in an effort to draw him into the fray</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers to sweep entire sky for signs of extraterrestrial life...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/feb/15/astronomers-to-sweep-entire-sky-for-signs-of-extraterrestrial-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project is collaboration between privately-funded firm and New Mexico observatory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>change his official residence from New York to homes he owns in Colorado or Florida</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/407672/bloomberg-hillary-clinton-running-mate-trump-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIKE Bloomberg is thinking about making Hillary Clinton his running mate as he runs for president, according to a new report. “Polling found the Bloomberg-Clinton combination would be a formi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump supporter's defense of Mike...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/482796-a-trump-supporters-defense-of-michael-bloomberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Trump and Bloomberg rip each other for campaign advantage, tens of millions of desperately poor Americans need help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources close to Bloomberg campaign tell DRUDGE REPORT that candidate is considering Hillary Clinton as running mate</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/15/bloomberg-reportedly-considering-hillary-clinton-as-his-running-mate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg’s internal polling has found the combo “would be a formidable force,” campaign sources told the Drudge Report Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka in Abu Dhabi ahead of women's conference...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff0b1ea536afd8056d72dee415f5dedd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABU DHABI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Ivanka Trump, daughter of U.S. President Donald Trump, arrived in the United Arab Emirates on Saturday, where she met with women entrepreneurs and was to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>change his official residence from New York to homes he owns in Colorado or Florida</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/drudge-report-bloomberg-considering-hillary-clinton-for-running-mate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg is considering Hillary Clinton as a running mate, according to the Drudge Report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEEP CRACKS EMERGE IN BIDEN FIREWALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/15/joe-biden-south-carolina-firewall-114862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One South Carolina lawmaker says she switched allegiances after warning several Biden staffers that their grassroots approach was outdated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showdowns at political conventions are rare. Dems may get one...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Showdowns-at-political-conventions-are-rare-15058979.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speculation about a brokered, deadlocked or contested political conventionsurfaceseveryfouryears with the regularity of Brigadoon rising from the mist. Back in 1980, self-styled Democratic brokers called themselves the "wait in the weeds gang," ready to identify a compromise candidate between President Jimmy Carter and Sen. Ted Kennedy. Such predictions show up in virtually every cycle when there's even a hint of the possibility - usually early on, when a platoon of still-viable candidates suggests that a divided primary contest will fail to produce a winner. Just as frequent are the skeptical dismissals (I wrote one myself a dozen years ago) that note, with metronomic regularity, that there aren't any more brokers: no more Jake Arveys, Ed Flynns, Mark Hannas or Harry Daughertys to trade delegates like so many poker chips.  But this could be the year it really does happen. The Democrats may arrive in Milwaukee in July with no candidate having locked down enough delegates to win the nomination on the first vote. Three factors are present, even dominant, in the Democratic fight that are often absent: a genuine ideological split; four candidates (and possibly more) with enough money to wage long campaigns; and the long-standing Democratic method of allocating delegates proportionally, which can drag out primaries even if the outcome is clear months before the convention - which it certainly isn't today.  Conventions were not always the slick infomercials they've become in recent years, and the shift to primaries instead of smoke-filled rooms after the chaotic 1968 Democratic convention didn't immediately end the prospect of floor fights. In 1972, George McGovern beat back an attempt to deny him a first-ballot victory by contesting his right to all the delegates from California's winner-take-all primary. (He'd won 43.5...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources close to Bloomberg campaign tell DRUDGE REPORT that candidate is considering Hillary Clinton as running mate</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8007521/Mike-Bloomberg-wants-Hillary-Clinton-running-mate-say-sources.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bloomberg is considering making Hillary Clinton his running mate, a source close to his campaign has told Drudge Report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A woman was killed and skinned. Now Mexico is up in arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-woman-was-killed-and-skinned-Now-Mexico-is-up-15057813.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - One morning this week, Mexico City police received a radio call about an "aggression against a woman." Arriving at the scene - an apartment in a lower-middle-class neighborhood - they discovered a horror: the body of a 25-year-old who had been stabbed to death, cut up and partially skinned.  The killing of Ingrid Escamilla last weekend has gripped the nation and ignited a fresh round of protests over Mexico's high levels of violence against women.  On Friday, demonstrators hurled paint at the entrance to the National Palace to protest Escamilla's death and other "femicides" - murders of women because of their gender. Additional protests were planned for Friday evening and Saturday.  Escamilla's case shocked Mexicans not only because her death was so gruesome but because it was so publicized. Photos of her mutilated body were leaked to two tabloids. One of them, Pasala, headlined a photo spread, "It was Cupid's fault."  Mexicans struck back on social media, insisting that Escamilla should be memorialized not by such ghastly photos but instead by beautiful images. Thousands of people posted or shared pictures of flowers, rainbows and animals, using hashtags such as #IngridEscamilla and #IngridFotos.  "You deserve to be remembered for who you were, not what they did to you," said Twitter user @itsamonbebe, who posted nature pictures.  Prominent figures including the writer Valeria Luiselli and Mexico's ambassador to Washington, Martha Bárcena, joined the campaign.  Escamilla's husband confessed to the crime, according to media reports. The city's public security department confirmed his arrest.  Mexicans have voiced increasing frustration with violence against women. The country recorded more than 1,000 deaths classified as femicides last year, part of a historic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Daytona 500 appearance could include lap in presidential limo...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/sports/trump-daytona-500-nascar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is the latest of several sitting presidents to attend races at Daytona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: Julia Louis-Dreyfus and Will Ferrell's 'DOWNHILL' Worse Than Stale Popcorn...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/02/downhill-review-will-ferrell-julia-louis-dreyfus-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It doesn’t have a clue about what kind of movie it wants to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi urges more policing as virus toll rises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chinas-xi-urges-more-policing-virus-toll-rises-115750208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping has called for tightened control over online discussion and increased policing to ensure "positive energy" and social stability, state media said Saturday, as the country struggles to contain the deadly new coronavirus. Censors had allowed some online criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia emerges as South progressive leader under Dems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/55cdfed8d8f1bf661bc94f860a522fd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — In a state once synonymous with the Old South, Democrats are using their newfound legislative control to refashion Virginia as the region's progressive leader on racial,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions complicate efforts to contain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/137ebbee2968d17097e685f3141ad632</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Reports one day suggest the respiratory outbreak in China might be slowing, the next brings word of thousands more cases. Even the experts have whiplash in trying to determine if...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr Installs Outside Prosecutor to Review Case Against Flynn...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/justice-department-opens-inquiry-fbi-interview-heart-flynn-s-guilty-n1136481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AG Barr has asked a U.S. attorney to lead the inquiry. Flynn pleaded guilty to making false statements during the interview, but wants to withdraw his plea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Will Deploy Elite Tactical Agents to 'Sanctuary' Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/border-patrol-will-deploy-elite-tactical-agents-to-sanctuary-cities/ar-BB100Ejr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VALENTINE'S DAY AT DOJ</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/justice-dept-wont-charge-andrew-mccabe-the-former-fbi-official-who-authorized-the-investigation-of-president-trump/ar-BB100rHv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Reports First Death Outside Asia...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-evacuate-citizens-quarantined-ship-043646253.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A Chinese tourist died in France, the first death outside Asia from the coronavirus, the health ministry said, as the global toll now exceeds 1,500.U.S. citizens and their families on a quarantined cruise ship off the Japan coast, the largest infection cluster outside China, will be evacuated</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
