<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Sedition Hunters' Turn Capitol Insurrection Into Ultimate Online Manhunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2021-capitol-riot-sedition-hunters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amateur sleuths have turned the Washington D.C. insurrection on Jan. 6 into the ultimate online manhunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul v Mayweather ends in boos...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jun/07/logan-paul-vs-floyd-mayweather-boxing-fight-result-earnings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight between one of the greatest boxers in history and one of the best YouTube personalities in his family ended in predictable fashion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-haulers report improvement after vaccination, surprising experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/many-long-haul-covid-19-patients-report-improvement-after-vaccination-surprising-experts/ar-AAKKWI4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Wendy French of northwest suburban Lake in the Hills used to run 10 miles a day several times a week before she caught COVID-19 in September, which left her fatigued and suffering from a variety of symptoms for months after the virus was supposedly gone. The previously healthy 45-year-old stopped running and even began dreading typical household chores such as doing laundry, because ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His lonely war in Room 533: How patient fought to keep his life from crumbling...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lonely-war-room-533-covid-120059820.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Perry, who by his own sheer grit built a middle-class life for his family in Compton, was waging battle on two fronts: Fighting against COVID-19, and trying desperately to hold on to everything he had worked for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is someone stalking you? Tiny trackers make it alarmingly easy...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2021/06/06/news/nation/tiny-trackers-make-it-alarmingly-easy-for-someone-to-stalk-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proliferation of tracking devices — particularly the type of popular gadgets being sold to help you find your belongings, such as your wallet, keys or luggage — have led to an increase in fears of stalking, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When missing people don't want to be found: 'I'd removed myself to push the world away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/jun/05/when-missing-people-dont-want-to-be-found-id-removed-myself-to-push-world-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happens if you decide to disappear – then find yourself plastered over the internet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX RATES FALL OFF</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccination-rates-fall-off-imperiling-biden-e2-80-99s-july-fourth-goal/ar-AAKLD5I?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ‘last mile’ of delivering coronavirus shots has become a marathon, with health officials showing up at stores, parks and factories to entice people who might not otherwise get immunized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nowadays, having fun needs to be taken seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/with-pandemic-problems-easing-having-real-fun-needs-to-be-taken-seriously/ar-AAKLfZd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoyment can be social or solitary, something new or old. “Fun is a counterweight to the burdens of life, such as work, school and parenting” in today’s world, one expert says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  APPLE's tightly controlled App Store is teeming with scams...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/apple-s-tightly-controlled-app-store-is-teeming-with-scams/ar-AAKL0TG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple claims its App Store is carefully curated so that only the best apps get through. The truth is, the App Store is littered with scams and "fleeceware," which uses fake user ratings to trick customers into paying for something they don't want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Businesses Raise Fears of Future Lockdowns as Cases Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-k-businesses-raise-fears-of-future-lockdowns-as-cases-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Businesses Raise Fears of Future Lockdowns as Cases Rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PANTS STEAL SHOW AT COMEBACK SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/06/06/donald-trump-pants-backwards-speech-fly-north-carolina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump traveled to North Carolina for a speech to Republicans, but the headline may be in his pants!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eilish tough time on charts...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/06/billie-eilishs-latest-single-lost-cause-is-an-actual-lost-cause-image-change-from-slacker-to-femme-fatale-may-be-cause</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish, the teen phenom with 7 Grammy Awards from 2020, and more still this past year, is having a tough time on the charts right now. On Thursday she dropped her latest single, called &amp;#822…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We all said a little prayer, but we're good'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-da90ee6c8e2f6eccd7228faad7a137db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOINT BASE ANDREWS, Md. (AP) — A technical issue that involved “no major safety concerns” forced Vice President Kamala Harris' plane to return to Joint Base Andrews in Maryland about 30 minutes after she had left Sunday on a trip to Guatemala and Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grievances cloud Republican agenda...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-election-2020-campaign-2016-senate-elections-government-and-politics-861ce4d1c92c8026c5312a9ea922cf22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Republicans are fighting to seize control of Congress. Just don't ask what they'd do if they win. Look no further for evidence of the GOP's muddled governing agenda than battleground North Carolina, where party leaders packed into a convention hall Saturday night to cheer former President Donald Trump .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador looks to become world's first country to adopt crypto as legal tender...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-el-salvador-health-coronavirus-pandemic-technology-b1c08cae170aede89ea5cb41d97048cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador (AP) — El Salvador President Nayib Bukele announced in a recorded message played at a Bitcoin conference in Miami that next week he will send proposed legislation to the country's congress that would make the cryptocurrency legal tender in the Central American nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris in Air Force 2 scare...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3029035/air-force-two-kamala-harris-mexico-guatamala-trip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AIR Force Two was forced to return due to a “technical issue” just 30 minutes after Kamala Harris took off on Sunday for her first international trip as vice president. Harris is travel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First international trip cut short after 30 minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/vice-president-plane-return-guatemala-mexico-ab98ff30-cf79-44ac-bed4-524396dfed5c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m good, I’m good. We all said a little prayer, but we’re good,” Harris told reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin's opposition clouds future of Dem bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-voting-rights-bills-elections-government-and-politics-3eb2968199c9ceccd537c01c4cfdfb0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A key Democratic senator says he will not vote for the largest overhaul of U.S. election law in at least a generation, leaving no plausible path forward for legislation that his party and the White House have portrayed as crucial for protecting access to the ballot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayoral candidate wants to cut $1 billion from police. Pays for private security on her block...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ny-oped-mayas-choices-20201219-xixzzew55rd67div7eugnjwadq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Maya Wiley, the civil rights attorney and former de Blasio counsel who’s running for mayor, put out her first big position paper earlier this month, a gun violence prevention plan, what stood out was what wasn’t there: any productive role for the NYPD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alzheimer's Drug Poses Dilemma for FDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/alzheimer-s-drug-poses-a-dilemma-for-the-fda/ar-AAKK2Va</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration is on the verge of announcing one of its most contentious decisions in years: the fate of an Alzheimer’s drug that could be the first treatment approved after nearly two decades of failed efforts to find ways to curb the debilitating disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600+ quakes shake California-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/05/us/earthquakes-california-mexico-border/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 600 small earthquakes have been recorded this weekend in a rural area near the Salton Sea in Southern California, with the largest having a magnitude of 5.3, a US Geological Survey geophysicist told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman reveals dark hobby of seducing infamous serial killers by mail...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/05/couple-seduced-serial-killers-ramirez-dahmer-gacy-by-mail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the shocking letters a couple traded with serial murderers including John Wayne Gacy, Jeffrey Dahmer and Richard “Night Stalker” Ramirez.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes asked to review men-only draft law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-supreme-court-courts-government-and-politics-847452b349a4a00c6a6ff67d5c58f3c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court is being asked to decide whether it's sex discrimination for the government to require only men to register for the draft when they turn 18. The question of whether it's unconstitutional to require men but not women to register could be viewed as one with little practical impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top scientist being hunted by far-right sniper who has gone AWOL from army...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-top-covid-19-scientist-is-being-hunted-by-a-far-right-sniper-who-has-gone-awol-from-the-army/ar-AAKKUDJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientist Marc Van Ranst is in hiding with his family in a safe house with 24-hour security after a far-right sniper staked out his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WORST ELECTION DECEPTION'</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/netanyahu-right-wing-mouths-wont-be-silenced-670245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some hospitals mark first time being Covid-free...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/06/us/us-covid-hospitals-milestones-concerns/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Raul Magadia and his team all gathered in the basement of their Anniston, Alabama, hospital last month for a big announcement he was preparing to make through the intercom system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador looks to become world's first country to adopt crypto as legal tender...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/05/el-salvador-becomes-the-first-country-to-adopt-bitcoin-as-legal-tender-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Salvador President Nayib Bukele plans to introduce legislation that will make it the world's first sovereign nation to adopt bitcoin as legal tender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ says it'll no longer seize reporters' records...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-business-government-and-politics-67ac2f4f96b2dfd7f47446662e59ec6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department said Saturday that it no longer will secretly obtain reporters' records during leak investigations , a policy shift that abandons a practice decried by news organizations and press freedom groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Maintains Ban On Pride Flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/05/1003642736/pentagon-maintains-ban-on-pride-flag-and-other-flags-at-installations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DOD restricted what flags could and couldn't be flown on military installations last July. The Pentagon considered making a special case for Pride Month, but decided against the exception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli security chief warns of Jan. 6-type ahead of Bibi departure...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israeli-security-warns-january-6-violence-8142e896-7d01-4b72-81de-c68b07722bdc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Shin Bet director raised concerns about “serious radicalization in incitement and discourse on social media.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL JAZEERA: Reporter forcefully detained...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-d5902739395b065a2023b6214664d0e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli police arrested a Palestinian protest leader in the contested Sheikh Jarrah neighborhood of Jerusalem on Sunday, a day after forcefully detaining a prominent Al Jazeera journalist covering the campaign by Jewish settlers to evict dozens of Palestinian families from the area.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
