<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mariupol on the brink as surrender deadline passes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/live-blog/russia-ukraine-war-live-updates-mariupol-brink-surrender-deadline-pass-rcna24716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia offered to spare the lives of Ukrainian soldiers fighting in Mariupol if they laid down their arms Sunday, as the weeks-long resistance in the besieged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt agency accidentally kills 3,000 animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/article/us-government-agency-accidentally-killed-almost-3000-animals-in-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indiscriminate traps, used to reduce crop and safety threats, also snare federally protected species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA stuck going 83 mph on highway, driver alleges...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Tesla-stuck-going-83-mph-17084202.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The turn signals, hazard lights and accelerator all reportedly went haywire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male model testing gender norms in changing Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220417-the-male-model-testing-gender-norms-in-a-changing-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his hot pink hair extensions and leopard print pantsuit, model Ziad al-Mesfer was bound to turn heads during his recent public photo shoot in deeply conservative Saudi Arabia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea tests new tactical guided weapon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-south-korea-north-d528bd391034f565d9d80a4a09cd8fed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea has test-fired a new type of tactical guided weapon designed to boost its nuclear fighting capability, state media reported Sunday, a day before its chief rivals the United States and South Korea begin annual military drills that the North views as an invasion rehearsal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky urges Ukrainians to buy anti-radiation pills...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/zelensky-warns-russian-nuclear-attack-26730111</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volodymyr Zelensky has urged his country to be ready for the worst case scenario, warning that Russia's potential use of nuclear weapons in future cannot be ruled out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  12 injured, 3 detained in SC mall shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article260484432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the latest details on the Columbiana Centre mall shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portable nuke device missing from stolen vehicle in PA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/portable-nuclear-device-missing-stolen-vehicle-pennsylvania-rcna24686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“As long as the device is not tampered with or damaged, it presents no hazard to public safety,” David Allard, director of the Bureau of Radiation Protection, said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another wild protest breaks out during NBA game...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/16/protestor-chains-herself-to-basket-during-timberwolves-grizzlies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Timberwolves aren’t done with protesters delaying their games. An animal rights activist chained herself to the basket stanchion Saturday during Game 1 of the Timberolves-Grizzlies playoff seri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art Rupe, pioneering record executive, dead at 104...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/16/art-rupe-pioneering-record-executive-dead-at-104/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Music executive Art Rupe, whose Specialty Records was a premier label during the formative years of rock ’n roll and helped launch the careers of Little Richard, Sam Cooke and many …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crew of sunken warship 'shown for first time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-61129151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's defence ministry releases a video purportedly showing the crew of the Moskva in Sevastopol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Romance With Robots Already Here...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uncanny-future-romance-robots-already-013111368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyIn the late 2000s, a lifestyle reporter in Moscow named Eugenia Kuyda, then in her early twenties, decided to produce a cover story on Roman Mazurenko, the person at the center of Moscow’s creative hipster scene at the time. Right from the start, Eugenia and Roman both felt they had a profound connection, and soon became close friends.A few years later, Kuyda moved to San Francisco to start a chatbot-based virtual assistant company. Shortly after, Mazur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opponents of far-right protest as campaign enters final week...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-04-16/opponents-of-french-far-right-plan-protests-as-election-campaign-enters-final-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avian flu has spread to 27 states, sharply driving up egg prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/avian-flu-has-spread-to-27-states-sharply-driving-up-egg-prices/ar-AAWgZBQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly gun violence surges with at least 24 people shot in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/shooting-philadelphia-kensington-mantua-strawberry-mansion-20220415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shootings happened in neighborhoods across the city and at all hours of the day, police said, with bullets striking people who ranged in age from 18 to 65.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Reports Her First Fundraising Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/marjorie-taylor-greene-reports-her-first-fundraising-loss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) has been one of the biggest fundraisers for Republicans in the House. But to kick off 2022, she actually spent more than she took in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron should prepare for brutal shock after latest polls?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/comment/expresscomment/1596916/Macron-latest-frech-election-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ON EASTER Sunday, French President Emmanuel Macron should pray next week is uneventful. If it is, he will be reelected. Marine Le Pen should pray for someone or something to disrupt the political week. If that happens, she probably wins the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic mushrooms' for therapy? Vets help sway...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-matthew-butler-utah-salt-lake-city-lifestyle-3384fd864634204deba9fa8c21d4dcf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Matthew Butler spent 27 years in the Army, but it took a day in jail to convince him his post-traumatic stress disorder was out of control. The recently retired Green Beret had already tried antidepressants, therapy and a support dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA deeply concerned...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/us-deeply-concerned-by-jerusalem-violence-urges-care-for-temple-mount-status-quo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Department says it will continue contact with Israeli, Palestinian officials to deescalate tensions after 185 injured in police crackdown on Muslim rioting at Al-Aqsa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Kindness Strengthens Brain Health...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/04/15/kindness-cognitive-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doing an act of kindness can make you feel good about yourself, and a new study suggests it also benefits the brains of everyone living under one roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF THE 'PINK MOON'</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/space-news/full-pink-moon-rises-saturday-night/1172232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pink Moon will be the main astronomical event in the evening skies this weekend, but some lucky stargazers could be treated to an added celestial bonus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol mulls rolling out hi-tech 'smart walls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10719113/Border-Patrol-talks-roll-hi-tech-smart-walls-detect-intruders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology company DarkPulse claims it has pitched its sophisticated fiber-optic 'smart wall' cables to Department of Homeland Security officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fever Starts to Break in Boise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/housing-market-in-boise-idaho-starts-to-crack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Housing Market Fever Starts to Break in Boise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of conservative CCW event showing racist comments sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/3270390-video-of-las-vegas-conservative-ccw-event-showing-racist-comments-sparks-outrage-responses-from-attending-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (KLAS) — Racist comments made at a conservative political event are sparking outrage. The event, titled the “Vegas CCW” class, was held on Saturday, April 10, at a Las Vegas-Clark Library…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel's 'Great Comeback' Has Price: Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/travels-great-comeback-has-a-price-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arriving at London’s Gatwick Airport for his easyJet flight to Malaga, Spain, with his wife and 12-year-old daughter on April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky-High Pandemic Housing Market Finds Gravity Does Exist...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/the-sky-high-pandemic-housing-market-finds-gravity-does-exist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luis Solis, a real estate agent in Portland, Ore., marked a milestone weekend late last month. It was the first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Gamble Pivots to Very Different Battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/putins-ukraine-gamble-pivots-to-a-very-different-battlefield/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine — There are fields instead of city streets, farmsteads instead of apartment buildings. Open highways stretch to the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 under evacuation orders as New Mexico wildfire rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wildfires-new-mexico-colorado-fires-evacuations-2a4b21f7d5632b010a2b84b4f63bbfc5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Douglas Siddens’ mother was among those who made it out with just the clothes on her back when a deadly, wind-fueled wildfire ripped through a mountain community in southern New Mexico. The RV park where she lived was reduced to “metal frame rails and steel wheels,” said Siddens, who managed the site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden prepares for more clashes as far-right demos continue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sweden-europe-riots-b9c19932f7828bb8887ef69d10d568b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Police in Sweden say they are preparing for new violent clashes following riots that erupted between demonstrators and counter-protesters in the central city of Orebro on Friday ahead of an anti-Islam far-right group’s plan to burn a Quran there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War far from over as Kyiv strikes renewed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-kharkiv-moscow-0a9b737d09fec032affe3d9e5e82893a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces resumed scattered attacks on Kyiv, western Ukraine and beyond Saturday in an explosive reminder to Ukrainians and their Western supporters that the whole country remains under threat despite Russia’s pivot toward mounting a new offensive in the east.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai's covid siege: Food shortages, talking robots, starving animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/shanghai-e2-80-99s-covid-siege-food-shortages-talking-robots-starving-animals/ar-AAWgba7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities seek info after dolphin found impaled on Florida beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/health/authorities-seek-info-after-dolphin-found-impaled-on-florida-beach/article_d17a6427-28cc-5b1d-a3bd-b5cd71016228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are asking for the public’s health to find who was responsible after the body of a dolphin was found on a Florida beach that had been impaled with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER adopts 'poison pill' to thwart Elon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/15/twitter-board-adopts-poison-pill-after-musks-43-billion-offer-to-buy-company.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The board voted unanimously to adopt the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinking of Russian warship offers Ukraine boost...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/3270399-sinking-of-russian-warship-offers-ukraine-a-morale-and-maybe-strategic-boost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sinking of Russia’s Moskva cruiser has dealt a major blow to the Kremlin’s fleet in the Black Sea and offered up a big public relations win to Ukrainian forces.  The warship — which sank Thursd…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
