<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Gene Found In People From Greenland Makes Ice Cream As Healthy As Broccoli!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/genetic-variant-sugar-healthy-greenland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say up to three percent of Greenlanders are able to process sugar differently, making ice cream as healthy as broccoli!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new rules of Monopoly...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/27/monopoly-antitrust-new-rules-tech-525161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington has spent decades playing from the same rulebook in the game of keeping dominant businesses from snuffing out the competition. But a new breed of antitrust enforcers say those rules are rigged against consumers — and in favor of Big Tech. They say it’s time to change the game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE:  THOUSANDS More flights canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/27/business/flights-canceled-omicron-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 2,000 flights have been canceled Monday as Covid cases surge across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostradamus predictions for '22: Cannibals, robots, cryptocurrency...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/27/nostradamus-predictions-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the year comes to a close, the news is getting grimmer, folks — at least according to long-dead, divining daddy Nostradamus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Justice Roberts Tops Federal Leaders in Approval...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/358373/justice-roberts-tops-federal-leaders-americans-approval.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of 11 prominent federal government officials, Chief Justice John Roberts is the best rated by Americans and the only one with the approval of all party groups.lyd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global gloom over New Year's celebrations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-soccer-sports-lifestyle-health-beab3be1a11d1ef021e66fa3c6061c47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — After struggling with the coronavirus for far too long, the world understands all too well Belgium's word of the year, “knaldrang!” — the urge to party, the need to let loose. Yet as New Year celebrations approach, the omicron variant is casting more gloom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol panel to investigate Trump call to WILLARD hotel in hours before attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/27/capitol-attack-panel-investigate-trump-call-willard-hotel-before-assault</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Committee to request contents of the call seeking to stop Biden’s certification and may subpoena Rudy Giuliani</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury to resume deliberations in Ghislaine sex abuse case...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/jury-resume-deliberations-ghislaine-maxwell-sex-abuse-case-2021-12-27/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury in British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell's sex abuse trial is secheduled to resume deliberations on Monday, after breaking for a long weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man banned from leaving Israel for 8,000 years over child support payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-689839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's Big Year and the Many Roadblocks Ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2021-12-27/elon-musk-in-2022-faces-many-roadblocks-at-tesla-spacex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Outlets hurt by dwindling public interest in news...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-presidential-elections-arts-and-entertainment-7cc91db0950a8e7e7bcf50d5d23dfc26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. To a large degree, 2021 represented the inevitable hangover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese citizens slam Musk after space station near-misses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-citizens-slam-musk-online-after-space-station-near-misses-2021-12-27/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese citizens lashed out online against billionaire Tesla founder Elon Musk's space ambitions on Monday after China complained that its space station was forced to take evasive action to avoid collision with satellites launched by Musk's Starlink programme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX film has 'wildest' sex scene of year with gruesome incest twist...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/netflix-film-two-wildest-sex-25792224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Netflix release is enough to make anyone's stomach turn but it also features a painful-sounding sex scene which gets even more gruesome following a family revelation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Exodus Sees Record Spend on Homes Outside City...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/london-exodus-sees-record-spend-on-homes-outside-city-ft-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London Exodus Sees Record Spend on Homes Outside City, FT Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican optimism grows over red wave in '22...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/587193-gop-optimism-grows-over-possible-red-wave-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With less than a year to go until the 2022 midterms, Republicans are increasingly bullish on the prospect of a red wave that could flip both chambers of Congress and end Democrats’ unified control in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your DNA Test Could Send Relative to Jail...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/27/your-dna-test-could-send-a-relative-to-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On any given day, CeCe Moore’s inbox is flooded with strangers asking her to solve the mysteries of life and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Disgust Explains Everything...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/27/how-disgust-explains-everything/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. Two distinguished</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Other Arab States Falter, Saudi Arabia Seeks to Become Cultural Hub...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/27/as-other-arab-states-falter-saudi-arabia-seeks-to-become-a-cultural-hub/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEDDAH, Saudi Arabia — A pregnant Saudi woman, far from home, finds herself stalked by inner and outer demons. A</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's president to visit Iran 'very soon'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/finance/news/venezuelas-president-visit-iran-very-021752928.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro said on Sunday he will soon visit Iran to finalize new agreements on cooperation with the Middle Eastern country, which has become Venezuela's top ally in boosting oil output amid U.S. sanctions. Venezuela and Iran have strengthened their ties since last year. Maduro's government has received vital equipment for its oil industry from Iran, which in return has received crude and other primary resources from the South American country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAMPION OF HUMAN RIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenationalnews.com/opinion/obituaries/2021/12/26/desmond-tutu-south-africas-unwavering-champion-of-human-rights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archbishop preached love and forgiveness throughout his lifelong struggle against discrimination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan gets her court-mandated public apology from British newspaper...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/snyde/ny-meghan-markle-mail-apology-20211226-icsoe326pfhurisqt5nkt7vphi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her lawsuit win, Meghan Markle got a front-page apology from the British newspaper that published parts of a personal letter she wrote to her father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men across America are getting vasectomies 'as an act of love'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/men-across-america-are-getting-vasectomies-e2-80-98as-an-act-of-love-e2-80-99/ar-AAS9VJe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE:  Pandemic and weather complicate travel again...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pandemic-and-weather-complicate-travel-again-as-16730811.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic continued to scramble Americans' plans on the day after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Economy Now Set to Surpass $100 Trillion...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-economy-now-set-surpass-000500732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The world economy is set to surpass $100 trillion for the first time in 2022, two years earlier than previously forecast, according to the Centre for Economics and Business Research. Most Read from BloombergCoronavirus Can Persist for Months After Traversing BodyCases Surge Globally; Fauci Warns of Complacency: Virus UpdateWorld Economy Now Set to Surpass $100 Trillion in 2022China Reports Most Daily Local Infection Cases Since JanuaryAlex Jones' Wife Arrested on Domestic Violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's strict 'zero Covid' rules fail to stop spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4343809/chinas-strict-zero-covid-policy-lockdowns-failing-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA’S strict “zero Covid” policy with harsh lockdowns is failing in the battle against the Omicron variant. The country has the world’s strictest strategy with the most re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Border wait times swell as staffing shortages plague inspections booths...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2021-12-26/border-waits-look-ahead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public officials in the region have said they plan to press the federal government in the new year on the issue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military cracking down on 'questionable tattoos' to combat extremism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/military-is-cracking-down-on-e2-80-98questionable-tattoos-e2-80-99-to-combat-extremism-here-e2-80-99s-how/ar-AAS63zn?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci warns of complacency with virus set to fill hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/fauci-warns-of-complacency-with-virus-set-to-fill-hospitals/ar-AAS9LXW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corona can persist for months after traversing entire body...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/coronavirus-can-persist-for-months-after-traversing-body/ar-AAS9pry?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we feel pain when we dream?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/sleep/article-689779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot reacts to human invading its personal space!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/robot-compared-terminator-reaction-human-25789021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ameca the robot was filmed reacting to a human entering its "personal space" and it's sent the internet into a frenzy. Engineered Arts said the bot was "starting to freak us out"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MATRIX' FALLS INTO BOXOFFICE VOID...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/12/26/matrix-resurrections-is-the-sequel-no-one-wanted-and-no-one-went-to-see-doa-at-the-box-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Why Brain, Memories Have Such Strong Link To Smell...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/brain-memories-link-to-smell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brain cells in the olfactory cortex - the area of the brain that controls smell - make the link between specific scents and places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax podcaster hospitalized on ventilator...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/an-anti-vax-podcaster-has-reportedly-contracted-covid-19-and-now-is-hospitalized-on-a-ventilator/ar-AAS9LQL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic' Weight-Loss Pills, Covid Cures: Dr. Oz Under the Microscope...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/26/magic-weight-loss-pills-and-covid-cures-dr-oz-under-the-microscope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wealth of evidence now shows that the malaria drugs hydroxychloroquine and chloroquine were not effective at treating Covid-19 and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin to mull options if West refuses guarantees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-moscow-1f80249ac893d533fb6fcfdecb3d1ad3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin said Sunday he would ponder a slew of options if the West fails to meet his push for security guarantees precluding NATO's expansion to Ukraine. Earlier this month, Moscow submitted draft security documents demanding that NATO deny membership to Ukraine and other former Soviet countries and roll back its military deployments in Central and Eastern Europe.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
