<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Employee opened fire during union meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9621739/Police-respond-active-shooter-California-light-rail-yard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman - identified as Samuel Cassidy - opened fire a little before 7am local time at the yard. The victims include Valley Transportation Authority employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI emotion-detection software tested on Uyghurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-57101248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A software engineer tells BBC's Panorama about installing the system in police stations in Xinjiang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM's newest vehicle: Off-road, self-driving rover for moon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-moon-technology-business-science-e38637dc941374e20c352707e9005300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — General Motors is teaming up with Lockheed Martin to produce the ultimate off-road, self-driving, electric vehicles — for the moon. The project announced Wednesday is still in the early stages and has yet to score any NASA money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein 'recruiters, lovers' set to testify against Maxwell...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2963403/jeffrey-epstein-recruiters-lovers-pals-testify-ghislaine-maxwell-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein’s recruiters, lovers and pals are reportedly set to testify against Ghislaine Maxwell in her sex trafficking trial. Prosecutors in Maxwell’s trial said that material wil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conwomen trick 19 men into fake marriages, steal $312,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/people-culture/gender-diversity/article/3134919/wedding-scam-china-sees-two-conwomen-allegedly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Against a backdrop of more single men than women, a group of men in rural China have allegedly been conned by two women with and fake relatives in a wedding scam that netted US$312,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver nearly runs over workers giving shots, cops say...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-vaccines-driver-nearly-runs-175234558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She was yelling “no vaccines” as she sped through, witnesses said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baton to pass to new CEO July 5...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amazoncom-inc-jeff-bezos-business-0c901587710e5b3bea3447781137f1c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Amazon founder Jeff Bezos has picked a date to step down as CEO. Bezos, who grew Amazon from an internet bookstore to an online shopping behemoth, said Wednesday that Amazon executive Andy Jassy will take over the CEO role on July 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAMAS:  We have 10,000 terrorists within Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/hamass-sinwar-we-have-10000-terrorists-within-israel-669265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinwar claimed that Hamas has over 500 km of tunnels in Gaza and that not even 5% of the tunnels were damaged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: As Many As 7 Killed In Mass Shooting At CA Light Rail Facility...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/05/26/san-jose-vta-rail-yard-mass-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee opened fire in a mass shooting at a Santa Clara Valley Transportation Authority light rail facility in San Jose that left eight victims dead and multiple others wounded. The incident was connected to a separate house fire in the city at around the same time of the shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media's lab leak fiasco...</title>
      <link>https://www.slowboring.com/p/the-medias-lab-leak-fiasco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.slowboring.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge fuckup, with perhaps not-so-huge policy stakes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme stocks pop again as speculative trading ramps back up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/26/meme-stocks-gamestop-amc-are-popping-again-as-speculative-trading-ramps-back-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meme stocks have rallied double digits this week as enthusiastic investors piled back into speculative assets with the market near record highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate activists win EXXON board seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/26/engine-no-1-gets-at-least-2-candidates-elected-to-exxons-board-in-win-for-the-activist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New GB NEWS channel announces June launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-57252833</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new network will feature shows hosted by Andrew Neil, Simon McCoy and Kirsty Gallacher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theatres promise to only cast trans actors in trans roles...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2021/may/26/uk-theatres-promise-to-only-cast-trans-actors-in-trans-roles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trans casting statement signatories pledge to cast trans, non-binary and gender non-conforming performers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of bizarre MLB injuries grows when pitcher breaks thumb while removing shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/esports/list-of-bizarre-mlb-injuries-grows-when-cleveland-pitcher-breaks-thumb-while-removing-shirt/ar-AAKoUx7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zach Plesac was “rather aggressively ripping off his shirt” when it got snagged on a locker room chair, said Indians Manager Terry Francona, placing the 26-year-old starter in quite the club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With most Trump appointees fired from fine arts commission, Biden to put progressive stamp on federal architecture...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-most-trump-appointees-off-the-fine-arts-commission-biden-can-put-a-progressive-stamp-on-federal-architecture/ar-AAKozSA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New appointments give the design group more diversity. This administration should also expand its purpose and scope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  The Don intervened to stop probe of Patriots' Spygate scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/31484993/son-ghostwriter-late-senator-say-trump-intervened-stop-probe-patriots-spygate-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the enduring mysteries of Spygate is the identity of the person who reached out to Sen. Arlen Specter to coax him into dropping his Senate probe. Now the late Specter's son and ghostwriter have come forward with a name: Donald J. Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentines Expect Inflation to Hit 50% in Next Year...</title>
      <link>https://batimes.com.ar/news/economy/poll-shows-argentines-expect-inflation-to-hit-50-in-the-next-year.phtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;batimes.com.ar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Heartland Cities Are the Fast-Growing Immigration Hubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/american-heartland-cities-are-the-fast-growing-immigration-hubs/ar-AAKp0xD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cities in the U.S. heartland have turned into hubs for immigration, a new study shows, helping in some cases to reverse generations of declining birthrates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to Own Trump's 'APPRENTICE' Tapes?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/is-jeff-bezos-about-to-own-trumps-scandalous-apprentice-tapes-colbert-makes-the-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon officially signed an agreement to acquire film studio Metro Goldwyn Mayer (MGM), and Stephen Colbert has some guesses as to why Jeff Bezos agreed to pay the hefty $8.45 billion sum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner: Kardashians NOT producing gubernatorial bid...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/555511-caitlyn-jenner-my-family-not-involved-whatsoever-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner says she doesn't want her famous family to be involved "whatsoever" in her California gubernatorial bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Bishop Robbed At Gunpoint During Afternoon Rosary Walk...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/05/25/oakland-catholic-bishop-michael-barber-robbed-gunpoint/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catholic Bishop of Oakland was robbed over the weekend at gunpoint as he was on his afternoon walk, saying his rosary, near the Paramount Theater, church officials confirmed on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEIR WE GO AGAIN:  Oprah and Harry team for more spillage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15074397/prince-harry-oprah-apple-tv-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Harry and Oprah are set for ANOTHER Apple+ show on Friday – days after the explosive release of their documentary. Viewers can expect more “truth bombs” as the pair discuss…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitt granted joint custody of kids with Angelina after NASTY trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/2961808/brad-pitt-granted-joint-custody-kids-angelina-jolie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAD Pitt and Angelina Jolie have reportedly been awarded joint custody of their five kids. The decision comes after the Hollywood exes have been duking it out in a nasty custody battle over the la…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP GRAND JURY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/prosecutor-in-trump-criminal-probe-convenes-grand-jury-to-hear-evidence-weigh-potential-charges/ar-AAKnuWB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move by Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus R. Vance Jr. suggests his investigation of the former president’s business has entered an advanced stage after more than two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate MCDONALD'S giving away iPhones to find workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/a-mcdonalds-is-so-desperate-for-workers-it-is-giving-away-iphones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A McDonald’s restaurant in Illinois is offering iPhones to try to attract new workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning photos show Super Moon dazzling skies around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9619899/Supermoon-obscured-clouds-graces-night-sky.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This month's full moon is a Super Moon, as the moon is at its closest point to Earth in its orbit of the planet. Pictures from the UK, Turkey, US and more have been shared showing the stunning phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change may allow scientists to grow human embryos longer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-science-health-cfa61338240a926e8748c9a4d8b074ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — New guidelines released Wednesday remove a decades-old barrier to stem cell research, recommending that researchers be allowed to grow human embryos longer under limited conditions.  The “14-day rule,” an international ethical standard that limits laboratory studies of human embryos, has been in place for decades and has been written into law in countries including Britain and Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New American status symbol: Backyard that's basically fancy living room...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/the-new-american-status-symbol-a-backyard-that-s-basically-a-fancy-living-room/ar-AAKoEd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outdoor rugs, TVs, day beds and $5,500 lamps: Welcome to the Great Fauxdoors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resistance to vax mandates building. Powerful network helping...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/resistance-to-vaccine-mandates-is-building-a-powerful-network-is-helping/ar-AAKp8jm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York firm has filed suit or sent letters to employers in several states, part of an effort spearheaded by one of the largest anti-vaccination groups in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Warner, GOP Senate stalwart with air of glamour, dies at 94...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/john-warner-gop-senate-stalwart-with-air-of-glamour-dies-at-94/ar-AAKp3Ua</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Warner, a Republican who represented Virginia in the U.S. Senate for 30 years and brought to Washington a rare aura of glamour including a marriage to actress Elizabeth Taylor, has died. He was 94.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rx for pain relief: 30 mins with a story...</title>
      <link>https://californianewstimes.com/rx-for-pain-relief-30-minutes-with-a-story/360520/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californianewstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you know or have children suffering from a pandemic turmoil, there may be a way to avoid using medications to relieve their pain and stress: read the story to them. Brazilian scientists who studied the effects of storytelling and Riddle-based games on children admitted to the intensive care unit found that stories lower stress …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermittent Fasting May Improve Long-Term Memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/intermittent-fasting-memory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intermittent fasting (IF) is becoming a common practice among dieters trying to burn fat and lose weight, but a new study finds it may hold cognitive benefits as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope kisses Auschwitz tattoo of Holocaust survivor...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/pope-francis-kisses-auschwitz-tattoo-of-polish-survivor-of-holocaust-01622035723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lidia Maksymowicz showed the pope the number tattooed on her arm by the Nazis, and Francis leaned over and kissed it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Raises Heat on TWITTERGOOGLEFACEBOOK in Online Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/26/russia-raises-heat-on-twitter-google-and-facebook-in-online-crackdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Russia is increasingly pressuring Google, Twitter and Facebook to fall in line with Kremlin internet crackdown orders or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as anchor-shaped UFO leaves trail of smoke before crashing into sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15071971/mystery-ufo-smoke-crashing-into-sea-indonesia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the mysterious moment an anchor-shaped UFO left a trail of smoke in the sky before crashing into the sea in Indonesia. The bizarre footage of the long, black object plunging into the water …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reveals 'God of War' stealth bomber...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2959618/china-reveals-stealth-bomber-us-air-bases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has revealed a new stealth bomber capable of hitting major US bases in the Pacific with nuclear weapons. The 5000-mile range of the Xian H-20 means it is able to strike Guam and other key fac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazonian tribe with 'healthiest hearts ever' may hold key to slowing aging...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9621093/Amazonian-tribe-healthiest-hearts-studied-hold-key-slowing-AGEING.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tsimane indigenous people of the Bolivian Amazon experience less brain atrophy as they age than their American and European peers, researchers in California have found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From suicide to 'eco-anxiety', climate change spurs mental health crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210526120959-puazp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mental stresses are growing for families hit by more extreme heat, flooded homes and worries about a hotter planet - but the impacts are little measured so far</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to buy MGM STUDIOS for $8.45 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/26/amazon-to-buy-mgm-studios-for-8point45-billion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deal emphasizes Amazon's willingness to spend deeply to remain competitive in a crowded streaming market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUVRE Gets First Female Leader in 228 Years...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/26/louvre-gets-its-first-female-leader-in-228-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Louvre is to have a female president for the first time in the Paris museum’s 228-year history. Laurence des</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super blood moon dazzles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lunar-eclipse-blood-moon-2021-7db680bdfe3188b8db66e2c450b726ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — Earth's shadow crept across the moon on Wednesday night as people in New Zealand and around the world waited for a cosmic event known as a super blood moon. As the eclipse deepened, it appeared as though half the moon had vanished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year later, Krasinski's 'QUIET PLACE' ready to make noise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-696e865c8d62cd54b94783d53307ca9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — John Krasinski, whose “A Quiet Place Part II” is one of the biggest studio releases to open exclusively in theaters this year, recently returned to the movies, himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Putin set meet in Geneva...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210525125506-hzi40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/ (URGENT):Biden, Putin to meet in Geneva on June 16</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evening Best Time of Day to Exercise?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/26/the-best-time-of-day-to-exercise-for-metabolic-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evening exercise may be more potent than morning workouts for improving metabolic health, according to a helpful new study of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more bite? How NETLIX defanged Ryan Murphy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2021/may/25/no-more-bite-how-netflix-defanged-ryan-murphy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Was getting into bed with the streaming giant a huge mistake for the most prolific man in TV? It seems so: his new shows are anaemic, disposable – and will leave you feeling queasy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYPILLOW Lindell thrown out of Republican gov meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/26/mike-lindell-rga-490914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEO, a top Trump ally, has been sued for defamation over his false assertion that a company’s voting machines stole the election for Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super flower moon dazzles...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/gallery/2021/may/26/mays-super-flower-moon-lights-up-the-night-skies-in-pictures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The May full moon, known as the flower moon, coincided with it being at its closest to the Earth during its orbit, making it appear larger and brighter. May’s supermoon also coincides with a lunar eclipse in which the moon will turn red, but that will only be visible in parts of South America, Australia and south-east Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Passengers Warned to Behave Ahead of Holiday...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/air-passengers-warned-to-wear-masks-and-behave-ahead-of-holiday/ar-AAKmXi9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. government officials monitoring the airways say they won’t tolerate passengers who refuse to don masks as airline travel surges ahead of the summer season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLLAR DOUBTS:  BIG SPENDING THREATENS TO UNDERMINE RESERVE ROLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/408d4065-f66d-4368-9095-c6a8743b0d01</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extraordinary stimulus measures in the US could undermine confidence in the greenback if inflation takes off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New lockdown fears in Melbourne...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9619223/Covid-19-Testing-clinic-chaos-Melbourne-thousands-race-check-theyre-infected.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melbourne's Covid-19 testing clinics have been stretched to their limits as thousands of the city's residents rushed to be swabbed amid the latest outbreak in cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Airlines re-route to avoid Belarus, opposition says journalist beaten..</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210525164324-iyx5i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELARUS-POLITICS/ (WRAPUP 5, TV, PIX):WRAPUP 5-Airlines re-route to avoid Belarus, opposition says journalist beaten</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Japan most people want to cancel Olympics, but govt won't listen...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/may/24/japan-cancel-olympics-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime minister Yoshihide Suga risks playing host to a coronavirus spike, says Koichi Nakano of Sophia University, Japan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Mars Ambition Could Be Riskiest Human Quest Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/elon-musks-mars-ambition-could-be-the-riskiest-human-quest-ever/ar-AAKnxFb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half a century after Neil Armstrong took mankind’s giant leap on the moon, another space race is heating up. This time, the promising new frontier for Earthlings is Mars, the planet next door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire's Fishing Lodge Faces Seizure in Record Tax Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.fa-mag.com/news/billionaire-s--15-million-fishing-lodge-faces-seizure-in-record-tax-case-62262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fa-mag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government only has to show an asset was “the product of tainted funds” to take it in a civil forfeiture proceeding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burnout and Depression Spiral Among India's Traumatized Doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-25/burnout-and-depression-spiral-among-india-s-traumatized-doctors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the silent toll of India’s deadly second wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another summer of power outages poses threat to Newsom as he faces recall...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/another-summer-california-power-outages-120023612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the COVID pandemic wanes, potential summer and fall outages are a test for a governor whose first term has been defined by emergencies beyond his control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE'S THE NEW DONALD...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/has-trump-lost-his-media-commanding-mojo-to-marjorie-taylor-greene-sure-seems-like-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump seems to be freaking out. No matter what he says in statements released via his Save America PAC or on his goofy “From the Desk of” blog, he can barely merit a ripple in media attention. Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, on the other hand, is currently enjoying her time as “It […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC sues AMAZON for antitrust...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/25/dc-attorney-general-sues-amazon-on-antitrust-grounds-alleges-it-illegally-raises-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., Attorney General Karl Racine is suing Amazon on antitrust grounds, alleging it unfairly raised prices through third-party seller contracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDICTMENT SUMMER?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-trump-investigations-business-government-and-politics-80592eae7ba9ca508a3161e085a0fec6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York prosecutors have convened a special grand jury to consider evidence in a criminal investigation into former President Donald Trump's business dealings, a person familiar with the matter told The Associated Press on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Please save him' plead blogger's parents...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/please-save-him-plead-belarus-190120308.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From their new home in Poland, the parents of Belarusian journalist Roman Protasevich have been in anguish since he was seized after his flight was forced to land in Minsk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mag 4.5 Quake Rocks Oklahoma Town...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/05/25/earthquake-shakes-northwestern-oklahoma-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Geological Survey reported the quake struck about 1:25 p.m. near Shattuck, a town of nearly 1,500 population about 145 miles northwest of Oklahoma City and near the border with the Texas Panhandle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diaper Prices Next To Rise Over 'Supply Chain Disruption'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/05/24/colorado-diaper-debacle-families-brace-price-hike-supply-chain-disruption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diapers are a major cost for families and soon a manufacturing issue may prompt companies to raise their prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Say Human Lifespan Could Nearly Double -- To 150...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/humans-could-live-to-be-150/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An iPhone app that estimates biological aging discovered that life expectancy has the capacity to be almost double the current norm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Garcia catapults into lead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/25/garcia-jumps-to-lead-over-adams-yang-in-new-mayoral-survey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former city Sanitation Commissioner Kathryn Garcia has shot to the top of the heap in a new poll of the candidate vying for the Democratic nomination for mayor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant loses 2 teeth in assault...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/union-chief-says-flight-attendant-141423600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest Airlines flight attendant was assaulted by a passenger and lost two teeth in the attack last weekend, according to a union president, who complained to the airline’s CEO about unruly passengers. “Unfortunately, this is just one of many occurrences,” said the union president, Lyn Montgomery. A Southwest spokesman said Tuesday that the incident happened Sunday morning after a flight from Sacramento landed in San Diego and involved a female passenger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New court filing inadvertently reveals more details of Giuliani probe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/court-filing-inadvertently-revealed-federal-171357235.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an improperly redacted letter to a judge, Lev Parnas' lawyer said the feds seized multiple accounts and devices connected to the Giuliani probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian soldier who called on troops to refuse vax distribution faces mutiny related charge...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/national/defence-watch/soldier-who-called-on-troops-to-refuse-vaccine-distribution-faces-mutiny-related-charge/wcm/b1c875de-21ca-4f69-b3bd-681483fda253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young rocked by new hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/25/us/new-york-gen-z-students-antisemitism-soh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In New York, some Gen Z Jews are surprised and angry at anti-Semitic attacks they're seeing on the streets and online, and wondering where their supporters are.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
