<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Man missing since tsunami 16 years ago 'found in psychiatric hospital'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/policeman-missing-boxing-day-tsunami-23751131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police believe they have found Zainal Abidin, known as Asep, who was one of tens of thousands of people missing after the 2004 Boxing Day tsunami that hit Aceh, Indonesia killing a staggering 230,000 people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahomans Say 'Liberal' Donald Won't Convince Them to Get Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/oklahoma-diner-customers-tell-cnn-they-wont-get-vaccinated-even-if-trump-told-them-to-why-listen-to-a-liberal-new-yorker-like-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oklahoma diner customers unanimously tell CNN they won't get vaccinated, some refuse even if Trump told them to get the shot: Why listen to a ‘liberal New Yorker?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angelina Jolie Claims 'Proof' of Alleged Domestic Violence Against Brad Pitt...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/angelina-jolie-claims-she-has-proof-of-alleged-domestic-violence-against-brad-pitt-in-new-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to court records, the actress also filed a document regarding testimony of their minor children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly Woman Who Clobbered Attacker Talks About Assault In San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/18/elderly-asian-woman-beats-up-man-attacking-her-in-san-francisco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elderly woman being attacked on Market St. in San Francisco Wednesday - the latest victim in a wave of attacks on Asians in the Bay Area - turned the tables on her assailant, leaving him with injuries that required a trip to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHEN WILL IT END?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/when-will-it-be-over-3-key-numbers-scientists-are-n1261198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There won't be an on/off switch for the pandemic, but epidemiologists are watching certain metrics for signs of improvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZIL CASES RAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-56424611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's health service is on the brink of collapse amid a surge of coronavirus cases and deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Asian Spa Workers: 'America Is Getting Worse'...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/03/atlanta-spa-workers-on-shootings-america-is-getting-worse.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buying Guns For Protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/aaronsmith/2021/03/18/asian-americans-buy-guns-for-protection-from-hate-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian-Americans are buying guns to protect themselves amid a spike in anti-Asian hate crimes fueled by the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Shrank Global Middle Class for First Time Since 1990s...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/pandemic-shrank-global-middle-class-for-first-time-since-1990s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pandemic Shrank Global Middle Class for First Time Since 1990s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharon Stone on How 'BASIC INSTINCT' Nearly Broke Her...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/03/sharon-stone-on-how-basic-instinct-nearly-broke-her</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive excerpt from her memoir, Stone writes about predatory directors, being a “difficult” woman in Hollywood, and her most iconic role: “It’s about more than just a peek up my skirt, people.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WENT TO REHAB...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9376449/Georgia-massage-spa-shooter-went-rehab-sex-addiction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Aaron Long, 21, murdered eight people including six Asian women on Tuesday at three different parlors in a three-hour killing spree in Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catalytic Converter Thief Crushed To Death After Car Collapses On Him...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/03/17/apparent-catalytic-converter-thief-crushed-to-death-collapsing-car-anaheim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Anaheim police, the body of a man was found underneath a Toyota Prius at an auto repair lot on Placentia Avenue at about 6 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to attempt 'hot fire' test of megarocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/nasa-sls-megarocket-hot-fire-test-march-2021-webcast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In turnabout, Netanyahu courts Arab voters he once called threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-turnabout-netanyahu-courts-arab-voters-he-once-called-a-threat/ar-BB1eIzqe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing an electoral challenge from the right, Israel’s prime minister seeks votes wherever he can find them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli elections: Drones to monitor voting lines from air...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-elections/israel-elections-airport-to-have-polling-stations-for-first-time-662376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New election systems to be fielded to overcome challenges that the virus presents to voting, including airport ballots and line-monitoring drones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West becomes richest black man in American history...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/kanye-west-becomes-the-richest-black-man-in-us-history-12249521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West became a certified billionaire a year ago - as did his soon-to-be ex-wife Kim Kardashian West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp Awaits Retrial Decision In 'Wife Beater' Libel Case...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/johnny-depp-granted-appeal-damaging-wife-beater-libel-case-1234717121/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK Court of Appeal heard today why Johnny Depp’s legal team believe he should be granted a retrial in his libel case with The Sun publisher News Group Newspapers. Central to their argumen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON's 'collateral damage': Families struggle to pull loved ones back from brink...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/qanons-collateral-damage-families-struggle-120004197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No easy answers when a family member has fallen into the clutches of "Q," the conspiracy theory popular with supporters of former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Nearly Every Senior Prescribed Medication That Can Cause Falls...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/older-americans-medications-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;94 percent of Americans over the age of 65 was prescribed at least one drug that raised their risk of falling in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border officials say migrant 'crisis' getting worse...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/18/us-border-officials-say-the-migrant-crisis-getting-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Border Patrol officials said officers are “overwhelmed” by the influx of migrants at the US-Mexico border, a spiraling “crisis” that intensified this week when a gun bat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic buttons and bulletproof vests: Fearful lawmakers stock up on protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/18/lawmakers-protection-jan-6-476929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What may seem like an idle threat may not be an idle threat anymore," said one Massachusetts legislator, describing the post-Jan. 6 world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan feared Biden would be soft. So far, pleasantly surprised...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/taiwan-feared-biden-would-be-softer-trump-china-so-far-n1261274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing-Washington tensions remain high, setting the scene for the first meeting between the two governments this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri dad's testimony against trans sports ban goes viral...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/missouri-dad-e2-80-99s-testimony-against-transgender-sports-ban-goes-viral-e2-80-98let-them-have-their-childhoods-e2-80-99/ar-BB1eIskH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brandon Boulware's emotional speech to Missouri lawmakers about his experience raising a transgender daughter has garnered more than 7 million views on Twitter as many states debate bills banning transgender youth from sports teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds in multiple cities protest violence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/543764-crowds-in-multiple-cities-protest-violence-against-asian-americans-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrations protesting violence against Asian Americans erupted in multiple cities on Wednesday after a shooting spree in Atlanta left eight people dead, six of whom were Asian women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New American Policy Takes Shape...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/17/as-biden-and-xi-begin-a-careful-dance-a-new-american-policy-takes-shape/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden is engineering a sharp shift in policy toward China, focused on gathering allies to counter Beijing’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheltered from virus, Kauai plans cautious return to tourism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-lihue-coronavirus-pandemic-hawaii-economy-de27d1e36aa4352d37b154a7e0367794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIHUE, Hawaii (AP) — As the coronavirus ravaged other parts of the U.S., residents of this rural Pacific island watched safely from afar. Kauai, one of the world’s most sought-after vacation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-level lockdown: Six weeks underground in cave...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/next-level-lockdown-french-group-goes-underground-in-cave-for-six-weeks-to-study-isolation-effects-2393285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after France entered uncharted territory with its first coronavirus lockdown, a small group of volunteers has embarked on a more extreme confinement: nearly six weeks underground, with no notion of time, to study the effects of acute isolation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula's Comeback Roils Brazilian Politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/lula-e2-80-99s-comeback-roils-brazilian-politics-and-chills-investors/ar-BB1eIimM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annulment of convictions against the ex-president will likely open the door for him to challenge Bolsonaro next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to Reach 100 Million Vaccinations Goal Six Weeks Early...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-to-reach-100-million-vaccinations-goal-six-weeks-early/ar-BB1eHWg4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is poised to meet his goal of delivering 100 million Covid-19 vaccine shots in his first 100 days in office as soon as Thursday, reaching the milestone more than a month ahead of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ex-PFIZER scientist who became anti-vax hero...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210318095859-p4gnd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VACCINES-SKEPTIC (SPECIAL REPORT, PIX):SPECIAL REPORT-The ex-Pfizer scientist who became an anti-vax hero</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locked-down Spaniards seethe with envy as Germans flock to Mallorca...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210318085624-girdx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN-TOURISM (TV, PIX):Locked-down Spaniards seethe with envy as Germans flock to Mallorca</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living on Moon? Prepare $325,067 a Month for Mortgage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencetimes.com/articles/30166/20210317/living-moon-prepare-325-067-month-mortgage.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's Artemis program aims to land the first woman and the next man on the moon by 2024, hoping to pave the way to establish a lunar location for further space exploration missions - and a new study estimates the cost of living there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida resort touted as potential gambling destination...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-e2-80-99s-florida-resort-touted-as-potential-gambling-destination/ar-BB1eGppU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Republicans are exploring an expansion of casinos in the state, and the former president’s company could be a beneficiary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady and superyacht: How mogul pitched Florida leaders on Miami Beach casino...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/tom-brady-and-a-superyacht-how-a-mogul-pitched-florida-leaders-on-miami-beach-casino/article_728bc349-c78e-5da2-8860-e6ae09a1a588.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — The night he won his seventh Super Bowl, Tom Brady partied maskless aboard the superyacht of his friend, South Florida billionaire real estate mogul Jeffrey Soffer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breyer mum as liberals urge him to quit Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-ruth-bader-ginsburg-amy-coney-barrett-us-supreme-court-courts-0cd3d0f19759077a13264a1f09ea6244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Forgive progressives who aren't looking forward to the sequel of their personal “Nightmare on First Street," a Supreme Court succession story. The original followed Justice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubled US-China ties face new test in Alaska meeting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-alaska-antony-blinken-yang-jiechi-wang-yi-fc23cd2b23332fa8dd2d781bd3f7c178</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States and China will face a new test in their increasingly troubled relations when top officials from both countries meet in Alaska. Ties between the world's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFECTION SPIKE IN 14 STATES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/18/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US may be on the cusp of another Covid-19 case surge, one expert says -- a surge that health officials have repeatedly warned about as state leaders eased restrictions and several lifted mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming got buried beneath record blizzard, trapping meteorologists in their office for 5 days!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Wyoming-got-buried-beneath-a-record-blizzard-16033399.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just because you forecast the weather doesn't mean you're immune to it. Meteorologists at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUNG FLU:  Shootings coincide with rise of hate online...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Atlanta-spa-shootings-coincide-with-rise-of-16033696.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday's fatal shootings of six Asian women in Georgia have turned a spotlight on a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents helped authorities catch him!</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/spa-shooting-suspect-s-parents-helped-authorities-catch-him/article_6737636b-8f52-57f0-8ebf-68945bd1ebd8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — Once Cherokee County deputies received a surveillance capture of Robert Aaron Long leaving Young’s Asian Massage near Acworth Tuesday afternoon, the trail of the suspected killer grew red</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS FACES WEEKEND LOCKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210317-france-set-to-announce-new-covid-19-measures-lockdown-possible-for-paris-region</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government will impose tougher restrictions for some regions including Paris from this weekend to counter the accelerating spread of COVID-19 infections, spokesman Gabriel Attal said on We…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador health ministry raided over vaccine scandal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ecuador-health-ministry-raided-over-210844431.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuador investigators raided the health ministry on Wednesday as part of a probe into influence peddling against former health minister Juan Carlos Zevallos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZIL RECORD CASES</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210317201244-9fgd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL-CASES (URGENT):Brazil reports record 90,000 new COVID-19 infections, a day after setting deadly record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  South Florida veterinarian charged with child porn had sex with dogs, feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article249978479.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Aventura veterinarian was arrested on Tuesday on allegations he possessed a trove of child pornography — and also sexually abused dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys kill woman after chasing her off roof to her death in wild rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/monkeys-chase-woman-roof-falls-23748052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 21-year-old was said to be playing a game of badminton with her friends on a terrace when the tribe attacked in the Warangal district of Telangana in southern India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Asian-Americans, shooting sows fresh fear...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210317215522-i5rcs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRIME-GEORGIA/SPAS-FEAR (PIX, TV):For Asian-Americans, Atlanta shooting sows fresh fear after a year of mounting discrimination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest virus surge in Europe cautionary tale for USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-coronavirus-surge-cautionary-tale-for-us-051e996d5b7e31711bb741e2f9ba724f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Optimism is spreading in the U.S. as COVID-19 deaths plummet and states ease restrictions and open vaccinations to younger adults. But across Europe, dread is setting in with another wave of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's taxes in hand, Manhattan DA probe heats up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-new-york-subpoenas-manhattan-trump-investigations-218987d4dbac510158c35d5850f5e492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — With former President Donald Trump’s tax returns finally in hand, a team of New York prosecutors led by a newly hired former mob-buster is sending out fresh subpoenas and meeting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: World demand for gasoline may NEVER recover...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-69638551c3eabe4a8d0f94f6bbb8c4a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The world's once-insatiable demand for gasoline is unlikely to recover to pre-pandemic levels, according to a report Wednesday from the International Energy Agency. Gasoline...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pollution Blamed For Rising Number Of Boys Born With Testicles In Wrong Place...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/undescended-testicles-pollution-blamed-for-rising-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French researchers say babies born with undescended testicles has shot up by as much as 50%, especially in places with coal mines and metal works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskless John Kerry on Flight Sparks Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://tennesseestar.com/2021/03/17/exclusive-maskless-climate-envoy-kerry-endangers-passengers-on-boston-to-dc-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tennesseestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Forbes Kerry, the U.S. special presidential envoy for climate, while sitting in first-class, took off his mask today as he settled into his book moments before his American Airlines flight from Boston to Washington took off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army prepping robotic combat vehicles for big test...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/digital-show-dailies/global-force-symposium/2021/03/17/us-army-prepping-robotic-combat-vehicles-for-big-test-with-soldiers-in-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army is taking receipt of robotic combat vehicle prototypes in order to prep them ahead of a major company-led evaluation at Fort Hood, Texas, next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey: 'I'd Be A Fool Not To' Consider Running For Gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/matthew-mcconaughey-texas-benefit-governor-consideration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar-winning actor and his wife Camila Alves are hosting "We're Texas," a virtual benefit concert to help the Lone Star state after it was devastated by a massive winter storm in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Elderly Woman Turns Tables, Beats Up Man Attacking Her On San Fran Street...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/17/elderly-asian-woman-beats-up-man-attacking-her-in-san-francisco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elderly woman being attacked on Market St. in San Francisco Wednesday - the latest victim in a wave of attacks on Asians in the Bay Area - turned the tables on her assailant, leaving him with injuries that required a trip to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brin Secretly Building Massive Airship...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Sergey-Brin-Google-airship-blimp-zeppelin-LTA-16030652.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's the deal with the Google co-founder's secretive Mountain View airship company?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow closes above 33,000 for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/16/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed said it expects benchmark interest rates to remain near zero for the next two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy agencies warn of growing domestic terror threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210317182107-yr189</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TERRORISM/ (URGENT):U.S. spy agencies warn of growing domestic terrorism threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animating Dead Relatives with AI Cathartic or Creepy? Yes...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3vaq8/is-animating-dead-relatives-with-ai-cathartic-or-creepy-yes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deep Nostalgia presents a predicament that is as old as death itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy missed remote school. Police showed up with $439 fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/mar/17/us-remote-school-pandemic-police-fine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Punitive truancy policies mean US families may face fines. A health crisis, recession and bad internet can make remote learning impossible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobbyist in $60 million bribery probe found dead in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/nation-world/2021/03/16/lobbyist-in-60-million-ohio-bribery-probe-found-dead-in-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neil Clark, who faces federal charges, was found dead near a pond in Collier County,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow recalls ambassador to USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-moscow-russia-united-states-697e73e5dafb2a2bca55ce6aab1ba6bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia is recalling its ambassador to the United States for consultations, the foreign ministry said Wednesday without citing a specific reason. The move to bring Anatoly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS pushes tax deadline to May 15...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/17/irs-pushes-april-15-us-tax-deadline-to-may-15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRS is planning to push back the deadline for the tax filing season about one month, to May 15 from April 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed sees higher inflation... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/17/fed-decision-march-2021-fed-sees-stronger-economy-higher-inflation-but-no-rate-hikes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As widely expected, the policymaking Federal Open Market Committee also voted to keep short-term borrowing rates steady near zero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphic details emerge from sex-assault suit filed against star NFL QB...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/17/deshaun-watson-lawsuit-graphic-details-emerge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit filed in Harris County against NFL star Deshaun Watson alleges the Houston Texans quarterback “assaulted” a massage therapist at her home “by touching her with his penis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC to Seek Primetime TV Rates -- for Streaming...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/nbcuniversal-primetime-tv-rates-peacock-advertising-streaming-1234932762/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood’s streaming wars are likely to spur clashes on Madison Avenue. The priciest stuff on TV for advertisers always runs in primetime. When viewers can stream “This Is Us” or “Young Rock” at m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had 'really bad day'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/17/atlanta-shooting-suspect-had-a-really-bad-day-before-massacre-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sheriff’s captain in Georgia claimed the Atlanta spa shooter had “a really bad day” prior to committing a massacre that left eight people dead, authorities said Wednesday. Capt.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm whales shared ship attack information...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/mar/17/sperm-whales-in-19th-century-shared-ship-attack-information</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whalers’ logbooks show rapid drop in strike rate in north Pacific due to changes in cetacean behaviour</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's rolling disaster is threat to world...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-rolling-coronavirus-disaster-is-a-threat-to-the-world/ar-BB1eFhPN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As covid-related deaths and infections spike, scientists fret that Brazil is incubating possibly deadlier new strains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada expands use of ASTRAZENECA jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/17/health/astrazeneca-vaccine-canada-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada has expanded its rollout of Oxford-AstraZeneca's coronavirus vaccine, reversing an earlier recommendation that it not to be given to seniors, even as more European nations moved to suspend its use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing Music Too Loudly Inside Car Could Lead To $2000 Fine...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/17/mesquite-noise-ordinance-distresses-disturbs-2000-fine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's probably not a good idea for folks in Mesquite to have the speakers in their cars vibrating, or walls shaking in the house from the cranked up stereo. The City Council has approved updates to part of the City Code that addresses noise complaints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSAGE MASSACRE SUSPECT 'SEX ADDICT'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/georgia-massage-parlor-shootings-leave-8-dead-f3841a8e0215d3ab3d1f23d489b7af81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — A white man accused of killing eight people, most of whom were of Asian descent, at massage parlors in the Atlanta area told police the attack was not racially motivated and that he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARVEL reveals its first gay Captain America...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/marvel-reveals-its-first-gay-teen-captain-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new character, Aaron Fischer, represents the first LGBTQ character to pick up Cap's shield in the comic's 80-year history.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
