<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu ahead but win uncertain in new Israel vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210322-netanyahu-ahead-but-win-uncertain-in-new-israel-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu ahead but win uncertain in new Israel vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops' posts to private FACEBOOK group show hostility, hate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-race-and-ethnicity-shootings-police-22355db9b0b7561ce91fa2ddfbcd2fc1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — In a private Facebook group called the Pittsburgh Area Police Breakroom, many current and retired officers spent the year criticizing chiefs that took a knee or officers who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where would major tsunami strike? Malibu, Venice, Long Beach get ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/projects/la-tsunami-maps-tracking-risk-california-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. tsunami maps: Tracking risk along the California coast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flock to Iceland's erupting volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210322-thousands-flock-to-iceland-s-erupting-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands flock to Iceland's erupting volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base jumper plunges to death from at Florida hotel after parachute failed to open in time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9388307/BASE-jumper-plunges-death-14th-floor-balcony-Florida-hotel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man, believed to have been in his 20s, has died after his parachute failed to open in time during a BASE jump from a 14th floor balcony at the Sunrise Beach Resort in Panama City Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Das Auto' goes electric as VW takes on TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/das-auto-goes-electric-vw-103617199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Volkswagen chief executive Herbert Diess joined Twitter in January, he used his first tweet to warn pioneering electric car maker Elon Musk that he was coming after him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Determined to Tax Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-determined-to-tax-rich-after-windfalls-from-covid-crisis/ar-BB1ePhGQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden’s economic team at the White House is determined to make good on his campaign pledge to raise taxes on the rich, emboldened by mounting data showing how well America’s wealthy did financially during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Navy Starts Drills to Protect Oil Sites as Attacks Mount...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-navy-starts-drills-protect-064903110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Arabia started naval exercises in the Persian Gulf to improve its ability to foil “terrorist attacks” on oil facilities, underscoring the kingdom’s concern about a rise in drone and missile strikes claimed by Yemen’s Houthi rebels.The exercises will enhance the security of vital installations and oil fields, and secure freedom of navigation in the region’s waters, the official Saudi Press Agency said. They will be conducted by the Royal Saudi Navy with participation from Saudi Aramco, the state oil company.This month alone, the Houthis, who are backed by Iran, have claimed assaults on a fuel depot in Jeddah, the Ras Tanura export terminal and a refinery in Riyadh, the Saudi capital.The Saudi government said the missiles used for the March 19 refinery attack were made in Iran.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's Digital Dollar Momentum Worries Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/federal-digital-dollar-momentum-worries-060000433.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The financial services industry, braced for what could be its biggest disruption in decades, is about to get an early glimpse at the Federal Reserve’s work on a new digital currency.Wall Street is not thrilled.Banks, credit card companies and digital payments processors are nervously watching the push to create an electronic alternative to the paper bills Americans carry in their wallets, or what some call a digital dollar and others call a Fedcoin.As soon as July, officials at the Federal Reserve Bank of Boston and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, which have been developing prototypes for a digital dollar platform, plan to unveil their research, said James Cunha, who leads the project for the Boston Fed.A digital currency could fundamentally change the way Americans use money, leading some financial firms to lobby the Fed and Congress to slow its creation -- or at least ensure they’re not cut out.Seeing the threat to their profits, the banks’ main trade group has told Congress a digital dollar isn’t needed, while payment companies like Visa Inc. and Mastercard Inc. are trying to work with central banks to make sure the new currencies can be used on their networks.“Everyone is afraid that you could disrupt all the incumbent players with a whole new form of payment,” said Michael Del Grosso, an analyst for Compass Point Research &amp; Trading LLC.Lawmakers, U.S. Treasury Department officials and the Fed haven’t yet approved the rollout of a U.S. virtual currency, which could still be years away. Nor have they decided how a digital dollar would interact with the existing global payments network. Still, the U.S. and other countries seem committed enough to digitizing their currencies that it’s making financial industry executives nervous.“The fire has been lit,” said Josh Lipsky, who has helped convene government officials from the U.S. and other countries working on digital currencies as director of the GeoEconomics Center at the Atlantic Council. “The world is moving very quickly on these projects.”At issue are forms of digital cash being considered by the U.S. and other governments. The growing popularity of Bitcoin, Ethereum and other cryptocurrencies, whose market value has grown to more than $1 trillion, inspired the projects. Unlike those privately created tokens, the new currencies would be issued by central banks as an alternative to paper bills. Cash wouldn’t go away, but its use would likely decline.Using the currencies could be as simple as holding up the screen of a mobile phone to be scanned. Behind the scenes, the digital cash would move from one account to another. This is similar to how most money already works -- the majority of U.S. dollars are just digital entries in bank accounts -- but the new currency could potentially avoid the go-between of a commercial bank or credit-card network. For vendors, settlement would happen almost immediately, without having to wait for the money or worry about fraud.The U.S. effort got an extra push last month, when Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said such a project could help Americans who don’t have access to the banking system.In video remarks last week to a payments conference in Basel, Switzerland, Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell may have eased some of the banks’ concerns when he said “digital currencies would need to be integrated into existing payment systems alongside cash and other forms of money.”Cunha said the Boston Fed and MIT hope to unveil some of their work in the third quarter, including at least two prototype software platforms that could move, store and settle transactions made with digital dollars. He wouldn’t say if either platform uses the blockchain technology that underlies Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Once the prototypes are released, Cunha said, others will be able to see and build on the code.The Fed’s work is meant to show what’s possible without taking a stand on major issues that the central bank, Treasury and Congress must address, Cunha said. These include whether the Fed itself should host customer accounts, whether to allow anonymity, and what protections consumers would have in case of a cyber-breach or mistaken transaction.“We think it’s important that we not wait for the policy debate because then we’ll be a year or so behind,” Cunha said. “This will take significant outreach to the industry and serious debate.”The potential that the central bank could cut banks out of their middleman role in the lucrative U.S. payments system is causing angst among banks.So is the push coming from Ohio Democratic Senator Sherrod Brown, the new chairman of the Senate Banking Committee. Brown is urging the Fed to move quickly to create digital-currency accounts for Americans who can’t easily access the financial system and have been forced to deal with payday lenders who charge higher fees and interest rates. Brown’s plan could threaten the deposits that commercial banks rely on to make mortgages and other loans.“Rushing anything of this potential magnitude could introduce unintended consequences that threaten the stability of the banking system without contributing meaningfully to economic inclusion,” said Steve Kenneally, senior vice president of payments at the American Bankers Association.The ABA, which says it’s lobbying Congress on the issue, last year in written testimony called the digital dollar a costly solution in search of a nonexistent problem.Two lobbyists for a large bank said they’re in contact with lawmakers to keep track of the issue. They expect lobbying to pick up once banks can actually see the Fed’s work and how it might affect them, said the lobbyists, who requested anonymity to discuss internal conversations.Interest in a digital currency has gathered momentum in part because many banks take days to give consumers access to checks deposited in their accounts and some charge stiff overdraft fees. Those without bank accounts sometimes must pay high fees to cash paychecks or transmit money to relatives.Some of the profits of credit-card companies, such as Visa and Mastercard, could be at risk if the new currencies let Americans more easily make transactions without their involvement and fees.Spokespeople from both companies say their firms are working with central banks to ensure the new currencies can run over their networks. Mastercard in February began to issue pre-paid debit cards loaded with the “Sand Dollar,” a digital currency issued by the Bahamas.“We’re increasingly having conversations with central banks as they think about designing potential central bank digital currency, CBDC, and we’re talking to them about how they think about design,” said Visa’s North America president Oliver Jenkyn, at a Morgan Stanley conference earlier this month. “So there’s a lot of talking, but there’s actually a lot of action alongside it as well.”Other countries are further along. China is currently piloting a digital yuan in several cities. Lipsky said there’s a chance its currency could be ready for a broader debut at the 2022 Winter Olympics in Beijing, which he said could cause tensions if American athletes are asked to use a currency that the Chinese government can completely track.Brown earlier this month sent a letter to Powell urging him to speed up the research. “We cannot be left behind,” Brown wrote.Among other threats, Brown pointed to the development by Facebook Inc. and other companies of their own cryptocurrency, once called Libra. That currency, since renamed Diem, was slated to launch in 2020 but has struggled to win regulatory approval.Advocates of existing cryptocurrencies, like Bitcoin, have mixed feelings about the Federal Reserve muscling into the industry.A Fedcoin could acclimate Americans to purchasing Bitcoin, said Jerry Brito, who heads Coin Center, a cryptocurrency advocacy group. But depending on the government’s direction, such a currency could be used to track Americans’ spending, destroying the partial anonymity that was once the promise of crypto, he said.A U.S. digital dollar could also put the final nail in the coffin for Bitcoin as a means of exchange, Brito said. Crypto enthusiasts have already started to acknowledge that’s happening anyway, and instead tout the currency as a store of value or “digital gold.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Next phase' of criminal probe into Trump finances: Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-investigation-witnesses-ins/next-phase-of-criminal-probe-into-trump-finances-finding-witnesses-idUSKBN2BE15X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators in a criminal probe of former U.S. President Donald Trump’s real-estate business are combing through millions of pages of newly acquired records with an eye toward identifying witnesses who can bring the documents to life for a jury, say two people familiar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police detective divorces wife after she was photographed with another man at MAGA riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9386187/Police-detective-divorces-wife-photographed-man-Capitol.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Heinl (left), 55, of Ross Township, Pennsylvania, was photographed inside the US Capitol building alongside Kenneth Grayson on January 6, the FBI alleges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after drone found with a bag of heroin on board...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/man-arrested-drone-found-bag-191047706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation is continuing to determine whether the suspect was using the drone to sell drugs, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender Islamic school in Pakistan breaks barriers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321235557-he6bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PAKISTAN-LGBT/MADRASA (TV, PIX):A transgender Islamic school in Pakistan breaks barriers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI BEACH DECLARES EMERGENCY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-19-pandemic-miami-us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-4c4ac71405e13f063e38dde30ef260d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Pointing to over 1,000 arrests in one of the nation’s top party spots, Miami Beach officials warned Sunday that the unruly spring break crowd gathering by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys indictment says group leaders used radios and encrypted chats to coordinate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/proud-boys-capitol-riot-coordination-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say the men used paramilitary gear, handheld radios and encrypted messaging applications to coordinate with other Proud Boys before and during the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremists in police ranks spark growing concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/elections/2021/03/21/police-charged-capitol-riot-reignite-concerns-racism-extremism/4738348001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Racially biased policing was already a concern. Now, charges against officers in the Capitol riot inflame fears of extremists infiltrating law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global shortage in computer chips 'reaches crisis point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/mar/21/global-shortage-in-computer-chips-reaches-crisis-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer price rises loom while dearth of semiconductors slow production from Samsung to Ford</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH BEACH OVERRUN BY MASKLESS HORDES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/miami-beach-freaks-out-over-massive-spring-break-crowds-declares-state-of-emergency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Time and time again during this pandemic, tourists are ruining everything,” a Miami Beach resident said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago suburb's plan to pay Black residents reparations could be national model...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-race-reparations/chicago-suburbs-plan-to-pay-black-residents-reparations-could-be-a-national-model-idUSKBN2BD0B8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades ago, in the Chicago suburb of Evanston, Cordelia Clark ran a restaurant out of her kitchen and parked cabs for her taxi company in her backyard because Black residents were effectively barred from owning or renting storefronts in town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  How 'Owning the Libs' Became GOP's Core Belief...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/03/21/owning-the-libs-history-trump-politics-pop-culture-477203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The weird journey of a tongue-in-cheek catchphrase from conservative-mocking putdown to the defining tenet of the Republican Party’s way of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican AGs take blowtorch to President's agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/21/gop-attorneys-general-biden-477365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On everything from climate change to immigration and abortion rights, GOP attorneys general are leading the charge to dismantle White House policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Vaccine Obsession Hasn't Swung Election to Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahu-vaccine-obsession-hasn-t-swung-election-to-him/ar-BB1eNCYc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccine “world champions.” Israel’s “the first” to return to normal life. Other leaders in awe of Benjamin Netanyahu’s achievements in taming the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRAZENECA, once touted as a pandemic slayer, faces challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/astrazeneca-once-touted-as-a-pandemic-slayer-faces-challenges/ar-BB1eODgv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the stakes hadn’t been so high, the saga might have felt like a soap opera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Biden's failure to contain the border surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/no-end-in-sight-inside-the-biden-administration-s-failure-to-contain-the-border-surge/ar-BB1eNeEh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration has emerged as one of the administration’s most urgent challenges — seized on by Republicans as a political cudgel, posing risks to Democrats in the 2022 midterms and potentially undermining Biden’s governing agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black leaders react to crackdown: 'Unnecessary force'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/black-leaders-react-to-south-beach-spring-break-curfew-crackdown-unnecessary-force/ar-BB1eOwEy?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mar. 21—After weeks of uninhibited partying on South Beach by spring breakers, police turned away throngs of people — many of them Black — from world-famous Ocean Drive with a SWAT truck, pepper balls and sound cannons. The tactics were intended to enforce an 8 p.m. curfew announced only hours earlier on Saturday to rid the city of what police and politicians have described as unruly and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company says ORAL covid vaccine on its way...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israeli-company-says-oral-covid-19-vaccine-on-its-way-662712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oral vaccine could potentially allow for people to self vaccinate at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considering releasing illegals into USA without court date...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-rio-grande-valley-considering-releasing-migrants-into-u-s-without-court-date</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Fox News has learned from a senior source with Customs and Border Protection (CBP) that a plan is under consideration for Border Patrol agents in the Rio Grande Valley Sector (RGV) to begin releasing illegal border crossers who claim asylum without issuing a Notice to Appear (NTA) - meaning they will depart custody without a court date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEEN VOGUE staffer who supported editor's ousting used 'N-word' in tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/senior-teen-vogue-staffer-mccammonds-ousting-used-n-word-in-decade-old-tweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Teen Vogue staffer who posted a letter expressing concern about Alexi McCammond for past tweets racist against Asian Americans used the N-word in tweets from over 10 years ago herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Germany police clash with protesters against new virus measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9386215/Angela-Merkel-extends-Germanys-Covid-restrictions-month-despite-anti-lockdown-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of protesters angry at Covid-19 restrictions rallied in cities across Europe over the weekend, even as several nations reimposed partial lockdowns to fight new surges in infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAT TEAMS MOVE IN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9384843/Miami-Beach-unveils-curfew-uncontrollable-crowds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spring breakers invading Miami Beach have become so uncontrollable that authorities imposed a curfew on Saturday as SWAT teams were seen moving in to clear people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad arrested after taking toddler into elephant enclosure at San Diego Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/21/us/san-diego-zoo-arrest-elephant-toddler/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A visitor at the San Diego Zoo was arrested on Friday shortly after taking his two-year-old daughter into an elephant enclosure, according to a press release from the San Diego Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 unaccompanied children in CBP custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/20/politics/unaccompanied-migrant-children-cbp/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more than 5,000 unaccompanied children in US Customs and Border Protection custody, according to documents obtained by CNN, up from 4,500 children days earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS: Govts 'to insist' on vaccines for flying...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-56460329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Governments are going to insist" on vaccines for international travellers, Qantas' boss tells the BBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Pilots Bumpy All-terrain Rig On Siberian Holiday...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/putin-pilots-bumpy-all-terrain-rig-on-siberian-holiday-01616327706?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin, during a holiday in Siberia with Defence Minister Sergei Shoigu, piloted an all-terrain vehicle through thick woodland and traversed a swaying rope bridge, Kremlin footage showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUSH FOR NEW NATIONAL HOLIDAY, 'EMANCIPATION DAY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/national-holiday-emancipation-e9e8dc33-04e7-4390-a3bb-c1d867b3e036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a movement to create an official holiday, but not all supporters agree on the best date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/JanineStanwood/status/1373062537332293635?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid long-haulers still suffer extreme symptoms -- year later...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/20/these-covid-long-haulers-suffer-side-effects-a-year-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after getting COVID, these New Yorkers are still suffering shocking complications — forcing them to give up their jobs and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli court upholds school's barring of refusenik teacher...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321125834-n0iq2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-VACCINE (PIX):Israeli court upholds school's barring of COVID refusenik teacher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges fight against organised crime as mafia milks pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210321113002-71rem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-MAFIA/ (PIX, TV):Pope urges fight against organised crime as mafia milks the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Springs military community works to address 'ideologies'...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/military/colorado-springs-military-community-to-address-extremism/article_effc1e48-839b-11eb-a6ee-03012c27f35d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spurred by the Jan. 6 storming of the U.S. Capitol, the military is taking a hard look at extremism in its ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infections continue to climb in Turkey amid relaxed measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-turkey-istanbul-coronavirus-pandemic-financial-markets-d501dffbb5a9cacedd28d81a3d60aa6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey’s weekly regional COVID-19 figures keep increasing and deaths rising as the country maintains more relaxed restrictions for now. The country's official death toll in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of 1 murder says he really killed 16...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-woodbury-new-jersey-new-mexico-missouri-tigers-mens-basketball-d2ac672be586e5332a7bc36e3b9e47c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOODBURY, N.J. (AP) — A man charged with beating to death a New Jersey resident he says sexually abused him as a child now claims he has killed a total of 16 people, including his ex-wife and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON 'OUT INDEFINITELY'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nba-los-angeles-los-angeles-lakers-lebron-james-trae-young-d546428403947a7dbaf21a2b9ff983a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — LeBron James left in the second quarter with a high right ankle sprain that the Lakers said will sideline him indefinitely, and Los Angeles went on to fall 99-94 to the Atlanta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Married 66 years, husband, wife pass minutes apart of virus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-florida-fort-lauderdale-lebanon-coronavirus-pandemic-ed9ea972b0ff037952a02aa864399043</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Bill and Esther Ilnisky spent nearly seven decades together as Christian ministers and missionaries, including stints in the Caribbean and Middle East before preaching...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US ties with Russia, China sink as Biden toes tough lines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-russia-vladimir-putin-china-national-security-550deda11d43e6bb7c1a8230ee8917ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. relations with its two biggest geo-political rivals are facing severe tests as President Joe Biden tries to assert America's place in the world and distinguish himself from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE WAR WITHOUT END:   Defense chief arrives in Kabul on 1st trip to Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-afghanistan-lloyd-austin-ashraf-ghani-6d57e76434b146c6dfb93aeb208f3464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, on his first visit to Afghanistan as Pentagon chief, said Sunday that the Biden administration wants to see “a responsible end” to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama-era officials return to White House worth millions...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/obama-era-officials-return-white-house-worth-millions/story?id=76582015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As several Obama-era officials return to the White House under President Joe Biden, they're reuniting with fuller pockets according to new financial disclosure reports.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
