<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Faces Probe on Whether He Lied Over Partygate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-faces-probe-on-whether-he-lied-over-partygate/ar-AAWs5vB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA company accused of faking hundreds of COVID test results...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/beyond-outrageous-la-company-accused-of-faking-hundreds-of-covid-test-results/ar-AAWrjOt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE TYSON REPEATEDLY PUNCHES MAN ON PLANE...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/04/21/mike-tyson-repeatedly-punches-man-face-plane-bloodies-passenger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Tyson seemed to lose his cool on a plane on Wednesday night ... repeatedly punching a man in the face after the guy had apparently annoyed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jon Stewart Lost His Edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2022/04/the-problem-with-jon-stewart-tucker-carlson/629608/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jon Stewart is comedy royalty. But the world has changed since he was at the height of his powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The superyacht that FLIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10738823/Luxury-656ft-vessel-transported-world-AIRSHIP-unveiled-new-concept-design.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept of the AirYacht, thought up as an eco-friendly alternative to a conventional luxe cruiser, would contain no engine and be positioned in harbour by tugboats once dropped off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Fast Walkers Live 16 Years Longer!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/walking-faster-live-longer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Leicester have discovered a link between a person's walking pace and the rate at which they age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iger comeback?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/20/as-disney-flails-hollywood-weighs-a-possible-bob-iger-comeback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood insiders questioned whether 71-year-old Bob Iger would be able to restrain himself from reaching for the wheel at Disney after a series of missteps by Bob Chapek.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad claims Mariupol win but won't storm holdout...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-kyiv-business-europe-f0e1cd893715eda1e6bef696d9c47db3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin tried to claim victory in the strategic port of Mariupol on Thursday, even as he ordered his troops not to storm the last pocket of Ukrainian resistance in the war’s iconic battleground .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewest Americans collecting jobless aid since 1970...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-economy-unemployment-629c9afb8baaaed5502b12573ff27822</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Applications for unemployment benefits inched down last week as the total number of Americans collecting aid fell to its lowest level in more than 50 years. Jobless claims fell by 2,000 to 184,000 last week, the Labor Department said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Wants Free Speech on TWITTER After Spending Years Silencing Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/musk-wants-free-speech-on-twitter-after-spending-years-silencing-critics/ar-AAWrjGk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia missile test fuels fears of isolated Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/04/21/world/russia-missile-test-fuels-us-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is growing concern in Washington that Russia is now so cut off from the world that Putin sees little downside to provocative actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Army plane heading to Nationals Park parachute jump prompts Capitol evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/national-international/police-order-evacuation-of-us-capitol-over-aircraft-threat/3030383/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident suggested a stunning communications failure between the military, the Federal Aviation Administration and the Capitol Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19-year-old awakes to man groping her on flight. He says he had 'nightmare'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/19-year-old-awakes-to-man-groping-her-on-flight-feds-say-he-says-he-had-nightmare/ar-AAWqpEx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror master Cronenberg makes art from 'beautiful' kidney stones...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220421-horror-master-cronenberg-makes-art-from-beautiful-kidney-stones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian film-maker David Cronenberg has been shocking audiences for decades with his graphic "body horror" movies but he has now gone further by creating art from his own insides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reinforces tight control over plane crash mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220421-china-reinforces-tight-control-over-plane-crash-mystery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cause of China's deadliest air crash in decades remains a mystery, with authorities giving few details in a preliminary report on Wednesday while enforcing strict censorship one month after the d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Pardon for Bannon, 2 to Admit Bilking Donors to Border Wall...</title>
      <link>https://thenyledger.com/news/after-pardon-for-bannon-2-to-admit-bilking-donors-to-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenyledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The defendants defrauded hundreds of thousands of donors, capitalizing on their interest in funding a border wall to raise millions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of era as NETFLIX faces stagnation challenges...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-04-era-netflix-stagnation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having lost subscribers for the first time in more than a decade, Netflix faces the new challenge of stagnation from a position of strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After life of trauma, Liberian lab chimps settle into retirement...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2022-04-life-trauma-liberian-lab-chimps.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Floating on a river boat near a Liberian island, vet Richard Ssuna watches intently as animal carers wade towards the shore hurling fruits and imitating chimpanzee calls as they go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I've Had It With This Guy': GOP Leaders Privately Blasted Trump After Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/21/ive-had-it-with-this-guy-g-o-p-leaders-privately-blasted-trump-after-jan-6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the days after the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol building, the two top Republicans in Congress, Representative Kevin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA's Star Witness: Indict The Don Now or I'm Out...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/manhattan-da-star-witness-indict-091218324.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Luis G. Rendon/The Daily Beast/GettyIf Manhattan prosecutors don’t indict former President Donald Trump with the grand jury they’ve got in the next nine days, the key witness investigators have used to build their entire case says he won’t help revive it in the future.Michael Cohen, the New York lawyer Trump used for years as his family company’s trusted consigliere, told The Daily Beast he’s already wasted too much of his time on a case that slowly and then suddenly doesn’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Zelensky's blue-collar hometown, praise for president's 'steel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-zelensky-e2-80-99s-blue-collar-hometown-praise-for-the-president-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98steel-e2-80-99/ar-AAWrah0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-year-old Jewish survivor of Nazi-occupied Mariupol dies during Russian siege...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/91-year-old-jewish-survivor-of-nazi-occupied-mariupol-dies-during-russian-siege/ar-AAWr3We</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wedding spirals into chaos after bride laces food with pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/wedding-spirals-into-chaos-after-bride-allegedly-laced-food-with-pot/ar-AAWqBH9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busing migrants, halting trade: Abbott bets future on border plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/busing-migrants-halting-trade-abbott-bets-future-on-divisive-border-plans/ar-AAWqpWg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions of federal dollars to cut emissions will come with few strings attached...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/billions-of-federal-dollars-to-cut-emissions-will-come-with-few-strings-attached/ar-AAWqSO4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers push to uncover riches shielded by state secrecy laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/lawmakers-push-to-uncover-riches-shielded-by-state-secrecy-laws/ar-AAWrm1v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas Split With SPOTIFY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/topstocks/the-obamas-are-leaving-spotify/ar-AAWrAUU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA sticks to tough stance on unruly flyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/transportation/unruly-airplane-passengers-tsa-20220420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,200 unruly passenger incidents were reported this year through mid-April, roughly 800 of which were related to masks, according to the FAA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan state senator gains national spotlight pushing back against 'hateful garbage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/michigan-state-senator-gains-national-spotlight-pushing-back-against-hateful-garbage/article_8e014b02-3ec2-5e62-b93b-fa2728a96224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. — A five-minute speech from Michigan Sen. Mallory McMorrow gained national attention Tuesday and more than 9 million views on social media as the Royal Oak Democrat spoke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to appeal ruling...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/20/cdc-asks-doj-to-appeal-ruling-to-bring-back-mask-mandate-on-planes-trains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department filed a notice Wednesday that it will appeal a Florida federal judge’s order striking down the long-running rule that forced plane and train passengers to wear masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Giuliani unveiled on 'MASKED SINGER,' prompting judge to walk off...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rudy-giuliani-unmasking-masked-singer-081444123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The Hangover’ star was not impressed by the revealing of Donald Trump’s former advisor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Stumble Warning Sign for Streaming Industry...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/20/netflixs-stumble-could-be-a-warning-sign-for-streaming-industry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many entertainment executives, tired of playing catch-up to a Silicon Valley interloper, have been waiting for the comeuppance of Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza violence intensifies as Jerusalem clashes resume...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-jerusalem-middle-east-tel-aviv-gaza-strip-f9eb9b51e57ac3883de98a0c64cfa692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israel’s air force and Palestinian militants traded fire across the Gaza frontier early Thursday as clashes erupted again at Jerusalem’s most sensitive holy site, worsening an escalation that has been eerily similar to the lead-up to last year’s Israel-Gaza war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy 'kills' drone with LASER for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5164733/us-navy-kills-drone-with-electric-powered-laser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Navy has deployed a new electric laser weapon with massive defensive upside. The weapon can take lethal and non-lethal measures to disable or destroy targets. The laser was tested on a drone…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai children in Hazmats...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5168424/unsettling-footage-children-shanghai-hazmat-suits-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNSETTLING footage appears to show young children in Shanghai dressed in hazmat suits amid China’s zero Covid policy. The dystopian clip shows a group of youngsters covered from head to toe h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron, Le Pen in final push for votes after fiery debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220421-macron-le-pen-in-final-push-for-votes-after-fiery-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Emmanuel Macron and far-right rival Marine Le Pen on Thursday launched a final push for votes in working class heartlands of France after a pre-election debate marked by bitter clashes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskaholics still covering...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/the-failed-covid-policy-of-mask-mandates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wearing a mask may still give some people a sense of security, but they could breathe more easily if they’d face the facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMING IS BLEEDING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-canada-netflix-inc-abd9845644a87b434e53c1c13bbb377a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — An unexpected drop in subscribers sent Netflix shares into freefall Wednesday, forcing the company to consider experimenting with ads and -- hold onto your remote -- cracking down on millions of freeloaders who use passwords shared by friends or family .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio Carnival parade is back, as street bands ache to party...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-travel-business-arts-and-entertainment-559b38d96a78810da8bdf4e41fca78e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Rio de Janeiro's Mayor Eduardo Paes on Wednesday ceremonially handed control of the city to King Momo, a ritual representing the upheaval of the status quo -- but it remains to be seen how much post-pandemic partying is in store during the first Carnival in two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie has 'not ruled out' '24 bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/sanders-team-says-not-ruled-2024-bid-biden-doesnt-run-rcna25259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator's former campaign manager wrote in a memo that allies should keep a potential third run for the presidency in mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas Split With SPOTIFY...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-04-20/obamas-to-leave-spotify-seek-multimillion-dollar-deal-elsewhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL 'STUPID';  PENCE 'WEAK FOOL'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5166374/moment-donald-trump-storms-off-piers-morgan-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump stormed out of a world exclusive interview with Piers Morgan in a blazing row over the ‘stolen’ US presidential election. The ex-President reached boiling point after Piers…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN BLOCKBUSTER</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/you-lost-piers-morgan-and-trump-trade-vicious-insults-in-preview-for-upcoming-fox-news-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan has a new show coming soon and the first episode appears to be everything he and Fox Nation would want to be, at least judging by a preview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Antidepressants DON'T make people happier...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10734869/Antidepressants-DONT-make-people-happier-major-study-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at King Saud University, Saudi Arabia, found taking antidepressants does not have any long-term benefit for psychological well-being compared to not having the medication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech billionaire launches Senate campaign to take on TESLA from Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-tech-billionaire-launches-Senate-17105926.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — This tech billionaire wants to take on Tesla — on the way to the United...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump walks out of explosive Piers Morgan interview...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/20/trump-walks-out-of-piers-morgan-interview-after-being-pressed-on-2020-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump blasted Piers Morgan as “very dishonest” while walking out of an interview after being pressed on the 2020 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More arms, new training for Ukraine: U.S. gambles on 'empty threats'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/more-arms-new-training-for-ukraine-us-gambles-on-russia-s-empty-threats/ar-AAWpGtM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin set to vote on guaranteed basic income...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/austin-city-council-to-vote-on-1-18-million-guaranteed-basic-income-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austin, Texas could be the latest city to implement a guaranteed basic income for certain citizens when the city council votes on the proposal Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA analyst 'got bloodied' in tangled U.S. war on Al Qaeda...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/ex-cia-analyst-says-she-got-bloodied-in-tangled-u-s-war-on-al-qaeda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside CA off-grid 'free city' where lawless residents live as throuples...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/18308515/slab-city-ben-fogle-mermaids-pirates-throuple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IN his quest to meet people who buck convention and live life in the wild, Ben Fogle has come across some colourful characters in the last ten years. But his latest adventure, to the off-grid “Utop…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy limits air conditioning amid energy crisis fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/apr/20/operation-thermostat-italy-limits-air-conditioning-amid-energy-crisis-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schools and public buildings to be banned from having thermostats below 25C as Ukraine war exacerbates crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims Heard severed his finger with vodka bottle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10736279/Johnny-Depp-details-REALLY-happened-2015-blowout-Australia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp detailed the explosive fight he and Amber Heard had in March 2015 in Australia where the top of his finger was severed when Heard allegedly threw a bottle of vodka at him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside New Right, Where Thiel Placing His Biggest Bets...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2022/04/inside-the-new-right-where-peter-thiel-is-placing-his-biggest-bets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re not MAGA. They’re not QAnon. Curtis Yarvin and the rising right are crafting a different strain of conservative politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Insane war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/20/business/oleg-tinkov-ukraine-insane-war/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oleg Tinkov, the billionaire founder of a big Russian digital bank, has blasted Russia's "insane war" in Ukraine and urged the West to help President Vladimir Putin find an off-ramp to "stop this massacre."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firm Made Republicans Go Viral. Now It's Falling Apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2022/4/20/23033650/arsenal-media-group-campaign-marketing-firm-madison-cawthorn-kari-lake-benny-johnson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benny Johnson yelled at staff who say they weren’t paid on time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Election Officials Face Biggest Threat Yet -- Jail Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/u-s-election-officials-face-their-biggest-threat-yet-jail-time/ar-AAWnmLu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Arrest Vaccine Scammer With 'Top Secret' Clearance Hookup...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkp9n9/fake-vaccine-card-scams</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the alleged perps was such a Donald Trump fan, that he posted a picture of himself wearing only a Trump flag. He was aided by a friend with top secret government clearance, authorities say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds charge 21 people with fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/20/politics/feds-charge-21-people-with-covid-related-fraud/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors on Wednesday announced charges against 21 people for allegedly seeking to defraud government health care programs of $149 million in a variety of pandemic-related scams, including selling fake Covid-19 vaccination cards and submitting claims for unnecessary medical tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legacy media disrupted NETFLIX. Could mean mutually assured destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/20/legacy-media-disrupted-netflix-with-streaming-offerings-now-it-risks-similar-fate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of legacy media shares soaring as they imitate Netflix, the industry has brought Netflix down to a degree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney tells Biden to focus on economy, soaring inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10735573/Mitt-Romney-tells-Biden-ditch-woke-advisors-focus-economy-soaring-inflation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Mitt Romney tore into President Biden for doing 'pretty much everything wrong' on the economy and said the president needs to ditch his 'woke advisors' in order to fix the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Adds Yuan to Reserves in 'Philosophy' Change...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/israel-adds-yuan-206-billion-093856435.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for our Middle East newsletter and follow us @middleeast for news on the region.Most Read from BloombergKremlin Insiders Alarmed Over Growing Toll of Putin’s War in UkraineNetflix Breaks Its Own Rules After Subscriber Losses Batter SharesIn Defense of Elon Musk's Managerial ExcellenceUkrainian Troops Risk Being Encircled in New Russian OffensiveUkraine Update: Mariupol on Brink; China Stands With MoscowIsrael’s central bank has made the biggest changes to its allocation of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Europe Unit Paid No Taxes on $55 Billion Sales...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-europe-unit-paid-no-132010460.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Amazon.com Inc.’s main European retail business reported 1.16 billion euros ($1.26 billion) of losses in 2021, which allowed the company to pay no income tax and receive 1 billion euros in tax credits, corporate filings seen by Bloomberg show.Most Read from BloombergKremlin Insiders Alarmed Over Growing Toll of Putin’s War in UkraineNetflix Craters After Shock Subscriber Drop, ‘About-Face’ on AdsUkrainian Troops Risk Being Encircled in New Russian OffensiveIn Defense of Elon Musk'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A$AP Rocky detained at LAX in connection to shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/04/20/asap-rocky-arrested-lax-rihanna-pregnancy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A$AP Rocky was taken into custody as he flew into LAX Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China May Have Taken the Lead in Quantum Computing Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2022/04/china-may-have-just-taken-lead-quantum-computing-race/365712/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s record-shattering processor is 1 million times faster than what Google achieved three years ago–but we are years from the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin test-fires 16,000mph 'Satan' nuclear missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5163399/putin-test-fires-nuclear-missile-russia-satan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has successfully launched its ‘Satan’ missile, capable of firing up to 12 nuclear warheads at once, Vladimir Putin has claimed. The launch of the Sarmat intercontinental ballisti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump silence as Tenn. GOP kicks his candidate off ballot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-silent-as-tenn-gop-kicks-his-candidate-off-ballot/ar-AAWpwbS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Most Powerful...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/history/worlds-most-powerful-nuclear-missile-russian-icbm-nicknamed-satan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although its replacement is being hyped by Russia, the original Soviet-made Satan missile is still a devastating weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Governor Rips DeSantis For 'Socialist Attacks on the Private Sector'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/colorado-governor-rips-desantis-for-socialist-attacks-on-the-private-sector-were-ready-for-mountain-disneyland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jared Polis lit into Ron DeSantis on Tuesday over what Polis called Florida’s “authoritarian socialist attacks” on the free market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30% of  patients suffer from 'long Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-704636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprisingly, ethnicity, older age, and socioeconomic status, all linked with severe illness, were not associated with the long COVID syndrome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman murdered on FACEBOOK Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-murdered-live-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Janice David, 34, was choked, beaten, and stabbed in what police called a "very gruesome, very evil act" that was streamed live on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Temple loses effort to set up elementary school club...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/satan-club-rejected-at-elementary-school</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania school board has rejected an after-school Satan Club for an elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden calls off weapons test...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/18/us-to-end-anti-satellite-asat-testing-calls-for-global-agreement.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To date, four countries â€” the U.S., Russia, China and India â€” have destroyed their own satellites in ASAT tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All hope isn't lost for Dem in November?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/3272140-all-hope-isnt-lost-for-democrats-in-november/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We got a story to tell; just got to tell it,” former President Obama replied to a question about Democrats’ chances in the 2022 midterms as he left a news conference with President Biden. I watche…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
