<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon lasers beam messages into head...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9629895/pentagon-laser-weapon-message-enemy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILITARY scientists at the Pentagon are developing ‘talking’ lasers which can beam warnings straight into the enemy’s head from hundreds of miles away. Weapons researchers at the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark chocolate lowers risk of depression for 24 hours?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/08/01/dark-chocolate-lowers-risk-depression-24-hours-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is food news guaranteed to put a smile on your face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, EILISH!  Lana Del Rey Drops August 30th...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/08/01/lana-del-reys-long-awaited-long-postponed-album-norman-fcking-rockwell-drops-august-30th</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long awaited, and long postponed by her label: Lana del Rey’s “Norman F**cking Rockwell!” is dropping on August 30th. It’s about f**cking time! Originally meant for earlier …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Gets His Wall at Last -- But It's in Zimbabwe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-za/news/africa/donald-trump-gets-his-wall-at-last-but-its-in-zimbabwe/ar-AAFaWii?li=BBqfP3n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Producer: My Humble Quest to Live Forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/gavin-polone-my-humble-quest-live-forever-1228036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By undergoing the latest in genetic and medical testing at a cutting-edge San Diego facility, the film and television producer seeks early detection to avoid the fate of his parents and cheat death or dementia indefinitely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDONESIA: Caned in public for getting too close to opposite sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7310301/Eleven-people-caned-public-hooded-Sharia-officer-Indonesia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One woman begged for mercy and another sobbed uncontrollably in the provincial capital of Banda Aceh in Indonesia as 11 people were flogged for breaking Islamic law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Greenerati'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7309805/Backlash-barefoot-Prince-Harry-hypocrite-celebrities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 114 fuel-guzzling planes are scheduled to land in Palermo for the event, according to Italian media, while others brought their super-yachts to the three-day conference in Italy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says tested crucial new rocket launch system...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/09c7059291d846a091e139183fe7c4b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Scared' rapper A$AP Rocky testifies in Sweden assault trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/717/scared-us-rapper-aap-rocky-testifies-sweden-assault-trial-doc-1j89rm3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs: CIA Pressured Michael Bay To Change Benghazi Movie...</title>
      <link>https://shadowproof.com/2019/07/30/cia-pressured-michael-bay-change-13-hours-benghazi-movie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;shadowproof.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED CUTS QUARTER AS ECONOMY FLASHES WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/57dfaefd18e64a4e9f3698f5f3c92bfb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From everyteen to annoying: Young readers turning on 'CATCHER IN RYE'?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2019/aug/01/the-catcher-in-the-rye-fans-jd-salinger-holden-caulfield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JD Salinger’s Holden Caulfield once seemed the universal voice of teenage angst, but now he’s too quaint for young people. Can we learn to love it again, asks Dana Czapnik</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden memoir to reveal whistleblower's secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2019/aug/01/edward-snowden-memoir-to-reveal-whistleblowers-secrets-permanent-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man who helped build the US’s mass surveillance tech will recount how his work led him to make the biggest leak in history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This California town wants to be 2nd Amendment 'sanctuary' for guns, ammo...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-07-30/needles-second-amendment-sanctuary-california-town</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the coming months, Needles officials say they plan to work with state representatives on legislation that would exempt the city — and possibly other border towns — from rules on purchasing ammunition out of California and reciprocity with other states over concealed weapons permits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN: Panderfest...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/455700-mark-penn-democrats-debate-was-a-panderfest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When not pandering to gender, racial or ethnic groups with offers of cash, the candidates attacked each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE: To crush Trump, Michelle Obama needs to run...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/455702-michael-moore-urges-michelle-obama-to-run-against-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Michael Moore said in a new interview that there is only one candidate up to the challenge to “crush” President Trump in 2020, “and her last name rhymes with Obama.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX Pitcher Smashes TVs In Dugout After Rough Start...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/08/01/boston-red-sox-rick-porcello-dugout-tvs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rick Porcello wasn’t happy with his start Wednesday night against the Tampa Bay Rays. He took out his frustration on a pair of televisions in the Red Sox dugout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady set for 20th season: 'Hard to imagine doing anything else'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/patriots/2019/07/31/new-england-patriots-tom-brady-retirement-contract-bill-belichick/1878379001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just a few days shy of turning 42, Tom Brady addressed questions about retirement and his contract with the New England Patriots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic cockroach weighs 0.07 grams -- can withstand weight of human...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/robotic-cockroach-weighs-just-007g-18810982</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of California, Berekely have developed a tiny robot that measures just 3cm by 1.5cm, and weighs less than 0.07 grams</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists create fabric that smells better more you sweat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/scientists-create-fabric-that-smells-better-the-more-you-sweat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your gross workout gear could double as an air freshener.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once shrine to retailer's brand, 'flagships' lose luster...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6cb0379d61dc4cad983ffad5bc040555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Talking lasers' beam messages to ears...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/31/talking-lasers-that-beam-messages-to-our-ears-in-the-works-pentagon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hold on to your tinfoil hats, because there’s certainly a conspiracy theory a-brewin’ here. The Pentagon has confirmed it’s testing lasers that can talk. Huh? Weapons researchers …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 'Send her back!' chant, Ohio rally test for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/send-her-back-chant-ohio-042103341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's latest rally will be a test for both candidate and crowd. The Cincinnati gathering Thursday night will be Trump's first since his audience chanted "Send her back!" about a Somali-born congresswoman during a July rally in North Carolina , raising the prospect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>218,400 released into USA since December...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/ice-let-loose-218-400-migrant-family-members-into-the-us-since-december</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal Homeland Security agency tasked with removing people illegally present in the country has released a couple hundred thousand immigrant families into the interior of the United States since late December, according to data obtained by the Washington Examiner. Those let loose will not be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dating App Addiction Fueled By Loneliness, Social Anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cant-stop-swiping-dating-app-addiction-fueled-by-loneliness-and-social-anxiety-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dating apps like Tinder and Bumble have changed the way millions of people meet each other and make connections, but just like so many other aspects of digital life these apps have a tendency to become habit-forming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Bans Non-Patriotic TV Shows Ahead of 70th Anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3020970/no-period-dramas-or-pop-idols-chinese-censors-say-patriotic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broadcasters told content in August must be ‘appropriate for the whole environment’, while Sina TV survey of 783,000 people shows 39 per cent of viewers are unhappy with restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going to Burning Man? Don't Forget to Pack Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/01/fashion/masks-air-pollution-burning-man-dust.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As air quality becomes a bigger concern for consumers, demand for a practical yet playful accessory is growing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENEZUELA: Socialist 'Death Squads' Targeting Opposition Activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/08/01/venezuela-socialist-death-squads-targeting-opposition-activists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maduro dictatorship in Venezuela is stepping up the operations of "death squads" aimed at eliminating all opposition to the socialist regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Ebola Outbreak Is U.S. National Security Threat...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/congo-ebola-outbreak-isn-t-103010715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- In 2014, the U.S. led the effort by governments to blunt the world’s biggest outbreak of Ebola, which took more than 11,000 lives in West Africa before it was declared over in mid-2016. Now, a smaller but more complex outbreak rages in the Democratic Republic of Congo, and the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE: To crush Trump, Michelle Obama needs to run...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2019/08/01/msnbc-lets-michael-moore-rant-12-minutes-need-liberal-nominee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC on Tuesday night donated 12 minutes of air time to far-left filmmaker Michael Moore as the director demanded that Democrats nominate a very liberal nominee or risk losing. Of that time, six and a half minutes came totally uninterrupted as host Brian Williams just let Moore go on and on. As for a strategy, he declared, “Let's get out the Democratic base of young people, women, and people of color.” He warned Democrats: “The worst thing to do is to moderate, to go to the center, and to think that's how we're going to win. This is how we're going to lose.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first AI bar opens...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/worlds-first-ai-bar-opens-18810841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bar, called 5cc Harrild &amp; Sons, has enlisted the help of an artificial intelligence system to help the bartenders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns protesters with military video...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/hong-kong-protest-china-warns-slick-military-video-11772064</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG: China's military has released a slick propaganda video showing a drill of armed troops quelling a protest in Hong Kong, in a thinly ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was FBI informant in Florida?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7306597/Jeffrey-Epstein-got-sweetheart-plea-deal-FBI-informant-government-records-reveal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal investigation into the pedophile led by the  FBI was closed out on September 18, 2008 when Epstein 'provided information to the FBI as agreed upon' according to the case agent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALARM:  Biden repeatedly stumbles over words and stats...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/biden-stumbles-over-statistics-phrases-and-titles-in-2020-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden, 76, repeatedly stumbled over numbers and phrases throughout his second Democratic presidential primary appearance Wednesday night, at one point accidentally endorsing one of his primary rivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabbard vs. Harris: You Kept Prisoners Locked Up For Labor...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/07/31/gabbard_vs_harris_you_kept_prisoners_locked_up_for_labor_blocked_evidence_that_would_free_man_on_death_row.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Tulsi Gabbard takes on Sen. Kamala Harris over her prosecutorial record in California and her record on criminal justice reform, the death penalty, and the war on drugs during the second Democratic presidential debate in Detroit. SEN. KAMALA HARRIS: Now, I would like to also talk about this conversation about Eric Garner, because I, too, met with his mother. And one of the things that we've got to be clear about is that this president of the United States, Donald Trump, while he has been in office, has quietly been allowing the United States Department of Justice to shut down consent decrees, to stop pattern and practice investigations.  On that case, we also know that the... TAPPER: Thank you, Senator. HARRIS: ... Civil Rights Division -- this is important. The Civil Rights Division of the United States Department of Justice said charges should have been filed, but this United States Department of Justice usurped -- and I believe it is because that president did not want those charges to go forward. And they overrode a decision by the Civil Rights Division of the United States Department of Justice. TAPPER: Thank you, Senator. HARRIS: Under my administration, the Civil Rights Division... TAPPER: Thank you, Senator. HARRIS: ... will rein and there will be independent investigations.  TAPPER: Vice President Biden, Vice President Biden, I want to give you a chance to respond to what Senator Harris just said. BIDEN: When Senator Harris was attorney general for eight years in the state of California, there were two of the most segregated school districts in the country, in Los Angeles and in San Francisco.  And she did not -- I didn't see a single solitary time she brought a case against them to desegregate them. Secondly, she also was in a situation where she had a police department when she was there that in fact was abusing people's right. And the fact was that she in fact was told by her own people that her own staff that she should do something about and disclose to defense attorney's like me that you in fact have been -- the police officer did something that did not give you information of what (inaudible) your -- your client. She didn't do that. She never did it. And so what happened. Along came a federal judge and said enough, enough. And he freed 1,000 of these people. If you doubt me, google 1,000 prisoners freed, Kamala Harris. TAPPER: Thank you, Vice President Biden. Senator Harris, your response. HARRIS: That is -- is simply not true. And as attorney general of California where I ran the second largest Department of Justice in the United States, second only to the United States Department of Justice, I am proud of the work we did.  Work that has received national recognition for what has been the important work of reforming a criminal justice system and cleaning up the consequences of the bills that you passed when you were in the United States Senate for decades. It was the work of creating the -- one of the first in the nation initiatives around reentering former offenders and getting them jobs and counseling.  TAPPER: Thank you, Senator. HARRIS: I did the work as attorney general of putting body cameras on special agents in the state of California. (CROSSTALK) TAPPER: I want to bring in Congresswoman .... HARRIS: And I'm proud of that work. TAPPER: I want to bring in Congresswoman Gabbard. Congresswoman Gabbard, you took issue with Senator Harris confronting Vice President Biden at the last debate. You called it a quote, false accusation that Joe Biden is a racist. What's your response? GABBARD: I want to bring the conversation back to the broken criminal justice system that is disproportionately negatively impacting black and brown people all across this country today. Now Senator Harris says she's proud of her record as a prosecutor and that she'll be a prosecutor president. But I'm deeply concerned about this record. There are too many examples to cite but she put over 1,500 people in jail for marijuana violations and then laughed about it when she was asked if she ever smoked marijuana. (APPLAUSE) She blocked evidence -- she blocked evidence that would have freed an innocent man from death row until the courts forced her to do so. She kept people in prison beyond their sentences to use them as cheap labor for the state of California.  (APPLAUSE) And she fought to keep ... TAPPER: Thank you, Congresswoman. GABBARD: Bail system in place that impacts poor people in the worst kind of way. TAPPER: Thank you, Congresswoman. Senator Harris, your response? (APPLAUSE) HARRIS: As the elected attorney general of California, I did the work of significantly reforming the criminal justice system of a state of 40 million people, which became a national model for the work that needs to be done.  And I am proud of that work. And I am proud of making a decision to not just give fancy speeches or be in a legislative body and give speeches on the floor, but actually doing the work of being in the position to use the power that I had to reform a system that is badly in need of reform. That is why we created initiatives that were about reentering former offenders and getting them counseling. TAPPER: Thank you. HARRIS: It is why (ph) and because I know that criminal justice system is so broken ... TAPPER: Thank you, Senator. HARRIS: That I am an advocate for what we need to do to not only decriminalize, but legalize marijuana in the United States. (CROSSTALK) TAPPER: Thank you, Senator.  Your time is up. I want to -- I want to bring Congresswoman Gabbard back in. Your response, please (ph). GABBARD: The bottom line is, Senator Harris, when you were in a position to make a difference and an impact in these people's lives, you did not. And worse yet, in the case of those who were on death row, innocent people, you actually blocked evidence from being revealed that would have freed them until you were forced to do so. (APPLAUSE) There is no excuse for that and the people who suffered under your reign as prosecutor owe -- you owe them an apology. TAPPER: Senator Harris? (APPLAUSE) HARRIS: My entire career I have been opposed -- personally opposed to the death penalty and that has never changed. And I dare anybody who is in a position to make that decision, to face the people I have faced to say I will not seek the death penalty. That is my background, that is my work.  I am proud of it. I think you can judge people by when they are under fire and it's not about some fancy opinion on a stage but when they're in the position to actually make a decision, what do they do.  When I was in the position of having to decide whether or not to seek a death penalty on cases I prosecuted, I made a very difficult decision that was not popular to not seek the death penalty. History shows that and I am proud of those decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein's Plan to Seed Human Race With His DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jeffrey-epstein-hoped-to-seed-human-race-with-his-dna/ar-AAF8Mbq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Is he running for president of space?'</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/claudiakoerner/joe30330-biden-gave-out-wrong-website-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"is he running for president of space?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXELROD: THIS MAY BE BEST HE CAN DO...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/07/31/axelrod-bad-news-for-biden-is-this-may-be-the-best-he-could-do/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During CNN's coverage of Wednesday's CNN Democratic debate, CNN Senior Political Commentator David Axelrod stated that 2020 Democratic presidential | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A$AP Rocky takes stand in Sweden assault trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/us-rapper-aap-rocky-takes-stand-sweden-assault-trial-doc-1j82ie2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden blasts decriminalizing illegal immigration: 'It's a crime'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/31/joe-biden-blasts-decriminalizing-illegal-immigrati/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joseph R. Biden blasted fellow Democrats who want decriminalize illegally crossing the border, saying Wednesday it would be an invitation to a new surge of illegal immigration from across the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN SWINGS AND DUCKS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/second-democratic-debate-live-attack-tracker-july-31-2019-n1037606</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ll be tracking candidate attacks through the evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker Torches: You Destroyed Communities Like Mine...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/booker-stuns-audience-by-torching-biden-on-criminal-justice-reform-you-destroyed-communities-like-mine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a stunning multi-part exchange, Sen. Cory Booker (D-NJ) absolutely torched former Vice President Joe Biden on several different topics – including, notably, criminal justice. In a tense skirmish ea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTORS INTERRUPT DEBATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7308359/Protesters-hit-Dem-debate-Bill-Blasio-hit-Eric-Garner-Joe-Biden-hit-immigration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters were removed after they demanded Bill de Blasio fire Daniel Pantaleo, who put Eric Garner in a deadly chokehold, while another hit Joe Biden on immigration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early tech and mic problems plague...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/watch-tech-problems-plague-second-night-of-democratic-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The opening statements of the second night of the CNN Democratic presidential debate were plagued by technical problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala calls Biden 'senator' after he addressed her as 'kid'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/shade-kamala-harris-calls-joe-biden-senator-after-he-addressed-her-as-kid  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Joe Biden referred to her as "kid," California Sen. Kamala Harris repeatedly called the former vice president "senator" as they debated healthcare during the second night of presidential debates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penis frozen after death...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9629302/jeffrey-epstein-dna-baby-factory-ranch-penis-frozen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein wanted a baby-making factory to spread his DNA – and to have his penis frozen after his death, it was reported last night. The paedo billionaire, 66, confided in scientists th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New migration surge this fall?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/to-deter-migrants-trump-administration-builds-elaborate-scaffolding-at-the-border-and-on-the-books/ar-AAF847i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTORS INTERRUPT DEBATE...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/politics/news/cory-booker-democratic-debates-chanting-1203287621/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters confronted New York mayor Bill de Blasio Wednesday night during New Jersey Senator Cory Booker’s opening statement at CNN’s second round of democratic debates. The protesters…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  GOOGLE's celeb-obsessed search for climate change answers is hypocritical joke...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/31/googles-celeb-obsessed-search-for-climate-change-answers-is-a-hypocritical-joke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It doesn’t get more hypocritical than A-listers jetting in on private planes to bemoan climate change at Google’s private party in Sicily this week. The Gulfstreams, mega-yachts and gas-guzzling Ma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton says NKorea tests didn't violate pledge to Trump...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190801000507-d1jg7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/USA-BOLTON (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Bolton says N.Korea tests didn't violate pledge to Trump, but no word on talks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein's Plan to Seed Human Race With His DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/jeffrey-epstein-seed-dna-cryo-865841/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unnamed sources tell The New York Times about accused sex trafficker’s plan to have women inseminated with his sperm, birth his children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bin Laden's son dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/u-s-has-intel-osama-bin-laden-s-son-heir-n1037236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The officials would not provide details of how Hamza bin Laden died or if the U.S. played a role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT NIGHT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/democratic-debate-july-31-2019/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty Democratic presidential hopefuls will face off at the CNN primary debate in Detroit. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Less than half of students say US is most powerful country...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=13514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other countries topping the list included...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audience member assaults comedian during open mic show in San Francisco...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/assault/open-mic-assault-278593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A comedian at a small San Francisco venue was attacked by an audience member who was told to “stop talking” during the victim’s performance Saturday afternoon. As seen above, the July 27 assault was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany rejects US call to join Gulf taskforce...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/07/31/germany-rejects-us-call-join-gulf-taskforce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany has rejected US pressure to send warships to protect shipping in the Persian Gulf from seizure by Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military spent $33M on tech known to be vulnerable to Chinese cyberespionage...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1679475/dod-spent-30m-on-china-hackable-tech-from-lenovo-gopro-others/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The list includes computers banned for use by State Department employees since 2006.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome bans MCDONALD's from ancient site...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/mcdonalds-rome-ruins-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy's culture ministry has banned the McDonald's from building yet a restaurant in Rome near the ancient Baths of Caracalla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Binge Drinking Among Older Americans On Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/binge-drinking-older-americans-on-the-rise-new-study-finds-morning-rounds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People 65 and older are more sensitive to alcohol, which can exacerbate chronic health conditions or interfere with prescription medications</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big broadcasters sue non-profit that streams TV channels for free...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-usa-broadcasters-lawsuit/big-broadcasters-sue-non-profit-that-streams-tv-channels-for-free-idUKKCN1UQ2FT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four major U.S. television networks on Wednesday sued a non-profit group bac...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark History Behind Year's Bestselling Debut Novel...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/culture/2019/07/delia-owens-crawdads-murder-africa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few have made the connection between Where the Crawdads Sing and the story told in a 2010 New Yorker feature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can diet help cancer treatment? Study in mice offers clues...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/diet-help-cancer-treatment-study-mice-offers-clues-180127830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diet is already a key part of managing diseases like diabetes and hypertension, but new research adds to a growing body of evidence that it could help cancer treatment too. The study, published Thursday in the journal Nature, found restricting intake of an amino acid found in red meat and eggs significantly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein's Plan to Seed Human Race With His DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/31/business/jeffrey-epstein-eugenics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Epstein, the accused sex trafficker, was fascinated by eugenics. He told scientists and others of his vision of using his New Mexico ranch to impregnate women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Woodstock 50 canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/music/woodstock-50-embattled-anniversary-festival-officially-canceled-n1037331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are saddened that a series of unforeseen setbacks has made it impossible to put on the festival we imagined," said one of the key organizers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court files shed light on Kamala's awkward donation from Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/court-files-shed-light-on-kamalas-awkward-donation-from-donald-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris has a long record of political stances from her prosecutor days that don’t quite square with her current national profile as a liberal champion —but one of the most awkward items from her past may be her acceptance of a $5,000 donation from Donald Trump nearly a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Tlaib Donor Has Been Deceased for 10 Years...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/tlaib-donor-has-been-dead-for-10-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic representative Rashida Tlaib received a generous donation in the name of a man who died more than 10 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Costliest U.S. Warship Ever, Navy Can't Get Munitions on Deck...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-07-30/flawed-elevators-on-13-billion-carrier-miss-another-deadline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>107-Year-Old On Secret To Her Longevity: 'Never Got Married'...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/07/31/107-year-old-bronx-woman-gets-birthday-bash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louise Signore turns 107 Wednesday. They threw her a party was at the Bartow Community Center in Coop City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland cuts teen drinking with curfews, youth centers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/83d5e39462164327a861ba34dcb3752c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy fighter jet crashes; Search team dispatched to Death Valley...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/navy-f-a-18e-fighter-jet-crashes-in-inyo-county;-pilots-status-unknown/5433048/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A single-seat Navy fighter jet crashed Wednesday morning in Inyo County and the pilot's status was unknown, officials confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic-testing scam targets seniors...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/aging/genetic-testing-scam-targets-seniors-rips-medicare-n1037186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Capitalizing on the growing popularity of genetic testing, scammers are persuading seniors to hand over their DNA, not knowing it may lead to identity theft and Medicare fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half House Dems now support impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df43f187ef524e9a9f168b251b4687a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATIMES' disappointing digital numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.niemanlab.org/2019/07/the-l-a-times-disappointing-digital-numbers-show-the-games-not-just-about-drawing-in-subscribers-its-about-keeping-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.niemanlab.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We will all benefit if the Los Angeles Times becomes a West Coast counterweight to those dailies in New York and D.C. But it'll take a bigger investment in reader retention to get there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Ring Alerts Tying Up Police With False Alarms; Videos Of People In Innocent Act...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/amazon-ring-alerts-often-tie-up-police-with-false-alarms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are inundated with video of people just going about their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly unearthed audio...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/reagan-made-racist-remarks-taped-conversation-nixon-153701802.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then-California governor Ronald Reagan made racist remarks about Africans, calling them "monkeys" in a newly-discovered taped conversation with US president Richard Nixon. The tape of the October 1971 phone call was unearthed by Tim Naftali, former director of the Richard Nixon Presidential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skydiver Knocked Unconscious After Colliding Mid-Air With Other Skydiver!</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/07/30/ottawa-skydiver-collision-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was an incredible, and safe, return to earth Tuesday after a scary collision between two skydivers in LaSalle County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil inmates 'suffocated' during transfer after jail riot...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/brazil-inmates-suffocated-during-transfer-jail-riot-155356113--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four inmates involved in one of Brazil's deadliest prison riots suffocated while being transferred to another jail, officials said Wednesday, taking to 62 the number killed over two days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  It's cheating to have sex with robot...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/millennials-dating-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials are apparently holding off on dating, because it's too expensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP  'PSYCHIC FORCE' IN AMERICA</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/marianne-williamson-trump-emboldening-a-dark-psychic-force-in-america </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marianne Williamson warned her fellow 2020 Democratic presidential candidates to stop focusing on the details of policies and put more effort into defeating the “dark psychic force” that is President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Marie Presley to 'tell all' on Michael Jackson in explosive book...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9623020/michael-jacksons-secrets-lisa-marie-presley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LISA Marie Presley is writing a book that will reveal the most explosive secrets about her marriage to Michael Jackson, it has been reported. The only daughter of Elvis Presley has signed a deal wo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein Trial Will Have 'Million Pages' of Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-trial-will-have-a-million-pages-of-evidence-lawyers-tell-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say it will include materials found on devices seized from the financier's Manhattan mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILLIAMSON WARNS OF 'DARK DAYS' FOR DEMS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/marianne-williamson-gets-rapturous-applause-for-denouncing-trumps-dark-psychic-force-of-collectivized-hatred/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marianne Williamson got rapturous applause from the crowd when she brought up race issues numerous times during the Democratic debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT CAMERA READY:  Mayor Pete Smudge on Head Was Smushed Bug!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/gross-mayor-pete-reveals-weird-smudge-on-his-head-during-debate-was-a-smushed-bug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 presidential candidate Mayor Pete Buttigieg guessed that a weird smudge on his forehead during the Democratic debate was probably a bug he squished and didn't wipe off his head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Hollywood Agent Ari Emanuel Buying $35M Bel Air Mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/ari-emanuel-buying-35m-mansion-bel-air-1227892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say the 58-year-old Endeavor CEO is purchasing the seven-bedroom, five-bathroom Fredericks residence on Chalon Road that was once the home of billionaire David Murdock and, before that, Mossimo Giannulli and wife Lori Loughlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW SUMMER SLUMP IN RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2019/07/30/msnbcs-rachel-maddow-slips-to-5th-place-in-july-ratings/#52dfa08760a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, Donald Trump's favorite morning show, Fox &amp; Friends, pushed CNN's New Day to its lowest ratings in five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mysterious bright objects appear over Area 51...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/795262/Area-51-mystery-bright-object-appear-over-base-twice-two-days-Nevada-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual guru most-searched candidate during debate; Wins DRUDGE Poll...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7304065/Marianne-Williamson-searched-candidate-Google-tops-Drudge-Report-poll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-help author Marianne Williamson and nine other presidential hopefuls fought to stand out over the course of the three-hour showdown on Tuesday night in Detroit, Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILLIAMSON: 'Violent Video Games' Make World Hate America...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/07/31/marianne-williamsons-foreign-policy-violent-video-games-make-world-hate-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Violent video games" have played a role in anti-American violence, Marianne Williamson claims on her website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rides stream of consciousness to spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/188b537760cd45cb8521a8324744eee9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Experimenting With Augmented Reality Art Installations...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/07/apple-augmented-reality-art-installation-new-museum-nick-cave-pipilotti-rist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company is using the allure of big-name artists to get as many of its customers as possible engaging with AR technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems call for more than $200 trillion in spending...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/analysis-dem-candidates-call-for-more-than-200-trillion-in-spending/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic candidates for the 2020 nomination have promised more than $210 trillion in new spending, analysis by the Washington Free Beacon shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'West Side Story', 'Fiddler', 'Phantom'... MORE </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/07/harold-prince-dies-broadway-legend-produced-original-west-side-story-fiddler-phantom-more-1202657794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harold Prince, the Broadway icon who produced or directed some of the 20th century’s most famous musicals West Side Story, Fiddler on the Roof, Damn Yankees, Cabaret, Evita and The Phantom of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B'WAY LEGEND HAL PRINCE DEAD AT 91...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0b6998e352984b2d85e8cb021fd554f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow Ratings Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/07/31/nolte-russia-hoax-queen-rachel-maddows-ratings-crash-to-fifth-place-in-july/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in nearly a year, Russia Hoax Queen Rachel Maddow has failed to finish in the top three shows among cable news viewers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
