<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Daring clandestine op to crack El Chapo encrypted comms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/08/nyregion/el-chapo-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cristian Rodriguez was hired by the Sinaloa drug cartel to create a secure encrypted communications network. Then he helped the F.B.I. break into it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: City living giving animals cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6569765/City-life-giving-animals-CANCER.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big polluted cities such as New York and London increase the likelihood that animals will get cancer. Birds, squirrels, rats, mice and hedgehogs are some of the affected wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL FIGHT GOES PRIME TIME!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cb9df4c458e647db9866ffa4c0db1fa2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump made a televised plea for border wall funding Tuesday night, seeking an edge in the shutdown battle with congressional Democrats as he declared there is "a humanitarian crisis, a crisis of the heart and a crisis of the soul." Addressing the nation from the Oval Office for the first time, Trump argued for funding on security and humanitarian grounds as he sought to put pressure on newly empowered Democrats amid an extended partial government shutdown. Trump called on Democrats to return to the White House to meet with him, saying it was "immoral" for "politicians to do nothing."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police serve warrant for male staff DNA samples where vegetative patient gave birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.azfamily.com/news/investigations/hacienda_healthcare/phoenix-pd-obtain-dna-samples-from-hacienda-healthcare-staff-week/article_cba20c0c-13a3-11e9-85a3-e396464e906c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azfamily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hacienda HealthCare confirmed the search warrant for DNA samples Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact widens on 18th day of govt shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-shutdown-departments-factbox/factbox-impact-on-us-government-widens-on-18th-day-of-shutdown-idUSKCN1P22AB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shutdown of about a quarter of the U.S. government reached its 18th day on Tue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Deficit Climbs Again, On Track for $1,000,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/08/us/politics/budget-deficit-trillion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporate tax receipts are falling and federal spending is rising. More revenue from tariffs isn’t enough to bridge the gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese middle class buying up US residential real estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/08/chinese-middle-class-buying-up-american-residential-real-estate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese consumers have been the top foreign buyers in both units and dollar volume of residential housing for six years straight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How author uncovered secret plot to kill George Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/brad-meltzer-new-book-the-first-conspiracy-plot-to-kill-george-washington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best-selling author details an effort to undermine the American Revolution just before the signing of the Declaration of Independence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sealed v Sealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/18/sealed-v-sealed-robert-mueller-mysterious-case-subpoena</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretive dispute over subpoena revealed to concern an unnamed corporation, but many questions remain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey claims alleged victim lied about age, welcomed flirtation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-ent-kevin-spacey-says-victim-lied-about-age-20190108-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey claims his alleged sex assault victim lied about his age and encouraged a mutual flirtation, according to a Nantucket District Court filing obtained by the Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Penny Found in Child's Lunch Money Could Auction for $1.7M...</title>
      <link>https://www.geek.com/culture/rare-penny-found-in-boys-lunch-money-could-fetch-up-to-1-7-million-in-auction-1768904/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare 1943 copper Lincoln cent — found by a Massachusetts teenager in his change after he paid for lunch at a school cafeteria — is expected to fetch up to $1.7 million when …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama warns drivers not to stop and eat chicken tenders spilled on highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/nation-world/national/article224080395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Alabama Emergency Management Agency issued a hazard warning this week, telling people not to eat hundreds of chicken tenders spilled across a state highway. It happened Sunday in Cherokee County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Journalist Jailed for 'Paradise Papers' Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.icij.org/investigations/paradise-papers/turkish-journalist-sentenced-to-prison-over-paradise-papers-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.icij.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Istanbul court has sentenced ICIJ member Pelin Ünker to imprisonment for 13 months after being found to have defamed her nation’s former prime minister and two of his sons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB scores record revenue as attendance dips, player salaries fall...</title>
      <link>https://mlb.nbcsports.com/2019/01/07/a-warning-about-major-league-baseballs-record-revenues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mlb.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Making money is a good thing, but Major League Baseball’s gravy train seems unsustainable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home security cam catches prowler licking doorbell for 3 HOURS...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/video-prowler-spends-3-hours-licking-doorbell-at-ca-home/5033951/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are trying to track down a man who spent three hours licking a doorbell at a California home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Undecided on Emergency Declaration for Border... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-undecided-on-emergency-declaration-for-border-wall-officials-say-11546959778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump isn’t expected to declare a national emergency at the southern border when he addresses the nation Tuesday night about his request for funding for his long-promised wall along the U.S.-Mexico boundary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Psychiatrist Can See Your Child Now, Virtually...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-psychiatrist-can-see-your-child-now-virtually-11546877610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a growing shortage of psychiatrists and other mental-health professionals for children and adolescents, more health-care providers are turning to technology to fill the gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court declines to intervene in mysterious Mueller subpoena fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/08/supreme-court-declines-to-intervene-in-mysterious-mueller-subpoena-fight-1088050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court declined to intervene in a fight apparently involving a foreign-government-owned company and the special counsel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Americans Warm to Facial Recognition Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/01/survey-americans-warming-use-facial-recognition-tech/153987/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans do not favor strict limits on facial recognition technology, according to a new national survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin brothers both serving prison time for separate killings...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-twin-brothers-prison-sentences-evanston-20190107-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominic Connerly was sentenced for the fatal shooting of an Evanston man to 15 years in prison. Connerly's twin brother Darien is already in prison on a murder conviction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple CEO confident of prospects despite naysayers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/apple-ceo-confident-prospects-despite-naysayers-192510373.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Apple nudged higher on Tuesday after Chief Executive Tim Cook touted the company's technology pipeline and characterized worries about the company's future as overwrought. Cook, in an interview with CNBC just six days after a sales warning sent shares skidding, highlighted a "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Dems identify as liberals for first time...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/245813/leans-conservative-liberals-keep-recent-gains.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's ideological balance held steady in 2018, with conservatives and moderates each at 35% and liberals remaining at last year's record high, 26%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Workers Start Driving For UBER, LYFT...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/01/08/federal-workers-going-to-work-for-lyft-uber-during-government-shutdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The partial government shutdown is wreaking havoc on the ride-sharing industry, especially in the nation's capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt shutdown starting to affect air travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b0034bf33e214cd6b6a85ae1c23bdcaf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — The partial government shutdown is starting to affect air travel. Over the weekend, some airports had long lines at checkpoints, apparently caused by a rising number of security officers calling in sick as they face the prospect of missing their first paycheck this week. Safety inspectors aren't even on the job. A Federal Aviation Administration spokesman said Monday that inspectors are being called back to work on a case-by-case basis, with a priority put on inspecting airline fleets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PM May defeated in parliament, lawmakers create new obstacle to no-deal Brexit...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190108190607-wbrpf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/NODEAL (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-UK PM May defeated in parliament, lawmakers create new obstacle to no-deal Brexit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May defeated in parliament... </title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-nodeal/may-defeated-in-parliament-mps-create-new-obstacle-to-no-deal-brexit-idUSKCN1P21BD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May's government suffered a defeat in parlia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT REDACTIONS REVEALED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6570217/Paul-Manafort-shared-campaign-polling-data-Russian-spy-ran-Trumps-White-House-bid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Donald Trump campaign chair Paul Manafort sent campaign polling data to an alleged Russian spy in the midst of the 2016 campaign, an incorrectly redacted document reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMSUNG users shocked: Can't delete FACEBOOK app...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-08/samsung-phone-users-get-a-shock-they-can-t-delete-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractor driver levels ATM in heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/washingtoncounty/2019/01/tractor-driver-levels-wells-fargo-atm-in-hillsboro-heist-police-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver and a second person, who had been waiting in a U-Haul van, stole an undetermined amount of cash, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexa awkwardly interrupts tech exec during demo...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-amazon-alexa-awkwardly-interrupts-tech-executive-20190108-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It seems as if Amazon’s Alexa actually has a mind of its own, after the device awkwardly interrupted a tech executive at a press conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers: Manafort suffers from depression, anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/608b9fcbca5941348e2ac8796e94c8cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort is suffering from depression and anxiety and is at times confined to a wheelchair because of gout. That's according to a court filing from defense lawyers Tuesday responding to allegations that Manafort has repeatedly lied to special counsel Robert Mueller's team of investigators. Manafort's lawyers say he was awakened before dawn on the days he was interviewed and normally spent the entire day talking with investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN! Heathrow flights grounded after drone spotted...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8149197/heathrow-airport-flights-grounded-after-drone-spotted-over-runway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEATHROW Airport flights have been grounded amid reports of a drone sighting today just weeks after the chaotic Gatwick shutdown. The airport has said they have stopped departures while they invest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst measles outbreak in decades sweeps New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6569129/Worst-measles-outbreak-decades-sweeps-New-York-cases-surge-Oregon-Washington-abroad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 160 cases of measles have been reported in New York with most spreading among unvaccinated religious communities. Measles outbreaks have cropped up in over 20 US states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-felons begin registering to vote in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0086670a6df42c9a3d2857d1606e027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The right to vote was restored for most Florida felons as of Tuesday, increasing the pool of eligible voters by as many as 1.4 million people in a battleground state infamous for its narrow margins in key elections. The Florida Rights Restoration Coalition planned to get people together over breakfast before registering online or going to their local election supervisors' offices to fill out the forms. "We are encouraging our members to celebrate," said organization's president, Desmond Meade. "Our members are going into the supervisor of elections with their loved ones. And that is very key— with their loved ones— because we really want to highlight that concept of love."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor who called Orlando massacre victims 'scum' ousted over prostitution allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/fort-worth/2019/01/08/fort-worth-pastor-called-orlando-massacre-victims-scum-earth-ousted-prostitution-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fort Worth pastor known for praising the Pulse nightclub shooting and condemning the victims will be replaced Sunday, after accusations that he'd...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside FACEBOOK 'cult-like' workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/08/facebook-culture-cult-performance-review-process-blamed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Facebook employees detailed how the company's leadership and performance review system have created a "go along" culture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Facility CEO resigns after woman in vegetative state gives birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bill-timmons-hacienda-healthcare-ceo-nursing-facility-vegetative-woman-gave-birth-resigns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Timmons quit days after baby was born to woman patient in vegetative state; CBS affiliate reports claim that he covered up prior incident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Denies Making Secret Overtures to Tehran...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/trump-admin-denies-making-secret-overtures-to-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Tuesday denied claims by senior Iranian officials that the United States has been making secret overtures to Tehran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian attorney charged with obstruction of justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/russian-attorney-natalia-veselnitskaya-charged-with-obstruction-of-justice-in-us-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian attorney Natalia Veselnitskaya, who was at the center of a controversial 2016 Trump Tower meeting, was charged in federal court on Tuesday with obstruction of justice in connection to a civil money laundering and forfeiture case involving a Russian tax refund fraud scheme, first uncovered by the late Sergei Magnitsky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Teen Girl Violent MCDONALD'S Rampage After Asked To Leave Kids' Play Area...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/07/video-teens-allegedly-start-violent-melee-in-inland-empire-mcdonalds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teenage girls were caught on camera hurling heavy objects at McDonald's employees in Moreno Valley after being asked to leave a children's play area – causing thousand dollars worth of damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networks to carry Pelosi, Schumer rebuttal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9f3362c235dd47f6ac0ae580ae7265e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and the partial government shutdown (all times local): 10:55 a.m. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer will give the Democratic response to President Donald Trump's remarks to the nation Tuesday on his proposed wall on the U.S.-Mexico border. An impasse over wall funding has led to a partial government shutdown, now in its third week. Pelosi and Schumer have flatly refused to pay for the wall. They said Tuesday they will deliver their response to Trump after his address at 9 p.m. EST. Trump says there is a security crisis at the U.S.-Mexico border that can be addressed only by spending $5.7 billion on a wall as a way to prevent people from crossing into the U.S. illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's the Rush? Power of Slow Morning...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/whats-the-rush-the-power-of-a-slow-morning-11546958541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an antidote to our tech-obsessed society, slow-morning practitioners wake up early to meditate, read, exercise or do nothing at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Digisexuals' ditch dating; Turn to sex dolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7962025/sex-dolls-better-than-real-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUNGING on a sofa in a leather corset and holding a can of beer, Kristal is Nick’s perfect woman.   So she should be, as the truck driver forked out over £6,000 on the silicone sex doll, who…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC MAYOR GUARANTEES HEALTH CARE FOR ALL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/NYC-Health-Care-Guarantee-Mayor-de-Blasio-504046171.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will begin guaranteeing comprehensive health care to every single resident regardless of someone's ability to pay or immigration status, an unprecedented plan that will protect the more than half a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Death Rates 25-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64439-cancer-death-25-year-low.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. cancer death rates have declined continuously for the last quarter of a century, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharpshooting all-female squad hunts poachers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/the-brave-ones-zimbabwe-domestic-violence-survivors-trained-sharpshooters-hunt-poachers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abused and disadvantaged women have become Zimbabwe's hidden weapon against poachers who kill elephants and rhinos for their tusks and horns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students hate Trump's immigration quotes, don't realize they're Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;See their reactions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: GINSBURG MISSES SECOND DAY AT SUPREME COURT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/424287-ginsburg-misses-second-day-in-a-row-at-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was absent from the Supreme Court bench for the second day in a row on Tuesday.Chief Justice John Roberts noted Ginsburg’s absence when the justices took their seats for the second time in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery shrouds Manafort case...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/424281-mystery-shrouds-manafort-case-as-attorneys-appear-to-miss-key</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for President Trump’s former campaign chairman Paul Manafort appear to have missed a court-ordered deadline to reply to special counsel Robert Mueller’s accusations that Manafort breached a plea agreement by lying to federal pr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networks plan to carry rebuttal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/424290-networks-plan-to-carry-dem-response-to-trump-primetime-address</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most major broadcast networks indicated Tuesday they plan to carry the Democratic response to President Trump's primetime address from the Oval Office on the partial government shutdown and the situation at the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,500-a-month doggy daycare prompts growls in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jan/08/dog-daycare-san-francisco-doggy-style</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doggy Style, whose top-tier membership requires $7,500 fee, sparks backlash amid housing crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Confused' 86-year-old beat husband to death with cane...</title>
      <link>https://www.pnj.com/story/news/2019/01/07/police-86-year-old-florida-woman-beat-husband-death-walking-cane/2501771002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pnj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 86-year-old woman has been arrested on suspicion of murder for allegedly beating her 89-year-old husband to death with a walking cane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS OVAL OFFICE ADDRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cb9df4c458e647db9866ffa4c0db1fa2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump will argue to the nation Tuesday night that a "crisis" at the U.S.-Mexico border requires the long and invulnerable wall he's demanding before ending a partial government shutdown that has hundreds of thousands of federal workers fearing missed paychecks on Friday. Trump's first Oval Office speech will be followed by a Thursday visit to the southern border to highlight his demand for a barrier. White House press secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders tweeted that he will "meet with those on the front lines of the national security and humanitarian crisis."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron facing mountain of challenges in new year...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0984f26a923e445287cf59b64f9f43da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French President Emmanuel Macron is facing a mountain of challenges in the new year — starting with yellow vest protesters who are back in the streets to show their anger against high taxes and his pro-business policies that they see as favoring the wealthy rather than the working class. Once Europe's rising star, Macron is now fighting to save his image and his vision for transforming France's welfare state and economic model. Here's a look at three major issues he will need to tackle in 2019: YELLOW VEST CRISIS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Most Democrats identify as liberals for first time...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/424280-most-democrats-identify-as-liberals-for-first-time-gallup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Democrats now identify as liberal rather than moderate or conservative, a Gallup poll released Tuesday found, marking the first time since the polling giant began asking the question in the 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELTDOWN: Woman flips out at airport, calls JETBLUE worker 'rapist'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/08/woman-flips-out-at-airport-calls-jetblue-worker-a-rapist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This irate woman screamed until she was JetBlue in the face — but she still wasn’t allowed to board her flight. Viral video posted Monday on Instagram shows the unnamed passenger hurling insults an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Teacher Smears Feces On Tables, Grills At Principal's Party...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/01/07/florida-teacher-human-feces-principals-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida substitute teacher is accused of spreading human feces on tables and grills at a park where a principal was set to host a birthday party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone uncomfortable legal limbo persists...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-adviser-roger-stone-uncomfortable-legal-limbo-persists/story?id=60220161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the waning weeks of 2018, longtime GOP operative Roger Stone told reporters he believed he could be indicted and become the next target of Robert Mueller's probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS said to ask bankruptcy judge to liquidate... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sears-bankruptcy-liquidation-exclusiv/exclusive-sears-to-ask-bankruptcy-judge-to-liquidate-sources-idUSKCN1P218J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears Holdings Corp will ask a bankruptcy judge on Tuesday if it can proceed wit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.4 MAG QUAKE STRIKES OFF JAPAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-japan-earthquake-large-64-13828696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquake was 24 miles deep and centred 116km south southeast of Kagoshima in Japan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nude restaurant closes after 15 months due to lack of customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6568949/Pariss-NAKED-restaurant-closes-15-months-lack-customers.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'naturel, which opened in November 2017 with the promise of a discreet Parisien dining room where guests eat naked, will close in February this year after failing to attract customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family says US Navy veteran held for months in Iranian prison...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/424272-family-says-us-navy-veteran-has-been-held-for-months-in-iranian-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of a U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science races against tick-borne virus...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-01-science-tick-borne-virus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two groundbreaking discoveries by USC researchers could lead to medications and a vaccine to treat or prevent a hemorrhagic fever transmitted by a new tick species before it spreads across the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect, 20, held over massive politician data hack...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/suspect-20-held-over-massive-german-politician-data-084921899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police said Tuesday they have arrested a 20-year-old suspect in the case of private data stolen from hundreds of politicians, including Chancellor Angela Merkel, and published online. "The prosecutor's office in Frankfurt, the Central Office for Fighting Internet and Computer Crime and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warehouses Test New Breed of AI Robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/warehouses-test-a-new-breed-of-ai-robots-11546948800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Logistics providers and retailers are using mobile robots to cut down on the number of steps workers take, and deploying AI-aided mechanical arms for more nuanced tasks long deemed possible only for human hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HYUNDAI reveals WALKING car...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/hyundai-reveals-walking-car-concept-13827385</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hyundai believes the car could one day be used by first responders in response to natural disasters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Positive thinking key to healthy old age...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6565563/Is-key-happiness-married.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at University College London questioned more than 7,000 people aged 50 to 90 on how meaningful they felt their life was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Patriarch Warns 'Antichrist' Will Control Humans Through Gadgets...</title>
      <link>https://themoscowtimes.com/news/russian-patriarch-warns-antichrist-will-control-humans-through-gadgets-64060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview, Patriarch Kirill warned against “falling into slavery” to smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kevin Spacey went from megastar to pariah in just over year...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/01/07/how-kevin-spacey-went-from-megastar-to-pariah-in-just-over-a-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just four years ago, Kevin Spacey was standing onstage at the Golden Globes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right leader severely beaten in 'assassination attempt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8142936/german-far-right-leader-severely-injured-after-being-beaten-in-assassination-attempt/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FAR-right German politician has been brutally attacked in an “attempted assassination.” Frank Magnitz, chairman of Germany’s AfD party, was left with a gaping wound in his head after being knocke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't Afford to Lose...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-cant-afford-to-lose-11546909031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of defeat would be higher for President Trump than for Speaker Pelosi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown Weighs on Federal Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/shutdown-weighs-on-federal-workers-11546906831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many federal employees, the uncertainty and stress of the government shutdown is building into a sense of helplessness as they face the prospect of missing their first full paycheck on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMSUNG Echoes APPLE's Gloomy Outlook as Tech Woes Get Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/samsung-electronics-profit-outlook-surprisingly-weak-11546909783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samsung Electronics expects its fourth-quarter operating profit will decline 29%, surprise guidance that fell far below analysts’ estimates and the latest sign of challenges hitting the tech industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMERGENCY DECLARATION?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ap-explains-trump-emergency-build-wall-010333900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is weighing using a national emergency declaration to circumvent Congress and the budget stalemate and force construction of the president's long-promised southern border wall. "We're looking at a national emergency because we have a national emergency," President</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
