<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest person record stood for decades. Then came conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-world-s-oldest-person-record-stood-for-13528896.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The email came just hours into the new year, landing in the inboxes of the two renowned French gerontologists who had validated the age of the oldest person ever documented in the modern world. Also copied was the consultant who analyzed age-related cases for the Guinness World Records, which had given Jeanne Calment the title before she died at 122 in 1997. "Colleagues, take action, take evidence for verification," read the email, from the account of Russian doctor Valery Novoselov, continuing in cryptically rendered English. "Otherwise, there will be many people who will want to participate in this show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Bezos Shared Wife's Pillow Talk With Mistress, Boasted About U2 Bono...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalenquirer.com/celebrity/jeff-bezos-shared-wifes-pillow-talk-with-mistress-lauren-sanchez/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalenquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RANDY tech tycoon Jeff Bezos shared bedroom talk with his long-suffering WIFE to his MISTRESS — as the suspecting spouse began to question him about their affair. In another blockbuster text messag...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINTER WALLOP!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-01-11-winter-storm-gia-impacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the latest impacts from Winter Storm Gia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest protests hit with police water cannon, tear gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests/renewed-yellow-vest-protests-hit-with-police-water-cannon-tear-gas-in-paris-idUSKCN1P60GX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris police fired water cannon and tear gas to push back "yellow vest"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Serial predator': LA writer sounding alarm on Dem donor for year...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/serial-predator-l-writer-has-been-sounding-alarm-ed-buck-n957776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long before a second man died in the political donor's home, writer Jasmyne Cannick has been publishing accounts from his alleged victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hi, I'm Tom Brady': How 41-year-old QB relates to teammates...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Hi-I-m-Tom-Brady-How-the-Patriots-13528788.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. - Phillip Dorsett sat on a table inside the New England Patriots' training room, having just completed the physical that made him an official member of the franchise. Just then, one of his new teammates entered the room and walked straight toward him. "Hi," the teammate said. "I'm Tom Brady." "I'm like, I know who you are," Dorsett said this week, laughing. "You don't have to introduce yourself." Dorsett, a wide receiver, is like almost every other Patriot. As Brady was winning Super Bowls and becoming an international celebrity, Dorsett was growing up. He was 9 when Brady won his first Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castro launches...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/julian-castro-announcement-2020-white-house-bid-candidate-for-president-today-views-stance-issues-age-live-updates-01-12-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 44-year-old former HUD secretary formed a presidential exploratory committee in December</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Sickouts Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/rate-of-tsa-sickouts-rises-as-u-s-government-shutdown-drags-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rate of TSA Sickouts Rises as U.S. Government Shutdown Drags on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In states, Dems start delivering on health care pledges...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bd8bb50ed7f7457fa560f8c1ae718eb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Riding the momentum from November's elections, Democratic leaders in the states are wasting no time delivering on their biggest campaign promise — to expand access to health care and make it more affordable. The first full week of state legislative sessions and swearings-in for governors saw a flurry of proposals. In his initial actions, newly elected California Gov. Gavin Newsom announced plans to expand Medicaid to those in the country illegally up to age 26, implement a mandate that everyone buy insurance or face a fine, and consolidate the state's prescription drug purchases in the hope that it will dramatically lower costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUT LONGEST EVER</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b3867898a78740f39d8cc8538c5db196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The partial government shutdown became the longest closure in U.S. history when the clock ticked past midnight into early Saturday as President Donald Trump and nervous Republicans scrambled to find a way out of the mess. A solution couldn't come soon enough for federal workers who got pay statements Friday but no pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology brings images of Holocaust survivors to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9fcf828b8d454169b7ebea8819ddbaed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Max Glauben was 17 and had already lost his mother, father and brother at the hands of the Nazis when U.S. troops rescued him while he was on a death march from one German concentration camp to another. The recollections of the Dallas resident who as a Jew in Poland survived the Warsaw Ghetto and Nazi concentration camps are now being preserved in a way that will allow generations to come to ask his image questions. Glauben, who turns 91 on Monday, is the latest Holocaust survivor recorded in such a way by the University of Southern California Shoah Foundation . The Los Angeles-based foundation has recorded 18 interactive testimonies with Holocaust survivors over the last several years, and executive director Stephen Smith says they're in a "race against time" as they work to add more, seeking both a diversity in experiences and testimonies in a variety of languages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Superbug shows concerning mutation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/health/sd-no-pseudomonas-update-20190111-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention issued a travel warning this week, notifying the public that 11 Americans who traveled to Tijuana hospitals for weight-loss surgery had become infected with drug-resistant infections during their stays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb film star dog cloned...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/753111/china-celebrity-dog-juice-cloned-cloning-experiment-pets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: Kevin Hart Film Set To Be Studio's First No. 1 Opener...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/kevin-hart-the-upside-aquaman-keanu-reeves-replicas-dogs-way-home-weekend-box-office-1202533526/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4TH UPDATE, Saturday AM Writethrue after Friday 11:39PM: In a slow weekend, STXfilms is reaping the box office spoils with The Upside on course to make $19.2M, which would rep the studio’s fi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Antigovernment Protesters March for Ninth Straight Weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/french-antigovernment-protesters-march-for-ninth-straight-weekend-11547303859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the ninth consecutive Saturday, thousands of protesters clad in yellow reflective vests gathered in French cities in what is becoming a weekly test of the momentum of their antigovernment movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Slagging 2019:  Dirt Thrown Against 'GREEN BOOK,' Others Worse Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/01/11/oscar-slagging-2019-dirt-thrown-against-green-book-other-films-is-carefully-orchestrated-and-not-a-coincidence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past when something ugly was uncovered about an Oscar movie, people pointed to Harvey Weinstein as the culprit. But this season, Haevey is really out of the race and the dirt being dug up an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington State Wants to Stop Theft of Mile 420 Signs. Its Solution? Mile 419.9...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/state-battles-theft-of-69-and-420-mile-marker-signs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state Department of Transportation has replaced some mile-marker signs with the numbers 68.9 or 419.9, or removed mileposts 69 and 420 altogether, to combat thefts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil says it recognizes Venezuelan opposition leader as president...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190112140040-1djls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-VENEZUELA:Brazil says it recognizes Venezuelan opposition leader as president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campus police want students to report acts of 'bias'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/red-alert-politics/campus-police-want-students-to-report-acts-of-bias</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media posts from the University of Illinois campus police are encouraging students to report “acts of intolerance” to the school’s Bias Assessment and Response Team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephants evolving to lose tusks following decades of poaching?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/11/elephants-evolving-lose-tusks-following-decades-ivory-poaching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a development that would have delighted Darwin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third Of Americans Can't Name All Four Grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/family-tree-history-third-americans-cant-name-all-grandparents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How much do you know about your family tree? For many folks, it's not very much. A recent survey finds that a third of Americans can't even name all four of their grandparents, incredibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA: 'Apocalypse asteroid' that could strike Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/753130/nasa-asteroid-bennu-photo-space-mission-planetary-defence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Gas blast' in Paris kills two firefighters; Dozens injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46849633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emergency services were responding to a gas leak when a "dramatic explosion" took place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Will Be First-Ever To Officiate NFL Playoff Game...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/01/11/sarah-thomas-nfl-history-inspiring-female-football-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Thomas will be the first woman to officiate an NFL playoff game. Among all the eyes sure to be on her – a special group of supporters – her fellow female football officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCHES/WARNINGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/wundermap/?isPresentationActive=0&amp;renderer=2&amp;Units=english&amp;zoom=5&amp;lat=37.80307138624724&amp;lon=-90.50826873347978&amp;wxstn=0&amp;wxstnmode=tw&amp;radar=0&amp;radaropa=0.7&amp;satellite=0&amp;satelliteopa=0.8&amp;insertHurricaneNameHere=false&amp;goes16opa=&amp;severe=1&amp;severeopa=0.9&amp;sst=0&amp;sstopa=0.8&amp;sstanom=0&amp;sstanomopa=0.8&amp;cam=0&amp;fronts=0&amp;hur=0&amp;models=0&amp;modelsmodel=ecmwf&amp;modelsopa=0.8&amp;modelstype=SURPRE&amp;lightning=0&amp;fire=0&amp;fireopa=0.9&amp;rep=0&amp;surge=0&amp;tor=0&amp;windstr=0&amp;windstrDensity=undefined&amp;windstreamSpeed=undefined&amp;windstreamSpeedFilter=undefined</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thief breaks into two State Dept buildings, steals phones... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/thief-breaks-into-two-state-department-buildings-steals-phones/2019/01/11/5fc1d67c-15e0-11e9-b6ad-9cfd62dbb0a8_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thief slipped into two buildings, one in the District and one in Arlington County, and made away with dozens of cellphones, but all were recovered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge gives extension to secret grand jury... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fbi-opened-probe-whether-trump-working-russians-031122996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Bureau of Investigation opened an inquiry in 2017 into whether US President Donald Trump was working on behalf of Russia, The New York Times reported on Friday. The investigation -- a dual counterintelligence and criminal probe -- was launched after the president fired FBI director James</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>http://images.intellicast.com/WxImages/Radar/usa.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;images.intellicast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother of American Jailed in Iran Pleads for His Release...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/american-man-jailed-in-iran-has-life-threatening-cancer-mother-says-11547254320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Navy veteran who has been jailed in Iran on undisclosed charges suffers from cancer and may die without access to medical care, according to his mother, who pleaded for his release in a statement on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Internet censors turn attention to rest of world...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612638/when-chinese-hackers-declared-war-on-the-rest-of-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many thought the internet would bring democracy to China. Instead it empowered rampant government oppression, and now the censors are turning their attention to the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brits to vote again? Brexit delay creates headache for Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-election/brits-to-vote-again-brexit-delay-creates-headache-for-europe-idUSKCN1P51TT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brexit paralysis has prompted talk of a British election or a second referendum ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Briton who knocked Liberia offline with cyber attack jailed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-46840461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Kaye attacked an African mobile phone company, inadvertently taking Liberia offline in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widely cited study of fake news retracted by researchers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/11/widely-cited-study-of-fake-news-retracted-by-researchers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, a study was published in the Journal of Human Behavior, explaining why fake news goes viral on social media. The study itself went viral, being covered by dozens of news outlets. But now…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France vows tough response as new 'yellow vest' demos loom...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-vows-tough-response-yellow-vest-demos-loom-021748280.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France braced for a fresh round of "yellow vest" protests across the country on Saturday, with the authorities vowing zero tolerance for violence after weekly scenes of rioting and vandalism in Paris and other cities over the past two months. Armoured vehicles and 5,000 officers will be deployed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much longer can Mitch McConnell sit it out?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/government-shutdown-how-much-longer-can-mitch-mcconnell-sit-it-out/ar-BBS7HQA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Opened Inquiry Into Whether Trump Was Secretly Working on Behalf of Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/fbi-opened-inquiry-into-whether-trump-was-secretly-working-on-behalf-of-russia/ar-BBS83LZ?fdhead=newflex-views</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border security workers miss paychecks because of shutdown over border security...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-border-shutdown-paychecks-20190111-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of federal employees on the front lines of border security — Border Patrol agents, Coast Guard crews, and immigration judges — missed paychecks Friday because of the partial government shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez mocks aging Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6581851/New-party-dis-Ocasio-Cortez-mocks-aging-Joe-Liberman-hoping-shes-not-future.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Who dis?' is a response to a text message from an unknown number. Among millennials, the phrase has morphed into a snarky tool for rejecting someone by framing their approach as a mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC says it's another severe flu season with 7 million sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/11/cdc-about-7-million-have-been-sick-with-the-flu-so-far-this-season.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the numbers are milder than last season, the CDC's "influenza like illness level" last week was elevated at 4.1 percent, almost twice national baseline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster snowstorm to blanket more than half of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/major-snowstorm-to-snarl-travel-from-st-louis-to-cincinnati-this-weekend/70007114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump stops short of emergency declaration in wall fight...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190111204933-xn1b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Trump stops short of emergency declaration in border wall fight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City pipeline hit by 'sabotage' amid crackdown on fuel theft...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190111203201-aakvw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-OIL/THEFT:Mexico City pipeline hit by 'sabotage' amid crackdown on fuel theft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New calf seen among Puget Sound's critically endangered killer whales...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environment/new-orca-calf-spotted-among-puget-sounds-critically-endangered-killer-whales/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The J, K and L pods have not had a successful pregnancy in three years. Scientists caution the new calf might not survive, meeting the same fate as other recent calves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TULSI GABBARD: I'M IN...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/11/tulsi-gabbard-2020-president-run-1098629</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I have decided to run and will be making a formal announcement within the next week,” she said during an interview on CNN's &amp;quot;The Van Jones Show.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castro looks to regain spotlight he once enjoyed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/01/11/julian-castro-launches-presidential-bid-texas-democrat-looks-regain-spotlight-enjoyed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Castro's keynote speech at the 2012 Democratic National Convention was a potential star-making appearance designed in part to catapult the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't like Elizabeth Warren? She wants to know why...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2019/01/11/don-like-elizabeth-warren-here-how-you-can-tell-her-how-you-feel/rVe35RsVT0RE5AmXJXPQPP/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren’s presidential exploratory committee’s website includes a questionnaire for visitors to say why they don’t support her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet opioid prescriptions soar. But who's really using meds?</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/health/opioids-pets-veterinary-medicine-abuse-20190111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We found that the increased quantity of opioids prescribed by our hospital was not due to increased patient volume alone,” said study author Dana Clarke, an assistant professor at the vet school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIRD tries to forcibly remove story detailing how to hack, keep e-scooters...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/1/11/18179004/bird-scooters-boing-story-removal-report-hacking-copyright</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The story described a way to modify scooters through a cheap conversion kit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generates images of finished meal -- based off recipe ingredients...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/tel-aviv-ai-generates-food-pictures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitaltrends.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feeling hungry? Researchers from Tel-Aviv University in Israel have created an A.I. that's able to generate complete photos of meals, based only on reading the written recipes. Here's how it works and which meals the system finds easier or harder to generate accurately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded seals cause town chaos: Crying out, block roads and driveways...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-newfoundland-town-asks-for-help-as-stranded-seals-cause-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seals have been blocking roads, driveways and doors and residents are unable to move them because it is illegal to touch marine mammals, mayor of Roddickton says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman can't hear men's voices due to rare condition...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Woman-can-t-hear-men-with-deep-voices-due-to-rare-13526385.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman in China is making headlines for a rare type of temporary hearing condition that makes her unable to hear low frequencies, such as men's voices. According to the Daily Mail, the patient, only identified as Ms. Chen, woke up one morning and couldn't hear her boyfriend speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling forced marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/19e43295c76d4d249aa51c9f643eb377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Thousands of requests by men to bring in child and adolescent brides to live in the United States were approved over the past decade, according to government data obtained by The Associated Press. In one case, a 49-year-old man applied for admission for a 15-year-old girl. The approvals are legal: The Immigration and Nationality Act does not set minimum age requirements for the person making the request or for that person's spouse or fiancee. By contrast, to bring in a parent from overseas, a petitioner has to be at least 21 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over last decade, US govt granted 5,556 requests to bring child brides...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/11/us-immigration-child-brides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Government is not only complicit; they're stamping this and saying: Go ahead'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NYTIMES editor not happy with reporters' punditry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ddbbc16111d432887c1dde7d127e0af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Former New York Times editor Jill Abramson takes a dim view of many of the appearances that reporters at her former newspaper and The Washington Post make on cable networks to talk about President Donald Trump. "I really think that all the cable appearances on panels, particularly on CNN and MSNBC, are a huge mistake," she said. Abramson, editor of the Times from 2011 to 2014, spoke to reporters Friday before the publication of her book on the media, "Merchants of Truth."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane carrying FL Gov. makes emergency landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/florida/plane-carrying-gov-ron-desantis-makes-emergency-landing-in-st-pete/1697928039</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plane carrying Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis was forced to make an emergency landing in St. Petersburg Friday afternoon, according to the governor's spokesman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Honeytrap' who lured TV exec to grisly death now married to rising Labour star...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6581917/Honeytrap-beauty-lured-TV-exec-death-MAYORESS-four-years-jail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mundill Mahil, who lured an infatuated Sikh TV executive to his grisly death, is to become a mayoress just four years after leaving prison after her husband was made mayor elect of Redbridge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Biker gang forced to give up trademarked logo... </title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/01/11/o-c-federal-jury-orders-mongols-motorcycle-club-to-forfeit-logo-trademarks-following-racketeering-conviction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal jury on Friday decided an outlaw motorcycle club should be stripped of the trademarks it holds on its coveted logo as punishment in a racketeering case, delivering a victory to the U.S. government in its unusual legal fight to dismantle the notorious organization. Last month, at the end of a lengthy trial, a jury in Santa Ana convicted the Mongols motorcycle club of racketeering and conspiracy charges, finding the group shared responsibility for several violent acts and drug crimes committed by individual Mongol members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA starts withdrawing supplies, but not troops, from Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a8b9ccfc02984818b12ad4bfe7bbe395</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. military said Friday it has started pulling equipment, but not troops, out of Syria as a first step in meeting President Donald Trump's demand for a complete military withdrawal. The announcement fueled concern about how quickly the U.S. will abandon its Kurdish allies, amid contradictory statements recently by administration officials on an exit timetable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>101-Year-Old Man Secret To Longevity: Daily COORS LIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/01/10/coors-light-golden-brewery-andrew-slavonic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man says the secret to his longevity is enjoying a Coors Light beer every day. Andrew Slavonic should know, he's 101 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$0 PAY STUBS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d95c567185f4592b4a6e59fa9317f7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OGDEN, Utah (AP) — Federal workers received pay stubs Friday with nothing but zeroes on them as the effects of the government shutdown hit home, deepening anxieties about mortgage payments and unpaid bills. All told, an estimated 800,000 government employees missed their paychecks for first time since the shutdown began three weeks ago. Fuming employees posted pictures of the $0 pay stubs on Twitter and vented their frustration as the standoff entered its 21st day. This weekend, it will become the longest shutdown in U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
