<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Top Chinese scientist demands WHO probe USA lab for leak!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2365701/world-health-organization-us-weapons-lab-covid-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE World Health Organization should probe a US bioweapons lab for allegedly “leaking Covid”, a leading Chinese scientist has claimed. Zeng Guang, a chief epidemiologist at the Chinese …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Too Much Coffee Bad For Heart; Filtered, Instant Brews Best...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/too-much-coffee-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over six cups of coffee each day contributes to more lipids (fat) building up in the blood. The more you drink, the worse it gets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Springsteen Arrest Report Includes 24 Pages Held Back by Dept. of Interior 'Pending Trial'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/02/18/exclusive-bruce-springsteen-arrest-report-includes-24-pages-held-back-by-dept-of-interior-pending-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE What is the government hiding about Bruce Springsteen’s arrest? And whatever it is, could it help his case? I filed a Freedom of Information Act request with the Department of the I…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.2 mag quake felt in Kansas City...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article249368090.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was felt 270 miles away in Kansas City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Hyped-up flu or a fatal pandemic?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/coronavirus-a-hyped-up-flu-or-a-fatal-pandemic-659400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please keep safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty Grocery Store Shelves Add To Hopelessness...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/18/dfw-area-store-shelves-empty-winter-storms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I know it’s unnerving for customers when they come in the store and it doesn’t look like the grocery store they know and love,” said a spokesperson for Tom Thumb and Albertsons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: LUCKY HE DID NOT TO DIE OF COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2366281/fauci-says-trump-lucky-survive-covid-his-age-weight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump was “lucky” to survive the coronavirus given his age and weight, Dr Anthony Fauci said of the former president this week. The nation’s leading infectious disease expe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIFE MOANED HOME WAS FEEEZING... 
'Anyone want to leave?'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2364018/ted-cruz-wife-freezing-ritz-carlton-cancun-texts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REPUBLICAN Senator Ted Cruz has admitted his Cancun getaway was a “mistake” as texts revealed his wife wanted to flee “freezing” Texas. After dashing to a luxury resort in M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN CURRENCY FIRST TO GO DIGITAL?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2362406/russia-currency-digital-ruble/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA could become the first country to make its entire currency digital, as cryptocurrency booms.  Discussions are underway about the launch of the digital ruble with local banks and the cou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power grid was 'seconds and minutes' from total failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/18/texas-power-outages-ercot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials with the Electric Reliability Council of Texas said that grid operators implemented blackouts to avoid a catastrophic failure that could have left Texans in the dark for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Quite Possibly Wonderful Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-quite-possibly-wonderful-summer/ar-BB1dPuUF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Families will gather. Restaurants will reopen. People will travel. The pandemic may feel like it’s behind us—even if it’s not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Two women dress as 'grannies' to jump line...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2021/02/18/young-florida-women-dressed-as-grannies-to-get-coronavirus-vaccine-and-it-worked/#//</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With bonnets on their heads and bespectacled faces, two young women pretended to be grannies so they could get the coronavirus vaccine, and it seems their rouse may have actually worked at least one time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 MINS:  JUSTICE SONIA SOTOMAYOR WAS TARGETED BY GUNMAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/esther-salas-sonia-sotomayor-60-minutes-2021-02-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. District Judge Esther Salas says the FBI found evidence the man who killed her son targeted Supreme Court Justice Sonia Sotomayor. 60 Minutes reports, Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-President's Return to Spotlight Lands With a Ripple...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/trumps-grand-return-to-the-spotlight-makes-a-ripple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump ascended to the presidency thanks, in no small part, to his ability to relentlessly dominate headlines and consume news cycles. His opinions on matters of foreign policy, the birthplace of presidents, and the cosmetic surgeries of cable news hosts were deemed urgently newsworthy by the national press for half a decade. When Trump […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Democracy under assault'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/biden-acknowledge-democracy-stress-us-restore-place-global/story?id=75982189</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will aim to restore the United States' place as a world leader, the official said, following four years of President Donald Trump in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faced with cold, music professor slept with 330-year-old violin to protect it...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/arts-entertainment/performing-arts/2021/02/19/faced-with-the-cold-smu-music-professor-slept-with-his-330-year-old-violin-to-protect-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As his Plano thermostat dropped below 50, the owner of a precious instrument was forced to get creative in caring for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Profane anti-Biden flag causing controversy in Connecticut, around nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/news/connecticut/hc-news-ct-anti-biden-flag-20210219-hynyidazsvezreqpzp67pn4zxy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flags flying outside two homes in the Terryville section of Plymouth proclaim in stark -- and some have complained, vulgar and inappropriate language -- the residents’ rejection of the November election results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CADBURY under fire for same-sex kiss in new Creme Egg commercial...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/19/petition-targets-same-sex-kiss-in-new-cadbury-egg-commercial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who wants chocolate?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half state without water...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210219135408-fv8ak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Nearly half of all Texans without water even as 'fragile' power grid returns to life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATER WOES GROW IN TEX</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/power-texas-water-shortage-south-b1cad8589083d0f6c79020ef642995d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Many of the millions of Texans who lost power for days after a deadly winter blast overwhelmed the electric grid now have it back, but the crisis was far from over in parts of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AOC raises $1 million for relief, plans trip to Houston...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/539550-ocasio-cortez-raises-1-million-for-texas-relief-plans-trip-to-houston</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Quite Possibly Wonderful Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2021/02/summer-2021-pandemic/618088/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Families will gather. Restaurants will reopen. People will travel. The pandemic may feel like it’s behind us—even if it’s not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bullying, screaming': In Albany, Cuomo wields phone as weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/19/andrew-cuomo-phone-bullying-screaming-470025</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many describe receiving angry calls late in the evening and being unable to get off the phone with New York’s most powerful official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnetic catastrophe 'that wiped out Neanderthals' due to happen again, scientists warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/14097356/magnetic-pole-flip-killed-neanderthals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DISASTROUS collapse of the Earth’s magnetic field wiped out the Neanderthals and could happen again, according to a new study. Researchers say the event left Earth exposed to burning cosmic radia…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The TESLA Mafia: Musk's Ex-Employees Vie To Become His Top Rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2021/02/19/the-tesla-mafia-elon-musks-ex-employees-vie-to-become-his-top-rival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk hasn't simply revolutionized the electric vehicle market — he's created his own billion-dollar rivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: Will helicopter fly on Red Planet?</title>
      <link>https://www.inverse.com/science/theres-now-a-helicopter-on-mars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inverse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's Perseverance rover landed on Mars along with the Ingenuity helicopter, which is set to make the first test flight on another planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA rover lands on Mars in mission to search for past life...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/NASA-s-Mars-rover-Perseverance-poised-for-bull-s-15960073.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's rover Perseverance landed safely Thursday on Mars to begin an ambitious mission to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-old boy dies of hypothermia in mobile home...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/An-11-year-old-boy-died-in-an-unheated-Texas-15962627.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though he was still in bed after 2 p.m. on Tuesday under a pile of blankets in their unheated mobile home in Conroe, Texas, Maria Elisa Pineda wasn't concerned when she checked on her son. After all, Cristian Pavon, 11, was known for sleeping in, his mother told Univision.  But when Pineda nudged the boy, Cristian did not respond to her touch.  It was too late by then. Cristian was pronounced dead that afternoon, and authorities are investigating whether the otherwise healthy boy died of hypothermia after the family's home lost power over the weekend and temperatures in Conroe dipped to single digits earlier this week.  "He was OK," Pineda told Univision. "I never imagined this could happen. We think it was because of the cold because he was doing well. He had dinner, played and he went to bed."  Cristian is among the youngest to die since Sunday, when winter storms left millions without electricity and water. So far, at least 47 people have died in the frigid cold weather, a figure authorities say is likely to rise as freezing temperatures continue and future wellness checks reveal the full magnitude of the tragedy.  At least 30 of those deaths came in Texas, The Washington Post reported, a state where continuous power outages have exposed residents to dangerously low temperatures. Some have died of carbon monoxide poisoning after turning to their ovens or trucks to stay warm. Others, like a 75-year-old man in Crosby, Texas,whose oxygen machine stopped working after his home lost power, have been found dead of hypothermia inside their homes or cars.  Cristian, who was born in the coastal city of Tela, Honduras, came to Texas in 2019 to reunite with his mother, who he had not seen for over a year, Univision reported.  On Monday, he saw snow for the first time after the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy crises stretches to 7th day...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcentv.com/article/news/local/texas-residents-cling-to-hope-as-deep-freeze-continues/500-56f8a0d0-04db-4d03-bc39-02ccdfc46f69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcentv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 30,000 Central Texans are still in the dark on Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD LOW TEMPS ON WAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/19/weather/texas-winter-storm-friday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Texas begins restoring power after a devastating week of freezing temperatures and winter storms, the state is confronting a new crisis: overwhelmed water systems that could extend misery for much of the population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain Hoped Catalonia's Separatists Would Fade. They're Gaining Ground...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/19/spain-hoped-catalonias-separatists-would-fade-theyre-gaining-ground/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID — For years, Spain’s government dismissed the separatist movement in the Catalonia region as little more than a “soufflé”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill would allow U.S. news publishers to team up when negotiating with FACEBOOK, GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-media-facebook-us-exclusive-idUSKBN2AJ16X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bipartisan members of Congress plan to introduce a bill in coming weeks to make it easier for smaller news organizations to negotiate with Big Tech platforms, said Rep. Ken Buck, the top Republican on the House Judiciary Committee's antitrust panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry and Meghan stripped of Royal titles and won't return to any duties...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14099414/meghan-markle-prince-harry-quit-royal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN Markle and Prince Harry have officially quit the Royal Family with the Duke stripped of his military titles, Buckingham Palace announced today. The Queen today said she was “saddened&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. Sheriff's Department Investigating Marilyn Manson Abuse Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/la-sheriffs-department-investigate-marilyn-manson-abuse-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non, merci: French village rejects Musk and his satellite internet antenna...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210219-non-merci-french-village-rejects-elon-musk-and-his-satellite-internet-antenna</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To realise his dream of satellite-powered internet, tech billionaire Elon Musk needs to install antennas around the world. In northern France, a village hopes he’ll decide to keep those antennas far…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Capitol cops suspended for alleged roles in riot; 29 investigated...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/18/politics/capitol-police-officers-suspended/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six US Capitol Police officers have been suspended with pay, and 29 others have been placed under investigation, for their actions in the January 6 riot, a department spokesman said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates live alongside stagnant urine and feces-filled toilets...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Texas-inmates-stuck-with-clogged-toilets-15962538.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a winter storm sent Texas spiraling into crisis with widespread power outages, a lack...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One night in Cancun: Ted's disastrous decision to go on vacation during storm crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/One-night-in-Cancun-Ted-Cruz-s-disastrous-15962524.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Usually, it takes at least one full day in Cancun to do something...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready to Meet With Iran...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-says-u-must-lift-094022475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Iran said the U.S. must first return to the 2015 nuclear deal and lift sanctions if it wants to start talks with the Islamic Republic, appearing to snub an effort by the Biden administration to begin direct discussions before officially rejoining the accord.The “key sequence” for nuclear talks between the Iran and U.S. is commitment, action then a meeting, Iranian Foreign Ministry spokesman Saeed Khatibzadeh said in a tweet on Friday.The reaction -- and a similar comment from Iran’s foreign minister -- highlighted the challenges in ending an impasse that has threatened to tip the Persian Gulf region into a new conflict in the years since former President Donald Trump exited the 2015 deal and reimposed sanctions.On Thursday, the Biden administration said it would be willing to meet with Iran to discuss a “diplomatic way forward” in efforts to return to the nuclear deal, a first step toward easing tensions.“The United States would accept an invitation from the European Union High Representative to attend a meeting of the P5+1 and Iran to discuss a diplomatic way forward on Iran’s nuclear program,” State Department spokesman Ned Price said in a statement. The P5+1 refers to the participants in the nuclear deal with Iran: China, Russia, France, the U.K., the U.S and Germany.Biden also lifted travel restrictions on Iranian enjoys and reversed a Trump-era claim that the U.S. had reimposed -- or “snapped back” -- United Nations sanctions on Iran, according to a letter sent to the UN Security Council and seen by Bloomberg.U.S. Says It’s Willing to Meet With Iran to Restore Nuclear DealThe offer is a politically risky effort by President Joe Biden to move beyond the standoff after the slew of U.S. sanctions cratered Iran’s economy and infuriated other world leaders, who argued that the accord and the inspections regime it created had reined in Tehran’s nuclear program.European parties to the nuclear deal welcomed the U.S. overture. Kremlin spokesman Dmitry Peskov told reporters on a conference call Friday that Russia has “repeatedly reaffirmed its commitment” to the nuclear pact.While a turn away from a policy of sanctions is “by itself” a good thing, “it is the restoration of the JCPOA regime that is important,” Peskov said, using a formal abbreviation for the accord.The U.S. offer to hold talks was aimed at restoring a diplomatic pathway with Iran, which has been gradually abandoning its commitments under the nuclear deal in response to the Trump administration’s “maximum pressure” sanctions campaign.U.S. and European officials are particularly alarmed by Iran’s decision to stop letting the International Atomic Energy Agency conduct snap inspections by suspending the so-called Additional Protocol from Feb. 23.But politics loom large on both sides. The Biden administration doesn’t want to be seen as offering too much to Tehran and risk getting burned if an agreement can’t be reached.President Hassan Rouhani wants to save the accord and his legacy before he leaves office later this year, but he’s determined not to cave into U.S. demands. His hardline opponents -- who control most of Iran’s powerful state institutions and are likely to dominate June’s presidential elections -- oppose any engagement with the U.S. and want closer ties with Russia.(Updates with background on Iran and additional Biden measures; Kremlin reaction.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen interviewed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210219004853-5vxwu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/INVESTIGATION-COHEN (PIX):Trump’s former fixer Cohen interviewed by Manhattan DA’s office and newly hired litigator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lighter days of CNN's Cuomo Brothers show long gone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-nursing-homes-andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-pandemic-chris-cuomo-096f81a0e4456a8f8ddb866d96d424b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Some television shows age much better than others. For CNN, last spring's prime-time banter between Chris Cuomo and his older brother, New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, looks worse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK makes power move in Australia -- and may regret it...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lawsuits-australia-mark-zuckerberg-e0b545d3ba541c2de8389c6bd0a6f23f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Facebook has been in a defensive crouch amid a slew of privacy scandals, antitrust lawsuits and charges that it was letting hate speech and extremism destroy democracy. Early Thursday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two young women in Florida 'dressed up as grannies' to get jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/two-young-women-in-florida-dressed-up-as-grannies-to-get-vaccinated-health-official-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The women, both younger than 45, wore bonnets, gloves and glasses to disguise themselves as older than 65, the age cut-off to be prioritized to get the coronavirus vaccine in Florida. They were in line for their second dose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TED ON THE ROPES...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/19/texas-storm-response-cruz-abbott-perry-470109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The swaggering, Texas brand of free-market governance that’s central to the state’s political identity is taking a beating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins have similar personality traits to humans, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/dolphins-have-similar-personality-traits-to-humans-study-finds/ar-BB1dPn0a </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to Ditch 'America First' in Appeal for Global Partnership...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-to-ditch-e2-80-98america-first-e2-80-99-in-appeal-for-global-partnership/ar-BB1dPbxH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will re-introduce himself and the U.S. to world leaders at a pair of international conferences on Friday, calling on industrialized democracies to partner in confronting the pandemic and climate change in a sharp departure from his predecessor’s foreign policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone's Here': Microstate Unlikely Hub for YOUTUBE Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/everyone-s-here-microstate-is-unlikely-hub-for-youtube-stars/ar-BB1dPii8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tiny, isolated nation in the Pyrenees is turning into a creative hub for some of Spain’s biggest social media stars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She used to be agent. Now one of Border Patrol's loudest critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/she-used-to-be-an-agent-now-she-is-one-of-border-patrols-loudest-critics/article_34d07bbf-a337-55e4-8122-e8078ad863b1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — The migrant girl was around 6 years old, dehydrated, fluish and despondent. Her head looked too big for her body — a sign of malnutrition — and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese fighters buzz Taiwan air zone as it appoints new defense minister...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210219100552-nm4rb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/SECURITY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Chinese fighters buzz Taiwan's air zone as it appoints new defence minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Nears $1 Trillion Value as Crypto Jump Tops Other Assets...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-nears-1-trillion-value-055731771.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin is closing in on a market value of $1 trillion, a surge that’s helping cryptocurrency returns far outstrip the performance of more traditional assets like stocks and gold.The largest token has added more than $415 billion of value in 2021 to about $956 billion, data compiled by Bloomberg show. The Bloomberg Galaxy Crypto Index, which includes Bitcoin and four other coins, has more than doubled.Speculators, corporate treasurers and institutional investors are thought to have stoked Bitcoin’s volatile ascent. Crypto believers are dueling with skeptics for the dominant narrative around the climb: the former see an asset being embraced for its ability to hedge risks such as inflation, while the latter sense a precarious mania riding atop waves of monetary and fiscal stimulus.FOMO -- fear of missing out -- may be at play, said Shane Oliver, head of investment strategy with AMP Capital Investors Ltd. in Sydney, adding that “in times of easy money this gets magnified and it’s partly what’s driving the current interest.”Bitcoin traded at around $51,300 as of 1:30 p.m. on Friday in Hong Kong after quintupling in the past year. The crypto index’s performance towers over stocks, gold, commodities and bonds in 2021.This month, Tesla Inc. disclosed a $1.5 billion investment and MicroStrategy Inc. boosted a sale of convertible bonds to $900 million to buy even more of the token. That brought the coin closer to corporate America.“If companies’ fundamentals are going to become closely tied to movements in Bitcoin because they’ve suddenly become speculators on the side, we’re going to be in bubble territory before you know it,” said Craig Erlam, senior market analyst with Oanda Europe Ltd.Tesla Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk posted a somewhat cryptic tweet Friday that appeared in part to defend the company’s action, saying Bitcoin “is simply a less dumb form of liquidity than cash” while adding that the electric vehicle maker’s decision isn’t “directly reflective of my opinion.”Read More: Musk Defends Tesla Bitcoin Move, Says Token Less Dumb Than CashThe “long Bitcoin” trade is seen as among the most crowded in the world alongside technology exposure and dollar shorts, according to the February edition of Bank of America’s global fund manager survey.AMP’s Oliver said if Bitcoin “falls out of favor -- for example due to government regulation or investors just moving on to the next new thing -- then it could quickly plunge.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They left family poodle Snowflake behind!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9276959/Ted-Cruz-LEFT-family-poodle-named-Snowflake-fled-frigid-Texas-resort-Cancun.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snowflake, the Cruz family poodle, was left behind when they left Houston on Wednesday afternoon. The house, Ted Cruz said, was without heat and in the 30s. Cruz returned 24 hours later, chastened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICAL STORM WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Texas-Democrats-call-for-Cruz-to-resign-after-15960036.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Sen. Ted Cruz was met with a wave of fury Thursday on his return to Houston...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter storm confronts Biden with early leadership test...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Amid-winter-storm-Biden-seeks-to-showcase-15961142.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden has quickly approved states of emergency in Texas,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REGRETS CANCUN TRIP...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9273075/Ted-Cruz-jets-Cancun-millions-Texas-remain-without-power.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ted Cruz on Thursday evening landed back in Houston, after a one-night trip to Cancun made while 3.4 million Texans were still without electricity. He insisted it was to drop off his daughters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancun jaunt 'so bizarre'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/02/18/ted-cruz-knows-politics-is-theater-thats-why-his-cancun-jaunt-is-so-bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People want to know their leaders care about them. A quick trip to Mexico communicates the opposite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More hospitals evacuate patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox4news.com/news/beleaguered-texas-hospitals-with-no-water-evacuate-patients-amid-winter-storm-power-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox4news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some hospitals in Texas were dealing with water shortages, loss of heat and have even been forced to evacuate patients following a deadly blast of winter weather this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC cidery unveils 'Cruz in Cancun' cocktail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/539442-dc-cidery-unveils-cruz-in-cancun-cocktail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Sen. Ted Cruz (R) already has a cocktail named after his widely criticized trip to Cancun amid the deadly winter weather crisis in his home state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy crises stretches to sixth day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218045837-xi4om</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/TEXAS-ENERGY (PIX, GRAPHIC):Texas energy freeze stretches to sixth day, raises Mexico's ire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATER WOES GROW IN TEX</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/texas-power-outages-icy-weather-186cf801ead7e2d21f001a99b3aaa936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Power was restored to more homes and businesses Thursday in states hit by a deadly blast of winter that overwhelmed the electrical grid and left millions shivering in the cold...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian tourists bribed airport screener with $3,000 to bypass protocols...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/hawaiian-tourists-bribed-an-airport-screener-with-243000-to-bypass-covid-19-protocols-police-say/ar-BB1dO5zO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two travelers from Louisiana were booked, released and flown back to the mainland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go-it-alone state rattled by failure to keep lights on...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/texas-the-go-it-alone-state-is-rattled-by-the-failure-to-keep-the-lights-on/ar-BB1dNYgi?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political leaders in Texas prize what they see as the state’s self-reliance, its go-it-alone ethos, and its cheap power – all of which they regard as related. The independence of the power sector may not last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas man freezes to death in recliner...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/texas-man-reportedly-freezes-to-death-in-his-recliner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Texas suffered through days of power outages, a man reportedly froze to death in his recliner with his wife clinging to life beside him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK CUT SHORT:  Cruz arrives back in Texas with armed police escort...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/18/sen-ted-cruz-arrives-back-in-texas-with-armed-police-escort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz touched down in Texas on Thursday afternoon with an armed police escort amid outrage over his 24-hour trip to Mexico during a catastrophic storm in the Lone Star State. The Repub…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest at Bay Area church that flouted public health orders dies of covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/priest-bay-area-catholic-church-180500539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sts. Peter and Paul Church closed its doors after a coronavirus outbreak sickened three priests and three caregivers. One of the priests has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Ready to Meet With Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2021-02-18/biden-administration-ready-to-meet-with-iran</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement regarding Tehran’s nuclear program offers the first clues on how President Joe Biden will address one of the thorniest foreign policy problems he faces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOREIGN COUNTRIES MOCK...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-02-18/an-ordinary-country-with-serious-shortcomings-us-foes-blast-deadly-texas-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration should spend more time trying to take care of its own citizens in Texas and elsewhere than denouncing other countries, one report published in China suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He repeatedly slammed OTHER politicians for vacationing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/18/politics/vacationing-during-crisis-ted-cruz/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Sen. Ted Cruz, who is facing backlash for traveling to Mexico as a winter disaster ravages his home state, has repeatedly criticized politicians who vacationed or took part in leisure activities during times of crisis, a CNN KFile review finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA on verge of decriminalizing psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/new-california-bill-would-decriminalize-psychedelics-expunge-criminal-records-n1258261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The war on drugs has been a complete failure," state Sen. Scott Wiener said. "It hasn't stopped people from using drugs and it hasn’t stopped addiction."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD roasted...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/under-fire-robinhood-ceo-apologizes-congress-restricting-trading-n1258285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Americans feel the system is stacked and, no matter what, Wall Street wins,” said Maxine Waters, Chairwoman of the House Committee on Financial Services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plumber Receives 2,200 Calls In 24 Hours!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/17/texas-plumber-calls-24-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many North Texans are feeling the effects of the deep freeze, with bursting pipes and floods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>53% Of People Kiss Their Dog More Than Their Partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-owners-risk-lives-for-pets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over half of married dog owners admit to kissing their hound more than their partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era for exploration...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/18/nasa-perserverance-mars-rove-landing-469771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perseverance begins a series of missions over the next decade to pave the way for humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top French TV presenter named in rape complaint...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/top-french-tv-presenter-named-195856970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of France's most famous television presenters Patrick Poivre d'Arvor is the subject of a rape investigation, prosecutors told AFP on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA Recruits Top Prosecutor for The Don Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/18/manhattan-d-a-recruits-top-prosecutor-for-trump-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Manhattan district attorney’s office steps up the criminal investigation of Donald J. Trump, it has reached outside its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia and China ready to sign deal to build first moon base...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/14089099/russia-china-sign-historic-deal-build-first-moon-base/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA and China are joining forces as they prepare to sign a historic deal to build the first moon base after they snubbed the US. The two countries are to collaborate on the international lunar s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell admitted Epstein DID have tapes of Trump, Clintons...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9270769/Ghislaine-Maxwell-admitted-Jeffrey-Epstein-DID-tapes-Donald-Trump-Clintons-2016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell appeared to admit Jeffrey Epstein was taping his famous friends, including Donald Trump and the Clintons, during a 2016 meeting with former CBS producer Ira Rosen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mr. Kitty' goes virtually to Washington...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-social-media-fee89914ac530675c0017a485b6aa8ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social media movement that made a beloved icon of GameStop enthusiast Keith Gill continued to rally behind the YouTube personality known as Roaring Kitty as he testified to Congress on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands reportedly attempt to obtain easily forged vaccinated certificate...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/thousands-reportedly-attempt-to-obtain-easily-forged-vaccinated-certificate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Green Pass' uses a simple QR code to store inoculation status and personal information; Health Ministry says it will fine those with fake documents, issue more secure ones soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC guidance would keep 90% of schools at least partially closed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/18/cdcs-classroom-guidance-would-keep-90percent-of-schools-at-least-partially-closed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new guidance would keep more than 90% of schools, including in almost all of the 50 largest counties in the country, from fully reopening, doctors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones' natural gas company 'hits jackpot'...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/02/17/texas-freeze-allows-jerry-jones-natural-gas-company-to-hit-jackpot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 4 million Texans have had no power during the historic winter weather experienced by the state this week. As of Wednesday night, 7 million in the state had water issues with either boil notices or no water at all. Fingers are pointing. Pipes are bursting. Homes are flooding. Grocery store shelves are [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax at Vatican? You might lose your job...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/italy-coronavirus-pandemic-rome-pope-francis-europe-f3214bfe787e783f8779d3f0fa9edfe8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican is taking Pope Francis’ pro-vaccine stance very seriously: Any Vatican employee who refuses to get a coronavirus shot without a valid medical reason risks being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames his kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/18/ted-cruz-cancun-power-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First spotted at an airport by a social media user who posted his photo, there was an immediate outcry overnight that a U.S. senator would travel out of the state amid the worst storm in many Texans' lifetimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Dems scramble to fight Newsom recall, close ranks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/18/california-democrats-newsom-recall-469795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But it may already be too late to convince the disorderly Democratic ranks to put aside their political differences and stand in unity with their embattled governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER In Standoff With India Over Free Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/17/968641246/twitter-in-standoff-with-indias-government-over-free-speech-and-local-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter blocked hundreds of accounts the Indian government said were inciting violence. Then it unblocked them. Now it's stuck between Indian law and defending free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolly Parton asks TN not to put her statue at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dolly-parton-tennessee-no-statue-capitol-ee80ab68ca93f29d5f600b99008fadfc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Dolly Parton is asking Tennessee lawmakers to withdraw a bill that would erect a statue of her on the Capitol grounds in Nashville. “Given all that is going on in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka WILL NOT challenge Rubio for Senate seat in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/539407-ivanka-trump-wont-challenge-rubio-for-his-senate-seat-in-2022-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump will not challenge Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Fla.) for his Senate seat in 2022, a source familiar with the matter confirmed to The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Earth its quietest in decades as lockdowns reduce seismic noise...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218132810-5xify</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambient noise generated by human activity such as travel and machinery dropped by 50% last year, researchers find</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
