<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Senator refuses to answer questions over Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/meet-the-press/video/-senator-johnson-please-gop-senator-refuses-to-answer-questions-over-ukraine-70725701857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ron Johnson (R-Wis.) talks to Chuck Todd about debunked "propaganda stuff" in response to a question about Ukraine, during an exclusive interview with Meet the Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triggers a reckoning... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/out-on-a-limb-inside-the-republican-reckoning-over-trumps-possible-impeachment/ar-AAIm4V3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$234M Global Launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-joker-gets-last-laugh-record-935m-bow-1245685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The edgy R-rated pic exceeded expectations despite heightened security at theaters across the country; overseas it raked in $140.5 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President blames Rick Perry for Ukraine call...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/trump-blames-energy-secretary-rick-perry-ukraine-call-center-impeachment-n1062931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump suggested to House Republicans Friday that it was a call he didn't even want to make, two sources familiar with the matter told NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000-Year-Old NYC-Style Metropolis Uncovered in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/5000-year-old-NYC-style-metropolis-uncovered-in-northern-Israel-603854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The find will change everything scholars know about the urbanization process in the Land of Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong lashed by fresh violence as thousands defy mask ban...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-braces-more-protests-lawmakers-court-023639292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong was rocked by fresh violence Sunday as tens of thousands hit the streets to defy a ban on face masks, sparking clashes with police, street fights and vandalism across the strife-torn city. Large crowds marched through torrential rain in peaceful but unsanctioned rallies on both sides of Victoria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town Moves Up Trick-Or-Treating Hours Over EEE Fears...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/10/04/halloween-trick-or-treat-hours-moved-methuen-eee-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Methuen says trick-or-treating will take place from 4:30 p.m. to 6 p.m. on Halloween this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Homeless Men Beaten to Death in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Four-Homeless-Men-Beaten-to-Death-Early-Saturday-Morning-in-NYCs-Chinatown-562257851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A homeless man was taken into custody after four other sleeping homeless men were beaten to death with a metal pipe overnight in Chinatown, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro accuser fires back after actor dismisses bombshell audio...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/de-niro-audio-harassment-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;De Niro accuser claims actor asked her to scratch his back and put away his boxers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman without ticket gets past security, onto DELTA flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/woman-managed-get-past-security-and-onto-delta-flight/3jd1HMi3rz9WiTVgyD7MeL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger traveling on a Delta flight from Orlando to Atlanta said another woman was in her s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US researchers on front line of battle against Chinese theft...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/afbf4d7f4aac4745b01852571179ceb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As the U.S. warned allies around the world that Chinese tech giant Huawei was a security threat, the FBI was making the same point quietly to a Midwestern university. In an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary drummer Ginger Baker dead at 80...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/oct/06/ginger-baker-wild-and-brilliant-cream-drummer-dies-aged-80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drummer who straddled jazz, blues and rock ‘passed away peacefully’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson will tell Queen: 'Sack me if you dare'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theaustralian.com.au/world/the-times/boris-johnson-will-dare-the-queen-to-sack-him-rather-than-resign-as-pm/news-story/5413c476b5c2cdc2152712faebad6de7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theaustralian.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell: Will fail 'with me as majority leader'...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/politics/mitch-mcconnell/2019/10/05/mitch-mcconnell-campaign-ad-says-trump-impeachment-fail/3879571002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new campaign ad on Facebook, the Kentucky Republican says anyÂ Trump impeachment attempt will fail as long as he remains in charge of the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Key witness' in Dallas cop murder trial shot and killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/6/joshua-brown-amber-guyger-murder-trial-witness-sho/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Brown, a “key witness” in the murder trial of a white Dallas police officer who fatally shot her black neighbor, has been killed in a shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 states account for half of 50 'most miserable'cities in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/california-new-jersey-well-represented-on-list-of-miserable-us-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to be miserable? Just three states offer an array of places you may like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Biden Donors Gather Amid Storm Clouds Over Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-biden-donors-gather-amid-storm-clouds-over-campaign/ar-AAIlmIc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD:  THEY'RE CHOKING....</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/bob-woodward-gop-senators-choking-on-trump-ukraine-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran journalist Bob Woodward said Republican senators are "choking" on President Trump's Ukraine scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WARNS TRUMP:  YOU WON'T DESTROY ME</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Biden-counterpunch-tries-to-turn-attention-to-14495561.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden on Saturday sought to take a more aggressive tone in combating President Donald Trump, a shift in strategy amid signs of worry among campaign donors and supporters that his message is getting lost in an onslaught from the White House.  Biden wrote an op-ed that was published Saturday night in The Washington Post, attempting to refocus attention on Trump's impropriety in asking Ukrainian leaders to investigate Biden's family.  "Enough is enough. Every day - every few hours, seemingly - more evidence is uncovered revealing that President Trump is abusing the power of the presidency and is wholly unfit to be president," Biden wrote. "He is using the highest office in the land to advance his personal political interests instead of the national interest."  "He does not understand the immense responsibility demanded of all those who hold the office of the president of the United States," Biden continued. "He sees only the power - and how it can benefit just one person: Donald Trump."  Biden's move came amid growing anxiety among Biden's supporters that he is unprepared to handle the dual challenges of running a general-election campaign against Trump while simultaneously facing an intensifying Democratic primary contest.  Sen. Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts has started to eclipse him in several polls, and Biden last week reported raising only $15.2 million during the last quarter - nearly $10 million less than Warren and Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt. Biden's supporters also have bridled that Democrats have been slow to rush to Biden's defense.  Biden's campaign on Saturday night distributed a memo to reporters from deputy campaign manager Kate Bedingfield. The subject of the memo highlighted the twin challenges that one of the leading candidates has faced: "Biden...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry: Tabloids hid hacking crimes for 20 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/oct/05/prince-harry-joins-court-case-against-tabloid-hacking-crimes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duke of Sussex joins case against Sun and Mirror in group action alleging documents were destroyed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart attack raises questions about Sanders' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Heart-attack-raises-questions-about-Sanders-14495377.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders' admission late Friday that he had suffered a heart attack three days earlier invited new scrutiny of the presidential candidate's age, health and ability to keep up with the rigors of a national campaign.  Sanders released a video hours after he was discharged from a Las Vegas hospital, thanking well-wishers for their support and promising to return "soon" to the campaign trail.  "I'm feeling so much better," Sanders said, his arm draped around his wife, Jane.  But neither Sanders, I-Vt., nor his campaign offered details about how serious his condition was, leaving open the question of how soon he would re-emerge and whether voters would lose confidence in his ability to serve as president.  The episode also brought new attention to a Democratic field that is currently dominated by three septuagenarians: Sanders, 78; former vice president Joe Biden, 76; and Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., 70 - each of whom would be the oldest president ever to take office.  "I think anybody's health is of concern when it comes to that high office," said Jeremy Dumkrieger, chairman of the Woodbury County, Iowa, Democratic Party, who supported Sanders in 2016 but is neutral so far this year. "You know, if the person was 40 and was having some issues, I'd have concerns about it too."  Sanders headed home Saturday to Burlington, Vermont, with no word on how long he would stay there. Jane Sanders said before his release that he would rest a "few days" but would take part in the Oct. 15 Democratic debate in Westerville, Ohio.  The campaign's decision to wait three days to reveal that Sanders had suffered a heart attack conjured images of Hillary Clinton's collapse in 2016 at a memorial service for the Sept. 11, 2001, terrorist attacks. Clinton, at the time the Democratic presidential nominee, had been diagnosed with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six elephants die trying to save each other at waterfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49944885</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident began after a baby elephant fell from a Thai waterfall and others tried to rescue it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Susan Collins turns?</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2019/10/05/politics/collins-calls-trumps-invitation-to-china-completely-inappropriate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maine senator was unequivocal in her statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As rural groceries fade away, lawmakers wonder whether to act...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/10/02/as-rural-groceries-fade-away-lawmakers-wonder-whether-to-act</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRUNI:  HOW TO SELL YOUR SOUL...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsrust.com/2019/10/opinion-how-to-sell-your-soul-to-donald.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsrust.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsrust.com is the leading provider of news and information on health, politics, education, sports, science, finance, travel news and opinion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Warren rises, debate over her ability to beat Trump intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-warren-rises-debate-over-her-ability-to-beat-trump-intensifies/ar-AAIiWBV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not so funny: Drama hobbles Ukraine's comic-president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f87294ec7f294bc6a12a25aa37323c26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — First the obsequious phone call, now the embarrassing text messages. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy's troubles might be just beginning. Revelations of how far...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA DECRIES BREAKDOWN OF TALKS USA SAYS WERE 'GOOD'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c66474b67b3e41cdad6d21ba3385ddc2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — North Korea's chief negotiator said Saturday that discussions with the U.S. on Pyongyang's nuclear program have broken down, but Washington said the two sides had "good...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  'JOKER' WILD AT BOX OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2a8dd107ea74e9da8d2115ab3a0f359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extra layers of security, intense on-screen action and a frightening incident inside a New York theater combined to create an unsettling experience for some moviegoers who went to see "Joker" on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Graham's evokes evangelical support...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5cfef4941efd4d23b06f7b4db8ca546a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENVILLE, N.C. (AP) — Rev. Franklin Graham did not utter the word "impeachment" as he spoke to thousands of Christians here this week, the latest stop on a long-running tour he has dubbed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  TOUCH OF EVIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/05/opinion/sunday/trump-chinatown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump drags us down to Chinatown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 men arrested in rape case involving an Alabama university...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/12-men-arrested-statutory-rape-case-involving-alabama-university-n1062836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The girls were making contact through social media connections and then coming onto our campus or adjacent to our campus to meet these individuals,” the university attorney said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Orders Big Cut to National Security Staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-orders-cut-to-national-security-staff-after-whistle-blower/ar-AAIj2sk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Never Trump' Coalition Decides He's Fine... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-never-trump-coalition-that-decided-eh-nevermind-hes-fine/ar-AAIjNMw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Harvey Weinstein Told Me He Liked Chinese Girls'...</title>
      <link>https://trendingpress.com/harvey-weinstein-told-me-he-liked-chinese-girls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trendingpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein told me he liked Chinese girls. He liked them because they were discreet, he said — because they knew how to keep a secret. Hours later, he attempted to rape me. You've most like</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA NUKE TALKS BREAK DOWN IN LESS THAN DAY</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/n-korean-us-officials-resume-nuclear-talks-latest-083427052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea's top nuclear envoy on Saturday said talks with the US in Stockholm had broken down, blaming Washington for bringing "nothing to the negotiation table" at the meeting, which came after months of stalemate. The talks with Stephen Biegun, US President Donald Trump's special</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters defy mask ban as city grinds to halt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-protesters-defy-mask-ban-city-grinds-095236488.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masked pro-democracy protesters marched through Hong Kong in defiance of a ban on face coverings as much of the city ground to a halt on Saturday, with the subway suspended and many shops shuttered following another night of violence. Thousands of protesters staged unsanctioned marches and flashmob</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans unlikely to reprise role played in Nixon exit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff1504ddaa5446e5903d4e883e79ff51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — On Aug. 7, 1974, three top Republican leaders in Congress paid a solemn visit to President Richard Nixon at the White House, bearing the message that he faced near-certain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President seethes over impeachment inquiry, slams critics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ddc2c70744a145549c7d11c2aa76fad0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is seething over an impeachment inquiry into his conduct after Democrats subpoenaed the White House about contacts with Ukraine and he signaled his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines disciplined at San Diego boot camp for abuse and racism targeting recruits, documents show... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/marines-disciplined-at-san-diego-boot-camp-for-abuse-and-racism-targeting-recruits-documents-show/ar-AAIjyYG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd Official Weighing Whether to Blow Whistle on Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/2nd-official-is-weighing-whether-to-blow-the-whistle-on-trumps-ukraine-dealings/ar-AAIiWJo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 Tons Of Water And 'Special Container' Used To Extinguish Burning TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/energy/11-tons-water-and-special-container-used-extinguish-burning-tesla-austria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE:  IT WAS HEART ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/bernie-sanders-had-heart-attack-week-campaign-says-n1062736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors diagnosed Sanders, 78, with a myocardial infarction, a medical term for heart attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mounting evidence buttresses facts...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Mounting-evidence-buttresses-the-facts-laid-out-14495008.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the revelation of an explosive whistleblower complaint that sparked an impeachment crisis for President Donald Trump, he and his Republican allies have coalesced around a central defense: The document was based on secondhand information, mere hearsay riddled with inaccuracies.  But over the past two weeks, documents, firsthand witness accounts and even statements by Trump himself have emerged that bolster the facts outlined in the extraordinary abuse-of-power complaint.  The descriptionof a July 25 phone call between Trump and the president of Ukraine, which formed the heart of the complaint and was still secret at the time the claim was filed in mid-August, matches a rough transcript of the call that the White House released a day before the complaint was made public.  The whistleblower's assertion that records related to the phone call were transferred to a separate electronic system intended for highly classified material has since been confirmed by White House officials.  And the whistleblower's narrative of the events that led up to the call - including a shadow campaign undertaken by Trump's personal attorney Rudy Giuliani and the attempts of U.S. State Department officials to navigate his activities- have been largely confirmed by the text messages of three diplomats released Friday, as well as Giuliani himself in media interviews.  Independent evidence now supports the central elements laid out in the seven-page document. Even if they disregarded the complaint, legal experts said lawmakers have obtained dramatic testimony and documents that provide ammunition for the whistleblower's core assertion: that the president of the United States used "the power of his office to solicit interference from a foreign country in the 2020 U.S. election."  "Everything we've found to date validates the information. . . ....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Faced His Biggest Challenge, and Struggled to Form Response...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/05/biden-faced-his-biggest-challenge-and-struggled-to-form-a-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — Joseph R. Biden Jr.’s presidential campaign was under attack, and he and his advisers were torn over what to do.For more than a week,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pompeo go home': Ugly scenes in Greece as rioters burn American flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7540881/Pompeo-blasts-harassment-Congress-impeachment-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo on Saturday accused members of Congress of harassing his department to obtain documents linked to the impeachment probe of Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snaps at press...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7540805/Joe-Biden-berates-reporter-question-Ukraine-conflicts-interest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a union forum in Los Angeles on Friday, Biden was asked about his work overseeing foreign policy for Ukraine as vice president while his son served on the board of a Ukrainian company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA NUKE TALKS BREAK DOWN IN LESS THAN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-49947836 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nuclear talks restarted in Sweden earlier on Saturday after months of stalemate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' WILD AT BOX OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a2a8dd107ea74e9da8d2115ab3a0f359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extra layers of security, intense on-screen action and a frightening incident inside a New York theater combined to create an unsettling experience for some moviegoers who went to see "Joker" on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans search for boogeyman...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/464460-gop-searches-for-impeachment-boogeyman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are hunting for a boogeyman in the burgeoning impeachment fight as the party struggles to unify behind a single strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The secret love nest of Frank Lloyd Wright haunted by fire and unspeakable ax murders...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/05/the-tragic-story-of-guggenheim-architect-frank-llyod-wrights-secret-love-nest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire at Taliesin had been deliberately set, and the arsonist had slaughtered his lover and the children with an ax before turning to six workers who were also at the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising Setback Stirs Questions About His Durability...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-fundraising-setback-stirs-questions-163549377.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joe Biden’s campaign was keeping its latest fund-raising numbers close to the vest. Then, on Thursday, the former vice president broke the news himself, putting the campaign on the defensive.At a private fundraiser in Palo Alto, California, Biden said his campaign had raised just over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMALL QUAKE JOLTS SAN FRAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-05/3-5-earthquake-near-daly-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 3.5 earthquake occurred one mile from Daly City, two miles from South San Francisco and three miles from San Francisco on Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUN SALES SPIKE...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/monthly-gun-sales-up-10-percent-since-last-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;September 2019 saw 10 percent more gun sales than September 2018, according to two analyses of background check data released this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney ramps up rhetoric on Trump, but what's his next move?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/76ab7ccee90441af97d0febc918c22b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — In the hours after President Donald Trump called on China to investigate his political foe — plowing through another political guardrail — Democrats and Trump critics looked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spits at audience, claps during violent scenes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/05/hero-confronts-unruly-man-who-terrified-patrons-at-joker-screening-witnesses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s the hero “Joker” fans deserved. A mystery man known only as “V for Vegas” confronted an unruly patron during a screening of the new Joaquin Phoenix flick Friday night in Time…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
