<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA CASES JUMP 50% IN WEEK</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/565740-florida-coronavirus-cases-jump-50-percent-in-one-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of coronavirus cases in Florida has jumped 50 percent over the past week, officials said Friday, as the state that already makes up a large chunk of the nation's total cases sees a surge in new infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much info will become public?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/07/30/justice-department-tells-treasury-to-turn-over-trump-tax-records-to-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOJ told the Treasury Department it must turn over former President Donald Trump’s tax returns to the House Ways and Means Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US sues TX over Abbott's order restricting transport of migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-sues-texas-over-abbott-s-order-restricting-transport-of-migrants/ar-AAMLoay?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Department of Justice filed suit Friday afternoon to stop an order by Texas Gov. Greg Abbott to restrict the transportation of migrants who had previously been detained by the federal immigration authorities. The suit, filed in El Paso in the U.S. District Court for the Western District, is the latest in an escalating battle between Abbott and the administration of President Joe ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA drought: Dozens of communities at risk of running out of water...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/california-drought-dozens-of-communities-are-at-risk-of-running-out-of-water/ar-AAMLz4v?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dry wells, low rivers and other problems are creating emergencies across Northern California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just say was corrupt + leave the rest to me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-to-acting-ag-according-to-aide-e2-80-99s-notes-e2-80-98just-say-the-election-was-corrupt-2b-leave-the-rest-to-me-e2-80-99/ar-AAMKRjt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump bluntly urged acting attorney general Jeffrey Rosen to back claims of voter fraud, which senior Justice officials told him were false.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Ed Buck's victims, being believed was first mountain to climb...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/he-was-a-white-man-who-had-money-ed-bucks-black-victims-fought-to-be-believed/ar-AAMKcMs?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victims of Ed Buck, who was convicted in the overdose deaths of two Black men, say it felt like no one believed them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald pressed officals to declare election was illegal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trump-urged-justice-department-to-declare-election-corrupt-0edf178869f33ddcf72d4c739bd18a5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump urged senior Justice Department officials to declare the results of the 2020 election “corrupt” in a December phone call, according to handwritten notes from one of the participants in the conversation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study: Vaccinated people can carry as much virus as others...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-coronavirus-pandemic-d9504519a8ae081f785ca012b5ef84d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another dispiriting setback for the nation’s efforts to stamp out the coronavirus, scientists who studied a big COVID-19 outbreak in Massachusetts concluded that vaccinated people who got so-called breakthrough infections carried about the same amount of the coronavirus as those who did not get the shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95% of Brits still wearing mask when out...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/30/95-of-british-adults-still-wearing-a-mask-outdoors-says-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Figure same as before legal requirement relaxed, while most still feel that complying with other Covid safety measures is important</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic Viewership Down 42% From Rio...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tokyo-olympics-ratings-rio-2016-suni-lee-simone-biles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at the most-watched and least-watched nights of the Tokyo Olympics so far -- and how viewership stacks up to the 2016 Rio Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  How I Learned To Stop Worrying And Live With The Virus...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/let-it-rip-f9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How I Learned To Stop Worrying And Live With The Virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Black woman to run St. Louis shaking up city with war on normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-first-black-woman-to-run-st-louis-is-shaking-up-the-city-with-a-war-on-normal/ar-AAMKmaB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tishaura Jones is among a wave of progressive leaders aiming to turn around struggling cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY making all employees...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/30/disney-employees-vaccinated-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Walt Disney Co. announced Friday it will require all salaried and non-union hourly employees at all of its U.S. sites to be fully vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Images Show New Tunnel At Test Site...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/30/1022209337/a-new-tunnel-is-spotted-at-a-chinese-nuclear-test-site</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite imagery showing a new tunnel comes just weeks after the discovery of two new nuclear missile fields in other parts of China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>125,682 'BREAKTHROUGH' CASES</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/breakthrough-covid-cases-least-125-000-fully-vaccinated-americans-have-n1275500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 125,682 "breakthrough" cases in 38 states represent less than .08 percent of the 164.2 million-plus people fully vaccinated since January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sets Cuba crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-readies-new-Cuba-sanctions-as-Biden-meets-16352270.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration announced new sanctions on Friday against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Privacy Battle APPLE Isn't Fighting...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/global-privacy-control-apple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has begun enforcing a browser-level privacy setting, but you still can’t find that option in Safari or iOS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only half of Israelis want 3rd jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/only-half-of-israelis-want-a-third-covid-19-vaccine-shot-survey-675419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli belief in the effectiveness of the Pfizer vaccine appears to be on the decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA plans 'sprint' to accelerate PFIZER review...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/07/30/fda-under-pressure-plans-sprint-to-accelerate-review-of-pfizers-covid-19-vaccine-for-full-approval/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers and prominent health experts have urged the FDA to expedite full approval of Pfizer’s vaccine, citing various potential benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART mandates -- for home workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Walmart-mandates-masks-for-all-workers-in-some-16352108.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Walmart is requiring that all home office workers as well as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74% of infected were fully dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/cdc-study-shows-74percent-of-people-infected-in-massachusetts-covid-outbreak-were-fully-vaccinated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC data published Friday was based on 469 cases of Covid associated with multiple summer events and large public gatherings in July in Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bin Laden Bel Air estate listed for $28M...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/30/osama-bin-ladens-bel-air-estate-is-on-sale-for-28m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The home was abandoned after the September 11 attacks. “Ready for redoing, owner has not been here for over 20 years,” the listing states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sir, there is something on your chin'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9844869/Staffer-passes-Biden-note-saying-Sir-chin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden was speaking on Zoom about the responses to raging wildfires throughout the country when an aide passed him a card, alerting him there was a spot on his face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China battles worst outbreak since Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-58021911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 200 people have been infected since the virus was first detected at Nanjing airport on 20 July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can masturbating beat Covid?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/3381486/can-masturbating-boost-your-immune-system-fight-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH a deadly virus circulating the past year and a half, many people have been wondering how they can boost their immunity. Masturbating is sometimes touted as a way to give the immune system a ki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt denies BLUE ORIGIN protest of human moon lander contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2021/07/30/government-denies-blue-origins-protest-of-nasas-human-moon-lander-contract/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GAO sided with NASA Friday denying protests submitted by Blue Origin and Dynetics of the agency's decision to pick only SpaceX's Starship for the first human moon lander contract.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYDNEY DEPLOYS ARMY</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-58021718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say the deployment is needed, but critics argue it will "pick on" marginalised groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US military warns China building more nuclear missile silos...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/07/30/us-military-warns-china-is-building-more-nuclear-missile-silos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The underground missile silo field in the Xinjiang region is the second one reported this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax returns can be released to Congress, DOJ says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/trump-tax-returns-can-be-released-to-congress-doj-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump has refused for years to voluntarily disclose his income tax returns. Congress can now see them, the Justice Department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlicensed Dog Grooming Alarms Local News Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/29/unlicensed-dog-grooming-alarms-local-news-reporter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do we really need the state to step in over an unfortunate tragedy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Mouthwash Test Just As Effective As Nasal Swabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mouthwash-tests-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both the nasal and mouthwash tests are of the polymerase chain reaction variety, which are highly sensitive and capable of producing a result in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYDNEY READIES ARMY</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/sydney-readies-for-the-army-as-lockdown-fails-to-squash-delta-outbreak/ar-AAMIAat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sydney readies for the army as lockdown fails to squash Delta outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC RESTURANTS ONLY FOR THE DOSED?</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-considering-vaccine-mandate-for-all-restaurants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio says "all options are on the table" when it comes to possibly require vaccines for patrons at restaurants across New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinated Woman Stuck In Mexico After Testing Positive...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/liz-collin-6p-pkg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maya Buckner doesn’t go far without her vaccine card showing she completed the Pfizer series in March -- including on a balcony in Cancun, Mexico, where she is now sick with COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loses $13.5 Billion After AMAZON Disappointment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/jeff-bezos-loses-135-billion-after-amazon-disappointment/ar-AAMKy55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc.’s weaker-than-expected second-quarter results has sent its founder’s fortune tumbling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway requires shot, covering for all shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210730-new-york-s-broadway-mandates-vaccines-masks-for-all-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's Broadway mandates vaccines, masks for all shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 47% of Republicans say time will come 'to take law into own hands'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/565610-47-percent-of-republicans-say-time-will-come-to-take-the-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 47 percent of Republicans believe that a time will come when “patriotic Americans have to take the law into their own hands,” according to a George Washington University</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Everyone Obsessed With Bezos Face?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-everyone-obsessed-jeff-bezos-082628628.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastJeff Bezos’ face looks, well, different lately: his lips are plumped up to near-Kardashian proportions, and his cheeks look more full, as if someone used Facetune to expand his face and head.It is unknown if Bezos has had work of any kind done. If he has, there’s no shame—unlike, his critics would say, union-busting, tax evasion, and shooting yourself into space while the rest of the world crumbles. And so many were quick to take to TikTok and so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaxed, waxed, but definitely not relaxed: Welcome to pandemic swerve...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaxed-waxed-but-definitely-not-relaxed-welcome-to-the-pandemic-swerve/ar-AAMK67j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delta variant rudely interrupts an optimistic summer with the realization that this ordeal is far from over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate moves to legalize pot at federal level. What are chances?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/senate-moves-to-legalize-pot-at-federal-level-what-are-the-chances/ar-AAMHopd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposed bill puts forth restorative justice measures, taxes marijuana and lays a framework for regulation. But it is unlikely to pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Brawl Between Homeless Erupts On Venice Boardwalk...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/29/caught-on-video-brawl-on-venice-beach-boardwalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cellphone video shows an all-out brawl between what appears to be at least three homeless men on the Venice Beach Boardwalk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Attempt To Test Air Force Hypersonic Weapon Fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41761/air-forces-fails-in-second-attempt-to-conduct-a-test-flight-of-its-first-hypersonic-missile</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The missile's rocket booster failed to ignite after separating from the B-52 carrying it, but the Air Force says it still gained valuable test data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA being overrun by freaky 'penis snakes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3379278/us-overrun-freaky-penis-snake-slither-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US faces being overrun by strange-looking “penis snakes” that appear to have slithered up from the Amazon. Caecilians can grow up to 32 inches long and one was found in a Miami canal in Novembe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Living Past 100 Lies In Gut?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/centenarians-gut-bacteria-live-longer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery could lead to yogurts and other probiotic foods that increase longevity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did bogus tale of U.S.-backed drug raids help set plot in motion?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/investigations/article253121148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A month before the assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moïse, two South Florida men turned up at an unusual meeting in the Caribbean nation, according to information presented to a Haitian prosecutor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key inflation indicator fastest gain since 1991...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/key-inflation-indicator-up-3point5percent-year-over-year-in-june-vs-3point6percent-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inflation indicator that the Fed uses as its key guide rose 3.5% in June, a sharp acceleration that was nonetheless right around expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million infected daily?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/30/dr-scott-gottlieb-estimates-up-to-1-million-americans-infected-with-covid-daily-as-delta-spreads.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I wouldn't be surprised if, on the whole, we're infecting up to a million people a day right now," Dr. Scott Gottlieb told CNBC on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unvaxxed athlete slammed for bareface...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/olympics/1003188/unvaccinated-us-swimmer-slammed-for-going-maskless-at-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'War Has Changed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/cdc-warns-internal-document-war-has-changed-coronavirus-n1275478</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccines continue to be effective, particularly at preventing severe disease, according to the document. But they may not be as good at preventing infection or transmission of the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brits outraged by U.S. cartoon depicting royal family as egotistical tea drinkers controlled by mafia boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brits-outraged-by-us-cartoon-depicting-royal-family-as-egotistical-tea-drinkers-controlled-by-mafia-boss/ar-AAMKm9z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The HBO Max series has been slammed by critics in Britain as "wrong" and "disgusting."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Deep new history of TESLA takes shine off Musk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/review-deep-history-tesla-takes-130057001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The polarizing founder shows up a lot in 'Power Play,' Tim Higgins' Tesla history — but usually in the role of a dramatic foil who will be overtaken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic police dogs: Useful hounds or dehumanizing machines?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/robotic-police-dogs-e32e371e8776b8565f1a0f6491e55c29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — If you’re homeless and looking for temporary shelter in Hawaii’s capital, expect a visit from a robotic police dog that will scan your eye to make sure you don’t have a fever. That’s just one of the ways public safety agencies are starting to use Spot, the best-known of a new commercial category of robots that trot around with animal-like agility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Front-line workers in FL say surge 'feels like impending storm'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/frontline-workers-florida-current-covid-19-surge-feels/story?id=79151882</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"In early July, we were down to 12 COVID-19 patients in the hospital, and today we have 80."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trolls targeting trans Olympian...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210730-online-trolls-targeting-transgender-olympian-kiwi-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online trolls targeting transgender Olympian: Kiwi official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYDNEY READIES FOR ARMY</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210730053158-jwg5n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 3,TV,PIX):UPDATE 3-Sydney readies for the army as lockdown fails to squash Delta outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After mudslide, priest gets narcos' help to build new town...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-caribbean-f0306dc68771d5166f918e863de6f185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION SAN FRANCISCO DE ASIS, Honduras (AP) — First came Hurricane Eta. Then, Hurricane Iota, unleashing rains of biblical proportions on the hillside community of La Reina. As Iota hammered La Reina for four days, residents kept watch on the mountain above their 300 homes for signs that they should flee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship tied to Israeli billionaire attacked off Oman, 2 killed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ship-israeli-billionaire-oman-c43203ff0262ba2c4bfafb31cc42fa50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — An oil tanker linked to an Israeli billionaire reportedly came under attack off the coast of Oman in the Arabian Sea, authorities said Friday, an assault that killed two crew members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese athletes face Chinese nationalists' wrath after beating at Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/30/china/china-japan-olympics-online-abuse-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of Japan's victorious Olympic athletes have been subjected to a storm of online abuse from Chinese nationalists following the defeat of their Team China opponents in Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They Thought I Was Dead': Haitian President's Widow Recounts Assassination...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/30/they-thought-i-was-dead-haitian-presidents-widow-recounts-assassination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — With her elbow shattered by gunfire and her mouth full of blood, the first lady of Haiti lay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qaddafi Son Alive. And Wants to Take Libya Back...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/30/qaddafis-son-is-alive-and-he-wants-to-take-libya-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. Ten years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Covid With a Vengeance' Consumes Politics...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/30/covid-with-a-vengeance-consumes-u-s-politics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American political system has come down with a case of long Covid. In Washington and the states, and in</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
