<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's rolling disaster is threat to world...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-rolling-coronavirus-disaster-is-a-threat-to-the-world/ar-BB1eFhPN </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Aliens Arrive, What Will They Look Like? Zoologist Has Answers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/16/when-the-aliens-arrive-what-will-they-look-like-a-zoologist-has-answers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ZOOLOGIST’S GUIDE TO THE GALAXY What Animals on Earth Reveal About Aliens — and Ourselves By Arik Kershenbaum Is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slay suspect was 'big into religion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/seven-killed-in-shootings-at-atlanta-spas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four of the victims were Asian women, and a 21-year-old was in custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Asian Americans verbally and physically attacked, shunned during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asian-americans-verbally-physically-attacked-182920825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 68% of the anti-Asian attacks documented during the pandemic were verbal harassment, 21% were shunning and 11% were physical assaults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE:  Candace Owens says she's '100% suing' Cardi B...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2524479/candace-owens-blasts-cardi-b-poisoning-minds-grammys/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOLLOWING a bitter back and forth over Twitter, Candace Owens said she’s planning on suing Cardi B after the rapper tweeted a fake tweet from saying Owens’ husband cheated on her with h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Russia boosted Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/03/16/us-intelligence-says-russia-boosted-trump-put-down-biden-in-2020-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia did not attempt to physically alter voting process or election results but did launch propaganda efforts against Biden and for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA-Based Dating? NETFLIX Series Isn't So Far Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/netflix-the-one-dna-match-dating-real-thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix’s new relationship drama series The One follows the founder of a fictional company that scientifically matches people with their perfect partner — using DNA. Though the show is based on the book of the same name by John Marrs and is completely fictional, you may be wondering whether DNA matching is possible in real […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS to get big stimulus boost as checks are spent on lattes...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/starbucks-upcoming-gains-from-restaurant-reopenings-and-federal-stimulus-drive-analyst-upgrade-11615908088</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurant restrictions are the biggest hurdle to getting young customers back through the door, according to BTIG data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside The Cuomo Impeachment Fight...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-the-new-york-democrats-messy-fight-over-whether-to-impeach-andrew-cuomo-213249118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With mounting sexual misconduct accusations and an alleged cover-up of nursing home deaths, New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo is facing an investigation from his fellow Democrats in the state Assembly that could result in his removal from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 killed in 3 shootings at Georgia massage parlor, spas... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/3-dead-shooting-georgia-massage-parlor-suspect-loose-n1261262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people were killed in Cherokee County, and in Atlanta, four people were shot at or near two spas. The shootings have not been linked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland', CBP want military support...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/03/16/border-deployments-could-be-extended-past-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security has asked for an extension to the mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admiral: China Used Covid to Expand 'Influence'...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/03/16/southcoms-faller-china-used-pandemic-to-expand-corrosive-insidious-influence-in-central-south-america-u-s-influence-eroding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has used the COVID-19 pandemic to rapidly expand its “corrosive, insidious influence” – from money laundering for transnational gangsters to using its own ships to illegally fish protected waters and benefit from illegal logging and mining – “in our neighborhood,” U.S. Southern Command’s top officer said Tuesday. “I can’t stress enough the full-court press” …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of hot spots emerge in Midwest, New York City...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/after-weeks-of-declining-cases-echoes-of-hot-spots-emerge-in-upper-midwest-new-york-city-area/ar-BB1eEs17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan has seen a rise in hospitalizations and positive test results. Minnesota’s numbers are creeping up, as are Maryland’s and New Jersey’s. Many places, including New York City and surrounding counties, are no longer seeing steady declines in cases, despite intensive vaccination efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Serial Stowaway Arrested AGAIN At O'Hare...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/serial-stowaway-marilyn-hartman-interview-cbs-2-investigators-brad-edwards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California heads toward recall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-elections-california-gavin-newsom-recall-elections-d0a0cba5a08af32d115a2d1f79b32661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCKLIN, Calif. (AP) — A plodding, months-long review kicks off Wednesday to confirm what appears inevitable: California Gov. Gavin Newsom will face a recall election that could oust the Democrat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Sharon Osbourne Referred to Julie Chen as 'Wonton', 'Slanty Eyes'...</title>
      <link>https://yashar.substack.com/p/exclusive-sharon-osbourne-frequently</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;yashar.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharon Osbourne, co-host of the CBS daytime panel show “The Talk,” would frequently refer to then-co-host Julie Chen, who is Chinese American, as “wonton” and “slanty eyes,” according to multiple sources, including former co-host Leah Remini.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAKERS star a 'noted YANKEES fan'...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nba/2021/03/16/lebron-james-becomes-part-owner-red-sox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James and longtime friend Maverick Carter reportedly entered the venture together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron becomes part owner of RED SOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/31076745/source-lebron-james-becomes-part-owner-boston-red-sox-joins-fenway-sports-group-partner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James has become a partner in the Fenway Sports Group, making the NBA superstar a part owner of the Boston Red Sox, a source has confirmed to ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human tear glands grown in lab actually cry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/human-tear-glands-grown-in-a-lab-actually-cry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers have an ambitious vision for their organoid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah campaign against porn marches on with phone filter plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/legislature-utah-coronavirus-pandemic-pornography-laws-d2f3911b7887f2f145918d1718bf2504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Conservative lawmakers in Utah have fired another salvo in their longtime campaign against online porn with a new requirement that all cellphones and tablets sold in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea 'readying first nuke weapons test' since Biden took office...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2524190/north-korea-planning-first-nuke-weapon-test-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korea is allegedly preparing to carry out its “first nuclear weapons test” since President Joe Biden took office, United States intelligence has learned. CNN reported on the news …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin pushed Joe misinfo to Don allies and media in '20 election, USA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/16/putin-pushed-biden-misinformation-to-trump-allies-during-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Vladimir Putin authorized intelligence assets to promote misinformation about President Joe Biden through people close to then-President Donald Trump, an intelligence report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Exvangelicals' Living Uniquely American Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akdbee/what-its-like-to-leave-the-evangelical-community-exvangelicals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abandoning the religion you were raised in is a long-standing tradition. But for former evangelicals, leaving the church is a lonely path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Lightning may have sparked life on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210316-lightning-may-have-sparked-life-on-earth-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lightning may have sparked life on Earth, study finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE: New strain might be able to evade tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210316-france-investigating-new-coronavirus-variant-detected-in-brittany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new coronavirus variant has been found in the French region of Brittany, the French health ministry said in a statement late Monday, adding that an initial analysis did not show this new variant to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAIBBI: The Sovietization of the American Press...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/opinion/matt-taibbi-the-sovietization-of-the-american-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Epidemic: Hundreds of burnt, stripped abandoned cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/local/article/oakland-abandoned-car-epidemic-16027155.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swaths of inoperable vehicles are plaguing Black and brown communities. Residents say the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jet packs on way to battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/03/16/jet-packs-are-on-their-way-to-a-battlefield-near-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 2021 will be good for something: Jet packs!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars Has Much More Water Than Previously Known...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5947142/water-on-mars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if most of Mars' water never actually drifted into space?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Can't Hear Signals -- Because Earth Too Loud...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSOM: CA recall appears to have enough signatures...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2021/03/16/newsom-california-recall-appears-to-have-enough-signatures-1368400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor has quickly signaled that his campaign will paint the recall effort as an outgrowth of pro-Trump extremists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why having kids doesn't necessarily make you happier, according to research...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/16/does-having-children-make-you-happier-science-of-parenthood-explained.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents are not happier than nonparents, according to research, but there are other benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports About to Look Like '19 Again...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/03/sports-are-about-to-look-like-2019-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Rangers and Wrestlemania are paving the way for crowded stadiums and arenas to become the norm within weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bereaved families call for judge-led public inquiry into UK response...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/mar/16/bereaved-families-call-for-judge-led-public-inquiry-into-uk-covid-response</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson can decide whether to heed calls for wide-ranging inquiry or keep a tighter focus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch scientists grow human tear glands...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/mar/16/for-crying-out-loud-dutch-scientists-grow-human-tear-glands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creation of mini-organs using stem cells will help research into tear-related disorders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope navigates divided church...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/on-same-sex-unions-pope-francis-must-navigate-a-divided-church/ar-BB1eEbR7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The polarization of Catholics around the world could explain the course the pope is trying to set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Dems Launch 'Ron Be Gone' to Oust DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.wptv.com/news/political/ron-be-gone-group-led-by-south-florida-democrats-aims-to-oust-desantis-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wptv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Florida Democrats have announced the creation of Ron Be Gone, a new political group aimed at ensuring Gov. Ron DeSantis doesn't win re-election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Elliot Page becomes first trans MAN to star on TIME cover...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/03/16/elliot-page-undergoes-top-surgery-it-transformed-my-life/?_ga=2.220168217.1444238805.1615859795-160136807.1611102406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He covers Time Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE TO MONITOR SLEEP, BREATHING</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-nest-adds-sleep-tracking-130000660.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Google’s Nest unit is expanding into health technology with a feature that tracks sleep patterns, offering a potential new revenue stream but also raising privacy concerns.The company unveiled the second-generation model of its Nest Hub smart display in a blog post Tuesday, and this time it comes with a function called Sleep Sensing that monitors the breathing and movement of a person sleeping next to the screen -- without a camera or needing to wear a device in bed.The system also detects disturbances such as coughing and snoring, along with light and temperature changes using the Nest Hub’s built-in microphones and ambient light and temperature sensors. Over time, it learns the user’s sleep patterns and gives personalized recommendations.Ashton Udall, a senior product manager at Google Nest, said Sleep Sensing will be available as a free preview until next year. That suggests the company may begin charging for the service in the future.Nest was a pioneer in so-called smart home technology through its internet-connected thermostat. Google acquired the company for $3.2 billion in 2014. Since then, Nest struggled with some new product launches, lost its founders and dealt with recurring privacy questions.On Tuesday, the internet giant addressed the privacy implications of Nest’s new sleep-sensing feature. The system relies on a low-energy radar technology called Soli to do the tracking, but it can be disabled.Audio of users’ snores and coughs will be processed on the Nest Hub device rather than being sent to Google’s servers. There’s even a hardware switch that physically disables the microphone. Users can also review and delete their sleep data at any time, and Google stressed that the information isn’t used for personalized ads.Google, Amazon.com Inc. and Apple Inc. have developed smart displays and speakers to expand their platforms further into consumers’ homes and lives.Fresh off its acquisition of Fitbit Inc., which makes wearable health devices, Google is also making a stronger effort to commercialize years of research it’s done on human health. The company said it will look for ways to integrate Nest with Fitbit’s sleep-tracking features in the future.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Threatens to Block TWITTER as Content Dispute Escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-social-media-russia-child-pornography-suicides-726fc480f89a499605623e9a08c19017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian authorities said Tuesday they would block Twitter in a month if it doesn't take steps to remove banned content, a move that escalates the Russian government’s drawn-out...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microbes Unknown to Science Discovered on Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/four-bacterial-strains-discovered-on-the-iss-may-help-grow-better-space-plants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The menagerie of bacterial and fungal species living among us is ever growing - and this is no exception in low-gravity environments, such as the International Space Station (ISS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive piece of junk tossed from ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/space-news/massive-piece-of-space-junk-tossed-from-iss-sets-record/916013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weighing in at nearly 3 tons, the object is the largest ever jettisoned from the International Space Station and is expected to float around in space for the next few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes First Major Tax Hike Since 1993...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-eyes-first-major-tax-060001525.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden is planning the first major federal tax hike since 1993 to help pay for the long-term economic program designed as a follow-up to his pandemic-relief bill, according to people familiar with the matter.Unlike the $1.9 trillion Covid-19 stimulus act, the next initiative, which is expected to be even bigger, won’t rely just on government debt as a funding source. While it’s been increasingly clear that tax hikes will be a component -- Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen has said at least part of the next bill will have to be paid for, and pointed to higher rates -- key advisers are now making preparations for a package of measures that could include an increase in both the corporate tax rate and the individual rate for high earners.With each tax break and credit having its own lobbying constituency to back it, tinkering with rates is fraught with political risk. That helps explain why the tax hikes in Bill Clinton’s signature 1993 overhaul stand out from the modest modifications done since.For the Biden administration, the planned changes are an opportunity not just to fund key initiatives like infrastructure, climate and expanded help for poorer Americans, but also to address what Democrats argue are inequities in the tax system itself. The plan will test both Biden’s capacity to woo Republicans and Democrats’ ability to remain unified.“His whole outlook has always been that Americans believe tax policy needs to be fair, and he has viewed all of his policy options through that lens,” said Sarah Bianchi, head of U.S. public policy at Evercore ISI and a former economic aide to Biden. “That is why the focus is on addressing the unequal treatment between work and wealth.”While the White House has rejected an outright wealth tax, as proposed by progressive Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren, the administration’s current thinking does target the wealthy.The White House is expected to propose a suite of tax increases, mostly mirroring Biden’s 2020 campaign proposals, according to four people familiar with the discussions.The tax hikes included in any broader infrastructure and jobs package are likely to include repealing portions of President Donald Trump’s 2017 tax law that benefit corporations and wealthy individuals, as well as making other changes to make the tax code more progressive, said the people familiar with the plan.The following are among proposals currently planned or under consideration, according to the people, who asked not to be named as the discussions are private:Raising the corporate tax rate to 28% from 21%Paring back tax preferences for so-called pass-through businesses, such as limited-liability companies or partnershipsRaising the income tax rate on individuals earning more than $400,000Expanding the estate tax’s reachA higher capital-gains tax rate for individuals earning at least $1 million annually. (Biden on the campaign trail proposed applying income-tax rates, which would be higher)White House economist Heather Boushey underlined that Biden doesn’t intend to boost taxes on people earning less than $400,000 a year. But for “folks at the top who’ve been able to benefit from this economy and haven’t been this hard hit, there’s a lot of room there to think about what kinds of revenue we can raise,” she said in a Bloomberg TV interview Monday.An independent analysis of the Biden campaign tax plan done by the Tax Policy Center estimated it would raise $2.1 trillion over a decade, though the administration’s plan is likely to be smaller. Bianchi earlier this month wrote that congressional Democrats might agree to $500 billion.The overall program has yet to be unveiled, with analysts penciling in $2 trillion to $4 trillion. No date has yet been set for an announcement, though the White House said the plan would follow the signing of the Covid-19 relief bill.An outstanding question for Democrats is which parts of the package need to be funded, amid debate over whether infrastructure ultimately pays for itself -- especially given current borrowing costs, which remain historically low. Efforts to make the expanded child tax credit in the pandemic-aid bill permanent -- something with a price tag estimated at more than $1 trillion over a decade -- could be harder to sell if pitched as entirely debt-financed.What Bloomberg’s Economists Say...“The next major legislative initiative, infrastructure investment, could provide the sort of durable economic gains that not only support higher pay, but promote diffusion of those gains across demographic lines and political persuasions.”--Andrew Husby and Eliza Winger, U.S. economistsFor the full report, click hereDemocrats would need at least 10 Republicans to back the bill to move it under regular Senate rules. But GOP members are signaling they are prepared to fight.“We’ll have a big robust discussion about the appropriateness of a big tax increase,” Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell said last month, predicting Democrats would pursue a reconciliation bill that forgoes the GOP and would aim for a corporate tax even higher than 28%.Kevin Brady, the top Republican on the House Ways &amp; Means Committee, said, “There seems to a be a real drive to tax investment of capital gains at marginal income rates,” and called that a “terrible economic mistake.”While about 18% of the George W. Bush administration’s tax cuts were allowed to expire in a 2013 deal, and other legislation has seen some increases in levies, 1993 marks the last comprehensive set of increases, experts say. That bill passed on a two-vote margin in the House and required the vice president to break a tie in the Senate.“I don’t think it is an understatement to say the current partisan environment is more severe than 1993” said Ken Kies, managing director of the Federal Policy Group, a former chief of staff of the congressional Joint Committee on Taxation. “So you can draw your own conclusions” about prospects for a deal this year, he said.Still, there could be some tax initiatives Republicans could get behind. One is a shift from a gasoline tax to a vehicle-miles-traveled fee to help fund highway projects.Read More: By-the-Mile Vehicle Tax to Help Fund Infrastructure Gains SteamAnother is more money for Internal Revenue Service enforcement -- a way to boost revenue without raising rates. Estimates have found that for every additional $1 spent on IRS audits, the agency brings in an additional $3 to $5.Democrats are also looking to revise tax laws that they say don’t do enough to stop U.S. companies from shifting jobs and profits offshore as another way to raise revenue, one aide said. Republicans could potentially support incentives, though it’s unclear whether they’d back penalties.White House officials including deputy director of the National Economic Council, David Kamin -- who wrote a 2019 paper on “Taxing the Rich” -- are in the process of fleshing out the Biden tax plans.As for timing, if passed, tax measures would likely take effect in 2022 -- though some lawmakers and Biden supporters outside the administration have argued for holding off while unemployment remains high due to the pandemic.Lawmakers have their own ideas for tax reforms. Senate Finance Committee Chairman Ron Wyden wants to consolidate energy tax breaks and require investors to pay taxes regularly on their investments including stocks and bonds that have unrealized gains.“A nurse pays taxes with every single paycheck. A billionaire in an affluent suburb on the other hand can defer paying taxes month after month to the point where their paying taxes is pretty much optional,” Wyden told Bloomberg in an interview. “I don’t think that’s right.”Warren has pitched a wealth tax, while House Financial Services Committee Chair Maxine Waters has said she would like to consider a financial-transaction tax.Democratic strategists see the next package as effectively the last chance to reshape the U.S. economy on a grand scale before lawmakers turn to the 2022 mid-term campaign.“Normally, the party in power gets one or two shots to do major legislative packages,” said Chuck Marr, senior director of Federal Tax Policy at the left-leaning Center on Budget and Policy Priorities. “This is the next shot.”(Updates with White House economist comments in first paragraph after bullet-pointed section.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran starts trial of new homegrown vax...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tehran-clinical-trials-iran-coronavirus-pandemic-fde9601ee7d3dabc381dbff67b057d3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's campaign to inoculate its population against the coronavirus and promote itself as an emerging vaccine manufacturer inched on as health authorities announced Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT IT HIM?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2522119/qanon-leader-q-revealed-ex-8chan-administrator-ron-watkins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CONSPIRACY documentary has claimed to have unmasked QAnon’s mysterious leader Q. Makers of the new six-part HBO docu-series Into the Storm have concluded Ron Watkins — the longtime administrator …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimulus check argument leads to quadruple murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/stimulus-check-argument-led-to-quadruple-murder-family-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man suspected of killing three adults and a child had pulled out a gun and opened fire following a heated argument over dividing a stimulus check, the family says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL TRIP:  Family Kicked Off Flight After 4-Year-Old Won't Wear Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/spirit-airlines-kicks-four-year-old-boy-with-autism-off-flight-for-not-wearing-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline says it's changing its policy to allow for medical exemptions but there were no exemptions when it happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU 'CONVINCED' VAX BENEFIT OUTWEIGHS RISK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/eu-regulator-astrazeneca-benefit-outweighs-risk-37c3f8fa9523c58576cbff6d9c13a103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — With coronavirus cases rising in many places, governments faced the grimmest of dilemmas Tuesday: push on with a vaccine that is known to save lives or suspend use of AstraZeneca...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With few other options, Texas Dems need Beto to challenge Gov. Abbott in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-few-other-options-texas-democrats-need-beto-orourke-to-challenge-gop-gov-greg-abbott-in-2022/ar-BB1eDlhQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS — With few other viable options, Texas Democrats are hoping that next year former Rep. Beto O’Rourke challenges Republican incumbent Greg Abbott for governor. The El Paso Democrat is considering running for governor, saying that Abbott has failed Texas during the pandemic. He later criticized his handling of the February winter storm that left millions of Texans without power and water. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside new facility already at 700% capacity...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9367667/Bidens-border-crisis-Inside-new-Texas-migrant-facility-700-capacity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The center - located in the Rio Grande Valley - opened on February 24 and was initially permitted to hold 250 migrants as they were processed by authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Wallen music sales still soaring six weeks after he was 'canceled,' but story bigger than him...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Morgan-Wallen-s-music-sales-are-still-soaring-six-16029374.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six weeks after critics cried that country star Morgan Wallen was being</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southwest border crossings on pace for highest levels in 20 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/southwest-border-crossings-pace-highest-levels-20-years-biden-admin-n1261192</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Emergency Management Agency is setting up a convention center in Dallas to hold up to 3,000 unaccompanied teenage migrants, NBC News confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel priests defy Vatican, vow to bless same-sex couples...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210316124934-4j1yv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Elliot Page becomes first trans man to star on TIME cover...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210316123602-zsqf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army initially pushed to deny District's request for National Guard before Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Army-initially-pushed-to-deny-District-s-request-16029067.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Army initially pushed to reject the Washington D.C. government's request...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists unearth meteorite from birth of solar system...</title>
      <link>https://www.spacedaily.com/afp/210316133356.03wdimd3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spacedaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-schooler, mother hacked school records to steal homecoming queen election...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/High-schooler-and-her-mother-hacked-school-16028988.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a sparkling silver dress, the homecoming queen at J.M. Tate High School in Cantonment,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican rips gay unions, says God 'does not and cannot bless sin'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vatican-decree-same-sex-unions-cannot-bless-sin-077944750c975313ad253328e4cf7443</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican declared Monday that the Catholic Church won't bless same-sex unions since God “cannot bless sin.” The Vatican’s orthodoxy office, the Congregation for the Doctrine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to house up to 3,000 migrant teens at Dallas convention center...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dallas-health-coronavirus-pandemic-immigration-border-patrols-fa567f671faa0e9eb33e37f30746f1b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — The U.S. government plans to house up to 3,000 immigrant teenagers at a convention center in downtown Dallas as it struggles to find space for a surge of migrant children at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror suspects part of surge?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-question-rep-kevin-mccarthy-s-claim-that-terrorists-are-crossing-the-border-he-is-either-wrong-or-lying/ar-BB1eDhGw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats from border states pushed back and demanded evidence to back up the House minority leader's assertions, which echo unsupported claims repeatedly made by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Israelis head back to elections, there's new twist: Dems in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/As-Israelis-head-back-to-elections-there-s-a-new-16028920.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - Israeli voters, trapped for two years in a vote-rinse-repeat cycle of toss-up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warehouse Raves Power Risky Nightlife in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-nightlife-scene-somehow-wilder-090036040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APMIAMI—A midnight curfew was no match for Juovani Dror.On Friday night, the 27-year-old Israeli bon vivant and a crew of friends raged at a techno party in Coconut Grove, an affluent waterfront neighborhood in Miami. It’s a city where nearly 245,000 coronavirus cases have been recorded since the beginning of the pandemic, almost triple the number in Orlando, the city with the second-highest number of cases in Florida.“It was a very good event: more than 1,000 people at a warehouse party,” Dror told The Daily Beast. “For the techno scene, it’s all warehouses now. And it’s a very good crowd made up of beautiful people and big money spenders.”Biker Week Is a Sick Joke for the Unvaccinated in FloridaLate Saturday afternoon, Dror said, he recharged with drinks at Joia Beach Restaurant and Beach Club, a flossy outdoor venue adjacent to a megayacht marina on Miami’s Watson Island. From there, he hopped across the MacArthur Causeway for a late-night dinner with friends at Astra Miami, a rooftop eatery and lounge in the city’s trendy Wynwood neighborhood.“We partied until 1:30 in the morning,” Dror said. “They usually close at midnight, but we were having so much fun. I had people standing on the chairs and we moved tables to have a bigger dance floor.”The turn-up was just getting started, he added. “From there, we went to M3 Studios for a techno party called ‘Aria.’,” Dror said. “It was me and about 20 people. We stayed until about 5 a.m.” View this post on Instagram A post shared by 3AM TECHNO (@3am_techno) Management at Joia Beach, Astra, and M3 Studios did not respond to requests for comment. But dozens of hashtags and geolocations for those and other Miami nightlife venues on Instagram, including posts by Dror, pointed to scenes of the juiced-up debauchery unfolding in the Magic City at the height of Spring Break.For several days now, videos have depicted maskless partygoers dancing on top of tables after curfew at other popular restaurants such as Komodo Miami and Kiki’s on the River. (Neither establishment responded to requests for comment). Other clips for a Saturday night underground party in Miami Beach featuring New York City DJ Roger Sanchez showed ravers, many sans masks, dancing shoulder-to-shoulder. (Sanchez could not immediately be reached for comment, and Dror insisted the establishments he frequents enforce mask-wearing if people are not eating, drinking, or dancing.)Interviews with nightlife denizens, promoters, and health experts suggest that thanks to Gov. Ron DeSantis, the city is far too wide open given the daily positivity rate has not fallen below 5 percent for consecutive weeks throughout the pandemic. Now, with a combination of Spring Break and a general sense from the federal government on down that the pandemic is in its final throes, the parties are getting even wilder.The only problem? Pandemic mutations are, too.The wilding isn’t confined to restaurants and warehouses hosting dance parties. On Friday night, the Miami Beach Police Department tweeted that officers on the streets and sidewalks were dealing with “very large crowds,” detaining people and “forced to use pepper balls” on civilians. Videos also showed partygoers twerking on a patrol car and a massive crowd dispersing when cops body slammed a man. 100 people were reportedly arrested in Miami Beach alone.Even for a seasoned party pro like Dror, Miami’s party scene has ratcheted up several notches.“It’s going crazy right now,” he said. “It’s definitely more intense. Some of it is Spring Break crowds, but a lot of people from all over the world are coming to Miami for a good time. You can go out on Thursday night and stay out until Monday morning without having to go home in between.”For folks not from Florida, Dror’s perspective may seem as foreign as a virus that spread from one side of the Earth to the other. Except in Miami, for several months now, party-minded residents and visitors have been freed from the lockdown shackles that some states are just beginning to loosen. In September, DeSantis relaxed a majority of COVID-19 business restrictions, including those allowing cities and counties to enforce fines against people who refuse to wear masks in public. Last week, he waived all fines against people and businesses that violated local curfews, indoor mask requirements, and other COVID-19-related ordinances. As a result, Miami-Dade stopped issuing citations this weekend, according to the Miami Herald, even as local officials have slammed DeSantis for hamstringing them. “We’re no longer doing it because the governor pardoned everything,” Detective Alvaro Zabaleta, spokesperson for the Miami-Dade Police Department, told the paper.A spokesperson for DeSantis did not immediately respond to a request for comment for this story.The freedom to party, pandemic fatigue, and the public perception the pandemic is nearing an end are combining to form a dangerous cocktail in Miami-Dade. Coronavirus-related hospitalizations and deaths have been tracking downward since the end of January following the holiday surge, according to infectious disease experts. But even as the 14-day daily positivity rate in Miami-Dade is currently at 6 percent, just north of the 5 percent benchmark used by some experts, the count still averaged nearly 1,200 new daily cases between March 1 and March 14.And Florida currently leads the nation in the number of cases involving new variants, such as the B.1.1.7 strain known as the U.K. variant, which some experts believe to be deadlier.“I understand people want the pandemic to be over, but it is not over,” Florida International University epidemiology Professor Dr. Mary Jo Trepka told The Daily Beast. “We are not even down to the number of daily cases that we had back in the fall. We need people to be careful to avoid increased transmissions.”Spring Break COVID-19 Mayhem Is Coming for FloridaEngaging in the type of behavior of Dror and other partygoers will only prolong the pandemic unnecessarily, Trepka added. “We are trending in the right direction,” she said. “But we are not quite there yet. Those types of behaviors increase the risk for everybody. And for those people coming from other parts of the U.S. and the world, they risk bringing back these variants to their communities if they get exposed here in Miami.”During his first presidential address last week, Joe Biden mandated all states make all Americans eligible for vaccines by May 1 and boldly claimed that people could look forward to possibly gathering in large groups for Independence Day. But in Miami, some young partygoers argue there’s no harm gathering now as long as they avoid family members, friends, and others who are at high risk from being hospitalized or dying from COVID-19, such as senior citizens 65 and over.On Saturday night, shortly after 11 p.m., Adrian Colon, a 38-year-old real estate agent, joined three other friends for a late dinner at Komodo Miami. He told The Daily Beast that he and other friends caught COVID-19 at different times over the summer. View this post on Instagram A post shared by Michael Aidala (@michaelaidalamusic) “I quarantined for two weeks,” Colon said. “A friend of mine recently got sick and he didn’t go out until he tested negative. And if you have elderly people in your family, then don’t be stupid and hang out with them after you go out partying.”Still, Colon, who sported a mask while speaking to The Daily Beast outside the restaurant’s entrance, said enforcement measures in the city were a joke.“You go into any place and people will wear their masks on for 10 seconds and take them off,” he said. “You will see 20, 30 people sitting at one table everywhere in Miami.”Dror said he and his friends follow a similar game plan. “I know friends who don’t see their parents and their grandparents since this all started,” he said. “It looks a little bit irresponsible going to all these parties. But some people really need to dance in order to live. It’s my thing, I live for the people.”Despite his carefree attitude, Dror insisted he’s not taken the coronavirus for granted. He’s gotten tested for COVID-19 a couple of times and he plans on getting vaccinated once he’s eligible, he noted. “I want people to feel comfortable being near me,” he said. “But I don’t think a lot of people look at Miami’s party scene in a bad way. It’s something very beautiful.”Of more immediate concern to Dror than the pandemic: He gained two new followers on Instagram from Chile who hit him up about meeting in Miami and partying.“I think a lot of people are saying, ‘I wish I could do that,’” he said. “Whoever is looking for a big party, they are coming to Miami.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO's QANON Docuseries Believes It Has Discovered Q's Identity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hbo-qanon-docuseries-q-storm-090017080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBOA mishmash of abject nonsense about global elite cabals, deep state operatives, and pedophilic child-sex traffickers who consume babies’ fear for its rejuvenating power, QAnon’s belief system is so absurd that it would be laughable if it wasn’t so popular—and thus so dangerous.Shot over the past three years, Cullen Hoback’s excellent Q: Into the Storm (March 21 on HBO) is a complex story about free speech, social media, anti-establishment fury, white nationalist intolerance, crackpot fantasy, and anarchist villainy, all of which contributed to the rise of the infamous conspiracy theory, which during Donald Trump’s presidency took hold of factions of the GOP, and helped fuel the insurrectionist January 6 Capitol riots. Part on-the-ground journalistic exposé, part sociological study of corrosive internet culture, and part whodunit, the six-part affair shines a spotlight on one of the darkest corners of contemporary American life.[Spoilers Follow]What it locates in that gloom, among other things, is the apparent identity of Q himself: Ron Watkins. Inside Woody Allen’s Close Friendship With Jeffrey EpsteinHoback’s docuseries focuses on a collection of out-there individuals, beginning—in the premiere’s opening scene—with Watkins, the administrator of 8chan, an everything-goes message board that was owned by his father Jim Watkins, and hosted on servers located (as Jim himself was) in Manila. Jim made money via a pig farm, local retail shops, and by hosting websites in places like the Philippines, where they weren’t beholden to other nations’ laws. One of those platforms was 8chan (now 8kun), which Jim purchased from Fredrick Brennan, a smart, talkative young disabled man who created the site when he was 19 years old before selling it to Jim, who promptly hired Fredrick as its maiden administrator and relocated him to Manila.8chan was an image board where anonymous users could indulge in unbridled free speech, including memes, photos, and diatribes about white nationalism, sexism, racism, and any other ugly or deviant thing that’s technically permitted by the First Amendment. It was there that, following a brief stint on 4chan (its more moderated ancestor), Q took up permanent residence. Claiming to be a military insider with “Q-level clearance” who was supposedly close to Trump, Q made regular posts (known as “QDrops”) that were full of coded warnings and premonitions about the coming “storm” that would unmask the deep state, and lead to the arrest, trial, and execution of alleged liberal criminals. Adherents began going on “digs” (i.e. research and analysis) to decipher the meanings of these messages, and then re-posting their conjecture in an effort to crowdsource further answers. As Q: Into the Storm defines it, QAnon (the “anon” is short for “anonymous,” in reference to both Q and those who frequented such boards) was “part interactive game, part religion, part political movement.”In its early going, the series depicts a few die-hard supporters while providing a handy primer on QAnon’s operation and terminology, including “red pill” (a Matrix-inspired phrase meant to imply someone's eyes being opened to the truth) and and its White Squall mantra, “Where we go one, we go all.” Its primary subject, however, is the drama surrounding 8chan. According to early QAnon supporter Paul Furber, Q’s posts changed when he moved to 8chan, suggesting that an imposter was actually posing as the mystery figure. Nonetheless, Q’s subsequent missives were eagerly received by 8chan denizens, fueling the site’s popularity and spawning a cottage industry around his every word, courtesy of Qtubers like Dustin Nemos, Craig James and Liz Crokin, all of whom wax rhapsodic about the movement. To them, Q was a veritable omniscient deity; Crokin claims that Q is so magical she’d now believe anything, including that the Earth is flat. But to Ron and Jim, who profess their disinterest in politics and Q, he was supposedly just one of many users on the site.Ron comes across as a soft-spoken, off-kilter narcissist whose every word is unreliable, and that goes double for Jim, who has a creepy twinkle in his eye, and an admitted fondness for politically incorrect off-camera speech. When 8chan refused to take down the manifestos of the 2019 Christchurch shooter (and two subsequent copycats), Fredrick had a contentious falling out with Ron and Jim, and their conflict is one of the central dynamics of Q: Into the Storm, since at the same time that 8chan was supplying a safe haven for murderous hatemongers, it was also giving rise to QAnon.In lucid fashion, Hoback’s docuseries explicates the evolution of this radical, incel-filled corner of the online universe, tracing a clear line from Gamergate (an attack on female video gamers and journalists by a hostile misogynistic mob), to Pizzagate (a 2016 conspiracy about Hilary Clinton and John Podesta trafficking children in the non-existent basement of Washington, D.C.’s Comet Ping Pong pizzeria), to QAnon, which was the culmination of this milieu’s disgusting, prejudiced, paranoid, conspiracy-minded ideas and elements. Ron Watkins HBO Q: Into the Storm is awash in wild players, weird terminology, and unhinged craziness. With the personable Hoback as its guide, it offers real-time access to Ron, Jim, Fredrick, Qtubers, OAN’s Jack Posobiec, and more, and is bolstered by an avalanche of news and internet clips, archival material, and interviews with experts (such as The Daily Beast’s Will Sommer). Q soon attracted the attention of right-wing bigwigs like Roger Stone, Michael Flynn, Steve Bannon, and Trump himself, who publicly claimed ignorance about QAnon but eventually began reposting Q memes and using Q phrases to court its followers. Over the course of its six installments, the docuseries dives headfirst into what appears to be a prank gone awry, with Q metastasizing from an online lark (or LARP, aka Live-Action Role-Playing game) to a feedback loop-fed crusade embraced by nihilistic loons and promoted by anti-democratic right-wingers like Marjorie Taylor Greene and Lauren Boebert.‘South Park’ Brutally Mocks Wacky QAnon Supporters in Vaccination SpecialRife with talk about inventive tripcodes, covert psyops, child porn, and Section 230 (which shields websites from being sued for what users say on them), Q: Into the Storm becomes a frightening look at the dangers of unfettered free speech, as well as a portrait of a 21st-century America in thrall to delusions, and the myriad people who promote those falsehoods for financial or political gain. In its final installment, which concludes shortly after the Jan. 6 riots (which he attended alongside Jim, camera in tow), Hoback persuasively points the finger at Watkins as the mastermind of this Q ruse. In doing so, he not only brings some closure to his wide-ranging investigation, but also illustrates how modern society is at the mercy of shadowy manipulators using the internet to turn their destructive lies into reality.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: More Americans than ever view China as greatest enemy...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/337457/new-high-perceptions-china-greatest-enemy.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' perceptions of China as their country's greatest enemy hit a new high; a record 63% see China's economic power as a critical threat to U.S. vital interests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Confesses To Killing Grandfather, Pulls Ears From Pocket During Questioning...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/15/florida-man-confesses-grandfather-murder-human-ears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida man is charged with murdering his 77-year-old grandfather and cutting the elderly man’s ears off with a knife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD WEIGHS RISK OF COVID VAX</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-summits-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-37c3f8fa9523c58576cbff6d9c13a103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — With coronavirus cases rising in many places, governments faced the grimmest of dilemmas Tuesday: push on with a vaccine that is known to save lives or suspend use of AstraZeneca...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look out, Labs: Could French bulldog become favorite pooch?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dogs-5c4ae261bc242119b45f68af02ae22f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Could the French bulldog become America's favorite purebred pooch? After riding a rocket ship to popularity over the last quarter-century, Frenchies came in second only to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O takes veiled swipe at Meghan's Oprah interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9367567/Michelle-Obama-Meghan-Markle-interview-Public-service-isnt-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michelle Obama took a thinly veiled swipe at Meghan Markle's Oprah interview on Tuesday morning, saying that she personally chooses to focus on the people she 'serves'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New poll shows Cuban-American voters align with GOP...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/florida/story/2021/03/16/new-poll-shows-cuban-american-voters-align-with-gop-1368365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A lot of the gains Democrats were making and did make during the Obama years seemed to have been wiped,&amp;quot; said the pollster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI facing allegation that its background check of Justice Kavanaugh was 'fake'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fbi-facing-allegation-that-its-2018-background-check-of-brett-kavanaugh-was-e2-80-98fake-e2-80-99/ar-BB1eD0D9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is facing new scrutiny for its 2018 background check of Brett Kavanaugh, the supreme court justice, after a lawmaker suggested that the investigation may have been “fake”. Sheldon Whitehouse, a Democratic senator and former prosecutor who serves on the judiciary committee, is calling on the newly-confirmed attorney general, Merrick Garland, to help facilitate “proper oversight” by the Senate into questions about how thoroughly the FBI...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Air Force will test bizarre 'hypersonic' weapon this month...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/us-hypersonic-missile-test.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The test has already been delayed, and there are real questions about the technology's purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea tells new U.S. administration to cease war games if wants to 'sleep in peace'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210316084341-lft53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-N.Korea tells new U.S. administration to cease war games if wants to 'sleep in peace'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists 'stunned' by plants found mile under Greenland icesheet, revealing previous total ice loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/03/210315165639.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencedaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists found frozen plant fossils, preserved under a mile of ice on Greenland. The discovery helps confirm a new and troubling understanding that the Greenland Ice Sheet has melted entirely during recent warm periods in Earth's history -- like the one we are now creating with human-caused climate change. The new study provides strong evidence that Greenland is more sensitive to climate change than previously understood -- and at risk of irreversibly melting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Warns Against Tech Excess in Sign Crackdown Will Widen...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/xi-jinping-warns-against-tech-excess-in-sign-crackdown-will-widen/ar-BB1eCFjy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s top leader warned that Beijing will go after so-called “platform” companies that have amassed data and market power, a sign that the months-long crackdown on the country’s internet sector is only just beginning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge fight looms?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/543314-huge-fight-looms-over-raising-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is gearing up for a battle over raising taxes as President Biden looks for a way to pay for his agenda while Republicans are planning to dig in their heels ahead of the 2022 elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special election a bellwether for Texas Dems...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/543319-special-election-a-bellwether-for-texas-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans and Democrats are lining up to replace the late Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC announces next fight will have no capacity limits on fans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/543340-ufc-announces-next-fight-in-florida-will-have-no-capacity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UFC President Dana White announced that UFC 261 mixed martial arts fight will take place next month with no capacity limits for audience members amid the ongoing coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
