<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Agrees to $1 Million Fine for Violating Human Rights Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-news-agrees-to-dollar1-million-fine-for-violating-human-rights-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News effectively admitted to a pattern of misconduct and has agreed to pay a civil penalty in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland limits indoor dining to fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210629-ireland-limits-indoor-dining-to-fully-vaccinated-over-delta-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ireland said on Tuesday it will restrict indoor drinking and eating in bars and restaurants to those who are fully vaccinated against COVID-19 or who have previously been infected by it due to concer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPad the size of CAR-WHEEL 'secretly being created'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3181101/apple-secretly-ipad-car-wheel-biggest-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE is considering building its biggest iPad yet to further blur the lines between laptops and tablets, according to a report. The Cupertino iPhone-maker could release a tablet with a much larger…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New gatekeepers: GOOGLE will warn you about 'fake news' websites before you click...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3174436/google-warn-fake-news-websites-click/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOGLE has begun warning users that its search results may be unreliable. The feature is aimed at breaking news stories, when information is often rapidly changing and sometimes inaccurate. Read al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivor describes escape: 'I kept going, screaming... I want to live'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/survivor-describes-escape-from-florida-condo-collapse-i-kept-going-screaming-i-want-to-live/ar-AALAzj3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maria Iliana Monteagudo was asleep early Thursday morning when the building started moving. She grabbed her purse, credit cards, and blew out a candle as she escaped her unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Wuhan lab's rumbling sewers and filthy cages...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3174242/wuhan-labs-leak-covid-chaotic-crowded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH crumbling sewers and filthy animal cages, these are the shoddy conditions of labs in Wuhan which could have unleashed Covid. A bombshell study found grotty sewage systems were potentially cont…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friendly dolphin could die if people keep riding it...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article252442433.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is clear that the dolphin is already in danger from the human interactions.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online activism spilling into streets of Southern California, sparking post-Trump movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Online-activism-is-spilling-into-the-streets-of-16281500.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA ANA, Calif. -- A week before California reopened its economy, a group of 100 or so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta variant  prompts new restrictions worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/spread-of-delta-variant-prompts-new-restrictions-worldwide/ar-AALwoub?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new curbs on travel and daily life stretched from Australia and Bangladesh to South Africa and Germany. The World Health Organization urged faster deployment of coronavirus vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailer: First look at 'SOPRANOS' prequel...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-videos/sopranos-prequel-trailer-many-saints-of-newark-1234973262/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first new Sopranos content in 14 years has been released. Below is the trailer for the long-awaited prequel movie The Many Saints of Newark. The film stars an ensemble cast that includes Michae…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant 'elephant pig' born with trunk and one eye baffles farmer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mutant-elephant-pig-born-trunk-24418776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deformed piglet looked barely able to move in a short video taken at the farm in the Philippines. Despite vets being called, it sadly died shortly after being born</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/slideshows/healthiest-communities-in-the-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;See the counties that scored the highest in U.S. News' annual Healthiest Communities ranking and analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Alamos County, NM, Named Healthiest Community...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-06-29/los-alamos-americas-healthiest-county-has-a-formula-for-battling-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Alamos County repeats as No. 1 in U.S. News’ Healthiest Communities rankings, boasting a reliance on science and a community that proved effective in dealing with the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS:  NSA SPYING ON NETWORK!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tucker-carlson-claims-the-nsa-is-monitoring-his-communications-in-an-attempt-to-take-this-show-off-the-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson claimed on Monday night that his communications are being monitored by the NSA "in an attempt to take this show off the air."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Did Netanyahu sabotage ties with USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/netanyahu-denies-sabotaging-ties-with-us-672274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former prime minister Benjamin Netanyahu denied charges that he was deliberately trying to harm Israel's relationship with the Biden administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming culture war over returning to the office...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/the-coming-culture-war-over-returning-to-the-office-090034061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has been a culture war from the very start: over lockdowns, masks, schools, vaccines. It's likely that it will be ushered out with an entirely new culture war, centered on cubicles and desks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN: LA urges everyone to wear mask indoors as variant spreads...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/l-a-county-urges-everyone-to-wear-masks-in-public-indoor-places-as-delta-variant-spreads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials in Los Angeles County now strongly recommend that people wear masks indoors in public places — regardless of their vaccination status — to prevent the spread of the highly transmis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani being investigated over Turkish lobbying...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/giuliani-investigated-turkish-lobbying-source/story?id=78557555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump's attorney Rudy Giuliani is facing a federal inquiry over possible improper lobbying for Turkey, a source familiar with the matter told ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JILL BIDEN GETS VOGUE COVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3180183/jill-biden-vogue-cover-melania-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JILL Biden has secured the Vogue cover Melania Trump always wanted – and used the interview to take a swipe at Donald, calling Joe “calmer.” The First Lady, wearing a floral Oscar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Great Resignation' gains steam as return-to-work plans take effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/29/more-people-plan-to-quit-as-return-to-work-plans-go-into-effect-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the pandemic, a growing number of workers are rethinking what they want in a job and a lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boring news cycle deals blow to partisan media...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/partisan-media-biden-trump-26f54a8b-d4e2-4319-a185-bd5f55ac661f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outlets most dependent on controversy have struggled to find a foothold in the Biden era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicidal crises, mental fatigue: Kids grapple with reentry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-cf6997107e7991393c70dd62ddbd196e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two suicidal crises during pandemic isolation, 16-year-old Zach Sampson feels stronger but worries his social skills have gone stale. Amara Bhatia has overcome her pandemic depression but the teen feels worn down, in a state of "neutralness.'' Virginia Shipp is adjusting but says returning to normal “is kind of unnormal for me.’’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill To Decriminalize Psychedelics, Ecstasy In CA Gains Momentum...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/28/sb519-proposal-decriminalize-psychedelics-mushrooms-mdma-lsd-gains-momentum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bay Area lawmaker's bill that would decriminalize the personal possession of several psychedelic drugs begins winding its way through the California State Assembly this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Prices Jump Most in Three Decades...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-housing-prices-jump-most-132347212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. home prices jumped the most in more than 30 years in April.Nationally, the S&amp;P CoreLogic Case-Shiller index of property values climbed 14.6% from a year earlier, the biggest gain in data going back to 1988. That came after 13.2% increase in March, and was the 11th straight month that price gains accelerated.Home prices in 20 U.S. cities, meanwhile, jumped 14.9%, beating the median estimate in a survey of Bloomberg economists and was the biggest gain since 2005.“April’s perfor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Revival of Stoicism...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxvmw/the-revival-of-stoicism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone from Silicon Valley billionaires to self-help enthusiasts is repurposing Stoicism for our modern age, with results that are good, bad, and highly indifferent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Secret History of Proud Boys' McInnes...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/the-secret-history-of-gavin-mcinnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the ’90s, he played punk rock and helped create Vice magazine. Five years ago, he founded a very different organization: the Proud Boys, the far-right group that came to personify the vilest tendencies of Trump’s America. A former Vice editor interviews one of our era’s most troubling extremists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When A City-Sized Star Becomes A Black Hole's Lunch, The Universe Roils...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/29/1011047410/city-sized-neutron-star-massive-black-hole-collide-gulps-universe-gravitational</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a smack down of one space monster by another: Scientists have made unprecedented observations of two black holes gobbling two neutron stars — among the weirdest space collisions ever detected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 40% Of San Fran Residents Plan To Move Amid Spike In Crime, Homelessness...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/29/poll-san-francisco-residents-consider-relocating-as-crime-worsen-quality-of-life-in-a-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As San Francisco tries to bounce back from the devastating impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, crime and homelessness now rank among the highest levels of concerns among local residents, many who are contemplating relocating, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations, Drownings...</title>
      <link>https://www.opb.org/article/2021/06/28/oregon-heat-wave-record-temperatures-health-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.opb.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures will begin to fall tonight and are forecast to be in the 90s for the rest of the week, bringing Oregonians some limited relief from dangerous heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letter sent in April warned damage was accelerating...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/29/us/florida-building-collapse-letter/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A correspondence from the board president of Champlain Towers South, which unexpectedly crashed to the ground last week in Surfside, Florida, describes the progression of decay at the building since 2018 saying, "the observable damage such as in the garage has gotten significantly worse since the initial inspection."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Wants to Scan Your Eyeball in Exchange for Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/sam-altman-wants-to-scan-your-eyeball-in-exchange-for-cryptocurrency/ar-AALzWOe </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson says 'Biden administration spying' on him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/560656-tucker-carlson-says-biden-administration-is-spying-on-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Tucker Carlson on Monday alleged that the Biden administration was “spying” on him in an effort to “take this show off the air.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF Australia in lockdown as Delta variant spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/australianz/half-of-australias-population-in-lockdown-as-delta-covid-19-variant-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brisbane became Australia's fourth regional capital city to restrict movement outside of homes.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 STILL MISSING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-miami-florida-a4a6051f1aa0168f73e833852617af9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Florida (AP) — The slow work of sifting through the remnants of a collapsed Florida condo building stretched into a sixth day Tuesday, as families desperate for progress endured a wrenching wait for answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans' long race to 2024 begins...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-michael-pence-election-2020-campaign-2016-government-and-politics-6c670a583ea8be1b46196ec75134623c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — In the past week alone, Nikki Haley regaled activists in Iowa, Mike Pence courted donors in California and Donald Trump returned to the rally stage , teasing a third campaign for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak in Fiji batters economy, tests health system...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fiji-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-business-health-10e9378c350adc39461e201308e92c15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUVA, Fiji (AP) — A growing coronavirus outbreak in Fiji is stretching the health system and devastating the economy. It has even prompted the government to offer jobless people tools and cash to become farmers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/heat-wave-builds-across-us-northwest-shattering-records/ar-AALxG5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unrelenting heat wave that shattered temperature records across the U.S. Pacific Northwest on Monday and threatens to smother the region for another six straight days has begun to trigger rolling blackouts in some parts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commodity Traders Making Billions...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/market/commodities/commodity-traders-make-billions-as-oil-copper-battery-metals-prices-rise-11624945411580.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From oil to steel, raw material prices are surging. As the world economy recovers, how much further does the boom have to run?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOFTBANK Mothballs Once-Hyped $1,800 Pepper Humanoid Robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/softbank-mothballs-once-hyped-1-800-pepper-humanoid-robot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SoftBank Halts Production of $1,800 Pepper Humanoid Robot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami condo parking garage flooded often before collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/champlain-towers-parking-garage-flooded-often-before-collapse-residents-and-ex-worker-say/ar-AALyroI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Columbia highest ever...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2021-06-28-record-heat-wave-northwest-washington-oregon-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's rewriting the record book. Here is a list of the records this heat wave has smashed already. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOLFF:  Giuliani was 'drinking heavily and incoherently telling Trump that Pence would overturn election results'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9734443/Book-Giuliani-drinking-heavily-telling-Trump-Pence-overturn-election-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani was 'heavily drinking' and fueling Trump's false belief that Pence could overturn the election results the day before the Jan. 6 Capitol riot, according to an upcoming book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Feinstein's Tahoe Compound For Sale at $41 Million....</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/06/26/sen-dianne-feinstein-tahoe-vacation-compound-for-sale-41-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Sen. Dianne Feinstein has put her picturesque Lake Tahoe vacation property up for sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil senators file case against Bolsonaro for malfeasance...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-senators-file-case-against-203820054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Brazilian senators formally accused President Jair Bolsonaro of malfeasance before the Supreme Court Monday over allegations he failed to have a top ally investigated for suspicions of massive corruption in the purchase of Covid-19 vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAT FIGHT:  New weight-loss tool prevents mouth from opening more than 2mm...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/jun/28/new-weight-loss-tool-dentalslim-diet-control</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DentalSlim Diet, which uses magnets, has been likened to ‘medieval torture device’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honeymoon fades as priorities downplayed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-honeymoon-with-liberals-fades-as-priorities-are-downplayed/ar-AALwmQs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s honeymoon with the most liberal wing of his party risks an abrupt and politically damaging end, with rising anxiety among progressives that the president won’t fulfill their aspirations for climate policy or expansions of voting rights and spending on social programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives say infrastructure compromise renews their doubts about Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/progressives-infrastructure-deal-gop-renews-201554001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's statement Saturday retreating from a threat to hold an infrastructure deal hostage to a bigger bill has left progressives fretting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico top court decriminalizes recreational marijuana use...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-top-court-decriminalizes-recreational-222500862.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's Supreme Court on Monday decriminalized recreational marijuana use for adults, drawing a cautious welcome from activists who said users face a "legal vacuum" until lawmakers pass a stalled legalization bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condo collapse in Miami triggers fear in coastal cities...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/condo-collapse-surfside-triggers-fear-215500288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the world spotlight shines on Surfside’s condo collapse, other coastal cities in South Florida are asking the question: Could it happen here? Those same cities want to make sure it doesn’t. Miami-Dade County is already planning an audit of older buildings after Thursday’s collapse of the Champlain Towers South condo. Coastal cities from Fort Lauderdale to Hollywood, Hallandale Beach and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo Musical Written by Harvey Weinstein Accuser, With Music from Diane Warren, Will Open Not Far from His Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/28/diane-warren-susan-stroman-musical-the-right-girl-to-get-autumn-workshop-in-upstate-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Right Girl” is the name of the musical with songs by Diane Warren, directed by Tony winner Susan Stroman. The musical is opening in the wrong place at the right time. Written by a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victim was in town for virus funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/miami-condo-collapse-man-in-town-for-covid-19-funeral-among-missing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay Kleiman traveled from Puerto Rico to go back to the condominium where he grew up north of Miami Beach for an old high school friend's funeral. But hours before the ceremony, the high-rise building in the affluent neighborhood of Surfside collapsed, leaving more than 100 people missing overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Marine shot in Midtown...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/28/police-to-flood-the-zone-in-times-square-after-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor de Blasio on Monday vowed police would “flood the zone” in Times Square in wake of the shooting that injured a tourist — as the Big Apple seeks to rebound from the COVID-19 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL says 'Football is gay'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2021/06/28/nfl-carl-nassib-football-gay-commercial/7783421002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A week after Carl Nassib publicly came out, the NFL released a new commercial, "Football is gay," showing support of the LGBTQ+ community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS:  Cracked concrete, standing water days before...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article252421658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was nothing unusual about the lobby and pool area at Champlain Towers South condo, which looked clean and well maintained to a commercial pool contractor who visited the building last Tuesday, just 36 hours before half of the building unexpectedly collapsed. Then, he saw the basement-level garage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New camo tech makes soldiers virtually 'invisible'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israels-camouflage-technology-soldiers-virtually-082656169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polaris Solutions is working with special forces units in Canada and the United States to bring the technology to North America, it was reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AS HELL: Pakistan city hottest place on EARTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3176259/pakistan-city-hottest-earth-52c-no-air-con/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PAKISTAN city is now the hottest place on Earth at 52C – where most homes don’t have air-con and it’s too hot to touch the floor. That’s far hotter than in 2015, when two heatwa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Bailout Plagued by Potential $260 Billion in Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/06/28/government-pandemic-loans-plagued-by-potential-260-billion-in-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hasty work behind the PPP and other relief loans shows the limits of big government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN staff angered at news chief's conflict of interest over Israel ambassador pick...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/28/cnn-workers-mad-at-top-news-chiefs-conflict-of-interest-over-israel-pick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN staff are furious after the husband of their top news chief was nominated for US ambassador to Israel – claiming the move is a conflict of interest, The Post is told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Nevada title won by trans woman for 1st time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nv-state-wire-nevada-entertainment-33ec7e16a75242ab51bbf19e1a816bb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — For the first time in the pageant’s history, the title of Miss Nevada USA has been won by a transgender woman. Kataluna Enriquez was crowned the winner Sunday at the South Point hotel-casino in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untold story of how racy sexts upended key Senate race and shifted power in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/opinion/article252334948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A phone call helped derail Cal Cunningham’s campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How daily lives are tracked by phones, laptops and even doorbells...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/15407421/daily-lives-tracked-doorbells-how-your-data-collected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN OXFORD professor has claimed that we are allowing more and more of our personal data to be used – and are being spied on by DOORBELLS.  Professor Carissa Veliz  has warned that o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order pushes enforcement throughout economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-white-house-prepares-order-directing-agencies-consider-antitrust-2021-06-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is working on an antitrust executive order that aims to push government agencies to consider how their decisions will impact competition in an industry, according to two sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant eruption of Costa Rica volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210628-giant-eruption-of-costa-rica-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Giant eruption of Costa Rica volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts share new theories...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/28/florida-building-collapse-reportedly-started-from-the-bottom-of-the-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dusenberry — who has investigated other building collapses — told the New York Times that the way the building went down suggests there could be an issue with foundation of the building — such as &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pools closed...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/weather/2021/06/portland-parks-pools-max-service-schools-closed-due-to-extreme-heat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out this list of businesses and services that are closed Monday due to historic high temperatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-Pound Chunk Of Ice Crashes Through Roof Of CA Home...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/25/10-pound-chunk-of-ice-falls-through-roof-of-yucaipa-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlett Yablonsky said she and her little dog, Doodles, had just gotten up off the couch and gone to bed Thursday night when what sounded like a bomb blast shook them back awake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's oldest person aged 119' credits diet of butter, honey, cheese and egg...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3173664/gran-worlds-oldest-person-119-diet-turkey-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GRAN claimed to be the world’s oldest person has celebrated turning 119 – and puts her long life down to her fatty diet of butter and cheese. Seker Arslan was reported to be even older yest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House prepping big assault on monopolies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/28/white-house-monopolies-executive-order-496749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An executive order being crafted for President Joe Biden's signature seeks to go beyond antitrust enforcement to promote competition throughout the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals struggle with jammed ERs after exodus of nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2021/06/hospitals-struggle-to-deal-with-jammed-emergency-rooms-after-exodus-of-nurses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ER surge has added more stress to the lives of front-line health care workers who hoped for a peaceful interlude after the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AMAZON Bullies, Manipulates, and Lies to Reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2021/06/amazon-journalists-pr-tactics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company's cutthroat corporate culture cripples critical coverage—and your right to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man threatened to blow up MCDONALD's over missing dipping sauce...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/dipping-sauce-threat-416058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 28--After realizing that dipping sauce was not included with his Chicken McNuggets order, an Iowa man called his local McDonald’s and threatened to blow up the restaurant, according to investigat</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
