<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Good' Cholesterol Vital To Liver Protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/good-cholesterol-hdl-liver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers reveal that a form of good cholesterol, known as HDL3, protects against liver inflammation by blocking inflammatory signals from gut bacteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You may be recovering from your workouts all wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.universalpersonality.com/you-may-be-recovering-from-your-workouts-all-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.universalpersonality.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Placeholder while article actions load You’re on the last set of squats at the gym at the end of a long week, and your legs feel like lead. You’re proud of your progress, but your muscles have gone on strike, and you’d like to make them feel better. You might think: Time to take it […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air stunt goes badly wrong as pilots try to swap planes 12,000ft up...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5194939/plane-swap-wrong-red-bull-spirals-out-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING footage shows the moment a Red Bull plane plunged to the ground after a stunt went wrong. Daredevil pilots and cousins Luke Aikins and Andy Farrington tried to complete a plane swap near E…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal today?</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/tech/technology/twitter-on-track-to-reach-deal-with-elon-musk-as-soon-as-monday/articleshow/91075205.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter may announce the $43 billion deal later on Monday once its board has met to recommend the transaction to Twitter shareholders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Voters Haven't Been Afraid Like This in Long Time...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/25/american-voters-havent-been-afraid-like-this-in-a-long-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rare convergence, America’s voters are not merely unhappy with their political leadership, but awash in fears about economic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden prime target if Republicans win Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-2022-midterm-elections-biden-europe-elise-stefanik-0e782fc6486c2c625194622ae244e4ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Intelligence officials had gathered to brief select members of Congress on future threats to U.S. elections when a key lawmaker in the room, No. 3 House Republican Elise Stefanik of New York, tried to move the discussion to a new topic: Hunter Biden’s laptop .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempers flare over emotion-sensing AI...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mood-emotion-sensing-ai-tempers-flare-a01efe11-362d-4fab-9d86-cee64ff839f1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology's already being put to use, but critics say it's inaccurate and dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest person dies at 119...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5195860/worlds-oldest-person-kane-tanaka-dies-aged-119/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s oldest person, Kane Tanaka, has passed away aged 119. Tanaka – who beat cancer and spent her life eating sweets and drinking cola – died in her nursing home in Japan o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly woman has car stolen, gets run over in church parking lot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-crooks-steals-car-run-victim-over-church-parking-lot-20220424-qdslfmph2fcupea6qysefgmswq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victim Lorraine Lombardo, 73, was seriously injured but is expected to survive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Virginia courthouse, fans clamor for seats. Alpacas must wait outside...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/in-va-court-depp-fans-clamor-for-seats-alpacas-must-wait-outside/ar-AAWyznc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID cases rising sharply again...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2667898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif. — Here we go again? COVID-19 cases and hospitalizations are rising once again across the country, driven by more contagious subvariants of the virus and leaving health experts unsure whether vaccination and immunity from prior infection will be ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing districts placed under lockdown as infections mount...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-china-beijing-04f6bab983b14f9ff89459d2e3c99fdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China’s capital Beijing began testing millions of residents and shutting down residential and business districts Monday amid a new outbreak of COVID-19. While only 70 cases have been found so far in the city of more than 21 million since the outbreak surfaced Friday, authorities have implemented extreme measures to prevent a further spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUNK AT 76: DEBBIE HARRY STILL ROCKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10748033/Debbie-Harry-76-shows-bold-sense-style-Glasgow-gig.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 76-year-old rocker wowed the crowd at Glasgow's Hydro arena on Friday night even before she sang a single note as the iconic American band group kicked off their first UK tour in five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin looks unsteady in Easter church service footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10748825/Putin-looks-unsteady-Easter-church-service-footage-showing-biting-lip-fidgeting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nervous-looking Putin bit his lip while attending the church service, fidgeting and appearing distracted while watching the church service. He appeared to chew his lips, shifting uncomfortably.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What doomed CNN+?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/24/cnn-plus-what-went-wrong-why-it-was-canceled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN executives wanted CNN+ to compete with The New York Times. But an unusual series of events doomed the streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor overseeing corona testing at BWI airport accused of health-care fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/doctor-overseeing-coronavirus-testing-baltimore-200038131.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prominent Maryland doctor overseeing coronavirus testing at Baltimore-Washington International Marshall Airport and other sites in Anne Arundel and Prince George's counties was indicted on Tuesday, accused by federal prosecutors of overcharging Medicare and other insurers by more than $1.5 million. Ron Elfenbein, 47, has been a frequent guest on local and national television news during broadcasts about coronavirus testing, treatments and vaccines. At an August ribbon-cutting for the new clini</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron remains Europe's de facto leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/france-s-macron-wins-presidency-holding-off-le-pen-s-far-right-threat-to-upend-europe-and-relations-with-russia/ar-AAWwXGc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTS TURN DEADLY IN PARIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/paris-police-shoot-two-dead-26788266 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bloodbath happened on the ancient Pont Neuf, in the centre of the city, soon after Emmanuel Macron’s re-election as President on Sunday night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Chinese Naval Base in Solomons a 'Red Line,' Australian PM Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2022-04-24/scott-morrison-china-naval-base-solomon-islands-red-line/101011710</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Morrison says the Prime Minister of Solomon Islands has assured him there will be no Chinese military bases and dismisses suggestions Australia's foreign aid cuts contributed to the security pact between the two nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How mom's illicit romance with her handyman ended in brutal murder...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/york-mom-illicit-romance-her-194500288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — It was a crime of passion, two years in the making, against a scandalous backdrop of illicit sex and deceit: A Queens mom and the local handyman were on-and-off lovers until their final, fatal meeting in the basement of her Tudor-style home. For Orsolya Gaal, 51, there was no inkling of the horrors ahead when she headed into Manhattan for a Lincoln Center show with friends on Good ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relief, not joy, at low-key election party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/relief-not-joy-low-key-220030276.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Emmanuel Macron's election party Sunday in the shadow of the Eiffel Tower, the atmosphere was restrained, the victory speech short and most people felt relief, rather than a desire to celebrate wildly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global military spending reaches record levels...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/military-spending-reaches-record-levels-162607950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global military spending rose again in 2021, setting new records as Russia continued to beef up its military prior to its invasion of Ukraine, researchers said Monday, predicting the trend would continue in Europe in particular.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In troubled France, no honeymoon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/analysis-troubled-france-no-honeymoon-185958539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emmanuel Macron may have seen off far-right leader Marine Le Pen, but his second term could be even rockier than the first with mounting political opposition and boiling social discontent. As his supporters savoured a hard-earned re-election at a rally by the Eiffel Tower on Sunday, Macron acknowledged in his victory speech that many people who voted for him did so to block Le Pen and not because they support his ideas. "No one will be left by the wayside," Macron said, flanked by his wife Brigitte.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER under shareholder pressure to seek deal with Musk... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-twitter-under-shareholder-pressure-200604992.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) -Twitter Inc kicked off deal negotiations with Elon Musk on Sunday after he wooed many of the social media company's shareholders with financing details on his $43 billion acquisition offer, people familiar with the matter said. The company's decision to engage with Musk, taken earlier on Sunday, does not mean that it will accept his $54.20 per share bid, the sources said. It signifies, however, that Twitter is now exploring whether a sale of the company to Musk is possible on attractive terms, the sources added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3-legged dog with cancer jumps into river to save baby otter...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article260719512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“First time swimming with three legs and he comes out of the water with a baby otter in his mouth.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE PEN DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/marine-le-pen-fighter-suffering-190552478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine Le Pen, who on Sunday lost the second round of France's presidential election to Emmanuel Macron, had fought hard to make her far-right party electable but in the end failed by a wide margin to win over a majority of voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE BLOWOUT! LE LANDSLIDE!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/macron-le-pen-france-faces-001327854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (Reuters) -French President Emmanuel Macron defeated his far-right rival Marine Le Pen on Sunday by a comfortable margin, securing a second term and heading off what would have been a political earthquake. European leaders also welcomed the news that pro-European Union Macron and not nationalist eurosceptic Le Pen had won. "I am very relieved - it had looked very close and populism was at our door," 42-year old Alessandro Paleni told Reuters at the Macron rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE PEN DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/macron-wins-key-quotes-frances-181942066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Emmanuel Macron triumphed over his far-right rival Marine Le Pen by a comfortable margin in France's election on Sunday, winning a second term and heading off what would have been a political earthquake. Even so, the far right scored its highest ever score in a presidential election. Marine Le Pen, defeated far-right challenger:"Tonight's result is in itself a remarkable victory (for us)."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeological dig in Turkey uncovers massive underground city...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/article-704928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers believe the underground city may be the largest in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ allows cops to smoke pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nj-legal-cannabis-off-duty-police-officers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey's attorney general says the state's new legal weed law doesn't prohibit cops from using cannabis while off-duty. But the mayor of Jersey City said he will fire any cop who tests positive at any time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN:  'He's a liar and a traitor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/warren-says-kevin-mccarthy-liar-traitor-0b4583d9-5a3e-48cd-a085-75361873be8e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts Democrat was asked about audio of the GOP leader saying he planned to urge President Trump to resign over the Jan. 6 riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20220424-live-follow-the-results-of-france-s-presidential-election-run-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French voters went to the polls on Sunday for the presidential election run-off pitting incumbent Emmanuel Macron against far-right National Rally candidate Marine Le Pen. FRANCE 24 brings you real-t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French presidential finale... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-french-election-voting-results-f5b549e3b99930ee05bed17a9d3870b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — From bucolic villages to humming cities, French voters on Sunday were choosing between two radically different futures for their country, with President Emmanuel Macron offering a centrist pro-European outlook if he is reelected while far-right challenger Marine Le Pen is pledging seismic changes for France and its allies if she becomes the country's first female leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm in Brussels as shock Pen victory would 'spell end of EU'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/18318364/france-election-le-pen-victory-eu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALARM bells are ringing in Brussels over fears a shock victory for Marine Le Pen today in today’s French presidential election could “spell the end of the EU as we know it”. The r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Royals Selling Homes, Yachts, Art as Crown Prince Cuts Income...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/economy/saudi-royals-are-selling-homes-yachts-and-art-as-crown-prince-cuts-income-11650801706282.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kingdom’s senior princes are trying to raise cash and avoid scrutiny from Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21,800 invading troops 'liquidated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1600252/ukraine-live-vladimir-putin-russian-investigation-sas-deployed-russia-war-updates-Zelensky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE'S resistance against Moscow's military had been "strong across all axes" and numerous Russian assaults along the line of contact in Donbas this week have been repelled, according to the latest UK intelligence update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why more people of color buying guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/guns-firearms-people-of-color-7f2ef104-35cd-4e9e-902e-c910958454f9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gun ownership is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
