<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Woody Harrelson involved in altercation at Watergate Hotel, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/woody-harrelson-involved-in-altercation-at-watergate-hotel-police-say/ar-AAPeR0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the move star struck a man “in self-defense” at the hotel’s rooftop bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet New Face of Russia's Anti-Putin Movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/yevgeny-roizman-is-the-new-face-of-russias-anti-putin-movement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Believe me, I am aware of all the risks,” career politician Yevgeny Roizman told The Daily Beast in an exclusive interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.1 MAG QUAKE JOLTS TOKYO... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007135828-bk79l/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (URGENT):Earthquake 6.1 jolts Tokyo, preliminary magnitude estimated at 6.1 - NHK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divorced parents going to court over dosing children...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/divorced-parents-are-going-to-court-over-vaccinating-their-kids-against-the-coronavirus/ar-AAPeIbD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family lawyers are seeing a surge in vaccine disputes, often caused by misinformation, bringing stress and legal bills to already worried parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary Committee details attempt to overturn election...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/07/politics/senate-judiciary-committee-investigation-trump-2020-election/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate Judiciary Committee on Thursday released a sweeping report about how former President Donald Trump and a top lawyer in the Justice Department attempted to overturn the 2020 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA mystery: Why didn't auto-braking stop crashes?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/a-tesla-mystery-why-didnt-auto-braking-stop-these-crashes/ar-AAPeA2O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While regulators investigate a spate of Teslas steering themselves into parked vehicles, Tesla owners have been reporting faulty collision avoidance systems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World waking up to Iran drone threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/the-world-is-waking-up-to-irans-drone-threat-681312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s drone program, unlike its nuclear weapons program, is not secretive. The Islamic Republic openly brags about its drone capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of inflation to average household: Extra $175 a month...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/06/cost-of-inflation-to-american-household-extra-175-a-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Americans whose income has not kept pace with inflation — up 5.3 percent in August as compared with last year — have had to foot the bill for more expensive products due to price …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Trust in judgment of voters, politicians new lows...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/355430/trust-politicians-voters-continues-ebb.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than half of U.S. adults say they have confidence in people who hold or are running for public office. Meanwhile, a small majority express confidence in the judgments of the American people under the democratic system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Trust in media nears record low...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/355526/americans-trust-media-dips-second-lowest-record.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' trust in the media to report the news fully, accurately and fairly has edged down four points to 36% since last year, making it the second-lowest reading in Gallup's trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harsh public justice and private despair reign in Taliban-ruled Herat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/harsh-public-justice-and-private-despair-reign-in-taliban-ruled-herat/ar-AAPem1F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the city in western Afghanistan, the Taliban has put corpses on display to deter crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan seeks international support after Chinese incursions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007045052-h72xt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-FRANCE/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Taiwan seeks international support after Chinese incursions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship anchored near oil pipeline made unusual movements...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-california-environment-and-nature-0e3d71b1f161822bb157ce8d73dbbd11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON BEACH, Calif. (AP) — A massive cargo ship made a series of unusual movements while anchored in the closest spot to a Southern California oil pipeline that ruptured and sent crude washing up on beaches, according to data collected by a marine navigation service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFAULT DELAYED</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/senate-poised-pull-nation-back-060000898.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Senate is nearing a deal on a short-term increase in the debt ceiling that would pull the U.S. from the brink of a payment default but threatens to exacerbate year-end clashes over trillions in government spending. Most Read from BloombergLeft-Wing Rage Threatens a Wall Street Haven in Latin AmericaHow Singapore's $50 Billion Financial District Will Change After Covid-19Before Interstates, America Got Around on InterurbansChristmas at Risk as Supply Chain ‘Disaster’ Only Gets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-SS camp guard, aged 100, on trial for 3,518 deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007112545-uqmr9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-NAZI/TRIAL (UPDATE 1, PIX,TV):UPDATE 1-Ex-SS camp guard, aged 100, on trial for 3,518 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland joins Sweden, Denmark in limiting MODERNA vax...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007092437-11532</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FINLAND-MODERNA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Finland joins Sweden and Denmark in limiting Moderna COVID-19 vaccine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World food prices hit 10-year peak...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007084335-s8h2o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-ECONOMY/FOOD (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-World food prices hit 10-year peak -FAO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Heart Damage Plagues Survivors Year After Infection...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/americas/heart-damage-plagues-covid-19-survivors-a-year-after-infection-study-shows-1.1633593286136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heart damage from COVID-19 extends well beyond the disease's initial stages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lib Activist Who Targets Republicans With MAGA Masquerade...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/07/the-liberal-activist-who-targets-republicans-with-a-maga-masquerade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Pence told her, “I love your heart.” Representative Jim Jordan of Ohio confided in her that Donald J. Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused in death of pharmacist brother for 'killing people' with jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-burnham-killed-pharmacist-brother-covid-vaccine-shots-poisoning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court documents show Jeffrey Burnham "wanted to confront" his brother "with the government poisoning people with COVID vaccines." He's also charged in two other deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Mystery: Where's $69 Billion Backing Stablecoin Tether?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-10-07/crypto-mystery-where-s-the-69-billion-backing-the-stablecoin-tether</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Beach' coworking spaces new craze in Sao Paulo...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beach-coworking-spaces-craze-sao-024000094.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 18 months of being locked up by coronavirus pandemic restrictions, Brazil's largest city Sao Paulo is breathing again, thanks in part to open-air coworking spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: 'HARDER THEY FALL' Vicious And Unapologetic Action Western...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/the-harder-they-fall-review-idris-elba-jonathan-majors-regina-king-1234851278/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When thinking of Western genre icons, John Wayne and Clint Eastwood often come to mind. It wasn’t until Mario Van Peebles’ 1993 film Posse was released and the first of its kind to trul…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD WORRIES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/the-world-is-questioning-washington-e2-80-99s-competence-fearing-prospect-of-us-default/ar-AAPdNBY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The political dysfunction on display could further erode perceptions of U.S. leadership on the world stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden, Denmark halt MODERNA shot for younger people...</title>
      <link>https://www.theolympian.com/news/nation-world/world/article254817917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theolympian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM — Sweden and Denmark decided to halt vaccinations with Moderna Inc.’s COVID-19 shot for younger people because of potential side effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DATA:  More people in USA have died so far THIS year than last...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-covid-more-deaths-2021-than-in-2020-johns-hopkins-coronavirus-20211006-2fpfjpomqzflnkpjgqtxf6mioy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus has killed 700,000 people, more than half of them this year. Since Jan. 1 of this year, more than 353,000 deaths have been reported from COVID-19, about a thousand more than last year’s 352,000 for the first 10 months of the pandemic last year, according to data from Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manilow Set to Break Presley's Vegas Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/06/barry-manilow-set-to-break-elvis-presleys-las-vegas-record-by-booking-105-shows-through-2023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence tests whether there is political life after MAGA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-weighing-2024-run-pence-tests-whether-there-is-political-life-after-trump/ar-AAPcY4h?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president is hopscotching the country giving six-figure speeches, sitting down for interviews with friendly conservative media outlets and hosting fundraisers for Republican candidates and causes as he considers a White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD OF ITALY:  34 inches in 24 hours breaks Europe's rainfall record...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/extreme-rainfall-in-liguria-italy-breaks-europe-record/1028429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rainfall that AccuWeather forecasters described as "ridiculous" set a new record for Europe and left one city with nearly a year's worth of rainfall -- in less than a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  Schlocky, overheated melodrama that's only degree or two removed from 'SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE'...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2021/08/31/impeachment-american-crime-story-review-fx-monica-lewinsky-bill-clinton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV docudramas always walk a fine line between illumination and exploitation. But American Crime Story’s first installment, The People v. O.J. Simpson, broke the mold by doing the impossible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorilla dies in arms of person who rescued her 14 years earlier...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/gorilla-dies-in-arms-of-person-who-rescued-her-14-years-earlier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A beloved orphaned mountain gorilla died in the arms of her caretaker and lifelong friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient's Kidney Op Cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/05/uchealth-kidney-transplant-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to UCHealth, the majority of transplant recipients and living donors are now required to be vaccinated against COVID-19. Neither woman has received their shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUNISHMENT:  KAISER Puts 2,200 Employees On Unpaid Leave...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/05/kaiser-permanente-covid-vaccine-leave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaiser Permanente says 2,200 of its employees are now on unpaid administrative leave after not meeting a COVID-19 vaccination deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Silent As Chappelle Blasted By GLAAD Over Gay Jokes In New Special...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/dave-chappelle-glaad-lgbtq-trans-netflix-special-homophobia-national-black-justice-coalition-1234851038/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day before Dave Chappelle’s Untitled documentary is set to screen at the Hollywood Bowl and the comedian is expected onstage, his new Netflix special The Closer is generating a growing back…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic super-yachts will feature crazy design detail...</title>
      <link>https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/yacht-design-void</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architecturaldigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Italian-built vessel features a customizable “void”—along with six luxurious suites—for unmistakable star power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Class Clowns Also Most Intelligent Students...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/class-clowns-intelligent-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers report children with higher than average levels of general knowledge and verbal reasoning tend to excel at humor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Now Largest City To Decriminalize Psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/10/05/seattle-just-became-the-largest-u-s-city-to-approve-quasi-decriminalization-of-natural-psychedelics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The resolution urges police to refrain from arresting people for noncommercial production and distribution as well as possession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Coke Users Stealing Meat to Pay Organized Crime for Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k78m9v/cape-breton-police-cocaine-meat-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Cape Breton cop claimed cocaine use has risen during the pandemic and blamed Canada's COVID emergency benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Concrete Cancer' Detected In Buildings At NH Nuclear Power Plant...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/10/05/iteam-seabrook-nh-nuclear-power-plant-concrete-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nuclear watch dog group says several structures at the Seabrook Nuclear Power Plant have concrete cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find culprit behind nearly all neurological diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10065423/Hope-dementia-Parkinsons-scientists-drive-diseases-affecting-brain-function.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists claim to have found a type of cell which normally help keep the brain healthy could be driving force behind nearly all diseases affecting brain function in what could help treat a variety of diseases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pandemic phase' ending soon?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/06/covid-dr-scott-gottlieb-says-antiviral-pills-kids-vaccines-key-to-ending-pandemic-phase.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former FDA chief and current Pfizer board member believes vaccines for kids and oral antiviral drugs will be "very important psychological events."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flush with Covid aid, schools steer funding to sports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-school-funding-sports-5b468b260ebd2593e53f03f9104d9bca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — One Wisconsin school district built a new football field. In Iowa, a high school weight room is getting a renovation. Another in Kentucky is replacing two outdoor tracks — all of this funded by the billions of dollars in federal pandemic relief Congress sent to schools this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL SUPPORTS RAISING DEBT CEILING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/06/mitch-mcconnell-may-offer-short-term-debt-ceiling-extension-following-pressure-from-biden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden and Democratic leaders in Congress amped up pressure on Republicans to act on the debt limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Sentenced 15 Months For Spreading Covid FACEBOOK Hoax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-hoax-facebook-texas-christopher-charles-erez-15-months-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 40-year-old posted two false, threatening messages on Facebook, claiming he paid someone infected with COVID-19 to lick items at a grocery store. He later admitted he lied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Cases, Deaths Declining...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-10-06/who-global-coronavirus-cases-deaths-have-been-declining-since-august</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. reported the most new coronavirus cases of any country last week, according to a World Health Organization report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Suspends MODERNA For Those Under 30...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/06/sweden-suspends-moderna-vaccine-for-those-30-and-under/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swedish health authorities on Wednesday suspended the use of Moderna’s COVID-19 vaccine for those ages 30 and under, saying the move was done out of precaution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 4 Injured In Shooting At TX High School; Teen Gunman Still At Large...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/06/possible-shooting-at-timberview-high-school-in-arlington/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “all clear” has been given at Timberview High School in Arlington after an active shooter situation Wednesday morning, but the search continues for a suspected teenaged gunman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON GRAVE WARNING</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-10-06/pentagon-warns-of-national-security-fallout-from-debt-ceiling-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin issued a statement condemning the political gridlock that he says would “seriously harm” troops, contractors and America’s ability to defend itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE removes R. Kelly channels after conviction...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/youtube-removes-r-kelly-official-145725944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube on Wednesday said it removed two official channels belonging to singer R. Kelly, who was recently convicted of operating a sex crimes ring that saw him abuse women and children for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho lt. gov. tries to send National Guard to border while governor is away...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/idaho-gov-will-rescind-lt-executive-orders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia building sovereign Internet -- with help from APPLEGOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Voices/2021/10/05/Russia-building-sovereign-Internet-Google-Apple/9721633435706/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the first day of Russia's parliamentary elections, Apple and Google agreed to demands from the Russian government to remove a strategic voting app developed by opposition leader Alexei Navalny from the app stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  'SNL' Season Premiere Lowest-Rated Episode in Show's History...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/snl-season-47-premiere-record-low-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owen Wilson picked the wrong year to host "Saturday Night Live." The Season 47 premiere was "SNL's" lowest-rated episode of all time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAN Network Gets 90% of Revenue From CNN Owner AT&amp;T?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/one-america-news-network-gets-revenue-from-att/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Telecom giant also played major role in creating and funding the network, Reuters investigation finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman 4th dies from J&amp;J...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/coronavirus/article254781422.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman in her late 30s died of a rare blood clotting condition tied to the vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-starved Trump pleads for TWITTER reinstatement...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-social-media-ban-6abdb177-6bf4-43d0-8b13-6c891f436d8c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His profile has dropped even further in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  MERCK Sells Covid Pill Molnupiravir for 40 Times Cost...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/10/05/covid-pill-drug-pricing-merck-ridgeback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Covid-19 treatment molnupiravir was developed using funding from the National Institutes of Health and the Department of Defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90- year old punches neighbor in face during 'get off my lawn' dispute...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/battery/get-off-my-lawn-arrest-275936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After demanding that an interloper get off his sprawling lawn, a 90-year-old Florida Man twice punched a neighbor in the face, according to cops who arrested the rowdy nonagenarian for battery and re</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA founders make FORBES list of America's richest during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Moderna-founders-make-Forbes-list-of-America-s-16513199.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three people with a stake in the coronavirus vaccine race have just made a list...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How coast crowded with ships, port gridlock and anchor may have caused Orange County oil spill...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/how-a-coast-crowded-with-ships-port-gridlock-and-an-anchor-may-have-caused-orange/article_701e7dd9-c47a-512c-87c6-449e6972351a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — In a year that has set records for the number of ships coming and going through the ports of Los Angeles and Long Beach, Friday was not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitamin May Really Change How You Feel After Long Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/this-vitamin-may-really-change-how-you-feel-after-a-long-flight-1.1662614</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wellness practitioner Jonathan Leary shares his travel tips, including the right tools to loosen up your muscles and get some real sleep after being stuck on a plane for hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Radical Surges With Talk of Arming Citizens, Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/french-radical-surges-with-talk-of-arming-citizens-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French Radical Surges With Talk of Arming Citizens, Civil War</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can USA shield 'state secret' that's not secret? Supreme Court to decide...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/can-the-us-shield-a-state-secret-thats-not-a-secret-supreme-court-to-decide/article_44c343ad-c755-5755-82f5-a6544cd64abf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The U.S. government subjected Abu Zubaydah to waterboarding and other brutality in 2002 at secret CIA sites in Thailand and Poland, believing wrongly that he was a close</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA EDGES TO DEFAULT</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unrelenting-political-brinkmanship-edges-u-060000007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democrats and Republicans must decide in the next day or two how far to take their deadlock over the U.S. debt limit, which is pushing the country perilously close to a catastrophic default.Most Read from BloombergChristmas at Risk as Supply Chain ‘Disaster’ Only Gets WorseLeft-Wing Rage Threatens a Wall Street Haven in Latin AmericaReshaped by Crisis, an ‘Anti-Biennial’ Reimagines ChicagoThis Is What Europe’s Green Future Looks LikeBefore Interstates, America Got Around on Interu</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
