<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>1 dead, 11 wounded in Minneapolis shooting, police say... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/21/us/minneapolis-shooting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man was killed and 11 others were injured in an overnight shooting in Minneapolis, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P!nk Shreds Trump Rally: 'I Sold Out That Same Place In Five Minutes'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/news/pink-shreds-donald-trump-tulsa-rally-attendance-one-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singer Pink, a longtime critic of President Donald Trump, mocked him for the smaller-than-expected [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says he ordered slower coronavirus testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/At-rally-Trump-blames-media-and-protesters-for-15354941.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. - President Donald Trump promoted his rally here on Saturday as an opportunity to reignite his reelection campaign and move past the coronavirus pandemic, which has killed more than 120,000 Americans and devastated the economy. He claimed that nearly 1 million people had requested tickets and boasted, "We've never had an empty seat, and we certainly won't in Oklahoma."  Instead, he addressed his supporters, most of them unmasked, in a 19,000-seat arena with many spots unfilled, hours after his campaign had announced that six members of the advance team staffing the event had tested positive for the virus.  He used his platform to belittle testing, which public health experts say is required to contain the outbreak. Because the strategy reveals what the president characterized as trivial cases, his direction was to curtail it. "So I said to my people, 'Slow the testing down,' " he said, as the audience cheered.  There was no massive overflow audience; the area outside the arena had emptied out by early evening, and plans for Trump to address the audience outside were quickly scrapped. The campaign blamed protesters; there were only scattered efforts to block entrances, which were resolved by police.  The campaign said quarantine procedures had gone into effect for the infected staff members and those in "immediate contact" with them. Meanwhile, Tulsa County reported 136 new cases Saturday - marking another high for both single-day and average cases - while the state as a whole reported 331 new infections.  Upon entering the rally grounds, attendees were handed blue face coverings - which many chose not to wear - and directed through a maze of metal fencing, which led to a touchless temperature screening conducted by volunteers in purple smocks. Most police officers and National Guard soldiers on the rally...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA LESS MEGA</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/trump-campaign-cancels-plans-to-address-overflow-crowd-because-not-enough-people-showed-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's campaign cancelled a planned outdoor rally to the "overflow crowd" in Tulsa, Oklahoma on Saturday after low turnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He was obviously kidding'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200621005728-6euqp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TRUMP-TESTING:Trump urges slowdown in COVID-19 testing, calling it a 'double-edge sword'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blames media and protesters for empty seats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1a59b4efe97f2249d414ae4f0b3c6495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. (AP) — President Donald Trump launched his comeback rally amid a pandemic on Saturday by declaring that “the silent majority is stronger than ever before," but what was meant to be a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p3jkf0LjPjw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday, June 20, 2020: Join RSBN for LIVE all day coverage of President Donald Trump's MAGA/KAG rally at the BOK Center in Tulsa, OK. Our live coverage wil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Epstein 'madam' Maxwell hiding out in luxury Paris Apt.... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1014441/jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-hiding-paris-flat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUGITIVE socialite Ghislaine Maxwell has been hiding out in a sprawling Paris apartment close to Jeffrey Epstein’s £7million paedo pad, we can reveal. Maxwell, one of the world’s most wanted women,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President will no longer speak outside; Overflow crowd fails to materialze...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-rally-tulsa-oklahoma/h_d50f71b9ed7379fc6ac37e6b4ed6a885</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As coronavirus cases rise in Oklahoma, President Trump is hosting a rally in Tulsa on Saturday that is expected to be attended by thousands. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters gather outside McConnell's home: 'No justice, no sleep'...</title>
      <link>https://disrn.com/news/protesters-gather-at-mcconnells-home-no-justice-no-sleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters gathered outside of Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell's Kentucky home early Friday, made loud noises, and held signs reading sayings such as, "No justice, no sleep," "Look us in the eyes," "Wake up, Mitch," and, "Breonna couldn't sleep, neither should Mitch."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign staff test positive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/23796a826ba86619527363b92ed49a33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's campaign says six staff members helping set up for his Saturday night rally in Tulsa, Oklahoma, have tested positive for coronavirus.  The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVERSEES TRUMP PROBES</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Barr-says-at-his-request-Trump-has-removed-15354618.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump on Saturday fired the top federal prosecutor in New York, a day after U.S. Attorney Geoffrey Berman had made clear he would resist an effort by Attorney General William Barr to remove him from office.  Barr informed Berman of the president's move in a sharply worded letter, informing Berman that his deputy, Audrey Strauss, will serve as the acting U.S. Attorney in Manhattan until the Senate can confirm his replacement.  Barr wrote that he had hoped for Berman's "cooperation to facilitate a smooth transition" in the office as Trump nominates the chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission, Jay Clayton, to fill the job permanently.  Instead, Barr wrote that Berman had chosen "public spectacle" by resisting the effort to remove him. "Because you have declared you have no intention of resigning, I have asked the President to remove you as of today, and he has done so," Barr wrote.  Berman's office did not immediately comment on the letter.  Offering little explanation, Barr announced late Friday that Berman would be replaced on an acting basis by the U.S. attorney in New Jersey, and that Trump would nominate Clayton for the position. Berman issued a remarkable statement in response, insisting he had not resigned and had no intention of stepping aside until the Senate confirms his replacement.  In an email sent to employees early Saturday morning, a copy of which was read to The Washington Post, Berman wrote that his only concern was "protecting this office and your work." On Saturday, Berman reported to work at his office in Manhattan.  The stalemate has generated significant legal and political questions, over how the dispute will be resolved and what's to become of several sensitive investigations involving people close to President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Bolton suggests possible 'obstruction' by Trump in SDNY Turkey investigation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bolton-suggests-obstruction-trump-sdny-turkey-investigation/story?id=71362785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration's ongoing efforts to oust the U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York Geoffrey Berman have set off a firestorm in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO suspends show of comedian embroiled in racism row with Mexican president...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-racism-hbo/hbo-suspends-show-of-comedian-embroiled-in-racism-row-with-mexican-president-idUSKBN23R0QO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television network HBO Latin America has suspended the TV show of a Mexican comedian who angered President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador and his wife with a remark about their child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to have sweeping powers over Hong Kong security law, stoking concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests-security/beijing-to-have-sweeping-powers-over-hong-kong-security-law-stoking-concerns-idUSKBN23R0FC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will have overarching powers over the enforcement of a new national security law in Hong Kong, according to details released on Saturday that signalled the deepest change to the city's way of life since it returned to Chinese rule in 1997.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime NY congressman tries to fend off challenger from left...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Longtime-N-Y-congressman-tries-to-fend-off-15354455.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAMORONECK, N.Y. - Standing outside a firehouse here, as 10,000 donated face masks were delivered, Rep. Eliot Engel confronted the questions that had put his 31-year congressional career in jeopardy.  How did the longest serving New York congressman suddenly face complaints of ignoring his district? How did Jamaal Bowman, a former middle school principal who has never run for office, turn Tuesday's Democratic primary into a pitched battle over who cared more about the north Bronx and southern swath of Westchester County?  "It's a farce," Engel said. "People know I bring millions of dollars home from Washington. I know virtually everybody in the district. If there are three people in a room and I'm invited, I'm there."  Two years after Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y., stunned the political establishment and unseated Joseph Crowley, then the fourth-ranked House Democrat, Engel is trying to fend off the same insurgency from the left. The House Foreign Affairs Committee chairman knew it was coming and has welcomed the help, from the endorsements of Hillary Clinton, Gov. Andrew Cuomo and top congressional Democrats to Republican donors funding a super PAC that backs him.  "I'm grateful to anyone who supports me," said the 73-year-old Engel.  A victory for Engel would humble his party's growing left wing after its favored candidates came up short in the race for the Democratic presidential nomination. A defeat would reveal the limits of a party establishment that, just a few years ago, could keep its incumbents safe with a simple premise: You know them, so why not keep them?  "It's like B.C. and A.D. - before AOC and after AOC," said Ritchie Torres, a liberal state legislator running in the 15th District, which neighbors Engel's. "In the post-AOC world, incumbency is no longer an entitlement, no longer a guarantee of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest woman wearing 'I Can't Breathe' shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-news-live-tulsa-rally-news-speech-coronavirus-protest-update-twitter-a9576876.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: HE'LL PAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8442775/Justice-Departments-attempt-block-John-Boltons-tell-book-DENIED.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Royce Lamberth denied the request for the former security adviser's book to be canned in a ruling Saturday, saying 'the damage is done' after 200,000 copies have already been released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh crisis for DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/503706-push-to-oust-manhattan-attorney-sparks-fresh-crisis-for-doj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department's push to oust a key U.S. attorney who spearheaded multiple probes involving associates of President Trump has spurred a new crisis for the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump coronavirus 'death clock' truck enters Tulsa ahead of rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/503715-trump-coronavirus-death-clock-truck-enters-tulsa-ahead-of-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Death Clock truck moved in to join the camaraderie in Tulsa, Okla., ahead of President Trump's rally there Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My terrifying five-day stay inside Seattle's cop-free CHAZ'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/20/my-terrifying-5-day-stay-inside-seattles-autonomous-zone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — On June 8, Seattle police frantically loaded what they could from the east precinct onto trucks and cars. Within hours, they boarded up and abandoned the station. That night, left-wing pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm just here to do my job,' imperiled prosecutor says...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e9ecba75a9d528ad1de7af33f978f007</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The powerful U.S. attorney in Manhattan who has been overseeing investigations of President Donald Trump's allies showed up at his office to work Saturday, defying the attorney...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As athletes return to campus, what are they signing up for?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9becba20565e275d1d9bd55a62cb4a74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio State calls it the Buckeye Acknowledgment and Pledge, a two-page document the school asked its athletes to sign before they could begin using team facilities during the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn Industry Having Major Meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-porn-industry-is-having-a-major-meltdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As adult performers realize they can create their own content and make money sans studios or dangerous agents, directors and performers, the future of porn may be worker-driven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TULSA: Protesters clash with Trump supporters ahead of rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/1012630/tulsa-rally-trump-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUPPORTERS have gathered in their thousands for a Donald Trump rally where the President is set to take the stage for the first time since the coronavirus outbreak. Huge lines of keen Trump support…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump third defeat in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/06/20/trumps-third-and-ultimate-defeat-this-week-judge-rules-john-boltons-book-about-presidents-incompetence-can-be-published-next-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge has ruled that John Bolton’s book about Donald Trump’s incompetent and criminal presidency, “The Room Where It Happened,” can be published by Simon &amp; Schuster. T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenin statue unveiled in western Germany after legal battle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lenin-statue-unveiled-west-germany-legal-battle-034816604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A divisive new monument to Soviet leader Lenin was unveiled in Germany on Saturday, in the middle of a global row over the controversial background of historical figures immortalised as statues. More than 30 years after the post-World War II communist experiment on German soil ended, the tiny Marxist-Leninist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India, China accuse each other of violating de facto border...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200620095151-h8179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA-CHINA/ (PIX):India, China accuse each other of violating de facto border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal barriers, MAGA gear...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e7311038d1c2f32bf9fdd7c727a9cc53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. (AP) — Supporters of President Donald Trump were lining up Saturday outside metal barriers surrounding the Tulsa stadium where the president will hold his first rally in months, ready...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But blasts conduct...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd4d178b8050739c915e455e022347ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal judge ruled Saturday that former national security adviser John Bolton can move forward in publishing his tell-all book despite efforts by the Trump administration to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Headed to Indoor Trump Rally, Raising Virus Fears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/07b7fc437494f98596f428dc90140140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of people from many states are converging on Tulsa for an indoor rally and other campaign events Saturday for President Donald Trump, raising concerns that the gatherings could...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia lawmakers advance bill to dissolve police department...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/georgia-house-passes-bill-that-could-abolish-police-department-after-arbery-shooting/5ANEWJX0ikQJk1Iv6lA2nL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Georgia House of Representatives passed a bill Friday that would allow voters to decide on abolishing county police departments, a move that came in response to the Glynn County Police Department's handling of the Ahmaud Arbery shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Rogan under fire for laughing about coercing women to have sex...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/20/joe-rogan-under-fire-for-laughing-about-coercing-women-to-have-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Rogan is in hot water after video surfaced of him laughing while friend and fellow comedian Joey “Coco” Diaz spoke about not allowing female comedians to go on stage unless they per…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beginning Of The End For Dollar?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/crisis-goes-gear-beginning-end-dollar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hawaii Became Rare Covid Success Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/06/19/hawaii-covid-success-story-322919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The islands’ geography and small population helped. But so did two enterprising doctors who pushed for aggressive tracing and testing—and sometimes found themselves at odds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos Show Teeming Throngs of Maskless Fans Lining Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-viral-videos-show-teeming-throngs-of-maskless-trump-fans-lining-up-for-tulsa-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday morning, stunning videos featuring teeming throngs of Trump supporters circulated on Twitter hours ahead of President Donald Trump's rally in Tulsa, Oklahoma — with very few coronavir</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Lenin statue to be unveiled in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/controversial-lenin-statue-to-be-unveiled-in-germanys-gelsenkirchen/a-53880002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statue of Soviet leader Vladimir Lenin has been revealed to the public in the western German city of Gelsenkirchen. The installation comes amid global protests against monuments to controversial historical figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St predicts administration will push vaccine approval before election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/wall-street-expects-a-covid-19-vaccine-before-the-u-s-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That date is increasingly important as Democratic challenger Joe Biden gains steam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of Venezuela Oil Fortune Looms Over Maduro Regime...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/end-of-venezuela-s-oil-fortune-looms-over-maduro-s-regime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;End of Venezuelaâ€™s Oil Fortune Looms Over Maduroâ€™s Regime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muhammad Ali son says dad would have hated 'racist' Black Lives Matter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/20/muhammad-alis-son-says-he-wouldve-hated-black-lives-matters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the fourth anniversary of his death, Muhammad Ali’s only biological son says that his father would be against Black Lives Matter, calling the movement “racist” and the protesters “devils.” The l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSE: Beijing Claims Valley Where Soldiers Brawled...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f90e883f12db90a39fdff89d16c3b1f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — China said the Galwan Valley high up in the Himalayan border region where Chinese and Indian troops engaged in a deadly brawl this week falls entirely within China, boldly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 states for tiny home living...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/tiny-home-most-popular-us-states-2020-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HomeAdvisor used Instagram data to find which states embrace the tiny living philosophy the most in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pick to lead media agency under fire from both sides...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/503676-trump-pick-to-lead-us-media-agency-under-fire-from-both-sides</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s new head of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters tear down statues of Ulysses S. Grant, Francis Scott Key...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/503685-protesters-tear-down-statues-of-union-general-ulysses-s-grant-national</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protestors in San Francisco on Friday toppled the statue of former President Ulysses S. Grant, who led the Union Army during the Civil War, in Golden Gate Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare 'ring of fire' solar eclipse to dim Africa, Asia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rare-ring-fire-solar-eclipse-dim-africa-asia-030128454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers along a narrow band from west Africa to the Arabian Peninsula, India and southern China will witness on Sunday the most dramatic "ring of fire" solar eclipse to shadow the Earth in years. Annular eclipses occur when the Moon -- passing between Earth and the Sun -- is not quite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR Confederate Flag Ban Faces Test in Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/20/nascars-confederate-flag-ban-faces-a-test-in-alabama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — Mike Harmon has spent much of his life driving the stock-car courses of the South, which also means</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senator, President Both in Trouble in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/20/joni-ernst-and-donald-trump-could-both-be-in-trouble-in-iowa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iowa was not on anyone’s bingo card of 2020 battlegrounds. Donald J. Trump carried the state by nine percentage points</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid wave of cultural change, Trump tries to stir backlash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/93378b5f2197f85216f800717d8a897e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It was June 2015, and Democrats felt the nation’s political and cultural winds blowing their way. The Supreme Court ruled in President Barack Obama’s favor on landmark gay...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
