<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Why Brain, Memories Have Such Strong Link To Smell...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/brain-memories-link-to-smell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brain cells in the olfactory cortex - the area of the brain that controls smell - make the link between specific scents and places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax podcaster hospitalized on ventilator...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/an-anti-vax-podcaster-has-reportedly-contracted-covid-19-and-now-is-hospitalized-on-a-ventilator/ar-AAS9LQL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic' Weight-Loss Pills, Covid Cures: Dr. Oz Under the Microscope...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/26/magic-weight-loss-pills-and-covid-cures-dr-oz-under-the-microscope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wealth of evidence now shows that the malaria drugs hydroxychloroquine and chloroquine were not effective at treating Covid-19 and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin to mull options if West refuses guarantees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-moscow-1f80249ac893d533fb6fcfdecb3d1ad3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin said Sunday he would ponder a slew of options if the West fails to meet his push for security guarantees precluding NATO's expansion to Ukraine. Earlier this month, Moscow submitted draft security documents demanding that NATO deny membership to Ukraine and other former Soviet countries and roll back its military deployments in Central and Eastern Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon, Mars and asteroid missions are top space goals for '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/space-science-missions-2022-15b89d24-fd17-4067-ade2-da8255878ddf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new year will see more Mars rovers, plus a space probe crashing into an asteroid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to expect from pandemic's third year...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/america-third-year-covid-c779feaa-b257-4544-968d-d2f1b9be862c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a devastating Omicron surge, life may finally be able to resemble normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMICRON PUSHING USA INTO SOFT LOCKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/omicron-is-pushing-america-into-soft-lockdown/ar-AAS9zNl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodgers breaks Favre's touchdown record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-cleveland-browns-green-bay-baker-mayfield-f76a41f10f29941c8e9bd026dfe57e4b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREEN BAY, Wis. (AP) — Rasul Douglas and the Green Bay Packers’ pass defense didn't let the Cleveland Browns spoil Aaron Rodgers’ milestone day. Rodgers surpassed Brett Favre to become Green Bay’s all-time leader in touchdown passes, and the Packers intercepted Baker Mayfield four times in a 24-22 victory over the Cleveland Browns on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech's Next Monopoly Game: Building Car of Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/12/27/self-driving-car-big-tech-monopoly-525867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From self-driving technology to entertainment and search, Google, Apple and Amazon are trying to gain exclusive access to your vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel PM enters isolation after daughter tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-689794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris charts own course as VP amid intense scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/26/kamala-harris-vice-president-first-year-scrutiny-joe-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris is navigating a position that comes with great influence but few formal responsibilities – and the stakes are even higher for her compared to past vice-presidents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buff Bezos shows off physique...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344573/Jeff-Bezos-57-shows-buff-body-St-Barts-girlfriend-Lauren-Sanchez.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buff billionaire Jeff Bezos, 57, lounged on a boat in St. Barts on Friday with his girlfriend Lauren Sanchez, 51. The pair looked loved up in the 81-degree heat as they celebrated the holiday with friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desmond Tutu dead at 90...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/26/africa/desmond-tutu-death-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archbishop Desmond Tutu, the Nobel Peace Prize-winning Anglican cleric whose good humor, inspiring message and conscientious work for civil and human rights made him a revered leader during the struggle to end apartheid in his native South Africa, has died. He was 90.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad claims 'Let's go Brandon' call with president was joke...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/25/oregon-dad-claims-lets-go-brandon-during-norad-call-was-a-joke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oregon dad who told President Biden “Let’s go Brandon” during the annual White House NORAD Santa-tracking phone call claims he used the coded vulgarity as “a joke,”…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robed in secrecy: How judges accused of misconduct dodge public scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/robed-secrecy-judges-accused-misconduct-can-dodge-public-scrutiny-rcna7638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public’s ability to scrutinize judicial conduct is crucial for transparency’s sake, and is as important as policing and prosecutorial overhauls, judicial ethics experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Texted Boyfriend To Kill Himself Before Suicide. Guilty Of Manslaughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/paigeskinner/boston-suicide-texts-you-urtula</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a plea agreement, Inyoung You accepted responsibility that her abusive text messages played a role in Alexander Urtula's suicide, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxing Day Havoc Continues...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/26/hundreds-of-more-flights-canceled-as-omicron-surge-wreaks-havoc-on-christmas-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flights continued to be canceled by the hundreds across the country on Christmas as airline workers come down with the highly contagious COVID-19 Omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's NYC restaurant turns away anti-vaxxers!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4340884/trump-tower-nyc-anti-vaxxers-proof-turned-away/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s NYC restaurant turned away a group of anti-vaxxers on Thursday for refusing to show proof of vaccination. The diners tried entering Trump Grill, located within the former president’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Personality Traits Explain Why People Binge-Watch TV Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/personality-binge-watching-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It turns out that binge watching may lead to a multitude of health issues stemming from behavioral addictions, according to a recent study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES: Airlines scrap nearly 1,000 on Christmas Day!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-airlines-scrap-hundreds-christmas-165427350.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Reuters) -U.S. airlines scrapped nearly 1,000 flights on Saturday, the second straight day of massive cancellations as surging COVID-19 infections have sidelined some pilots and other crew members, upending plans for tens of thousands of holiday travelers over the Christmas weekend. A total of 957 Christmas Day flights, including domestic flights and those into or out of the country, were canceled, up from 690 on Christmas Eve, according to a running tally on flight-tracking website FlightAware.com. At least one airline said that it expects hundreds more cancellations on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Elizabeth II, '21 brought sorrow and scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/for-queen-elizabeth-ii-2021-brought-sorrow-and-scandal-to-the-royal-family/ar-AAS71B7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruises once again facing disruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/cruise-ships-covid-19-disruption/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four ocean cruise ships were turned away from ports of call or were prohibited from letting passengers disembark in the Americas this week because of Covid-19 cases aboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES:  MORE DELAY DELAYS ON XMAS DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4334624/holiday-travel-airline-cancellations-omicron-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DELTA, United, and other US airlines have canceled more than 1,800 flights over Christmas weekend after the surge in the Omicron variant of Covid led to staff shortages. Globally, more than 5,800 f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France rocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211225-daily-covid-19-infections-in-france-cross-100-000-barrier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid infections in France hit six figures Saturday, health officials recording 104,611 cases over the previous 24 hours, the third consecutive day the numbers have been record highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Slams Judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344369/NYT-editorial-board-responds-judge-orders-return-documents-Project-Veritas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times has blasted a judge who ordered the paper to return documents they obtained from the conservative activist group Project Veritas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising art world star 'faked' works by pal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/25/rising-art-world-star-christian-rosa-faked-works-by-pal-raymond-pettibon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scandal of a rising Brazilian art star who allegedly counterfeited the work of his famous friend and mentor Raymond Pettibon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY warns of rise in child hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/25/new-york-dept-of-health-warns-of-rising-child-covid-hospitalizations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jump in hospitalizations of children is “concentrated in New York City and the surrounding greater metropolitan area.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice releases longest video yet of Capitol riot violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/justice-department-releases-three-hour-video-of-violent-capitol-riot-clashes-in-tunnel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department released the longest video yet from the government showing clashes between rioters and police at a U.S. Capitol tunnel on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candace Owens asks conservatives to go easy on Trump over vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344193/Candace-Owens-asks-conservatives-easy-Trump-Hes-old-research-vaccines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative Candace Owens says that former president Donald Trump only praised vaccines because he is 'too old' and not savvy enough to do better online research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Thousands of Russian troops withdrawing from Ukraine border...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thousands-russian-troops-withdrawing-ukraine-131138933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Russian troops are reportedly withdrawing from the Ukrainian border after conducting drills for roughly a month.Reuters reported on Saturday that more than 10,000 Russian troops were leaving a number of regions near Ukraine - including Crimea, Rostov and Kuban - and returning to permanent bases.The news service pointed to reporting from the Interfax news agency, which cited the Russian military."A stage of combat coordination of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Turns to Antitrust Enforcers to Combat Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-turns-to-antitrust-enforcers-to-combat-inflation/ar-AAS8D3w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron Divides Fans By Equating Covid to Flu, Cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/lebron-james-divides-nba-fans-with-meme-comparing-covid-to-the-flu-and-the-common-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James ignited a Twitter firestorm when he compared Covid-19 to both the flu and the common cold in a post on his Instagram account page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Dems who could run in '24 if Biden doesn't...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/586948-ten-democrats-who-could-run-in-2024-if-biden-doesnt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2022 midterm elections are less than a year away, but questions are already being raised about what the Democratic ticket will look like in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More shows go dark on Broadway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/24/thoughts-of-a-colored-man-and-waitress-go-dark-on-broadway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Great White Way was darker on Christmas Eve as two Broadway productions permanently closed due to surging COVID-19 cases in the Big Apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER booster's ability to prevent wanes within WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/uk-agency-pfizer-boosters-ability-to-prevent-symptomatic-covid-wanes-within-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data shows 3rd shot 70% effective in preventing illness after 2 weeks but only 45% after 10 weeks; Moderna seems to offer more durable protection, staying at 70% after 10 weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's well-oiled military machine launches 3 warships in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3161052/chinas-well-oiled-military-machine-launches-three-warships-one</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two vessels destined for Thailand and Pakistan while a third built to bolster PLA fleet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After years of doubts, hopes grow nuclear fusion finally real...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/12/22/science/after-years-doubts-hopes-grow-that-nuclear-fusion-is-finally-real-could-help-address-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After breakthroughs this year at MIT and elsewhere, scientists — and a growing number of deep-pocketed investors — insist that fusion is for real and could start sending power to electricity grids in about a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Webb telescope launches, starting nail-biting mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/12/25/nasa-james-webb-telescope-launches-south-america/9016763002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's flagship science instrument took flight from South America early Saturday, a high-stakes mission that will peer deep into the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy warship sidelined with outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/24/navy-warship-milwaukee-covid-526138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USS Milwaukee is staying in port.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Suspect charged with shooting man over loud music...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/story/news/crime/2021/12/25/boca-raton-christmas-eve-shooting-over-loud-music/9016891002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim's family was able to wrestle Zachary Moncada to the ground after he fired at them, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood banks experiencing biggest shortage in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2021/12/25/world/omicron-covid-vaccine-tests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blood banks across the country are struggling to maintain their usual three-day supply as virus cases make donors and medical staff scarce. Britain is administering booster shots throughout the Christmas holiday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
