<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Man eaten by bear had overdosed on meth...</title>
      <link>https://www.wate.com/news/local-news/autopsy-man-overdosed-on-meth-in-gsmnp-before-bear-scavenged-his-remains/1754392016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The autopsy report from the Knox County Regional Forensic Center revealed Monday that William Lee Hill Jr., 30, died of an "accidental methamphetamine intoxication" in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park in September, prior to his remains being scavenged by a bear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF ROBOT REPORTERS!</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/05/business/media/artificial-intelligence-journalism-robots.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fast, accurate and no typos! Bloomberg News, The Washington Post and The Associated Press test out machine-generated journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  'We will build a Human Wall if necessary'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/05/donald-trump-promises-human-wall-of-troops-to-block-migrant-caravans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump promised Tuesday to keep a flood of migrants from the southern border by sending in more military forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Killed After Vape Pen Explodes While Inhaling...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/05/texas-man-killed-by-exploding-vape-pen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 24-year-old man was killed in Texas last week when his vape pen exploded — slicing open his carotid artery and leaving his grandmother’s car covered in blood. William Brown died after his l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: No pictures from Ruth Bader Ginsburg 'public appearance'?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/mystery-no-pictures-from-first-ginsburg-public-appearance-since-surgery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg attended a concert put on by her daughter-in-law at the National Museum of Women in the Arts on Monday, marking her first public appearance since cancer surgery in December. Attendees at the Notorious RBG in Song described Ginsburg as “glam,” and “resplendent,” and “magnificent,” but you’ll have to take …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP APPROVAL 48%</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/political_updates/prez_track_feb05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin taunts Trump: 400 Russian military contractors sent in support of Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/4/vladimir-putin-backs-nicolas-maduro-military-contr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is playing a high-stakes game in the mounting crisis in Venezuela, where socialist President Nicolas Maduro has been mortgaging part of the country’s oil resources in exchange for financial and military support from Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deficit reduction remains pipe dream...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/the-state-of-the-union-deficit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The experience of the last two years illustrates the difficulty Congress has had in taking action on reducing the deficit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEFLON DONALD</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/02/04/trump-start-over-state-of-the-union-2019-224667</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State of the Union address rarely matters, but this one does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tijuana Trump' fends off critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/tijuana-trump-fends-off-critics/article_4c7cc6fc-5407-5323-945f-2e9a6f8962cd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico — When the mayor of Tijuana refused to apologize for comments he made about a caravan of Central American migrants, the coalition of human rights groups who demanded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRISPR revolutionized gene editing. Now its toolbox expanding...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldcourier.com/news/national/crispr-revolutionized-gene-editing-now-its-toolbox-is-expanding/article_1df85645-b2ad-56d0-82bf-7c6f12cd7960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gene-editing tool that has revolutionized biology is becoming even more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big hotel chains become arms of the surveillance state...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/archives/2019/02/05/hotel-surveillance-state-sex-trafficking </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How hotel chains became the new frontier in the surveillance state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE MELTDOWN! Waters begs Americans to 'turn the television off' during  State of Union...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/maxine-sotu-meltdown-trump-not-worthy-of-being-listened-to-i-hope-people-turn-the-television-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxine Waters doesn’t want to hear what Donald Trump has to say tonight. The California congresswoman melted down when asked if she would be listening to Trump’s second State of the Union address this evening. #AClassyClapback served the way only Auntie Maxine can- straight, no chaser. Read why @RepMaxineWaters still isn't here for Trump’s #SOTU …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incredible photos reveal Earth's stunning natural beauty in all its glory...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8357099/photos-freezing-penguins-waterfalls-earth-natural-beauty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INCREDIBLE entries to the world’s biggest photography competition have been revealed today as the shortlist has been decided. Now in its 12th year, the Sony World Photography Awards celebrates the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karl Marx grave vandalized in hammer attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2019/feb/05/karl-marx-london-grave-vandalised-suspected-hammer-attack-highgate-cemetery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friends of Highgate Cemetery calls attack a ‘particularly inarticulate form of political comment’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM mosquitoes: Playing God or only way to wipe out malaria?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/gm-mosquitoes-playing-god-way-wipe-malaria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The villagers of Bana in Burkina Faso survive by working the land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball killed woman at DODGER STADIUM; First foul-ball death in 50 years...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/espn/otl/story/_/id/25926592/fan-struck-head-foul-ball-dodgers-game-died-blunt-force-injury</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California woman died in August as a result of being hit in the head by a batted ball at Dodger Stadium, according to a Los Angeles County coroner's report obtained by ESPN's "Outside the Lines" and details her daughter revealed to OTL in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France carries out rare simulation of nuclear deterrent strike...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190205142736-nszld</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NUCLEAR/:France carries out rare simulation of nuclear deterrent strike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55 million devotees for busiest days of Hindu megafestival...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190205-55-million-devotees-busiest-days-hindu-megafestival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;55 million devotees for busiest days of Hindu megafestival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jogger kills mountain lion with 'BARE HANDS' in self-defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6668795/Colorado-jogger-fends-kills-mountain-lion-rural-trail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was jogging on the West Ridge of the Horsetooth Mountain Open Space in Colorado. He was attacked from behind by the juvenile lion but killed it in 'self-defense' with his bare hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census Bureau: 75 million more immigrants by 2060; 95% of future growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/census-bureau-75-million-more-immigrants-by-2060-95-of-future-us-growth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Census Bureau is projecting that the population of the United States will hit 404 million by 2060, and nearly all of the net growth will be from immigrants and their families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands pack stadium for first papal mass on Arabian Peninsula...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-emirates/tens-of-thousands-pack-stadium-for-first-papal-mass-on-arabian-peninsula-idUSKCN1PU0H9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of Catholics and several thousand Muslims attended an unpreced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'Super Bowl' of cockfighting, where roosters wear razors...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Inside-India-s-Super-Bowl-of-cockfighting-13589863.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIJAYAWADA, India -The four-lane highway stretches across this flat, riverine part of southern India, flanked by fields of rice and sugar cane. My guide twists around from the passenger seat to offer some advice: Keep a low profile and don't take pictures. The activity we seek is "strictly prohibited," he explains. But he assures me his brother-in-law will know where to go. It is the first day of Makar Sankranti, a major festival that takes place each January to celebrate the harvest and the advent of longer days. People light bonfires, discarding the old and welcoming the new. They prepare feasts and create intricate decorations made from brightly colored powders. And they hold cockfights - many, many cockfights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to talk again: Life without internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190205-learning-talk-again-life-without-internet-tonga</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learning to talk again: life without internet in Tonga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She says James Brown raped her. She also says someone murdered him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2019/02/us/james-brown-death-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twelve years after James Brown’s death, nearly a dozen people who knew him are calling for an autopsy or a criminal investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia welcomes Year of the Pig...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ce0f618e17c7443a919713caf3d7b69c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Asia welcomed the lunar Year of the Pig on Tuesday with visits to temples, family banquets and the world's biggest travel spree. Celebrations took place throughout the region, from Beijing and Seoul to Hanoi and Singapore. The streets of Beijing and other major Chinese cities were quiet and empty after millions of people left to visit relatives or travel abroad during the year's biggest family holiday. Families gathered at home for multigenerational banquets. Companies, shops and government offices closed for official holidays that ranged from two days in South Korea to a week in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah offers big stage for Beto re-emergence...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7a7de74cd5074caabad81eabb97b0b9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Beto O'Rourke's weeks of near-silence end on a massive stage when he sits down for an interview with Oprah Winfrey. The appearance Tuesday on "Oprah's SuperSoul Conversations from Times Square" comes ahead of a possible presidential campaign and puts O'Rourke's charisma put to the test. O'Rourke dazzled Democrats last year by nearly defeating Republican Sen. Ted Cruz in the country's largest red state. But his presidential prospects have been overshadowed more recently with the generally well-received 2020 campaign launches of Sens. Kamala Harris of California, Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts and Cory Booker of New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New app lets dog lovers swipe right for perfect pet match...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/196fe8e233784cc3bba697e21c4198d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VILNIUS, Lithuania (AP) — If the pooch melts your heart, swipe right. Animal lovers in Lithuania have created a mobile application inspired by the popular dating app Tinder to match up dogs in local shelters with new owners. Called GetPet, the app was launched last month and is getting hundreds of new users daily and already has made a few matches. It joins a growing market of apps for people looking to adopt a pet, including PawsLikeMe and BarkBuddy. "It is like Tinder, but with dogs," said Vaidas Gecevicius, one of app's creators. "You can arrange a meeting with the dog — a date."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runner kills mountain lion in self-defense after attacked on park trail...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/runner-kills-mountain-lion-self-defense-attacked-park-trail-123527385.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A runner in Colorado took survivalism to the extreme on Monday when he fought off and killed a mountain lion that attacked him on a park trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran warns Israel of 'firm response' if continues attacking targets in Syria...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190205122215-k8mh8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-CRISIS/SYRIA-IRAN-ISRAEL (URGENT):Iran warns Israel of a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Or is it breathing?</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/breathing-its-the-new-health-fad-are-you-sure-you-can-do-it-properly-tcvp6xg7p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might think breathing is as natural as, well, breathing. Most of us are able to complete the school run or pop to Pret for a bang bang chicken salad without giving the oxygen we inhale and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China gorging on double-muscle 'Frankenswine' pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8355116/chinese-new-year-of-pig-frankenswine-fatty-breeds/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUTANT pigs are to muscle their way onto the dinner tables of China – after the nation fell out of love with fatty meat. The giant beasts are to become a staple in the pork-loving country whi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's brains 'four years younger' than men's...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/feb/04/womens-brains-are-four-years-younger-than-mens-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis of metabolic brain age may explain differences in cognitive decline rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSSES OF SOCIAL MEDIA GIANTS COULD FACE ARREST OVER ONLINE HARM...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2019/02/05/bosses-social-media-giants-could-face-arrest-online-harm-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US social media bosses should be held legally responsible for the content on their platforms and could face arrest if they fail to rein in online harms, the UK&amp;rsquo;s minister for suicide prevention says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sommeliers of EVERYTHING...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Palate-grows-for-sommeliers-13587701.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My training as a honey sommelier at the American Honey Tasting Society culminates with eight wineglasses filled with various honeys, lined up from light to dark. My instructor, Carla Marina Marchese, tells me that when we taste honey, we don't do the ceremonial swirl - the wine expert's ritual - before we sniff. Honey sommeliers smear. "Smear it on the sides of the glass like this," she says, using a tiny plastic spoon. Once the honey is smeared, I can stick my nose in the glass to properly evaluate the aroma, then spoon a dollop onto my tongue. Marchese is leading me through an abbreviated version of her $595, four-day honey sensory certification course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rising Western skyline...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/once-flat-and-wide-on-the-frontier-western-cityscapes-are-now-rising-tall-and-sleek/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Development across the West will change the character of its big cities. Structures, some above 70 stories, will threaten mountain and ocean views. Historic neighborhoods are being squeezed by projects designed to attract wealthier residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former anti-Islam MP converts to Islam...</title>
      <link>https://www.dutchnews.nl/news/2019/02/former-outspoken-pvv-parliamentarian-converts-to-islam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dutchnews.nl&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A second former PVV politician has converted to Islam, this time after having a change of heart while writing what...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 'deadliest ever' Ebola will infect MILLIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/757822/ebola-disease-congo-doctors-without-borders-outbreak-goma-kivu-butemba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Magnetic Pole's Mysterious Journey Across Arctic...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6667057/Check-compass-The-magnetic-north-pole-move.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earth's magnetic pole has been drifting so quickly in the last few decades that they had to release new data early. The World Magnetic Model is used by consumer and military systems to navigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will world RUN OUT of people?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6666745/Will-world-RUN-people-Book-claims-global-population-start-decline-30-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In new book, Empty Planet, Canadian journalist John Ibbitson and political scientist Darrell Bricker argue that UN population predictions may have missed the mark completely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles outbreak climbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/04/health/washington-measles-outbreak/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year, Washington state is averaging more than one new measles case a day as officials try to help stop the disease's spread. Texas is among 10 states reporting measles this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems unleash wave of oppo against STARBUCKS Schultz...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/04/democratic-super-pac-unleashes-first-wave-of-opposition-research-against-howard-schultz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Bridge 21st Century is mounting an offensive against Schultz, whom many Democrats see as a threat to the party's nominee in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien ship may be among us, HARVARD astronomer insists...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/science/ct-harvard-astronomer-aliens-20190204-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ever since Avi Loeb’s controversial paper about the object, dubbed ‘Oumuamua, he has become a spokesman for the possibilities of extraterrestrial life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coup D'Etat Hysteria: In Caracas, Rumors Swirl Night and Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/coup-d-etat-hysteria-in-caracas-rumors-swirl-night-and-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coup Dâ€™Etat Hysteria: In Caracas, Rumors Swirl Night and Day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine Key to Reversing Rising Suicide Rate?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/ketamine-could-soon-be-used-to-treat-suicidal-ideation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ketamine Could Be the Key to Reversing Americaâ€™s Rising Suicide Rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record profits put new bull's-eye on tech giants...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/428451-record-profits-put-new-bulls-eye-on-tech-giants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Amazon and Google are racking up record profits following a year marked by public controversies over their privacy and business practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCAR LUNCH 2019:   'Inclusion, diversity, racial, ethnic and gender equality'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-oscars-nominees-luncheon/diversity-feted-as-oscar-nominees-gather-for-class-photo-and-lunch-idUSKCN1PU01R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop singer Lady Gaga, Mexican director Alfonso Cuaron and African-American filmm...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Baby shark used as bong...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/real-life/wtf/it-was-already-dead-group-defends-shocking-video-showing-baby-shark-being-used-as-bong/news-story/6a74b3832dc4c830f55b871ce467a632?from=rss-basic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC, DISTRESSING</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey 'Rain Tax' Becomes Law...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/02/04/rain-tax-likely-to-become-reality-in-new-jersey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey is one of the highest taxed states in the country. Now, residents and businesses could be taxed extra ... when it rains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Hare once again nation's busiest airport...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/business/chicago-ohare-airport-busiest-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'Hare topped Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta Airport for the first time since 2014.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCAR LUNCH 2019:   'Inclusion, diversity, racial, ethnic and gender equality'...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comInclusion, diversity, racial, ethnic and gender equality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comInclusion, diversity, racial, ethnic and gender equality&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALL FOR UNITY!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-to-call-for-bipartisanship-as-he-threatens-to-declare-emergency-11549320230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump in Tuesday’s State of the Union is expected to issue a plea for bipartisanship at a moment of deep partisan divisions, including an impasse over spending and a presidential threat to declare an emergency to pay for a border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHERN DISTRICT MOVES ON TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/lawyers-for-trump-inaugural-committee-receive-subpoena-for-documents-11549325383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for President Trump’s inaugural committee have received subpoenas for documents from the Manhattan U.S. attorney’s office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAVIN MCINNES SUES SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/gavin-mcinnes-to-sue-the-southern-poverty-law-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPLC listed Proud Boys as an extremist hate group and accused McInnes of promoting violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested over Paris inferno that killed 8...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6668165/At-eight-people-killed-huge-fire-Paris-neighbourhood-popular-tourists.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze, which took hold in an eight-storey block in the French capital's trendy 16th arrondissement, left 31 people, including six firefighters, injured as survivors climbed onto roofs to escape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Kids of Venezuela flaunt their wealth while nation starves... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6667889/Rich-Kids-Venezuela-including-Socialist-leader-Hugo-Chavezs-daughter-flaunt-wealth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rosines Chavez, daughter of socialist revolutionary Hugo, jumped on a plane to Paris after posing with a fist full of dollar bills on social media in 2016. She is one of the Rich kids of Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg makes 1st public appearance since cancer surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b94fea4b4a2a408fabcf756da790ff27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg is making her first public appearance since undergoing lung cancer surgery in December. The 85-year-old Ginsburg is attending a concert at a museum a few blocks from the White House that is being given by her daughter-in-law and other musicians. Patrice Michaels is married to Ginsburg's son, James. Michaels is a soprano and composer. The concert is dedicated to Ginsburg's life in the law. Ginsburg had surgery in New York on Dec. 21. She missed arguments at the court in January, her first illness-related absence in more than 25 years as a justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER army defends Ocasio-Cortez...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/04/dan-crenshaw-tries-to-take-shot-at-ocasio-cortez-gets-eviscerated-by-twitter-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressman Dan Crenshaw — the former Navy SEAL who got into a short-lived television beef with “SNL” cast member Pete Davidson last year — tried blasting a few shots at Rep. Alexandria…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cell of origin' thought to trigger disease discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6666441/Scientists-discover-cell-origin-thought-trigger-type-cancer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salford University researchers have described their discovery as being like managing to find the proverbial 'needle in a haystack'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Zap Patient So Could Laugh Through 'Awake' Brain Surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64682-calm-laughter-brain-surgery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY IN DIXIE</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/article_4d402530-2873-11e9-8e18-1fd05063605d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fairfax called the accusation a "smear" and said it's only coming up now because of the possibility he's about to become governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sierra Blizzard Drops So Much Snow That Ski Resorts Close!</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/02/04/sierra-blizzard-drops-so-much-snow-that-some-ski-resorts-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several ski resorts in the Eastern Sierra and Tahoe closed part or all operations Monday because of a blizzard that dropped as much as 9 feet of snow in the biggest storm system so far this season. Blizzard conditions with winds up to 50 mph are forecast in both areas through Monday, bringing up to 3 more feet of snow Monday evening and into Tuesday, according to the National Weather Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX Boss Landgraf Tears Apart NETFLIX Viewership Boasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/john-landgraf-netflix-ratings-not-remotely-accurate-fx/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has recently begun to release viewer data for its programming. Now FX boss John Landgraf is tearing about the service for boasting about ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squirrel on menu as diners turn to 'sustainable meat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/02/03/grey-squirrel-menu-diners-turn-wild-meat-help-boost-reds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are often an unwanted visitor to gardens, thanks to their reputation for raiding bird feeders and stripping trees of bark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash shows cockpit computers no substitute for pilot skills...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-lion-air-crash-20190204-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aviation experts say automated systems have made planes safer than ever and are a major reason why crash rates have declined all over the world. But they are also implicated in a series of incidents in which they made the wrong decisions and pilots did not fully understand the complex software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Ratings 'Myth'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/john-landgraf-smacks-down-netflix-ratings-myth-tca-1202549106/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FX CEO John Landgraf used his TCA appearance to take down Netflix’s release of selective — and, in his opinion, misleading — ratings information, as well as the reporters who swal…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious island didn't exist 4 years ago, now 'teeming with life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8350278/mysterious-island-that-didnt-exist-four-years-ago-is-now-teeming-with-life-sea-volcano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS volcanic island that suddenly burst from the Pacific Ocean is now teeming with life. The miracle outcrop known as Hunga Tonga has only existed for four years, yet creatures including h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY IN DIXIE</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/virginia/government-politics/updated-lt-gov-justin-fairfax-denies-sexual-assault-allegation-in/article_40dbcfef-5af6-5f91-9b4f-fa73050594d8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: After the Senate took a break, Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax addressed a swarm of reporters in the Capitol and said the woman alleging he'd assaulted her was lying in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo warns budget troubles as wealthy flee New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsday.com/news/region-state/state-budget-revenue-decline-1.26892647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuomo says he will have to revise his proposed budget as personal income tax collections drop $2.8 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORTHAM BEGS FOR POLITICAL LIFE</title>
      <link>https://wtkr.com/2019/02/04/embattled-northam-tells-cabinet-he-wont-resign-and-be-known-as-a-racist-for-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtkr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to that source, the governor specifically said that if he resigns, he would be resigning as a "racist for life," and that the only way he can clear his name is to stay in office and convince people that he is not in that photo and that the photo does not represent who he is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bettor X' loses nearly $3.8 million...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/bettor-x-lost-approximately-3-8-million-rams-super-bowl-loss-060611978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bettor X lost $3.8 million betting on the Rams on Sunday in the Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto investors locked out of $190,000,000 after exchange founder dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/feb/04/quadrigacx-canada-cryptocurrency-exchange-locked-gerald-cotten</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QuadrigaCX, Canada’s largest exchange, was unable to access password or recovery key after Gerald Cotten died last December</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danger as 'predictive data' threatens personal autonomy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/why-data-not-privacy-real-danger-n966621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While it's creepy to imagine companies are listening in to your conversations, it's perhaps more creepy that they can predict what you’re talking about without actually listening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of Mueller probe to push DOJ towards battle with Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/end-of-mueller-investigation-could-spark-battle-between-justice-dept-and-congress-over-release-of-special-counsels-report/ar-BBTaJgH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shocking' rise in obesity-related cancers among young adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/obesity-related-cancers-rising-fastest-among-millennials-study-finds-n966656</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study could be a warning that if the obesity epidemic continues, fat-sensitive cancers will explode in the years to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gut feeling: Depression linked to digestive bacteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190204-gut-feeling-study-links-depression-digestive-bacteria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gut feeling: study links depression to digestive bacteria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mystery of Pelosi's Favorite Bible Verse: Not in Bible...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/human-interest/2019/02/nancy-pelosi-bible-quote-minister-needs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the next best thing to the Prophet Isaiah himself appearing on the House floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liam Neeson says he wanted to kill a 'black b*st*rd' after friend's rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/liam-neeson-rape-black-man-attack-cosh-cold-pursuit-sexual-assault-interview-a8760866.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphic details published...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/washpost-pushes-back-against-justin-fairfax-statement-on-sexual-assault-allegation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graphic new details are emerging about a newly revealed allegation of sexual assault against Virginia Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax, as The Washington Post pushes back against Fairfax’s claim that the newspaper found serious problems with the original accusation when it initially opted not to publish the account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Half-Dozen Attend Draft Beto Event...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/hardly-anyone-attended-a-draftbeto-event-in-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  50% of Virginia Dems Approve Of Governor...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/02/04/virginia-voters-quickly-sour-on-northam-amid-blackface-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in Virginia have soured on Gov. Ralph Northam (D-Va.) in the immediate aftermath of the blackface scandal that has many leaders, including top Democrats, calling for him to resign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disbelief' In White House After Trump Schedule Leak...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/04/white-house-disgust-trump-executive-schedule-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Aghast and disgusted'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US preps to start building portion of Texas border wall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e653d5a305114835bb399e480ac44ab8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — The U.S. government is preparing to begin construction of more border walls and fencing in South Texas' Rio Grande Valley, likely on federally owned land set aside as wildlife refuge property. Heavy construction equipment was expected to arrive starting Monday, U.S. Customs and Border Protection said. A photo posted by the nonprofit National Butterfly Center shows an excavator parked next to its property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy Scouts inaugurate first all-girls troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/2/first-all-girl-troops-welcomed-boy-scouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., marked the end — and the beginning — of an era this weekend when the Boy Scouts of America established its first all-girl troops in the nation’s capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise and fall of 'El Chapo,' Mexico's most wanted kingpin...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-mexico-el-chapo-profile/the-rise-and-fall-of-el-chapo-mexicos-most-wanted-kingpin-idUSKCN1PT1XS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman is Mexico's most notorious kingpin who ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN anchor fired for leaking plans to sue...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/04/adnan-virk-plots-espn-lawsuit-after-firing-over-mlb-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fired ESPN anchor Adnan Virk is pursuing legal action against his ex-employer, sources have told The Post. Virk was let go Friday after being accused of leaking confidential information on multiple…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military steps in as Australia floods bring crocs to streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/military-steps-australia-floods-bring-crocs-streets-021942887.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's military has been deployed to tackle devastating "once-in-a-century" floods that have inundated homes, schools and airports in the country's northeast, forcing hundreds to flee and bringing crocodiles onto the streets. The Australian Defence Forces delivered 70,000 sandbags</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Stop Man In Brady Jersey Sneaking Into PATS Locker Room...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/02/04/video-shows-police-stopping-man-in-tom-brady-jersey-trying-sneak-into-patriots-locker-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cell phone video appears to show a Patriots fan with a security jacket trying to sneak into the team's Super Bowl locker room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspense Novelist's Trail of Deceptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2019/02/11/a-suspense-novelists-trail-of-deceptions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan Mallory, who writes under the name A. J. Finn, went to No. 1 with his début thriller, “The Woman in the Window.” His life contains even stranger twists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marie Kondo and the rise of clutter shaming...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/820681/marie-kondo-rise-clutter-shaming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In defense of stuff, and having a lot of it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: GANNETT turns down hedge fund buyout...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ca7b9e1e8f44e7db36db523b996c201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The publisher of USA Today and dozens of other newspapers said no to a hedge-fund backed media group with a reputation for slashing jobs, but the buyout fight may not be over. Gannett on Monday said its board has unanimously rejected an unsolicited $1.36 billion buyout from MNG Enterprises , better known as Digital First Media. Digital First then said that it might nominate new Gannett board directors to consider its offer.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
