<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper publisher resigns after N-word usage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/East-Bay-Express-publisher-resigns-after-13075990.php?t=5c5350a3f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publisher of the East Bay Express weekly newspaper resigned on Saturday, admitting to "indiscretions" and saying his presence had "become a threat to the mission ....of healthy independent journalism."         Stephen Buel stepped down one day after posting a lengthy "apology and pledge" on the newspaper's website in which he admitted that he used derogatory words while discussing a story he had unilaterally removed from the newspaper website that described "white people singing along to live hip-hop songs that contained the N-word."         "I said a couple of those words aloud," Buel wrote in his apology. "I should not have done so and am extremely sorry that my remark caused others pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveals 'brutal' president gave her:  Sue EU...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6782684/theresa-may-finally-reveals-brutal-brexit-advice-donald-trump-gave-her-to-sue-the-eu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May has finally revealed the explosive Brexit advice Donald Trump gave to her – to sue the EU. The Prime Minister said the US President told her not to even enter into a negotiation with Br…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES IN HELSINKI!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-russia-low-expectations-putin-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump gave an exclusive interview to "CBS Evening News" anchor Jeff Glor in Scotland ahead of his meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA recalls common heart drug over cancer concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/fda-recalls-common-heart-drug-over-cancer-concerns/i7TSPdFqzbclCMleFaDynO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: CON JOB...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/who-is-america-review-sacha-baron-cohen-spoof-bernie-sanders-dick-cheney-sarah-palin-showtime-1202426515/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When David Nevins called Sacha Baron Cohen “the premier provocateur of our time” in announcing the new Who Is America? series, the Showtime boss was certainly honest to a fault. Full of mild shock,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: CHARACTERS...</title>
      <link>http://www.vulture.com/2018/07/sacha-baron-cohen-who-is-america-characters-ranked.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vulture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Infowars-esque conspiracy theorist, an NPR liberal, a British ex-con, and an Islamophobic Israeli soldier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen nabs Bernie Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sacha-baron-cohen-targets-gop-congressmen-bernie-sanders-in-who-is-america-premiere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime’s ‘Who Is America?,’ premiering Sunday night, more than lives up to the hype, and stands as Sacha Baron Cohen’s most subversive work since ‘Da Ali G Show.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO recognizes 'compulsive sexual behavior' as mental disorder...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/recognises-compulsive-sexual-behaviour-mental-disorder-200546301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization has recognised "compulsive sexual behaviour" as a mental disorder, but said Saturday it remained unclear if it was an addiction on a par with gambling or drug abuse. The contentious term "sex addiction" has been around for decades but experts disagree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban reforms stress free market, private property and investment...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cuban-reforms-stress-free-market-private-property-investment-192824723.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socialist Cuba is planning a series of potentially far-reaching changes, with a new constitution set to recognize the free market and private property, while dividing political powers between a president and a prime minister. In a reform of the island nation's 1976 constitution expected to be quickly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYALS SNUB...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/royal-family-snub-trump-5kwvt5h5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Charles and Prince William were unwilling to meet Donald Trump on his visit to Britain, leaving the Queen to greet the US president alone. The first two in line to the throne let it be known...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans prep impeachment docs on Rosenstein... </title>
      <link>https://www.bizpacreview.com/2018/07/14/rosenstein-not-smiling-anymore-after-house-republicans-spotted-with-his-impeachment-docs-654125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bizpacreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two House Republicans are seeking to file impeachment documents against Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein as early as Monday, according to Capitol Hill sources who spoke with Politico. Reps. Jim Jordan and Mark Meadows, both members of the House Freedom Caucus, take issue with both the deputy attorney general’s poor handling of the Russia investigation and his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange faces eviction from embassy...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/14/assange-could-soon-be-evicted-from-london-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange may soon be evicted from the London embassy that has sheltered him for the last six years. Ecuador, which has played host to the political provocateur since 2012, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scottish Slam Security Bill For Trump Golf...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5954999/Outrage-5M-taxpayers-cash-spent-security-Donald-Trumps-private-trip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump sparked outrage again today after it was revealed his decision to visit Scotland and play golf at his Ayrshire course may cost the British taxpayer as much as £5million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May warns there could be 'no Brexit at all'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5954683/THERESA-MAYs-steely-warning-Tory-rebels-bully-boys-Brussels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May, writing for the Mail On Sunday, said: 'Brexit isn’t about trading with other countries instead of trading with Europe, it is about doing both.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists in Egypt discover mummification workshop...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/archaeologists-egypt-discover-mummification-worskshop-110445367.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — Archaeologists in Egypt stumbled upon a new discovery dating back to more than 2,500 years ago near Egypt's famed pyramids at an ancient necropolis south of Cairo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Goldmine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/14/a-goldmine-mummies-secrets-uncovered-in-egypt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists find mummification workshop in the Saqqara necropolis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST:  Fired BILLBOARD CEO probed for gay slurs, sex harassment, financial misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ousted-billboard-ceo-john-amato-being-probed-for-sexual-and-financial-misconduct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amato was forced to resign after current and former employees came forward with evidence that he harassed employees and engaged in other misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare double shark attack closes Florida beach; Bites were just minutes apart... </title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/national/rare-double-shark-attack-closes-florida-beach-bites-were-just/article_9ba28c16-62b2-5c55-a9d6-1738fb2ecca9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike southern Florida, shark encounters are relatively rare farther up Florida's Atlantic coastline and are almost unheard of in northernmost Nassau County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Having a Bawl in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/14/opinion/sunday/trump-having-a-bawl-in-europe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Baby kicks Jolly Old England when she’s down but embraces mendacious Mother Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Director Uncovered Whitney Houston's Secret Pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/13/movies/whitney-houston-documentary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of a new documentary said he consulted addiction experts and repeatedly interviewed her brothers to reveal her childhood abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British tabloid hits Trump for sitting in Churchill's chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/donald-trump-sparks-fury-posing-12914158</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You insult our country, attack our NHS, embarrass our Queen, undermine our ‘special relationship’, humiliate our PM...and then smugly pose in Winston Churchill’s armchair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haitian prime minister resigns after fuel riots...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/haiti/article214692715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haiti’s prime minister, Jack Guy Lafontant, and his 18 cabinet members resigned Saturday, one week after his government’s temporary suspension of an unpopular fuel price hike failed to halt a violent civil unrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students, civilians trapped in church amid gunfire by militias...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Students-civilians-trapped-in-Nicaraguan-church-13074966.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANAGUA, Nicaragua - The first student I met outside the Church of the Divine Mercy had a fresh bullet hole in his lower back. "It's ugly in there," he said. "In there" was the vast, jungly campus of the National Autonomous University of Nicaragua (UNAN), which by Friday afternoon had become a battleground. Far from the initial fighting was the Catholic church, a supposedly safe place for triage, and beleaguered and wounded students were arriving from the front lines by pickup truck, by motorbike, and on foot. "We had to evacuate," Jonas Cruz, 18, said. "They are invading the barricades. They are already inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaraguan protests getting deadlier, activists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/nicaraguan-protests-are-getting-deadlier-activists-say/article_92368de9-0b5e-5905-9e25-5238afe1d8e2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zayda Hernandez and Victor Cuadras are among the Nicaraguan university students risking their lives in mass protests against Nicaraguan President Daniel Ortega and his wife, Vice President Rosario Murillo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot addiction: Clinics braced for humans hooked on cyborgs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716215/sex-robot-dolls-addiction-clinics-humans-hooked-treatment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serena Williams denied historic Grand Slam title at Wimbledon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/14/serena-williams-denied-historic-grand-slam-title-at-wimbledon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Angelique Kerber was so steady, so patient, so accurate throughout the Wimbledon final. She never really gave Serena Williams much of a chance. Kerber won her first championship at the All…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Under Fire For 'Flipping Coin' To Decide Whether They'll Arrest Speeding Driver...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/13/georgia-police-flipping-coin-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To add insult to injury, the "coin" flipped in the woman's favor, but Roswell Police officers Courtney Brown and Kristee Wilson decided to arrest her, anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DOES IT AGAIN:  Gospel song flagged as 'political'...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/07/is-this-a-political-ad-facebook-thinks-so/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add one more arbitrary and capricious act of anti-Christian-censorship bigotry to the list of Facebook blocks. The Gospel music group Zion’s Joy! posted its new song “What Would Heaven Look Like,” a purely spiritual Christian praise song, to Facebook, boosting it with a $100 purchase – only to see the song censored for “political content.” […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller, pushing to wrap up parts of Russia probe, faces question of American involvement...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/philly/news/politics/presidential/robert-mueller-investigation-russia-probe-american-involvement-20180714.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are signs that the special counsel is moving to finish a significant portion of his investigative work by the end of the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man suspected of attacking wife with chain saw was deported 11 times...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-chainsaw-deported-20180713-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man suspected of attacking his wife with a chain saw in Whittier and then fleeing had been deported 11 times since 2005, according to immigration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago's last SEARS to close for good...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-sears-last-chicago-store-0714-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears' last remaining department store in Chicago, the company's longtime hometown, will close on Sunday after nearly 80 years in operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES IN HELSINKI!</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/trump-heads-to-putin-summit-with-no-clear-goal-and/article_1be21be3-115c-5dba-9701-c3997b4912cc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI, Finland — When President Donald Trump flew to Singapore last month to meet with Kim Jong Un, he had a clear agenda: to try personal diplomacy, rather than insults</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE HEATS BATTLE WITH CNN...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/397055-white-house-we-cancelled-boltons-interview-with-cnn-after-jim-acosta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders said Saturday that the White House decided to cancel an interview between CNN and national security adviser John Bolton after a CNN reporter “disrespected” President Trump earlier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem lawmaker dances to Drake song to promote millennial voter turnout...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/397054-dem-lawmaker-dances-to-drake-song-to-promote-midterm-voting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Democratic lawmaker posted a video of herself dancing to Drake's newly released song "In My Feelings" on Twitter Friday, urging the song's mysterious "Keke" to vote in November's midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump taunts protesters at Scottish golf course...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/donald-trump-taunts-protesters-scottish-134104963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump taunts protesters at Scottish golf course as they tell him to 'go home'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as Iceland fishermen kill rare whale...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/2265/outrage-iceland-fishermen-kill-rare-whale-doc-17l4iy1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widest daytime assault since 2014 war...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/violence-flares-israel-strikes-gaza-hamas-fires-rockets-034953865.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — The Israeli military carried out its largest daytime airstrike campaign in Gaza since the 2014 war Saturday as Hamas militants fired dozens of rockets into Israel, threatening to spark a wider conflagration after weeks of tensions along the volatile border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Trump ambassador lobbied Britain on behalf of jailed activist Tommy Robinson...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-britain-robinson/trumps-ambassador-lobbied-britain-on-behalf-of-jailed-right-wing-activist-tommy-robinson-idUSKBN1K331J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Brownback, the U.S. Ambassador for International Religious Freedom, complained to the British ambassador in Washington D.C. about the treatment of an English right-wing activist who is in jail for disrupting a trial, according to three sources familiar with the discussion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speculation grows ahead of Sacha Baron Cohen show: Who else might be victim?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/jul/14/who-else-might-be-a-victim-of-sacha-baron-cohens-new-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin and other US rightwingers have railed at being duped, but Cohen’s Who is America? is shrouded in mystery. Did he get as far as the White House?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ticks that carry Lyme disease spreading fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ticks-that-carry-lyme-disease-are-spreading-fast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Tick populations have exploded​," researchers say – even in counties where they were never seen before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State officials meet amid security concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2e11aadd40a349cdb020cb6fe25c1e30/State-election-officials-in-US-meet-amid-security-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — The top state election officials from throughout the U.S. are gathering this weekend in Philadelphia amid fresh revelations of Russia's interference in the 201</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Supreme Court battle roils DC, suburban voters shrug...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ce6cf10e0db47adb9f1865f2de14d09/As-Supreme-Court-battle-roils-DC,-suburban-voters-shrug</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Nebraska (AP) — It stands to shift the direction of the nation's highest court for decades, but President Donald Trump's move to fill a Supreme Court vacancy has barely cra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-Gaza Border Violence Flares With Mortars, Airstrikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/14/israel-gaza-border-violence-flares-with-mortar-fire-airstrike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel-Gaza Border Violence Flares With Mortar Fire, Airstrike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artists ditch canvases for humans at festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/real-body-artists-ditch-canvases-humans-art-festival-103235815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian model Corina gave her body as a canvas and patiently stood for six hours in order to be transformed into a blue Egyptian goddess for the annual World Body Painting Festival. "I visited the festival last year and during the presentation of the models I got goosebumps, so I decided to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Why didn't Obama do something?</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/396999-trump-on-russian-indictments-why-didnt-obama-do-something</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Saturday in his first comments about the indictment of 12 Russian military officers “for conspiring to interfere with the 2016 presidential election” by blaming former President Obama and the “deep state.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers 'bleeding from ears' after flight drops 30,000ft in 5 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/716352/Ryanair-flight-emergency-landing-FR7312-Dublin-Frankfurt-Germany-Zadar-Croatia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
