<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ANGER AT UNVAXXED...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jul/23/ala-gov-kay-ivey-fumes-over-worst-vaccination-rate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey said people are “supposed to have common sense” as she unloaded on unvaccinated people for driving coronavirus outbreaks and hospitalizations in her state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves in CA stealing scarce water amid extreme drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/22/us/california-water-thieves-drought/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an extreme drought grips California, making water increasingly scarce, thieves are making off with billions of gallons of the precious resource, tapping into fire hydrants, rivers, and even small family homes and farms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unarmed 75-year-old Tasered without warning by Colorado officer: 'What did I do?'</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Unarmed-75-year-old-Tasered-without-warning-by-16334698.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When police knocked on Michael Clark's door in Idaho Springs, Colo., in May, he emerged...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England quarantine rules relaxed to avoid shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-0aa163de10d84559aebdcea83d8e8907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The British government has sought to ease food supply pressures in England by exempting more than 10,000 workers from quarantine rules that led to staff shortages and empty shelves and fears of panic-buying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Americans spending again and AMEX booming...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-879a94ac579792e7021d31dab9bee477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Spending at restaurants, shops and entertainment venues has come back in force as vaccines become more common and it fueled a revenue surge at American Express during the second quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan 'rising sun' flag provokes ire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-japan-japan-olympic-team-south-korea-olympic-team-5a50f35230a3330226cdc92bf4abc66d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — Japan considers the “rising sun” flag part of its history. But some in the Koreas, China and other Asian countries say the flag is a reminder of Japan’s wartime atrocities, and is comparable to the Nazi swastika.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Nightmares May Scrub August Vacation Plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/travel-nightmares-may-scrub-your-august-vacation-plans/ar-AAMt8zK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have waited more than a year to get away, but a host of pandemic-related factors are conspiring to make another staycation the smart move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak pops travel bubble between Australia, New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/delta-variant-outbreak-pops-travel-bubble-between-australia-and-new-zealand/ar-AAMsVck </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Explodes in Cancun and Los Cabos as Third Wave Hits Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/covid-explodes-in-cancun-and-los-cabos-as-third-wave-hits-mexico/ar-AAMtzWj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third coronavirus wave fueled by the highly contagious delta variant is battering two of Mexico’s most popular tourist destinations on opposite coasts, Los Cabos in the Pacific and Cancun on the Caribbean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ Rights Force Hungary Into Moment of Reckoning at Pride March...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/lgbtq-rights-force-hungary-into-moment-of-reckoning-at-pride-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How LGBTQ Rights Forced Hungary Into a Moment of Reckoning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 100 US athletes unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/564488-at-least-100-us-olympic-athletes-are-unvaccinated-as-2020-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 100 U.S. Olympic athletes that are set to compete in Japan remain unvaccinated as the Games begin on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrack Heads Back to Court to Learn If He Wins Bail... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/564486-ex-trump-adviser-barrack-set-for-bail-hearing-friday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former campaign adviser to former President Trump is set to go back to court on Friday for a bail hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq war Marine walks U.S.-Mexico border to protest deportation of vets...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723104729-jwolx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/VETERAN (PIX, TV):Iraq war Marine walks U.S.-Mexico border to protest deportation of veterans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'congratulations' to 'fully canceled': CA cafe owners hit roadblock...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723084719-snmck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-CAFES (PIX):From 'congratulations' to 'fully canceled': California cafe owners hit roadblock</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Americans navigate conflicting mask advice, 'everyone confused'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723084719-qjmjj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-MASKS (PIX, GRAPHICS):As Americans navigate conflicting COVID-19 mask advice, 'everyone is confused'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats rattle PA county targeted in election audit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722222805-zzf1l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/PENNSYLVANIA (PIX):Threats rattle Pennsylvania county targeted in election audit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'QAnon Shaman' in plea negotiations after mental health diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/exclusive-qanon-shaman-plea-negotiations-after-mental-health-diagnosis-lawyer-2021-07-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The participant in the Jan. 6 U.S. Capitol riots nicknamed the "QAnon Shaman" is negotiating a possible plea deal with prosecutors, after prison psychologists found he suffers from a variety of mental illnesses, his attorney said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro once said he'd stage military takeover. Now Brazilians fear laying ground for one...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bolsonaro-once-said-he-e2-80-99d-stage-a-military-takeover-now-brazilians-fear-he-could-be-laying-the-ground-for-one/ar-AAMtihe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolsonaro's increasingly brazen comments have escalated a months-long campaign to erode faith in the electoral system of Latin America's largest democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two shot outside of popular restaurants in DC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/564476-two-shot-outside-of-restaurants-in-dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were shot outside restaurants on 14th street in Washington, D.C. Thursday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA HOTSPOT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/564470-florida-reports-highest-daily-covid-19-cases-since-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida on Wednesday reported 12,647 new cases of COVID-19, the highest daily number of cases since late January, according to data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Nomads: Surfing World for Risk and Profit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/23/crypto-nomads-surfing-the-world-for-risk-and-profit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is just after midnight in Hong Kong, and Sam Bankman-Fried stares at the trading data on his six monitors,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned by Hot Housing Market, Some Buyers Back Off...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/23/burned-by-hot-housing-market-some-buyers-back-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first house was in Midvale, Utah — a three-bedroom, just over 2,100 square feet, listed for $479,000. Rob Ettaro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Haitian President's Funeral Nears, Anger Burns in Streets...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/23/as-haitian-presidents-funeral-nears-anger-burns-in-the-streets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAP-HAÏTIEN, Haiti — Hours before mourners were due to pay tribute to the assassinated President Jovenel Moïse at a state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire at mansion owned by Beyoncé, Jay-Z investigated as possible arson...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fire-at-mansion-believed-to-be-owned-by-beyonc-c3-a9-and-jay-z-investigated-as-possible-arson/ar-AAMtprz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Orleans fire department said the property had been vacant for some time and that 22 responders attended the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL TESTS ORAL VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2021/07/22/oral-covid-vaccine-set-to-begin-trials-in-israel/?sh=7254f9021ba5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avoiding needles, oral vaccines are much easier to store, transport and administer, possibly helping to ease disparities in vaccine access around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: LeBron first in NBA history to make $1 billion while playing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/lebron-james-becomes-first-player-in-nba-history-to-make-1-billion-in-earnings-while-still-playing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James' earnings on and off the court have made him a ridiculous amount of money</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMES LIKE NO OTHER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-swimming-soccer-sports-tokyo-8b75b92f36477af48612c70a2b7104e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Disputed, locked down and running a year late, the Tokyo Games begin at last on Friday night, a multinational showcase of the finest athletes of a world fragmented by disease — and an event steeped in the political and medical baggage of a relentless pandemic whose presence haunts every Olympic corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>911 outages along East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3331697/fedex-ups-airbnb-delta-airlines-website-down-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MULTIPLE major US companies have been knocked offline today due to a nationwide outage, including Airbnb, FedEx, Delta Airlines, and HBO Max. Downdetector also flagged issues with Fidelity, USAA, U…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread Internet outage briefly disrupts retail, financial, travel sites worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/widespread-outage-disrupts-major-retail-financial-travel-websites-worldwide/3168859/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A widespread disruption caused severe outages for some of the world’s biggest websites on Thursday afternoon – and it was all caused by a software update gone horribly wrong. DownDetector.com showed a sharp and simultaneous spike in outage reports for prominent travel, retail, financial and gaming websites globally. In most cases, the spike in outage reports appeared to start around…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DNS failure'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/22/several-major-websites-go-down-in-widespread-internet-outage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several of the affected services blamed Akamai, a content delivery network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia disconnected from global internet in tests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722094330-21wee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tests were carried out between June and July to test the ability of the 'Runet', as part of Russia's cybersecurity efforts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pingdemic' grips Britain as fears of food shortages grow...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722050900-pa20w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record numbers of people were 'pinged' by the NHS COVID-19 contact tracing app asking them to isolate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware victim gets master key to unlock networks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-technology-joe-biden-europe-business-bb7298b31b7157640fbd5f90fc19c224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — The Florida company whose software was exploited in the devastating Fourth of July weekend ransomware attack, Kaseya, has received a universal key that will decrypt all of the more than 1,000 businesses and public organizations crippled in the global incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buses leaving Texas border town packed with illegals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/22/buses-leaving-texas-border-town-packed-with-illegal-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buses leaving the Texas city at the heart of the border crisis are struggling to keep up with business — because they’re full of illegal immigrants released into the US, The Post has le…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suddenly It's Bare Season...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/suddenly-its-bare-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who hasn’t had the nightmare? It’s the one about being caught in public dressed in your undies. Therapists and dream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi Brief in Crucial Supreme Court Abortion Case: Overturn 'Roe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/mississippi-brief-in-crucial-supreme-court-abortion-case-overturn-roe-and-casey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi attorney general Lynn Fitch filed a brief in the most important Supreme Court abortion case in three decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: 'ANOTHER PIVOTAL POINT'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-director-warns-us-at-another-pivotal-point-in-pandemic/ar-AAMrGDD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention struck a new tone of urgency on Thursday about the coronavirus pandemic, warning that the United States is “not out of the woods yet” and is once again at “another pivotal point in this pandemic” as the highly infectious Delta variant rips through communities with low rates of vaccination. The warning from the director, Dr. Rochelle Walensky, during a briefing by members of the White...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy to require 'pass' for many activities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-6e5ba18d35f3ac40d4f34e6b3b22d58d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — With daily COVID-19 cases sharply rising again, Italy will soon require people to have passes reflecting their health status to access gyms, museums, movie theaters, the inside of restaurants and other venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK moderators call for end to overly restrictive NDAs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/7/22/22587757/facebook-content-moderators-ireland-end-restrictive-ndas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook content moderators in Ireland call for change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin sisters forced to kneel, executed in horror INSTAGRAM livestream...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15655009/twin-sisters-executed-horror-instagram-livestream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWIN sisters were executed in a horrific Instagram livestream. The women, named locally as Amália and Amanda Alves, were forced to kneel before being shot in the back of the head because they ̶…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers detect first 'moon-forming' disc surrounding exoplanet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-researchers-detect-first-moon-forming-disc-surrounding-exoplanet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers detect first 'moon-forming' disc surrounding exoplanet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAC has not used any of $75M its raised to help fund election audits...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/564387-trump-pac-has-not-used-any-of-the-75m-its-raised-this-year-to-help-fund</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump’s leadership PAC has not yet used any of the roughly $75 million raised to help finance election reviews,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Can't Travel Because State Dept. Employees Won't Work...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/22/americans-cant-travel-because-state-department-employees-wont-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Massive passport-processing delays, due to COVID restrictions and staffing shortages, are ruining summer travel plans and prompting fantastical workarounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL reveals forfeit rule targeting unvaccinated players...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/22/nfl-reveals-forfeit-rule-to-punish-unvaccinated-players/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has laid out its strongest incentive yet for players to get the vaccine. According to a memo shared on Twitter by NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero, the league has mandated that a game cann…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris' laugh is sound check for divided country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/more-than-a-laugh-kamala-harris-is-a-sound-check-for-a-divided-country/ar-AAMpsMa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI's human protein database 'great leap' for research...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-ai-s-human-protein-database-a-great-leap-for-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI's human protein database a 'great leap' for research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalized man says he'd still rather be sick than get shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/louisiana-covid-19-hospital-unit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hospital's chief medical officer said if people don't get vaccinated, "we are going to accept death."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Details on FBI Inquiry Into Kavanaugh Draw Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/details-on-fbi-inquiry-into-kavanaugh-draw-fire-from-democrats/ar-AAMrpto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly three years after Justice Brett M. Kavanaugh’s tumultuous confirmation to the Supreme Court, the F.B.I. has disclosed more details about its efforts to review the justice’s background, leading a group of Senate Democrats to question the thoroughness of the vetting and conclude that it was shaped largely by the Trump White House. In a letter dated June 30 to two Democratic senators, Sheldon Whitehouse of Rhode Island and Chris Coons of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST reporter sues paper and former editor Marty Baron, alleging discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/22/media/washington-post-lawsuit-felicia-sonmez/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco buys $20K GUCCI trash cans...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/gucci-garbage-san-francisco-approves-usd20k-trash-cans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco is hoping to replace the long-despised green trash-cans littered throughout the city, as its board of supervisors voted Wednesday to approve using new designer prototype bins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEVIN TOPS NYT LIST AFTER 400,000 IN 1ST WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/nyt-no-1-mark-levins-american-marxism-sells-400-000-in-1st-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They don’t call conservative media mogul Mark Levin the “Great One” for nothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL TESTS ORAL VAX</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israel-to-become-first-in-world-to-test-oral-covid-19-vaccine-674563</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grieving Mother Bear Doesn't Leave Dead Cub's Side After Being Struck By Speeding Car In Yosemite...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/grieving-mama-bear-at-yosemite-wont-leave-her-babys-side-when-cub-gets-hit-and-killed-by-speeding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“So please, remember this. Remember that when traveling through Yosemite, we are all just visitors in the home of countless animals and it is up to us to follow the rules that protect them,” wrote the park ranger who discovered the dead cub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy, 5, Dies In GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/5-year-old-georgia-boy-dies-from-covid-19-as-delta-variant-rapidly-spreads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Wyatt would wave to strangers in the grocery store, because he knew that it absolutely made their day," his dad wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As employers get MORE desperate to fill jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/employers-desperate-worker-openings-8dcad7c2-0844-40a1-9ff6-2477ef3dadad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health care employers are particularly desperate to fill jobs now, according to new data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme weather wreaks havoc worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/summer-disaster-extreme-weather-wreaks-115720112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change is making the world more prone to floods like those in China and Europe and to heat waves and fires like those in the U.S. and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH FLORIDA HOTSPOT</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/20/covid-south-florida-hospitalizations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jackson Health System is sounding the alarm about what they are seeing in their hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Expressway Shootings Hit All-Time High...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/07/21/i-fear-getting-hit-from-behind-chicago-area-expressway-shootings-at-an-all-time-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Dan Ryan, in particular, has certain intervals where it’s probably repeat offenders here.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Easy making big comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/travel/article/How-the-Big-Easy-is-making-its-big-comeback-16332352.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TESTING AS CASES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/white-house-boosts-funding-covid-tests-infections-continue-surge-n1274677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As in early days of a pandemic, confirming illnesses and contact tracing are critical, public health officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In America's least air-conditioned cities, brutal heat changes people's minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/In-America-s-least-air-conditioned-cities-brutal-16332213.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Boise, Idaho, where the temperature topped 97 for a stretch of 14 out of 15 days this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Fencer Accused of Sex Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/u-s-olympic-fencer-accused-of-sexual-misconduct-kept-apart-from-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alen Hadzic, 29, of South Orange, N.J., is an alternate in the men’s epee event with the United States Olympic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Antonoff Doesn't Want to Just Take Up Space...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/jack-antonoff-doesnt-want-to-just-take-up-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To the outside observer, Jack Antonoff might seem like something of a workaholic. A widely trusted collaborator whose fingerprints are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Self-proclaimed 'incel' planned to kill sorority girls at university, feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/self-proclaimed-e2-80-98incel-e2-80-99-planned-to-kill-sorority-girls-at-an-ohio-university-feds-say/ar-AAMqMpI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tres Genco was charged Wednesday with attempting to conduct a mass shooting of women — a hate crime — and illegally possessing a machine gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Ratings Watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/tokyo-olympics-tv-ratings-preview-1234985186/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Games will almost surely bring NBC and its sibling cable networks their biggest primetime audiences in months. They’ll probably also fall well short of previous Games. How can both statem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Giant Sued Over Sex Harassment, Unequal Pay in 'Pervasive Frat Boy' Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/activision-blizzard-sued-california-over-095844879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Game giant Activision Blizzard has been hit with a lawsuit from the California Department of Fair Employment and Housing, alleging the company’s “pervasive frat boy workplace culture” resulted in women employees being continuously subjected to sexual harassment and being paid less than men. The California Department of Fair Employment and Housing filed a civil lawsuit […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of Messy Night Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyv5v7/freedom-day-england-clubbing-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 16 months, clubs in England are open again. VICE writer Izzy Copestake spent "freedom day" partying (and reporting).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES to go all-electric...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/autos/mercedes-benz-go-all-electric-2030-n1274708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We really want to go for it ... and be dominantly, if not all electric, by the end of the decade," said the head of Daimler, Mercedes-Benz's parent company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over rules gives new impetus to France's Yellow Vests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722113212-4lzpd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustration at government measures to curb the spread of COVID-19, which some people say are an attack on their liberty, has given the movement fresh momentum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Sparks Outcry for Calling Capitol Police Officer 'Angry Left-Wing' Activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fox-news-tucker-carlson-harry-dunn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Carlson sparked outcry Wednesday when he called Black Capitol police officer Harry Dunn an "angry left-wing political activist."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Reveals Trump Gushing Over Jan. 6 Mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/audio-reveals-trump-gushing-over-loving-jan-6-crowd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president got misty-eyed about the Capitol rioters in a newly released audio clip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MAGA's Biggest Porn Star on Being Booted from TPUSA Event...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/maga-biggest-porn-star-brandi-082351801.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ethan Miller/GettyBrandi Love is the most famous MAGA porn star on the planet. The adult-industry veteran boasts 831.5K followers on Twitter, has starred in hundreds of XXX films, penned the book Getting Wild Sex from Your Conservative Woman, and is a columnist for The Federalist. She enthusiastically supports Donald Trump and loathes antifa, BLM, and the Squad.And yet, on Saturday, she was banned from a conservative political conference just for being a porn star.Love, 48, had attended a number</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
