<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Venus is Russian planet -- say Russians...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/18/world/venus-russian-planet-scn-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No longer confined to territories here on Earth, Russia has now staked its claim on Venus, saying it is a "Russian planet."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA Collection to Expand...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/hamedaleaziz/ice-expanding-dna-collection-of-immigrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources said ICE officials have also explored advocating for the prosecution of immigrants who refuse to have their DNA collected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church's woke ad featuring Jesus with women's breasts, make-up sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8744095/Churchs-woke-advert-featuring-bearded-Jesus-womens-breasts-sparks-outrage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The advert, which apparently shows Jesus shaking his 'breasts' while dancing under a rainbow, appeared on the National Church's Facebook page on September 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog-Walker Escapes Gator Dragging Him Into Water By Poking Eye...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/09/18/florida-man-attacked-alligator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quick actions saved the life of a Port St. Lucie man who was attacked by a large alligator while he was out walking his dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Greek Letter System Forms...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/09/18/alpha-first-greek-letter-storm-portugal-hurricane-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subtropical storm Alpha has formed near the coast of Portugal, marking the first time since 2005, that a storm system was named using a letter from the Greek alphabet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: App tells child to create child porn, threatens strangulation...</title>
      <link>https://foxbaltimore.com/news/local/police-app-tells-child-to-create-child-porn-threatens-strangulation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foxbaltimore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANNE ARUNDEL COUNTY, MD (WBFF) - Police in Anne Arundel County say an app on a child's cellphone told a 5-year-old to take naked pictures in the bathtub and threatened the child with strangulation if the child didn't do as they were told. Police received a call for help on September 16th. Officers discovered that the child had several questionable cellphone apps: Talking Angela. Talking Angela 2. Talking Tom 2. Talking Ben 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless drown in medical debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2020/09/18/unemployment-americans-face-45-b-worth-medical-debt-collections/3480192001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of unemployed Americans are struggling to stay afloat after losing their health-insurance coverage following a historic wave of layoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Study Shows COVID Transmission From Animals To Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mink-study-first-covid-transmission-animals-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BASEL, Switzerland — A new study provides compelling evidence that coronavirus spreads between humans and animals. Researchers studying 16 mink farms in the Netherlands say that SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, was not only transmitted from human to mink, but vice versa. Just about nine months into this pandemic, the scientific community is still unsure…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man survives by perching on rock in river, fending off embers with chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesmanjournal.com/story/news/nation/2020/09/17/oregon-wildfires-update-beachie-creek-fire-man-survives-sheltering-river/3478742001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesmanjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trapped in a canyon by downed trees and flames, an Oregon man survived on a rock in the middle of a river. He made time for a beer, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov gifts maggot-infested apples during wildfire visits...</title>
      <link>https://www.king5.com/article/news/local/gov-jay-inslee-gifts-maggot-infested-apples-during-wildfire-visits/293-bb9dbdb9-b00b-4c1d-9b2a-cf7891fb03a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.king5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The county is asking Bridgeport and Douglas County residents or anyone who may have information for help locating the apples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outgoing ambassador: USA 'believed Chinese'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/18/china-ambassador-trump-coronavirus-pandemic-417648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remarks from the Trump appointee and former longtime Iowa governor represent an apparent break with the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC backtracks on controversial recommendations...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/18/cdc-reverses-course-on-testing-for-asymptomatic-people-who-had-covid-19-contact-417749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency is backtracking on controversial recommendations it made last month, reportedly over the advice of agency scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.K. Rowling Book Burning Videos Spreading Across TIKTOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/jk-rowling-books-burned-tiktok-transgender-issues-1532330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS 7-hour flight to nowhere sells out in 10 mins...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/flights-to-nowhere-qantas/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With international flights restricted, Australian carrier Qantas is the latest airline to offer a flight to nowhere, taking in local sights to passengers paying up to US$2,700.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash-strapped campaign awaits bailout from big donors...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/17/gop-donors-rush-to-rescue-trump-417364</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preserve America, a new super PAC backing the president, is planning another $25 million ad blitz attacking Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Coffee gives you edge to beat cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.enterprisenews.com/news/20200918/coffee-linked-to-longer-survival-in-patients-with-colorectal-cancer-study-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enterprisenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants who drank larger amounts of coffee – more than four cups a day – had an even greater benefit. These benefits held for both</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's own campaign manager didn't vote for him in 2016, public records show... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-s-campaign-manager-didn-t-vote-for-him-in-15577908.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's campaign manager didn't vote for his boss in the last presidential election. He didn't vote at all.  The last time Bill Stepien voted, according to public records, was 2015 when he lived in New Jersey and was registered there.  Stepien registered to vote in Washington, D.C., where he's been living since 2017, at the end of July - two weeks after he was tapped to take over Trump's reelection bid.  Stepien, a onetime aide to former New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie, R, first joined Trump's team in August 2016. A senior campaign official said Stepien requested an absentee ballot that never arrived, so he didn't vote in 2016.  He wasn't registered in either New Jersey or Washington to vote in the 2018 midterm elections.  Neither Stepien nor a campaign spokesman responded to further questions about his voting record, including whether he made additional efforts to obtain a ballot or considered voting in person to support Trump.  Trump, who this year voted by absentee ballot in Florida, repeatedly has attacked voting by mail, claiming without evidence that it is susceptible to widespread fraud and corruption. He has encouraged people to vote in person amid the coronavirus pandemic to ensure their vote is counted, even suggesting they try to vote once by mail and once at their polling place, which is illegal.  Despite Trump's antagonism to widespread voting by mail, at least 16 top Trump officials regularly vote that way, including Vice President Mike Pence, Attorney General William Barr and White House press secretary Kayleigh McEnany.  Stepien, however, appears to be the first high-level aide not to have voted in the 2016 GOP primary or presidential election when Trump was on the ballot.  Christie fired Stepien in 2014 amid the Bridgegate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming giant announces major deal with Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2020/09/17/netflix-signs-deal-saudi-arabian-animation-studio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Streaming giant Netflix announced on Wednesday that it has signed a five-year partnership deal with Saudi Arabian animation studio Myrkott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer of Disasters Set Grim Records, Left Trail of Ruin...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/summer-u-disasters-set-grim-131736376.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It was a summer of violent weather in the U.S., with massive wildfires, searing heat, floods and hurricanes leaving trails of destruction. The disasters have hit in nearly every region of the country. They’re further evidence that the Earth’s climate is changing, bringing hotter temperatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather Service runs out of hurricane names!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f76ed70054903dff6a7731b1f0ab9998</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORANGE BEACH, Ala. (AP) — A second death from Hurricane Sally was reported Friday in Alabama on a day that also saw the National Hurricane Center have to resort to using the Greek alphabet for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency tents back as Madrid struggles to curb...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/932f8a9a3b640db0e9a1f078a94bf6f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — A line of green tents labeled with a red cross stands empty Friday in the garden of a Madrid military hospital as a second wave of the coronavirus takes hold in the Spanish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada extends U.S. border restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7c926e38003ee9110d5f64a9f4a227cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Canada is extending the agreement to keep the U.S. border closed to non-essential travel to Oct. 21 during the coronavirus pandemic. Public Safety Minister Bill Blair said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority plan to vote before Election Day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d8b70cc5c9114ec214a3b9d7981bde3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — A majority of President Donald Trump's supporters plan to cast their ballot on Election Day, while about half of Joe Biden's backers plan to vote by mail, a sign of a growing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump compares Pelosi to an insect...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1494555/trump-pelosi-crazy-bed-bug-remove-speaker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENT Donald Trump has said House Speaker Nancy Pelosi “as crazy as a bed bug” as Republicans work to oust her from her coveted role in Congress. Trump called Pelosi the name during a campaign …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall of the Frat House: Students turn away from Greek life amid racial reckoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Fall-of-the-frat-house-Students-target-Greek-15574070.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graham Payne-Reichert logged onto Zoom from a lawn chair in the backyard of his unofficial fraternity house, surrounded by three other members of Delta Tau Delta and a futon that had mysteriously snapped in half a few months before.  He watched faces appear one by one on his screen - first his former roommate, then his Spikeball teammate, then the older fraternity brother who had put him at ease during a hard transition to American University just two years ago.  It was one month after the killing of George Floyd and Payne-Reichert, vice president of his fraternity, kicked off a virtual meeting that would break up the chapter he once adored.  For two hours, the virtual group of 26 men discussed the lack of diversity in their fraternity chapter and the Instagram pages that shared anonymous accounts of racism and sexual assault at their school. The meeting ended with a unanimous vote to disband the chapter of Delta Tau Delta.  "The pressure was on those of us in Greek life to justify our existence and we couldn't do it," said Payne-Reichert, 20. "I realized that remaining complicit in the system was a moral issue, and it was one I could not live with."  That day, Payne-Reichert and his brothers joined hundreds of students at more than a dozen elite colleges and universities nationwide who have cut ties with their fraternities and sororities over the past three months, saying the organizations with histories of sexual assault and White exclusivity are out of line with growing demands for social justice.  At Duke University, a Black sorority sister took off her lettered sweatshirt when grieving Floyd's death. At the University of Richmond, every member of the Panhellenic Executive Board, which governs campus sororities, resigned. And at Tufts University, the school's Panhellenic Council said on Instagram it suspended...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double life that brought them down...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-falwells-the-pool-attendant-and-the-double-life-that-brought-them-all-down/ar-BB19aRVj?ocid=ob-fb-enus-280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promise of October Vaccine Risks Letdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-promise-of-october-vaccine-risks-letdown-or-rejection/ar-BB19alBD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200,000</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/us-stands-on-verge-of-dark-new-milestone-200000-virus-deaths/ar-BB19aNjn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Nature Has Mystical Capacity to Bring People to God...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2020/09/17/pope-francis-nature-has-a-mystical-capacity-to-bring-people-to-god/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis said Wednesday that nature possesses a “mystical capacity” to bring humanity to God and into communion with creation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather Service runs out of hurricane names!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/new-tropical-storm-in-central-atlantic-grabs-the-name-wilfred/816085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT LANDFALL SOUTHERN TEX?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/budding-tropical-storm-wilfred-in-gulf-of-mexico/815250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Ryan Murphy: NETFLIX $300 Million Man Paying Off?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-state-of-ryan-murphy-is-netflixs-dollar300-million-man-paying-off-16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why have all of the prolific producer’s streaming shows been so bad?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling stops in Minnesota... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/517037-biden-trump-to-hold-dueling-campaign-stops-in-minnesota</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden are each taking their campaigns to Minnesota on Friday as polls show the former vice president with a solid lead in a state that Trump narrowly lost four years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election winner could depend on absentee rules in these states?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/know-biden-trump-wins-could-133022608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These states will likely decide if Biden or Trump wins the presidential election. And their absentee ballot laws could determine when we learn the outcome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPKINS WARNS...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/09/17/coronavirus-spread-cold-temperatures-johns-hopkins-research/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As temperatures begin to drop with the changing of the seasons, researchers at Johns Hopkins say COVID-19 could spread more during the colder weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big wedding in fictional home of 'GODFATHER' fuels cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df53b3534711f0f675e5460928489421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Sicilian town of Corleone, made famous by the fictional Mafia clan in “The Godfather,” has ordered schools closed and a limited lockdown after a spate of coronavirus infections...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$2.50 a Year in Interest? That's What $5,000 in Savings Gets...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/09/18/your-money/savings-interest-rates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Federal Reserve keeping rates low, home buyers are benefiting. But savers? Their average interest rate is just 0.05 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Joe +9 in Arizona, tied in NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/poll-biden-up-by-9-points-in-arizona-tied-with-trump-in-north-carolina/ar-BB19aSPI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pandemic fatigue' leads to resurgence In Europe where cases surge to fresh records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/18/pandemic-fatigue-leads-to-resurgence-of-coronavirus-in-europe-where-france-and-spain-hit-records.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Pandemic fatigue" has set in across parts of Europe, where the outbreak is on the rise again in some countries that were hailed early on for stamping out massive outbreaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Barr Goes All-In for Campaign Themes Weeks Before Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/barr-goes-all-in-for-trump-campaign-themes-weeks-before-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;William Barr Goes All-In for Trump Campaign Themes Weeks Before Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to block U.S. downloads of TIKTOK, WECHAT on Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/18/trump-to-block-us-downloads-of-tiktok-wechat-on-sunday-officials-tell-reuters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Commerce department announced Friday morning that it would ban U.S. business transactions with China-owned social apps WeChat and TikTok on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Tahoe Booms in Tech's Work-From-Anywhere Shift...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2020-09-18/lake-tahoe-booms-in-tech-s-work-from-anywhere-shift</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Rich Americans Fleeing To Caribbean...</title>
      <link>https://suntci.com/why-rich-americans-are-fleeing-to-the-caribbean-this-winter-p5420-135.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;suntci.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gospel of ayahuasca: Hallucinogenic inspires legal religious movement...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/17/gospel-of-ayahuasca-hallucinogenic-inspires-legal-religious-movement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “churches” use hallucinatory daime tea, also known as ayahuasca, for the purpose of spiritual ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel returns to lockdown as cases mount...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff70d10700ebe2ed7becc3b2a9e08bc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel went back into a full lockdown on Friday to try to contain a coronavirus outbreak that has steadily worsened for months as its government has been plagued by indecision and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Morrison rips 'fascist bullies' in anti-lockdown songs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2020/sep/18/van-morrison-fascist-bullies-anti-lockdown-covid-songs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Songwriter uses new material to condemn UK government, scientists and celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking healthy breath now luxury in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Taking-a-healthy-breath-is-now-a-luxury-in-15577244.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California wildfires have wreaked havoc on the students in Jesusita Rivera's fifth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launches combat drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/China-launches-combat-drills-in-Taiwan-Strait-15577121.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan - The Chinese military on Friday expressed its displeasure toward a senior State Department official's visit to Taipei by conducting "real combat" drills in Taiwanese airspace that further raised the stakes amid a period of intense military activity in the volatile Taiwan Strait.  The new drills came hours before Undersecretary of State Keith Krach was due to meet Taiwanese President Tsai Ing-wen in the capital and a day after news emerged that the Trump administration sought to push forward a multibillion-dollar sale of advanced weapons to the self-ruled island to beef up its defenses against Beijing.  China flew two bombers and 16 fighters that crossed the median line of the Taiwan Strait, the Taiwanese Defense Ministry said, adding that it responded by scrambling fighter jets and activating missile systems.  The latest provocation came two days after China flew anti-submarine aircraft into Taiwanese airspace and a week after China conducted a large-scale naval and air maneuver surrounding an outlying Taiwanese island as part of a steadily escalating pressure campaign against Taipei.  Taiwanese officials have decried the escalation in the strait, one of the world's most militarized flash points, and have warned that it could devolve into all-out war. Taiwan's presidential office on Friday urged Beijing not to be a "provocateur," saying that its aggressive actions did not help China's international image.  The new drills Friday were a "legitimate action of the Chinese military in promoting our security and sovereignty and territorial integrity," Col. Ren Guoqiang, a China Defense Ministry spokesman, told reporters. "The United States and the Democratic Progressive Party have been colluding recently, frequently stirring up trouble."  He accused the Taiwanese ruling party of "relying on foreigners" to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile launch or storm repairs? Flurry of activity fuels speculation of NKorea test...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles/missile-launch-or-storm-repairs-flurry-of-activity-fuels-speculation-of-north-korea-test-idUSKBN2690FN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts and security officials say they are watching for signs that North Korea may use an upcoming holiday to unveil new weapons or test fire a submarine-launched ballistic missile (SLBM), after a flurry of activity was detected at a key base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Stands on Verge of Dark New Milestone: 200,000 Virus Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-s-stands-on-verge-of-dark-new-milestone-200-000-virus-deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Stands on Verge of Dark New Milestone: 200,000 Virus Deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538: Dems favored to win Senate...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-election-forecast/senate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest forecasts and polls for the 2020 Senate elections by Nate Silver’s FiveThirtyEight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope seeks to 'liberate' Virgin Mary from Mafia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e136c852a49222b21d7574bb643a4f23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis is giving his blessing to a new Vatican think tank that is seeking to prevent the Mafia and organized crime groups from exploiting the image of the Virgin Mary for their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momentum for Basic Income Builds as Pandemic Drags On...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2020/09/17/momentum-for-basic-income-builds-as-pandemic-drags-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advocates see an opportunity to transform the safety net.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promise of October Vaccine Risks Letdown or Rejection...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-s-promise-of-october-vaccine-risks-letdown-or-rejection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s Promise of October Vaccine Risks Letdown or Rejection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Driver Pulled Over Going 93 MPH -- Completely Asleep!</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/tesla-driver-pulled-over-asleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The officer was able to obtain radar readings on the vehicle, confirming that it had automatically accelerated up to exactly 150 km/h [93 mph]."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sloppy Poisoning of Alexey Navalny Turned Merkel Against Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-sloppy-poisoning-of-alexey-navalny-turned-merkel-against-putin/ar-BB19aawc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked FEMA Memo Reveals 17% Jump in Virus Deaths Last Week...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/live-updates/coronavirus/?id=73065540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of confirmed COVID-19 cases has surpassed 30 million worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL fans brawl at socially distanced game!</title>
      <link>https://dailysnark.com/2020/09/17/browns-fans-brawl-in-the-stands-during-thursday-night-football-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailysnark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Sued By Parents of Toddlers in Doctored Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-racist-baby-video-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump was sued on Thursday by the parents of two toddlers featured in a doctored video that was shared by the president in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump slams Biden for using teleprompter  -- while using one himself!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8746137/Donald-Trump-slams-Joe-Biden-using-teleprompter-using-one-himself.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump criticized Democratic rival Joe Biden for using a teleprompter while using one himself during his Wisconsin rally on Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife Smashed Down Door; His drunken fall down stairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8745763/911-call-intoxicated-Jerry-Falwell-Jr-s-house-describes-lot-blood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Becki Falwell made a 911 call after returning home on August 31 to find her husband Jerry Falwell Jr. with lacerations to his face after hitting a trash can following a drunken fall down the stairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Accused of Watching INSTAGRAM Users Through Cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/facebook-accused-of-watching-instagram-users-through-cameras/ar-BB199T81?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEFS Announce Fan Infected With Covid Attended Opening Game; Other Fans Told To Quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/ten-nfl-fans-told-to-quarantine-after-coming-into-contact-with-infected-fan-at-texans-chiefs-opener/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NFL fan tested positive for COVID-19 after attending the Chiefs' opener</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Storm Landfalls This Year Are One Shy of 1916 Record...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-u-storm-landfalls-one-170754398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Hurricane Sally’s historic flooding of Florida and Alabama this week marked the eighth named storm to strike the continental U.S. this year, leaving the tally just one short of a record that dates back more than a century.With 10 weeks left in the Atlantic storm season, there’s a good</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBATE PREVIEW</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/joe-biden-cnn-town-hall-review-donald-trump-coronavirus-anderson-cooper-1234579013/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Joe Biden had to do to claim ground against Donald Trump in tonight’s CNN town hall was show up and show he cared. And that’s exactly what the former Vice-President did from the very start of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of infected doubling every week in England!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1492407/scientists-two-week-national-lockdown-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS advising the Government want a two-week national lockdown next month to battle the surge in coronavirus, it is reported. Experts suggested an October lockdown during half term before the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President contradicts health advisers on vaccine timetable...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-contradicts-health-advisers-on-vaccine-15576519.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's public rebuke of a top federal health official who did not parrot White House talking points about a fast-track coronavirus vaccine is the latest example of the president's effort to enforce an upbeat narrative about the pandemic,even if that does not square with the facts.  Robert Redfield, director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, is the most recent government physician or scientist to run afoul of Trump's coronavirus message machine. He did so in congressional testimony Wednesday, saying a vaccine greenlighted later this year would probably not be available to most Americans until sometime in 2021 because those most in need would get the first doses. Redfield also rankled Trump by saying face masks are "more guaranteed to protect me against covid than when I take a covid vaccine."  Trump said Redfield "made a mistake" on both counts, although the CDC director's projection about the timetable for vaccine approval and distribution mirrored those of other top officials, including Operation Warp Speed chief scientist Moncef Slaoui and Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases.  "It's just incorrect information," Trump said, adding that he had called Redfield after his Senate testimony.  With fewer than 50 days before the Nov. 3 election, Trump has keyed on a prospective coronavirus vaccine as a piece of good newsthat demonstrates his leadership amid a grinding pandemic, with continued job losses, school closures and disruptions to daily life. Trump argues that the worst of the crisis is past and that states should lift remaining restrictions meant to curb the spread of a disease that has killed nearly 200,000 Americans.  But health and science experts say his continued swipes at the government's own experts are undermining...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States plan to independently vet data...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2020/09/17/exclusive-states-plan-to-independently-vet-covid-19-vaccine-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials are skeptical of federal reviews of potential COVID-19 vaccines, with some planning to independently analyze clinical trial data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flat out disregard for human life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pence-s-former-top-aide-says-trump-called-coronavirus-a-good-thing-because-he-didn-t-like-shaking-hands-with-disgusting-supporters/ar-BB199CZw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW BLAMES TRUMP BUT SHOWS OBAMA CAGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/rachel-maddow-uses-photos-of-immigrant-children-held-in-cages-during-obama-administration-while-blaming-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC's Rachel Maddow used images of children held in cages during the Obama administration in a segment blasting President Donald Trump over the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Pence Covid Aide Voting for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/17/politics/former-pence-aide-coronvirus-task-force-slams-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former top aide to Vice President Mike Pence assailed President Donald Trump's response to the pandemic in a new video Thursday, adding to the growing list of former Trump administration officials who have criticized the President and, in several cases, endorsed his Democratic opponent Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE detainees complained about 'rough' treatment from Georgia doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/ice-detainees-complained-about-rough-treatment-from-georgia-doctor/S4V5UDBRKZCJZMSUPOJQRXKYNM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, women at a South Georgia immigration jail talked about Dr. Mahendra Amin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyeglasses may help protect against virus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/516945-eyeglasses-may-help-protect-against-coronavirus-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eyeglasses could offer additional protection against transmission of coronavirus, according to a study published in the Journal of the American Medical Associatio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director says antifa is an ideology, not an organization...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bdd3b6078e9efadcfcd0be4b65f2362e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — FBI Director Chris Wray told lawmakers Thursday that antifa is an ideology, not an organization, delivering testimony that puts him at odds with President Donald Trump, who has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN DRIVE-IN TOWN HALL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b4ff1bdcc7c0b6c05dd520598e349744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOOSIC, Pa. (AP) — Joe Biden on Thursday went after President Donald Trump again and again over his handling of COVID-19, calling Trump's downplaying of the pandemic “criminal” and his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  27% SAY COUNTRY HEADED IN RIGHT DIRECTION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab370b659775811cc6ee4d97375b98d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Less than seven weeks before Election Day, most Americans are deeply pessimistic about the direction of the country and skeptical of President Donald Trump’s handling of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under lockdown, Israel faces bitter start of Jewish New Year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6bfae480c85de99e6a091100330607ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Eating apples dipped in honey on Rosh Hashana is a Jewish tradition to symbolize a sweet start of the New Year. But in Israel, bitterness prevails on the eve of the holiday as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gulf between White House's words, Trump's actions on masks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/41dc3fc8f146db80754c8f5b2a474c98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — White House officials insist that President Donald Trump strongly supports face masks to prevent the spread of coronavirus and always has. But the president’s own words and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks changes that slowed mail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/27f8cfb536769d5b9b26ba354f501fca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — A U.S. judge on Thursday blocked controversial Postal Service changes that have slowed mail nationwide, calling them “a politically motivated attack on the efficiency of the Postal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before Sweetheart Deal From Trump, KODAK Sponsored His Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/before-it-got-a-sweetheart-covid-deal-from-trump-kodak-sponsored-his-celebrity-apprentice-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision to give the famous camera giant $765 million to help manufacture coronavirus drugs has raised numerous eyebrows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee will restart nursing home visits
...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/health/2020/09/17/tn-coronavirus-restrictions-nursing-home-visits-lifted/5772193002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting Oct. 1, nursing homes will be allowed to welcome visitors if they’ve gone two weeks without a new case of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>911 Call From Intoxicated Falwell's House Describes 'Lot Of Blood'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/911-called-to-allegedly-intoxicated-jerry-falwell-jrs-house-last-month-there-was-a-lot-of-blood-213552998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Becki Falwell told the operator that her husband had cuts on his face from falling after he’d been drinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sedition charge may apply to protest violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cbca8672a70f9f170a086a7a252a751e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a memo to U.S. attorneys Thursday obtained by The Associated Press, the Justice Department emphasized that federal prosecutors should aggressively go after demonstrators who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dam operator trapped for days...</title>
      <link>https://katu.com/news/wildfire-season-2020/detroit-dam-operator-mike-pomeroy-trapped-for-nearly-two-days-as-beachie-creek-fire-raged</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;katu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labor Day was windy. And Detroit Dam operator Mike Pomeroy knew there was a good chance a wildfire could threaten the dam. But by the time he was ready to evacuate, the Beachie Creek Fire was bearing down on him from the north. He jumped in his car and tried to drive east, but boulders and burning trees blocked the highway. He had no choice but to turn back and shelter in place inside the dam.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
