<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>In Town of 11 People, Mysterious Disappearance Turns Neighbor Against Neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/11/world/australia/larrimah-mystery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumors abound in a small outback town. Was Paddy Moriarty fed to a pet crocodile? Or could he have been baked into a meat pie?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight for FOX Local Sports Channels Could Shake Up Broadcasting...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/11/fight-for-fox-local-sports-channels-could-shake-up-broadcasting </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fight for Fox Local Sports Channels Could Shake Up Broadcasting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians involved in murder of Brazilian activist: govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180811-politicians-involved-murder-brazilian-activist-govt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay up or else: Spain warns of online 'sextortion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180811-pay-or-else-spain-warns-online-sextorsion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year in Paris as bad for health as smoking 183 cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180810-year-paris-bad-health-smoking-183-cigarettes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by the European Transport &amp; Environment association published on Friday confirmed that spending a few days in various popular European capitals is equivalent to smoking between one and four cigarettes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane stolen by 'suicidal' employee crashes near Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/701faeff7c7a44ab89b1186f6ffa63be/Plane-stolen-by-'suicidal'-employee-crashes-near-Seattle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATAC, Wash. (AP) — A "suicidal" airline employee stole an empty Horizon Air turboprop plane, took off from Sea-Tac International Airport and was chased by military jets before c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RELENTLESS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cbc36115f3c4dfda26693ffe1a2b5c8/Crews-battle-growing-wildfire-near-homes-in-California</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE ELSINORE, Calif. (AP) — Firefighters worked furiously Friday to keep a Southern California wildfire from burning more homes while crews in the north finally gained ground on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN ROCKET LIFTOFF! NASA GROUNDBREAKING MISSION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3c0d9bcef5904bf3a01717d66250cb3b/Last-minute-technical-problem-delays-NASA's-flight-to-sun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A last-minute technical problem Saturday delayed NASA's unprecedented flight to the sun.        The early morning launch countdown was halted wi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine row erupts in Italy as populist govt seeks to ease rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vaccine-row-erupts-italy-populist-govt-seeks-ease-031324205.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A row is erupting over vaccines in Italy as the country's new populist government fights to roll back a law that bans children from attending school if they haven't received a series of jabs. The law, adopted last year by the centre-left government that was booted out of power in March, made</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels' lawyer says Dems must fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/porn-star-lawyer-avenatti-takes-fighting-message-iowa-044149208--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEAR LAKE, Iowa (AP) — Michael Avenatti, the self-styled provocateur taking on the president for porn actress Stormy Daniels, told Iowa Democrats on Friday that the party needs a bare-knuckle fighter to take back the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Intelligent' crows to pick up litter at theme park...</title>
      <link>https://www.expatica.com/fr/news/country-news/France-tourism-birds-offbeat_2031808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.expatica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six crows specially trained to pick up cigarette ends and rubbish will be put to work next week at a French historical theme park, its president said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed by 2 pit bulls while on walk...</title>
      <link>http://www.montgomeryherald.com/news/article_a7fc2186-9cb4-11e8-8110-735d9be7ce56.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.montgomeryherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montgomery County Sheriff Chris Watkins released this statement Friday, August 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury Rules ROUNDUP Caused Groundskeeper's Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-jury-finds-monsanto-guilty-roundup-trial-224845050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California jury ordered chemical giant Monsanto to pay nearly $290 million Friday for failing to warn a dying groundskeeper that its weed killer Roundup might cause cancer. Jurors unanimously found that Monsanto -- which vowed to appeal -- acted with "malice" and that its weed killers Roundup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN ROCKET LIFTOFF! NASA GROUNDBREAKING MISSION...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nasa-sending-spacecraft-straight-suns-glittering-crown-192254533.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA is sending a spacecraft straight into the sun's glittering crown, an atmospheric region so hot and harsh any normal visitor would wither.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RELENTLESS!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-suspected-sparking-huge-california-forest-fire-facing-175454287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities battling massive wildfires in large swathes of California issued mandatory evacuation orders and health warnings Friday over the worsening air quality as the flames grew ever closer to populated areas. After almost a month of wildfires, the National Weather Service warned that satellite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba charges leading dissident with attempted murder... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cuba-charges-leading-dissident-attempted-murder-230745752.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of one of Cuba’s largest and most active opposition organizations was charged Friday with attempted murder after being held incommunicado for a week in eastern Cuba. Jose Daniel Ferrer, leader of the Patriotic Union of Cuba (UNPACU), was charged with deliberately trying to run over an official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border police: Woman in 80s smuggled drugs! </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/10/80-year-woman-caught-tecate-port-92-pounds-heroin-say-border-police/959529002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An older United States citizen attempted to cross the U.S./Mexico border near San Diego on Wednesday with 92 pounds of heroin in her car. Officials say cartels are known to manipulate people into carrying drugs over the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Acted with malice or oppression'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/aug/10/monsanto-trial-cancer-dewayne-johnson-ruling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court finds in favor of DeWayne Johnson, ill man who was first to take Roundup maker to trial over allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The stunning, devastating, weekslong journey of an orca and her dead calf... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-stunning-devastating-weekslong-journey-of-13147693.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grieving orca was spotted off the coast of Washington state Thursday, carrying her dead calf through the Pacific Ocean for the 17th day in a journey that has astonished and devastated much of the world. Tahlequah, as the mother has come to be called, gave birth on July 25 in what should have been a happy milestone for her long-suffering clan. As Allyson Chiu wrote for The Washington Post, the pod of killer whales that roams between Vancouver and San Juan Island has dwindled to 75 members over the decades. The cause is no mystery: Humans have netted up the whales' salmon, driven ships through their hunting lanes and polluted their water, to the point that researchers fear Tahlequah's generation may be the last of her family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Cities Dominate List of 'Boomtowns'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/texas/2018/08/10/texas-cities-dominate-list-of-u-s-boomtowns/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study this week that found Texas dominated the list of U.S. "boomtowns" and Austin scored the top spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orders MONSATO To Pay $290M In Damages...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/08/10/jury-rules-roundup-pesticide-caused-former-groundskeepers-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Francisco jury Friday ruled in favor of a former Benicia Unified School District groundskeeper who blamed his deadly cancer on the popular herbicide "Roundup" and sued its manufacturer Monsanto for damages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran test-fires ballistic missile...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/08/10/iran-test-fires-ballistic-missile-for-first-time-in-2018-officials-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in more than a year, Iran test-fired a ballistic missile in a brazen display of defiance months after President Trump pulled the United States out of a landmark nuclear deal and days before his administration slapped new sanctions on the Islamic Republic, three U.S. officials with knowledge of the launch tell Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA: All new music sounds same...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/08/10/madonna-slams-todays-music-everyone-sounds-same.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with Vogue Italia pop star Madonna talks about her year living in Lisbon and how most new songs sound the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump dines with APPLE Cook... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/401348-trump-to-dine-with-apple-ceo-tim-cook </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump will dine with Apple CEO Tim Cook on Friday, according to a tweet he sent late Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of living rises at fastest rate in decade... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/401321-cost-of-living-rises-at-quickest-rate-in-10-years </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of living in the U.S. is rising at its fastest rate in 10 years, according to new data from the Labor Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Why We Dug Through His Wife's Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/10/reader-center/bett-kavanaugh-wife-foia-request.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Readers have asked about the kind of public information requests our journalists make. Two of our investigative reporters explain how this worked with recent requests on President Trump’s Supreme Court nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N-WORD DRAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/10/omarosa-trump-book-the-apprentice-memoir</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Apprentice contestant and ex-White House adviser writes in new memoir that she witnessed ‘truly appalling things’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAROSA SHOW: INTERVIEW CONTRADICTS BOOK!?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/08/10/636955054/omarosa-tells-npr-she-heard-trump-n-word-tape-contradicting-her-own-tell-all-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former reality TV star and Trump aide Omarosa Manigault Newman spoke to NPR about explosive allegations in her new book, Unhinged, but part of her account changed in the interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER CIRCLING ROGER STONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/manhattan-madam-kristin-davis-testifying-before-grand-jury-1533919583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Stone claimed he had interactions with WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange during the 2016 presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauffeur May Bring Down Argentina's Political Elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/quicktakes/2018/08/10/how-a-chauffeur-could-bring-down-argentina-s-elite-quicktake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a Chauffeur Could Bring Down Argentina’s Political Elite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private TESLA? That's One Big Tiny Automaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/10/private-tesla-would-be-dwarfed-by-world-s-largest-automakers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Private Tesla? That’s One Big Tiny Automaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreigners face ban on buying homes in New Zealand after apocalypse bolthole fad hikes prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/10/foreigners-face-ban-buying-homes-new-zealand-apocalypse-bolthole/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreigners are set to be banned from buying homes in New Zealand after a spate of millionaires seeking luxury doomsday boltholes has apparently crowded out local buyers and pushed up property prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washed up whales on Irish beaches killed by military activity?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/dead-whales-washed-ashore-military-sonar-cuviers-beaked-royal-navy-a8485576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Catastrophic event’ likely to be behind ‘highly unusual’ multiple strandings, says marine conservation group</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE: 500,000+ Venezuelans fled to Ecuador this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/10/more-than-half-a-million-venezuelans-fled-to-ecuador-this-year-un-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quito declared a state of emergency after 30,000 migrants escaping violence and a collapsing economy came the first week of August</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Unable To Name Legislative Accomplishment...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/10/kamala-harris-unable-to-name-a-legislative-accomplishment-when-asked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris struggled to name a specific legislative accomplishment the 2020 hopeful was a part of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway to test free heroin for drug addicts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/norway-test-free-heroin-drug-addicts-102557686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway, which has one of the highest deadly drug overdose rates in Europe, will test prescribing free heroin to the most serious addicts to improve their living conditions, the government said on Friday. The Norwegian Directorate for Health and Social Affairs has been tasked with proposing an experimental</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper Calls for Coordinated Editorial Attack on President...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/newspaper-calls-war-words-against-193505874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Boston newspaper is proposing a coordinated editorial response from publications across the U.S. to President Donald Trump's frequent attacks on the news media. "We are not the enemy of the people," said Marjorie Pritchard, a deputy managing editor of The Boston Globe, referring to a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Sean Young wanted for questioning in burglary...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/actress-sean-young-wanted-questioning-burglary-125715971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Police say actress Sean Young is wanted for questioning after she was caught on surveillance video stealing laptops and video production software from a store in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Orders Chinese Company to Sell Building Near Trump Tower...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-orders-chinese-company-to-sell-manhattan-building-near-trump-tower-1533917797</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government has told Chinese conglomerate HNA Group it has to sell its majority stake in a Manhattan skyscraper whose tenants include a police precinct tasked with protecting Trump Tower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In France, Even Rats Have Rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-france-even-the-rats-have-rights-1533914241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodents overrunning Paris have defenders who say the varmint has a right to inhabit the City of Lights, too. ‘We really need to find a balance to live together.’ Reaching ‘Rat-Prochement’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Eases Restrictions on Nazi Symbols...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/germany-eases-restrictions-on-nazi-symbols-in-videogames-1533915852</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Games, which have often had to either not sell in Germany or scrub the imagery, will be judged on a case-by-case basis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Rubio Goes Nationalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/john-mccormack/rubio-goes-nationalist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet the new Marco . . .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8-person fight after tourists battle for best Rome selfie...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/10/selfish-selfie-takers-spark-trevi-fountain-fisticuffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight-person fight ensues after tourists battle for best spot in front of Roman monument</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacked satellite systems could launch microwave-like attacks, expert warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/news-blog/2018/aug/09/satellite-system-hacking-attacks-ships-planes-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Black Hat conference in Las Vegas, researcher says theoretical threat to ships, planes and military is ‘no longer theoretical’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Steele: She's Not Credible...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ex-rnc-chair-michael-steele-omarosa-not-credible-despite-trump-racist-tape-claim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former RNC Chair Michael Steele, now a prominent anti-Trump activist, called out ex-Trump aide Omarosa’s hypocrisy as a newfound voice against Trump’s racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin scammers target wealthy, threaten to expose 'secret'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article216448005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men in a wealthy Washington suburb have been receiving letters threatening to expose their dark secrets to their wives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Manhattan Madam' testifies before grand jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/10/manhattan-madam-mueller-trump-stone-771182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The infamous ‘Manhattan Madam‘ has ties to President Donald Trump's former political adviser Roger Stone, who is under suspicion in the Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh Hearing Set For Sept. 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/10/kavanaugh-confirmation-hearings-set-for-sept-4-773344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scheduling move tees up Republicans to meet their goal of getting President Donald Trump's pick seated on the high court by the time its term begins in early October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber experts urge pen and paper voting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/smartphones-or-pen-paper-cybersecurity-experts-split-tech-voting-n899591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the brightest minds in cybersecurity want the U.S. voting system to embrace technology. Others want to keep tech as far away as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/democrats-opposing-pelosi-n899536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;List of Democrats opposing Pelosi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers 'collapse' on sweltering VIRGIN flight -- which landed in wrong country...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-orlando-london-flight-forced-13059997?f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The VS1050 flight from Orlando, in the United States, was supposed to land at London Gatwick at 8.10am but was diverted to Shannon in Ireland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid reports of sexual extortion, other horrors, feds subpoena records, tour women's prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/special-reports/florida-prisons/article216371465.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lowell Correctional, Florida’s largest women’s prison, has been beset by allegations of physical, mental and sexual abuse. The reports have spawned a subpoena for extensive records and a tour by the U.S. Department of Justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW SEASON: Trump Trashes NFL Players For Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-trashes-nfl-players-for-anthem-protests-most-are-unable-to-define-what-they-are-protesting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: NBC Execs Panic Over Looming Sex Scandal Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/new-daily-beast-working-on-major-nbc-news-sexual-harassment-and-misconduct-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret DMV office serves California lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcra.com/article/secret-dmv-office-serves-lawmakers-capitol-staffers/22692865</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 2 KILLED, 307 WOUNDED IN CLASHES ALONG GAZA BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/One-killed-110-injured-in-clashes-along-Gaza-border-564600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A journalist was also said to have been wounded by Israeli fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rascal Flatts abruptly ends show over mystery 'security issue'...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/entertainment/music/2018/08/10/abrupt-end-rascal-flatts-concert-leaves-indiana-fans-puzzled/954328002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concert attendees say Ruoff Home Mortgage Music Center employees evacuated venue after Rascal Flatts encore failed to materialize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff: Teens tried to drown kitten in SNAPCHAT video...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldonline.com/news/local/crime/article216379895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in York County, South Carolina, charged teens, 13 and 15, with animal cruelty Thursday, August 9, 2018, after they posted a Snapchat video trying to drown a kitten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA counts down to launch of first spacecraft to 'touch Sun'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180810-nasa-counts-down-launch-first-spacecraft-touch-sun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combative Saudi foreign policy stirs international ire...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180810-combative-saudi-foreign-policy-stirs-international-ire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China warns US Navy in South Sea: 'Leave immediately'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1001656/China-US-latest-WW3-fears-South-China-Sea-US-Navy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Chinese military told a US Navy plane flying over the highly-disputed island in the South China Sea to “leave immediately”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA: Manafort trial resumes -- no explanation for delay...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/manafort-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's Day 9 of the Paul Manafort trial, and Prosecutors are expected to call their final witnesses. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY ON  BRINK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/10/turkish-lira-loss-deepens-as-pm-erdogan-calls-for-citizens-to-convert-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Turkish lira added to its steep losses on Friday, hitting a fresh record low, after President Donald Trump authorized the doubling of metals tariffs on Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants stumbling in social world they created...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/10/the-associated-press-tech-giants-still-stumbling-in-the-social-world-they-created.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media bans of conspiracy theorist Alex Jones have thrust Facebook, YouTube, Twitter and others into a role they never wanted — as gatekeepers of discourse on their platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone associate held in contempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/10/roger-stone-ex-aide-held-in-contempt--in-mueller-probe-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Miller lost a legal challenge earlier this month in U.S. District Court against Mueller's subpoena for him to appear before a grand jury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's new online cosmetics stars: Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/china-s-new-online-cosmetics-stars-men-10606040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Jiang Cheng first tried a bit of concealer during his first year of university in China it gave him self-confidence and he was instantly hooked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA package that fell from sky with note mentioning Trump sparks alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/south-brunswick-new-jersey-nasa-package-trump-note-sparks-alarm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suspicious package that fell from the sky over New Jersey caused some alarm because it contained a note that mentioned the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC serves WIKILEAKS with lawsuit via TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/dnc-serves-wikileaks-with-lawsuit-via-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DNC is suing the Trump campaign, the Russian government and WikiLeaks, alleging a massive conspiracy to tilt the 2016 election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 cops among 4 killed in eastern Canada shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/canada-shooting-fredericton-4-deaths-police-say-live-updates-2018-08-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Fredericton in New Brunswick, about 50 miles from the border with Maine, were warned to stay in their homes for hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Bill Murray 'Slammed Photographer Up Against a Door'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/08/09/bill-murray-involved-dispute-with-photographer-martha-vineyard-restaurant/95IiCWeAIT8M0d88Xsqi0L/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor and comedian Bill Murray was involved in a dispute with a photographer at a Martha’s Vineyard restaurant Wednesday night, according to a police report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Threatens to Shut Down GAB... </title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/microsoft-threatens-to-shut-down-gab-after-anti-semitic-posts-by-user/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where is Congress? Someone needs to let them know they have monopolies to bust and tyrants to regulate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Woman held in Dubai with daughter for drinking wine on flight...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/10/british-mum-jailed-daughter-4-drinking-glass-wine-flight-dubai-7821529/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mother-of-three may now have to spend up to a year in the Arab state waiting for the case to be sorted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Continue Classified Experiments on Humans...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/feds-continue-classified-experiments-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government continues to perform highly secretive experiments on human subjects, according to partial information about these continuing experiments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THEY HAVE DOLLAR, WE HAVE GOD'</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/istanbul-streets-defiant-turks-see-u-hand-behind-143514093--business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This crisis is created by America," she said. The lira has lost more than 35 percent against the dollar this year and hit a fresh low on Friday, its biggest one day fall since Turkey's 2001 financial crisis. Food, rents and fuel prices in Turkey have all surged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hopes to take House could stumble in Minnesota...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1bdd2dc0bff14f70911e500c3cd7a05a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WATERVILLE, Minn. (AP) — For all the talk of a blue wave sweeping Democrats back into the House majority this fall, their efforts could be thwarted in one of the nation's bluest s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear burned gets 'fish-skin'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wildlife-officials-vets-optimistic-tilapia-skin-heal-bear/story?id=57121689</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A black bear cub that was severely burned when a wildfire roared through her habitat in Northern California is receiving a fishy treatment for her wounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KIDS TAKE BREAK FROM TECH AT SUMMER CAMPS; AND LIKE IT!</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Lifestyle/wireStory/kids-summer-means-powering-camp-57133056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If teens are so attached to their phones and all things connected, why do so many of them wind up in no-device summer camps with smiles on their faces? Thirteen-year-old Daniela Blumenfeld of Scarsdale, New York, just finished her fifth summer at sleepaway camp with no devices beyond a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfire smoke travels 3,000 miles to NYC!</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/smoke-from-california-wildfires-reaches-nyc/3922350/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The smoke from the California wildfires has not only been impacting the West Coast. Incredibly enough, it has reached New York City -- 3,000 miles away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed-up locals setting scooters on fire, smearing with poop, burying at sea...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-bird-scooter-vandalism-20180809-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As cities from Santa Monica to Los Angeles to Beverly Hills struggle to control the rapid proliferation of electric pay-per-mile scooters, Westside vandals are waging a guerrilla war against the devices and destroying them in increasingly imaginative ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staggering death toll for firefighters...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-firefighters-deaths-20180810-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deadly toll for firefighters during California firestorms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady executed while ordering at fast food drive-thru...</title>
      <link>http://www.jacksonville.com/news/20180810/woman-shot-to-death-in-mcdonalds-drive-thru-in-jacksonville</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jacksonville.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman is dead following a shooting in the drive-thru of the McDonald's restaurant at 8590 Baymeadows Road, according to the Jacksonville Sheriff's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE:  'RIDDLED WITH LIES'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6047465/Omarosa-Trump-used-n-word-heard-slurring-Kellyannes-half-Filipino-husband.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House fired a missile at Omarosa Manigault-Newman on Friday following news that her tell-all book will accuse President Trump of making 'several' racial slurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem House candidate convicted of DUI unloads on cops: 'I hate this county'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailycitizen.news/news/local_news/i-hate-this-county-i-prayed-to-god-that-he/article_8c54d317-6930-55d9-b3e9-2e1458aa1bfa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailycitizen.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editor's note: Some of the language in this story may be offensive to some readers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-candidate charged with murder...</title>
      <link>http://www.augustachronicle.com/news/20180809/former-congressional-candidate-charged-with-murder-in-aiken</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.augustachronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Aiken County Sheriff's Office has made an arrest in connection to a murder at a residence on Old Powderhouse Road in Aiken.Kellie Lynn Collins, 30,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daredevils filmed riding atop speeding NYC subway cars...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/new-york/nyc-train-surfers-639508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of New York City daredevils--surely soon to be in the custody of the NYPD--filmed themselves riding atop a series of subway cars as trains barreled through Brooklyn and Queens. In videos post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-editing startups ignite the next 'Frankenfood' fight...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180810055953-l8hxy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAINS-TECH/GENE-EDITING (INSIGHT, PIX, GRAPHIC):INSIGHT-Gene-editing startups ignite the next 'Frankenfood' fight</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
