<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>1.4M acres burned so far...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/California-Newsom-press-briefing-wildfires-acreage-15510936.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom said in a Monday press briefing the state is "deploying every resource available to battle the historic wildfires" chewing up the landscape and swallowing homes across the state, while pumping out massive amounts of smoke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposed California ban on flavored tobacco sales sparks racism accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/proposed-california-ban-on-flavored-tobacco-sales-sparks-discussion-of-systemic-racism/ar-BB18ku2H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-RNC chair joins LINCOLN PROJECT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/24/politics/michael-steele-lincoln-project/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former chairman of the Republican National Committee Michael Steele is joining the Lincoln Project, a group of Republicans working to prevent President Donald Trump's re-election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia officials say some drinking bleach...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/georgia-public-health-officials-say-some-are-drinking-bleach-like-cleaners-to-fight-covid-19/URQAM7I6JZDWRCZYI3NMJCSFZI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Brian Kemp's office is warning people to stop drinking bleach to fight COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAD OF LIBERTY U RESIGNS</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/travisakers/status/1297994537000939520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/2020/08/24/wisconsin-police-shooting-black-man-jacob-blake-national-guard-way-kenosha-7-shots-in-the-back/3430507001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooting of a Black man in Kenosha and its aftermath has drawn criticism from state and national leaders. The National Guard was deployed Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASHES CUBA...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200824-laura-lashes-cuba-expected-to-become-hurricane-by-us-landfall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura lashes Cuba, expected to become hurricane by US landfall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Yo Jong could be NKorea's worst dictator yet...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/24/kim-yo-jong-could-be-north-koreas-worst-dictator-yet-experts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un's sister could be the Hermit Kingdom's most brutal leader if she succeeds him, experts told The Post on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Confirms 'Act of Sabotage' at Nuke Site...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-confirms-act-of-sabotage-at-nuclear-site/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran on Monday confirmed that a mysterious explosion last month at one of its nuclear facilities was an “act of sabotage,” but provided few other details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With tell-all on deck, Michael Cohen plots...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/08/michael-cohen-is-plotting-anti-trump-ads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After throwing his own manuscript into the Passover flames at Otisville to prevent leaks, the president’s ex-lawyer is dropping hints about his tell-all, partnering with a Democratic PAC during the RNC, and gearing up for a potential legal slugfest with Eric and Don Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFO opens first airport testing site in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/SFO-airport-COVID-19-rapid-testing-15501523.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first airport COVID-19 rapid testing site in the United States has opened in San...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Medical Mystery: Patients Come Off Ventilator But Linger In Coma...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2020/08/24/904347130/another-covid-19-medical-mystery-patients-come-off-ventilator-but-linger-in-a-co</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors are researching why some patients remain unconscious for days or weeks, even after sedating drugs are withdrawn. They also worry that these patients aren't being given time to recover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Edge in Party Affiliation Shrinks...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/317771/democratic-edge-party-affiliation-shrinks.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats maintain an edge in U.S. party identifiers and leaners, but the 11-point advantage they had in June has shrunk to six points in July and August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG investigating if President inflated assets in financial docs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/797fba199f9a3e7e08f6306184000c80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York’s Democratic attorney general asked a court Monday to enforce subpoenas into an investigation into whether President Donald Trump and his businesses inflated assets on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuation Ordered In TX City; Home To Largest Oil Refinery In US...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/08/24/evacuation-ordered-in-texas-city-as-marco-collapses-and-gulf-coast-braces-for-laura/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mayor of one South Texas city is calling for a city-wide evacuation, as Tropical Storm Warnings for Marco are cancelled and the Gulf Coast braces for the arrival of Laura as a potential Category 3 hurricane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo shattering precedent, sparking fury with speech...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/pompeo-shattering-precedent-sparking-fury-rnc-speech-72572476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Pompeo's planned speech to the Republican National Convention has sparked a fury of criticism for breaking decades of precedent for sitting secretaries of state avoiding overt partisan political activity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J-PK8t8vtSM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An investigation is underway after cellphone video shows police in Kenosha, Wisconsin shooting a Black man in the back. The 29-year-old victim, Jacob Blake, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/storminfo/13L_tracks_latest.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tropicaltidbits.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying robot nose swab to test for COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/8/24/21377011/robot-nasal-swab-machine-autonomous-covid-19-test-brain-navi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unsettling procedure even without a robot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Film Festival Wipes Out Best Actor/Actress, Goes Non-Gender. Trend for All Awards?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/08/24/berlin-film-festival-wipes-out-best-actor-actress-goes-non-gender-in-all-awards-will-this-be-a-trend-for-all-awards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best Actress, Best Actor? No more. At least at the Berlin Film Festival. They’re going non-gender and handing out one acting prize for lead and supporting this winter. I think it’s just…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens break into petting zoo, put lipstick on pony, terrorize animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/teens-broke-into-nj-petting-zoo-put-lipstick-on-animals-and-mistreated-them-farmer/2581753/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey farmer says some of the animals in his petting zoo were terrorized by a group of teens he says allegedly broke onto his property and abused them, including by putting lipstick on a miniature pony. Abma’s Farm in Wyckoff is a beloved Bergen County mainstay. Four generations live on the property and the farm’s market and petting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALL PREVIEW:  Melania Disparaging Comments About First Family Taped by Advisor; New book...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/former-melania-trump-adviser-claims-she-taped-flotus-belittling-trump-and-his-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former friend and adviser to Melania Trump claims that she secretly recorded the first lady making "disparaging remarks" about President Donald Trump and his adult children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandalism, looting...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/08/23/watch-gunshots-ring-out-as-armed-rioters-confront-police-in-wisconsin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed rioters shut down streets in Kenosha, Wisconsin on Sunday night as the city fell into chaos after a police-involved shooting earlier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin riots after police shoot black man in back...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0cbc14762c89304f9f052fd33a1f4445</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (AP) — Kenosha became the nation’s latest flashpoint city in a summer of racial unrest after police shot and wounded a Black man, apparently in the back, as he leaned into his SUV...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman pummelled father 'due to his flatulence'...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/florida-flatulence-battery-473291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 24--A Florida Woman was arrested yesterday for allegedly battering her father “due to his flatulence” inside their residence, police say. According to an arrest affidavit, Nicole Dozois, 40, sh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falwell says wife had affair with 'pool boy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/exclusive-falwell-says-fatal-attraction-threat-led-to-depression</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Falwell Jr., suspended as president of Virginia’s Christian-focused Liberty University after a string of embarrassing acts, today said that he has suffered depression caused by a former family friend who had an affair with his wife and has been threatening to expose it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KFC drops 'Finger Lickin' Good' slogan after 64 years; Not covid safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/money/12485489/kfc-finger-lickin-good-slogan-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KFC is pausing the use of its “Finger Lickin’ Good” slogan on all its new adverts after 64 years because of the coronavirus crisis. Instead, the fried chicken chain will blur out …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK users pretend to be dead Holocaust victims in sick new trend...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/1357455/1357455-tiktok-users-pretend-holocaust-victims-trauma-porn-trend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIKTOK users are pretending to be dead Holocaust victims in a disturbing new trend that has been dubbed “trauma porn” because it sensationalizes horrific events.  Footage on t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The WHOLE truth will come out'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8657391/Jerry-Falwell-Jr-says-wife-affair-pool-boy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Falwell Jr. claims his wife Becki had an affair in 2012 with then 21-year-old pool boy Giancarlo Granda who the couple befriended while staying in a Miami hotel and then brought on vacation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA CAT 2 HURRICANE AT LANDFALL?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-laura-shatters-record-sets-course-toward-us/799707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WEEK:  TX, LA...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-08-24-tropical-storm-laura-hurricane-forecast-texas-louisiana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura's Caribbean flood danger will morph into a major Gulf hurricane threat. Here's the latest forecast thinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area Wildfire Now Second Largest Blaze In State History...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/08/23/lnu-lightning-complex-fire-sunday-341000-acres-533-square-miles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive LNU Lightning Complex in the North Bay has burned more than 340,000 acres, as firefighters began a second week of battling what has become California's second largest wildfire on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Melania Disparaging Comments About Trump Family Taped by Advisor...</title>
      <link>https://yashar.substack.com/p/scoop-melania-trumps-comments-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;yashar.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope you’ll subscribe to my newsletter by clicking the button above or the button at the end of this post. Please follow me on Twitter and Instagram If you want to post this edition on social media, use the button above. Scoop: Former Melania Trump Friend and Advisor Taped Her Disparaging Trump and His Adult Children, Sources Say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZOOM Experiencing Widespread Outages...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/zoom-is-down-videoconferencing-platform-experiences-widespread-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outage is causing chaos as millions of children and teachers attempt to start the school year online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead' Woman Found to Be Breathing at Detroit Funeral Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/woman-pronounced-dead-later-found-to-be-still-breathing-at-detroit-funeral-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 20-year-old woman believed to have died was found breathing at a Detroit funeral home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans will soon grow new livers inside bodies?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8658283/Second-liver-grown-lymph-nodes-pigs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of Pittsburgh gave six pigs liver failure by diverting blood supply and removing a chunk of tissue and placed liver cells in the lymph nodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio Grande Valley riven by death and anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Coronavirus-has-left-the-Rio-Grande-Valley-riven-15510066.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MCALLEN, Texas - The grotto of St. Jude Thaddeus is covered in handwritten petitions for protection against the coronavirus, pinned funeral cards, hospital bracelets and photos of the sick and dying.  Graveyard workers lower caskets into the earth three or four times a day instead of once or twice a week. Masked mourners surround fresh mounds of dirt by the hour. Curanderas perform cleansing rituals for the grief-stricken. A parish priest cannot remember how many times he has rung the funeral bell. Helicopters swoop in, as if in a war, to spirit away the critically ill.  A friend watched her neighbor plead silently for prayer on live video days before she stopped breathing. A son waited with clasped hands every evening in the hospital parking lot with half a dozen other faithful, sending supplications heavenward.  Teachers. Janitors. Bankers. Politicians. Neighbors. Colleagues. Children.  Few here in Texas's lower Rio Grande Valley have been left untouched by the pandemic's lethal reach, as the virus has ripped through the border region, infecting tens of thousands of people and killing more than 1,500 just in the months after Texas thought it had escaped the virus's grip and started to reopen, according to Washington Post data.  The region of more than 1.2 million people in four counties accounts for approximately 15 percent of all of the state's virus-related fatalities. Though the governor has surged resources here, the pandemic has plunged the Valley into a state of perpetual grief.  "We just can't take another emotional step," said Ivan Melendez, Hidalgo County's health authority and a practicing doctor in McAllen. "There's not been one day in the last three months that someone hasn't asked me: 'Did you hear who died?' "  The Rio Grande Valley is a place that thrives...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: President faces pessimism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a464966595a326a6b2e4c6f9888f7d8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is promising to outline an optimistic vision for America at this week's Republican convention. But he’ll be speaking to a public deeply pessimistic about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German hospital: Poisoning signs found in Russian dissident...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/89051aea9fa1150cd04606ce50167204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Tests conducted on Russian dissident Alexei Navalny at a German hospital indicate that he was poisoned, but doctors said Monday they do not believe his life at immediate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. and future of Trumpism: He upended expectations four years ago. What now?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Donald-Trump-Jr-and-the-future-of-Trumpism-He-15509929.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The eldest son of the future president strode onto the stage at the 2016 Republican National Convention in a gray suit with his hair slicked back, awash in low expectations.  Donald Trump Jr.'s previous public appearances had been dutiful and less than dazzling - cameos alongside his father on "The Apprentice," speeches for business audiences, a failed math quiz on Howard Stern's radio show. Just a few months before his father entered the presidential race, Don Jr. was dabbling as a guest host of infomercials where he would interview executives marketing temporary office rentals and obscure construction techniques.  "What exactly is grip metal technology?" the real estate scion, stiff and unsmiling, asked one guest.  To prepare for his convention speech four years ago, Don Jr. practiced each day for a week. When he took the lectern, he started by praising his wonderful wife and mentioning their five children - and then identified himself as the son of "a great man."  The speech was notable for its polish. The candidate himself would fulminate in his own speech about violence in the streets, but Don Jr. eloquently heralded his father's common touch. His father "didn't hide out behind some desk in an executive suite. . . . We didn't learn from MBAs. We learned from people who had doctorates in common sense," Don Jr. told a rapt crowd. He didn't call Mexicans rapists. He didn't hurl insults. As he went on, the speech developed its own cadence; soon, the packed convention hall was calling out "Trump!" after each of his rhythmic sentences.  The political world was dazzled. "Poised and focused," wrote the New York Post's John Podhoretz, calling it a speech Trump Sr. would never have been able to pull off. "I think I watched the speech of a future politician there," said David Chalian, CNN's political director. "In fact, a much...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What would he do in second term?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/24/donald-trump-second-term-400541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top aides spent the last several weeks reviewing proposals attempting to answer that very question — and Trump will talk about them this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims Forced Into Filthy Warehouses in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/covid-victims-are-forced-into-filthy-warehouses-in-venezuela/ar-BB18jo6p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orwell's nightmare? Facial recognition for animals promises farmyard revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Orwell-s-nightmare-Facial-recognition-for-15509879.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YECHANG, China - There are many challenges to applying facial recognition technology to animals: Pigs don't have distinguishing features and cows often want to lick the cameras. But there is an advantage: Farmyard inhabitants tend not to complain about impingements on their civil liberties.  Having mastered facial recognition for humans to an alarmingly precise degree, even picking out wanted criminals from huge crowds, Chinese tech whizzes are turning their attention to furrier faces.  "We've been using it for sheep, pigs and cows," said Zhao Jinshi, who studied at Cornell University and founded Beijing Unitrace Tech, a company developing software for the agriculture industry.  "For pigs, it's more difficult because pigs all look the same, but dairy cows are a bit special because they are black and white and have different shapes," Zhao said as he checked on the technology installed in a pilot project here at a farm in Hebei province, outside Beijing.  China has led the world in developing facial recognition capabilities. There are almost 630 million facial recognition cameras in use in the country, for security purposes as well as for everyday conveniences like entering train stations and paying for goods in stores.  But authorities also use the technology for sinister means, such as monitoring political dissidents and ethnic minorities.  One Chinese AI company, Megvii, which has been blacklisted by the Department of Commerce for alleged involvement in the Chinese government's repression of Uighurs in Xinjiang, is applying its technology to a program to recognize dogs by their nose prints. Other tech companies around the world have had a go at identifying chimpanzees, dolphins, horses and lions, with varying degrees of success.  Chinese entrepreneurs see an opportunity to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary Guards say three US-linked infiltrators killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/iran-guards-say-three-us-linked-infiltrators-killed-01598270705 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French 'libertine' nudist resort sees spike...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200824122023-zfwnu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-NATURISTS:French 'libertine' nudist resort sees spike in COVID infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes campaign reboot as protesters clash on site...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200824114852-n1jx9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/CONVENTION (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Trump eyes campaign reboot with made-for-TV convention as protesters clash on site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE IN TEARS: TRUMP 'IS RACIST, EVIL'</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/george-conway-offers-tearful-plea-on-unfit-saying-trump-is-a-racist-he-is-evil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In exclusive clips from “#Unfit” filmed prior to his wife’s White House exit, George Conway—Lincoln Project co-founder, Kellyanne hubby—gets emotional about why he opposes Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran, Hamas and Islamic Jihad call for 'uprising' after UAE-Israel deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-hamas-and-islamic-jihad-call-for-uprising-after-uae-israel-deal-639735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PIJ rep said that the “Zionist regime... will remain an enemy" and that its destiny "is destruction and decay, and whoever has a relationship with it will be transferred to the dustbin of history."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economists see chance of a double-dip recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/24/economists-see-a-chance-of-a-double-dip-recession-survey-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a 1-in-4 chance the economy could fall into a double-dip recession, according to economists surveyed by NABE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: TV Industry Will Never Recover From Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2020-08-23/the-tv-industry-will-never-recover-from-the-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jim Bakker gets PPP loans during legal fight on fraud claims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c690094065ece9ba147feb4b18812d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the U.S. government extended pandemic hardship loans to thousands of religious institutions, Jim Bakker and Morningside USA, his ministry in Blue Eye, Missouri, were among the most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind Pence deference: Ambition...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Behind-Mike-Pence-s-deference-Ambition-15509715.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like many who served in Congress alongside the late John Lewis, then-Rep. Mike Pence made a pilgrimage to Selma, Ala., in 2010 to commemorate the 45th anniversary of "Bloody Sunday." He marched across the Edmund Pettus Bridge just a few feet from Lewis as they retraced the historic route, and posed for a photo at the foot of the span - the Indiana Republican in crisp gray and the Georgia Democrat in somber black, their shoulders touching.  But when Lewis died last month of pancreatic cancer at 80, Pence, now vice president, held off on issuing a public comment on the civil rights hero's passing. President Donald Trump was no fan of the late congressman and openly complained about Lewis's refusal to attend his inauguration. Only after the White House distributed a perfunctory proclamation on the death in Trump's name did Pence feel comfortable releasing a statement of his own, memorializing Lewis as not just an "icon" but also "a colleague and a friend."  That hesitation - deferring to Trump for cues, and then following his lead - was classic Pence. It exemplified the well-honed subservience of a man who once governed his home state of Indiana but who as vice president has transformed himself into a loyal student and servant of Trump - binding his political ambitions to a mercurial and capricious boss now at risk of losing in November.  On Wednesday night, Pence will formally accept his party's nomination for a second term as vice president in an address to the Republican National Convention from Fort McHenry in Baltimore, where he will praise Trump's leadership. The keynote serves as a bookend of sorts for one of the few high-ranking officials to survive Trump's first term. He is being repaid for his loyalty with a reward - remaining in the No. 2 slot - that in most other administrations would never have been in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAUGHTER CLAIMS 'PHYSICAL ABUSE'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1358184/claudia-conway-accuse-parents-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KELLYANE Conway’s daughter has accused her mom of ‘physical abuse’ and ‘putting on a show’ after the adviser sensationally quit her job “to spend time with famil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist Hotspot Bali to Remain Closed to Foreigners All Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/tourist-hotspot-bali-to-stay-closed-to-foreign-visitors-all-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourist Hotspot Bali to Stay Closed to Foreign Visitors All Year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falwell says wife had affair with 'pool boy'; Claims being blackmailed...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/933178/jerry-falwell-jr-says-wife-affair-florida-pool-boy-claims-being-blackmailed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suspended Liberty University leader Jerry Falwell Jr. confirmed to Washington Examiner columnist Paul Bedard late Sunday that his wife, Becki Falwell, had an affair with a young man they befriended and went into business with in Florida eight years ago. In a long statement, Falwell said he and his wife 'forgave each other' â€” he suggested he had also 'important smaller things' to atone for, quoting a Bible verse about visual adultery â€” and had decided to come forward because his wife's former lover had been extorting them for 'huge amounts of monies' to stay quiet. 'I'm just tired of it,' Falwell told Bedard. Falwell said the young man â€” Giancarlo Granda â€” had created a ''fatal attractionâ€™ type situation,' referring to a famous 1987 movie in which a jilted extramarital lover boiled a pet rabbit, among other acts of retaliatory intimidation. Granda, 21 at the time of the affair, told the Examiner in an email that 'any allegation of extortion' is false, 'defamatory, and belied by clear documentary evidence,' adding that the attempt by the Falwells 'to sandbag me' with this 'last-minute story' just 'reeks of desperation,' and 'the WHOLE truth will come out.' The salacious nature of the relationship between the Falwells and Granda emerged when Michael Cohen, the former fixer and lawyer for President Trump, told comedian Tom Arnold in a secretly taped conversation that he had destroyed riquÃ© 'personalâ€� photographs involving the 'pool boy' on behalf of Falwell weeks before Falwell unexpectedly endorsed Trump for president. Falwell said Sunday he 'was not involved' in his wife's 'inappropriate personal relationship' with Granda, and mentioned 'fantastic' and 'prurient, untrue aspects' of the relationship 'based on the individual's misrepresentations.' Liberty University, a conservative evangelical Christian college founded by Jerry Falwell Sr., confirmed Friday that Falwell has been placed on indefinite paid suspension while the university investigates 'various rumors and claims' about him and decides if he will be fired. He makes about $1 million a year as president of Liberty University, The News &amp; Advance reports. Falwell, 58, has been on leave since apologizing for posting (then deleting) a photo of himself with his arm around a woman, both their pants partially unzipped, at a 'Trailer Park Boys' costume party on a 164-foot, six-bedroom yacht owned by NASCAR mogul Rick Hendrick. Falwell's family has reportedly been taking family vacations on the yacht since Liberty University signed a multi-million-dollar sponsorship deal with Hendrick Motorsports. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro threatens to punch reporter in mouth...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-threatens-punch-reporter-221108150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro on Sunday threatened to punch a reporter repeatedly in the mouth after being asked about his wife&amp;#39;s links to an alleged corruption scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: 'No new taxes' for anyone making less than $400,000...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/biden-abcs-david-muir-raising-taxes-taxes-making/story?id=72554803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden and Harris' first joint interview airs Sunday at 8 p.m. ET on ABC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin protests after police shoot black man in back...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wisconsin-protests-us-police-shoot-094103371.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests erupted in the US city of Kenosha, Wisconsin, after police shot a black man in the back several times from close range as he got into a car on Sunday evening, according to cellphone video of the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Big Short 2.0': Hedge Funds Profited Off Pain of Malls...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/24/the-big-short-2-0-how-hedge-funds-profited-off-the-pain-of-malls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catie McKee was nervous. It was last October, and the 31-year-old hedge fund analyst, who had been scrutinizing the mortgages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Bannon's Wall Group Used Trump Ties and Social Media to Raise Millions...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/24/how-bannons-wall-group-used-trump-ties-and-social-media-to-raise-millions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the arrest of his former senior political adviser Stephen K. Bannon, President Trump has tried to distance himself from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KELLYANNE OUT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8eb785aff89898c18c2bb297235e4f43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Kellyanne Conway, one of President Donald Trump’s most influential and longest serving advisers, announced Sunday that she would be leaving the White House at the end of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ DENIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/doj-denies-brian-stelter-book-account-about-barr-pushing-murdoch-to-muzzle-andrew-napolitano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department said a CNN journalist's claim that Attorney General William Barr attempted to "muzzle" Fox News legal analyst Judge Andrew Napolitano is false.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
