<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>American flags, Dem political sign set afire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/american-flags-democratic-political-sign-set-afire-outside-homes-in-arlington/ar-AAQ4gUO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three American flags and one Democratic yard sign have been torched in Arlington in the last two weeks, but no houses were damaged and no one was hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore,</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/weather/bs-md-coastal-flooding-maryland-forecast-20211028-g3pmoudzxbagrf4g6zrk4d5nne-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports of flooding, storm damage and power outages began circulating rapidly Friday morning, as the winds strengthened on the Chesapeake Bay amidst a storm forecasters predicted to yield some of the worst flooding along Maryland’s coastline since Hurricane Isabel in 2003.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC brace...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/weather-news/2021/10/powerful-storm-system-brings-heavy-rain-flooding-to-dc-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful storm system is bringing heavy rainfall and flooding to parts of the D.C. region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  MORE REST FOR QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-queen-advised-doctors-rest-25332597</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors have advised the Queen to rest for at least the next two weeks following a bout of illness, meaning Her Majesty will not attend a Remembrance event on November 13, Buckingham Palace has announced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside controversial gunshot-detection firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-59072745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BBC News has been given access to ShotSpotter, the controversial US technology company that detects gunshots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick Equals NFL With Slavery In New NETFLIX Series...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/colin-kaepernick-review-netflix-nfl-colin-in-black-and-white-ava-duvernay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the very nature of its co-creators and the tale they have to tell, Colin Kaepernick and Ava DuVernay’s Colin in Black &amp; White was never going to be your standard coming-of-age drama. In that…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tidal Flooding Leaves Annapolis Underwater...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/10/29/live-tidal-flooding-inundates-downtown-annapolis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tidal flooding on Friday left streets in downtown Annapolis underwater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman struck victim in head with chicken inside WALMART...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/walmart-chicken-attack-745830</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 29--A Pennsylvania woman is facing a criminal charge after allegedly striking another woman in the back of the head with a “cold chicken” at a Walmart Supercenter, according to police and cou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley turns blood into human eggs?</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/10/28/1038172/conception-eggs-reproduction-vitro-gametogenesis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A well-connected startup company is trying to rewrite the rules of reproduction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/author-all/richard-johnson/0/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWYER UP...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/alec-baldwin-shooting-rust-david-halls-hannah-gutierrez-hire-lawyers-halyna-hutchins-1234864561/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A week after the fatal shooting of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins by Alec Baldwin on the New Mexico set of Rust, two crew members at the center of the police probe have hired a pair of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 MINS:  FUTURIST WARNS HUMANS WILL BE HACKED IF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE NOT REGULATED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/yuval-harari-sapiens-60-minutes-2021-10-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harari says global cooperation is needed to prevent human data from getting into the hands of a powerful few. 60 Minutes reports, Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS ABBA:  NOTHING SELLING...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/27/abba-sos-on-eve-of-marketing-launch-three-new-singles-in-a-row-have-failed-to-sell-or-get-radio-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Travelers Suffer Back Pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/10/half-space-travelers-experience-back-pain/186449/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The human spine is built to support our bodies under the gravitational forces experienced on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis says he should keep receiving Communion...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029143433-2n239</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-BIDEN/COMMUNION (URGENT):U.S. President Biden says Pope told him he should keep receiving Communion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KISS Roadies Blame Band for Covid Death of Guitar Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-features/kiss-francis-stueber-covid-tour-protocols-death-1249590/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The band, meanwhile, claims that some crew members concealed sickness and faked vaccine cards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Black athletes bring stories to screen, Kevin Durant delivers 'SWAGGER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/as-black-athletes-bring-their-stories-to-the-screen-kevin-durant-delivers-e2-80-98swagger-e2-80-99/ar-AAQ63qX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Durant and Colin Kaepernick are joining a growing movement of Black athletes telling their own stories with the help of Black filmmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy over Communion...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-visits-pope-francis-amid-political-controversy-over-communion/ar-AAQ57cE </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innoculated just as likely to spread delta within household...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/579068-vaccinated-just-as-likely-to-spread-delta-variant-as-unvaccinated-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who have received COVID-19 vaccinations are able to spread the delta variant within their household despite their vaccination status just as easily as unvaccinated individuals,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusually long meeting...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029121049-3xdpa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/POPE (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Biden has unusually long meeting with pope as abortion debate flares at home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween solar flare headed for Earth; Could disrupt power grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3957750/halloween-solar-flare-headed-earth-power-grid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SUN launched a massive solar flare yesterday that’s headed in Earth’s direction – the strongest storm seen in the current weather cycle. The volley of radiation may trigger the nort…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE MEETS POPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10144177/Joe-Jill-Biden-arrive-closed-door-meeting-Pope-Francis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden got a 75-minute meeting with Pope Francis on Friday, longer than his two predecessors in the Oval Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Employee Training Program Says, 'White People, You are Problem'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/t-employee-training-program-says-222048736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T Corporation is putting its employees through a racial reeducation program that teaches that “American racism is a uniquely white trait” and tells white people that they are “the problem,” according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT Just Sold for $532 Million -- But Didn't Really Sell at All...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/here-e2-80-99s-a-24532-million-nft-trade-that-wasn-e2-80-99t-what-it-appeared/ar-AAQ5nZY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white-haired, green-eyed pixelated character known as a CryptoPunk 9998 just sold for more than half a billion U.S. dollars -- or so it appeared -- the latest wild development in the booming non-fungible token space. But the Ethereum blockchain shows the money from the NFT trade ended up right back where it started, raising the question of why anyone bothered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation notches fresh 30-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/29/inflation-notches-a-fresh-30-year-high-as-measured-by-the-feds-favorite-gauge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annual inflation rose at its fastest pace in more than 30 years during September despite a decline in personal income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wages jump by most on record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-wages-salaries-increase-8ce98ea3bcc14c4810eb5a1111e1df49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Wages and salaries jumped in the three months ending in September by the most on records that date back 20 years as companies are forced to offer higher pay to fill a near-record number of available jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Fetty Wap busted on drug charges by FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3957561/rapper-fetty-wap-busted-by-fbi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAPPER Fetty Wap was reportedly busted by FBI agents on federal drug charges at New York City’s Citi Field stadium. Fetty Wap, whose real name is William Junior Maxwell II, was arrested by fe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG MERCILESSLY MOCKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10142433/Facebooks-parent-company-renamed-Meta-internet-reacts-merciless-memes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Mark Zuckerberg announced parent company Facebook Inc's rebrand to Meta on Thursday the new name was immediately the subject of many memes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 FEWER AMBULANCES</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/10/29/nyc-vaccine-mandate-deadline-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City officials are no doubt putting the final touches on contingency plans to deal with a possible shortage of first responders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma inmate dies vomiting and convulsing in first state execution since '15...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20211029-oklahoma-inmate-dies-vomiting-and-convulsing-in-first-state-execution-since-2015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Condemned Oklahoma prisoner John Grant convulsed and vomited before dying from a cocktail of drugs on Thursday as the state conducted its first execution in years despite questions about its lethal i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTO THE ETHER: Crypto Rises to Record High as Use of Ethereum Blockchain Surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/ether-rises-to-record-high-renewing-alt-season-expectations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ether Rises to Record High, Renewing Alt-Season Expectations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Hypersonic Gliders Scrambling Old Nuke War Equations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/china-s-hypersonic-gliders-are-scrambling-the-old-nuclear-war-equations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In This Nuclear Arms Race, China’s Hypersonic Gliders Are a Wake-up Call</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREHOUSES CLOSED</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/27/covid-vaccine-mandate-could-force-20-of-fdny-companies-to-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDNY is preparing to shutter as many as 20 percent of all NYC fire companies ahead of the impending deadline for all city workers to be vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden meets pope as abortion debate flares back home...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029100035-8e5v2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/POPE (PIX, TV):Biden meets pope as abortion debate flares back home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem cries to 'defund police' fade as crime surges...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029095834-c6dlz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/POLICING (PIX):Democratic cries to 'defund police' fade in U.S. mayoral races as crime surges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romantic encounters between zoo animals surge during quarantine quiet...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211028174548-h8oe2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CUBA-ZOO (TV, PIX):Romantic encounters between Cuban zoo animals surge during quarantine quiet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'America Is Back,' Joe Declared in June. World About to Test Him...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/29/america-is-back-biden-declared-in-june-the-world-is-about-to-test-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — When President Biden gathered with world leaders at an English seaside resort in June, it was a backslapping</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Producers of Baldwin Film Scrutinized After Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/28/producers-of-alec-baldwin-film-scrutinized-after-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Independent film productions that cost more than a few million dollars often carry two forms of insurance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For tribes, 'good fire' key to restoring nature and people...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-forests-california-native-americans-eb2f25b2a932f707d4526bffb6cecf3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEITCHPEC, Calif. (AP) — Elizabeth Azzuz stood in prayer on a Northern California mountainside, arms outstretched, grasping a handmade torch of dried wormwood branches, the fuel her Native American ancestors used for generations to burn underbrush in thick forest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Virginia, McAuliffe brings big names, Youngkin goes solo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/campaigns-michael-pence-virginia-election-2020-terry-mcauliffe-e5f5e08ce998ddd9456716e373bf5151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Democrat Terry McAuliffe has brought in the biggest names in Democratic politics to come to his aid in Virginia's hotly contested gubernatorial race: Obama, Harris, Abrams, Biden (both Joe and Jill).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in Arab world embrace new lingerie comfort zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/I-can-t-take-this-Victoria-s-Secret-push-up-16572296.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a recent evening, Dubai boutique owner Coralie Francois stuffed a large suitcase with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump real-estate empire pays the price for poisonous politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trumps-real-estate-empire-pays-price-poisonous-politics-2021-10-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former U.S. president Donald Trump’s slashing rhetorical style and divisive politics allowed him to essentially take over the Republican Party. His supporters are so devoted that most believe his false claim that he lost the 2020 election because of voter fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First responder unions resist for front line workers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/labor/577812-first-responder-unions-resist-covid-19-mandates-for-front-line-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of police officers, paramedics and health care professionals who are at the front line of the COVID-19 pandemic are at risk of losing their jobs for not complying with newly implemented mandates to be vacc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For First Time in Public, Detainee Describes Torture at CIA Black Sites...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/28/for-first-time-in-public-a-detainee-describes-torture-at-c-i-a-black-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUANTÁNAMO BAY NAVAL BASE, Cuba — A suburban Baltimore high school graduate turned Al Qaeda courier, speaking to a military</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Kicked Out Of Progressive Meeting?</title>
      <link>https://www.theuprising.info/p/sources-nancy-pelosi-kicked-out-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theuprising.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“She got kicked out and said she was leaving anyway.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH TO RIVAL APPLE?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3955591/leaked-image-appears-to-show-facebook-meta-watch-apple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN image leaked online appears to show a smartwatch that Facebook Inc., now known as Meta Platforms Inc., is developing – potentially to rival the Apple Watch. Discovered inside the Facebook V…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker draws bipartisan backlash for 'false flag' claim about Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Tucker-Carlson-draws-bipartisan-backlash-for-16572846.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Tucker Carlson, the most popular voice in conservative media, drew...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol has 'shadow unit' that protects agents when they kill, groups say...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2021/10/28/border-patrol-has-a-shadow-police-unit-that-protects-agents-when-they-kill-groups-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These "shadow police units" have been operating since at least 1987 and without any actual authority under federal law, according to a letter sent to Congress calling for an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA posts weakest growth of pandemic recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/business/career-workplace/2021/10/28/US-economy-weakest-growth-pandemic-recovery-supply-chain-problems-covid/stories/202110280121</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US economy slowed to a 2% rate last quarter in face of COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5% adults quit job due to opposition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-unvaccinated-vaccine-coronavirus-mandate-job-quit-economy-20211028-fuh65t6bnzbxdetzg443izsyo4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more workplaces initiate a vaccine mandate policy for employees, nearly five percent of unvaccinated workers have decided to quit their jobs in protest, a new survey by the Kaiser Family Foundation said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LADY GAGA PLOTS MURDER IN LATEST 'HOUSE OF GUCCI' TRAILER...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/film/watch-lady-gaga-plot-murder-in-house-of-gucci-trailer-3082601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film hits cinemas next month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban exile told sons he trained Oswald, JFK's accused assassin, at secret CIA camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuban-exile-told-sons-he-trained-oswald-jfk-s-accused-assassin-at-a-secret-cia-camp/ar-AAQ3OIg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 40 years after his death following a bar brawl in Key Biscayne, Ricardo Morales, known as “Monkey” — contract CIA worker, anti-Castro militant, counter-intelligence chief for Venezuela, FBI informant and drug dealer — returned to the spotlight Thursday morning when one of his sons made a startling claim on Spanish-language radio: Morales, a sniper instructor in the early 1960s in secret ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom banned as elementary school volunteer after anonymous letter reveals ONLYFANS page...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mom-banned-as-orange-elementary-school-volunteer-after-anonymous-letter-reveals-onlyfans-page/ar-AAQ4j33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a volunteer at Sand Lake Elementary where her two children attend school, Victoria Triece has spent hours helping organize class parties and assist in lab assignments in her older son’s classroom, something she said she wanted to do ever since she became a mom. “I always wanted to be involved in that aspect of life,” Triece said. “My mother did it for me and having her there was the best ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City officials in Texas went to cut man's overgrown lawn. He was killed in standoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/city-officials-in-texas-went-to-cut-a-man-e2-80-99s-overgrown-lawn-he-was-later-killed-in-a-standoff-with-police/ar-AAQ5HoK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man fired at police multiple times before an officer fatally shot him, the Austin police chief said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force first to face troop rejection of shot order as thousands avoid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/air-force-is-first-to-face-troops-e2-80-99-rejection-of-vaccine-mandate-as-thousands-avoid-shots/ar-AAQ4zI8 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G20 becomes showpiece for dysfunctional global order...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-G-20-becomes-the-showpiece-for-a-16573910.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This weekend, the Group of 20 major economies will convene for a top-level meeting in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refusal sidelines 2 dozen Chicago Fire Dept personnel...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-vaccine-mandate-police-fop-lawsuit-chicago-20211028-lgt7vi5pznc6hjxxymbtkmtj3m-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The firefighters union head said response times could be affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR FUTURE...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-changes-name-meta-signaling-184739627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's new corporate name, Meta, is a nod to the 'metaverse,' a concept from science fiction that combines virtual, augmented and mixed reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden announces 'historic' deal -- but still must win votes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-congress-democrats-budget-framework-60a1bc276d0ab8eb3e0347fc54ee8c2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden announced Thursday that he and Democrats in Congress have reached a “historic" framework for his sweeping domestic policy package. But he still needs to lock down votes from key colleagues for what's now a dramatically scaled-back bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX CRIME</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/andrew-cuomo-charged-with-forcible-touching-after-criminal-probe/3359554/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NY Gov. Andrew Cuomo will face criminal charges of forcible touching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Flight attendant suffers broken bones in 'one of worst displays of unruly behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/flight-attendant-suffers-broken-bones-in-one-of-the-worst-displays-of-unruly-behavior-in-the-skies/ar-AAQ4gfC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident prompted the pilots to divert the flight to Denver, where a passenger was detained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON, APPLE warn supply-chain woes, labor shortage could hamper holiday season...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/amazon-apple-warn-supply-chain-woes-labor-shortage-could-hamper-holiday-season/ar-AAQ4MK9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giants’ woes suggest headwinds for smaller companies without their financial might.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: PANTHERS coach resigns in wake of BLACKHAWKS sex abuse scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nhl/story/_/id/32498538/joel-quenneville-resigns-florida-panthers-coach-wake-chicago-blackhawks-sexual-abuse-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Quenneville has resigned as Panthers coach after an investigation into the Blackhawks' sexual abuse case revealed he had knowledge of the allegations when he was Chicago's coach in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burr probed for insider trading...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/579005-richard-burr-under-insider-trading-investigation-by-sec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is investigating whether Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO TO BE ARRESTED</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/28/andrew-cuomo-to-be-charged-over-alleged-groping-of-former-aide-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgraced ex-Gov. Andrew Cuomo was charged Thursday with groping a former aide in Albany’s Executive Mansion — a crime that could send him to jail for a year if he’s convicted.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stricken Colombian woman may choose to die, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211028-stricken-colombian-woman-may-choose-to-die-court-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Colombian judge Thursday ruled that a severely ill woman who had her euthanasia cancelled at the last minute, may reschedule a procedure to die "with dignity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree Shortage Causing Prices To Soar...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/10/28/christmas-tree-turkey-shortage-unlikely-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not even Halloween and already there's a warning about turkey and Christmas tree shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba laws gran greater rights as criticism of protesters' arrests heats up...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211028211701-d3mbj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUBA-PROTESTS/JUDICIAL REFORM (TV, PIX):Cuba approves laws granting greater rights as criticism of protesters' arrests heats up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidding war over two-year-old minivan? Used car market 'bananas'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/bidding-war-over-a-two-year-old-minivan-used-car-market-goes-bananas-over-lack-of-supply/ar-AAQ3izR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unraveling of the used car market is the most tangible result of a problem that has plagued the global economy for the last year: a dire shortage of computer chips that has hobbled auto manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP SLOWS TO 2%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/28/us-gross-domestic-product-increases-at-2point0percent-annualized-pace-in-q3-vs-2point8percent-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy grew at a 2% rate in the third quarter, its slowest gain of the pandemic-era recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE misses expectations for first time since '16...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/28/apple-aapl-q4-2021-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple reported earnings after the bell. Here are the results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEAKEST OF COVID RECOVERY...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-posts-weakest-growth-of-pandemic-recovery-on-supply-woes-1.1673343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. economic growth slowed more than expected in the third quarter to the softest pace of the pandemic recovery period as snarled supply chains and a surge in COVID-19 cases throttled spending and investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Prices Set To Soar As Oil And Gas Crunch Continues...</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Energy-General/Global-Food-Prices-Set-To-Soar-As-The-Oil-And-Gas-Crunch-Continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dramatic rally in oil and gas prices is weighing on global food supply chains, with transport and farming costs set to rise even higher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Criminal summons 'erroneously issued' against Cuomo...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/state/article/Criminal-summons-erroneously-issued-against-16572344.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A criminal summons charging Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo with forcible touching was erroneously...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulances could be scarce...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/drastic-nyc-first-responder-shortages-feared-as-vaccine-mandate-deadline-hits-friday/3358544/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no pool of substitutes this time around. And the FDNY expects 20% fewer ambulances on the road and 20% of fire companies closed come Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Weirdness of LaPierre, NRA's Reluctant Leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/10/the-weirdness-of-wayne-lapierre-the-nras-reluctant-leader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the National Rifle Association can’t shoot, can’t schmooze, and has the “backbone of a chocolate eclair,” says a former board member—yet commands one of the most influential right-wing organizations in politics. In his new book, ‘Misfire,’ Tim Mak outlines LaPierre’s fall upward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK GOES META</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-mark-zuckerberg-facebook-5ad543ab7780caae435935f0aca9fac6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg said his company is rebranding itself as Meta in an effort to encompass its virtual-reality vision for the future — what Zuckerberg calls the “metaverse.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother-in-Law Called Stock Broker 1 Minute After Call With Senator...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/burrs-brother-in-law-called-stock-broker-one-minute-after-getting-off-phone-with-senator</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the SEC, Sen. Richard Burr of North Carolina, then chairman of the Senate Intelligence Committee, had material nonpublic information about coronavirus impact. He and his brother-in-law dumped stock before the market dropped in March 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange lawyer argues WIKILEAKS founder still suicide risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20211028-assange-lawyer-argues-wikileaks-founder-still-suicide-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US general warns China's military progress 'stunning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/28/politics/hyten-stunning-china-military-progress/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of China's test of a hypersonic missile, the second most senior US general said Thursday that the pace at which China's military is developing capabilities is "stunning" while US development suffers from "brutal" bureaucracy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
