<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayoral candidate wants to cut $1 billion from police. Pays for private security on her block...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ny-oped-mayas-choices-20201219-xixzzew55rd67div7eugnjwadq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Maya Wiley, the civil rights attorney and former de Blasio counsel who’s running for mayor, put out her first big position paper earlier this month, a gun violence prevention plan, what stood out was what wasn’t there: any productive role for the NYPD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alzheimer's Drug Poses Dilemma for FDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/alzheimer-s-drug-poses-a-dilemma-for-the-fda/ar-AAKK2Va</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration is on the verge of announcing one of its most contentious decisions in years: the fate of an Alzheimer’s drug that could be the first treatment approved after nearly two decades of failed efforts to find ways to curb the debilitating disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600+ quakes shake California-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/05/us/earthquakes-california-mexico-border/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 600 small earthquakes have been recorded this weekend in a rural area near the Salton Sea in Southern California, with the largest having a magnitude of 5.3, a US Geological Survey geophysicist told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman reveals dark hobby of seducing infamous serial killers by mail...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/05/couple-seduced-serial-killers-ramirez-dahmer-gacy-by-mail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the shocking letters a couple traded with serial murderers including John Wayne Gacy, Jeffrey Dahmer and Richard “Night Stalker” Ramirez.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes asked to review men-only draft law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-supreme-court-courts-government-and-politics-847452b349a4a00c6a6ff67d5c58f3c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court is being asked to decide whether it's sex discrimination for the government to require only men to register for the draft when they turn 18. The question of whether it's unconstitutional to require men but not women to register could be viewed as one with little practical impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top scientist being hunted by far-right sniper who has gone AWOL from army...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-top-covid-19-scientist-is-being-hunted-by-a-far-right-sniper-who-has-gone-awol-from-the-army/ar-AAKKUDJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientist Marc Van Ranst is in hiding with his family in a safe house with 24-hour security after a far-right sniper staked out his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WORST ELECTION DECEPTION'</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/netanyahu-right-wing-mouths-wont-be-silenced-670245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some hospitals mark first time being Covid-free...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/06/us/us-covid-hospitals-milestones-concerns/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Raul Magadia and his team all gathered in the basement of their Anniston, Alabama, hospital last month for a big announcement he was preparing to make through the intercom system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador looks to become world's first country to adopt crypto as legal tender...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/05/el-salvador-becomes-the-first-country-to-adopt-bitcoin-as-legal-tender-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Salvador President Nayib Bukele plans to introduce legislation that will make it the world's first sovereign nation to adopt bitcoin as legal tender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ says it'll no longer seize reporters' records...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-business-government-and-politics-67ac2f4f96b2dfd7f47446662e59ec6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department said Saturday that it no longer will secretly obtain reporters' records during leak investigations , a policy shift that abandons a practice decried by news organizations and press freedom groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Maintains Ban On Pride Flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/05/1003642736/pentagon-maintains-ban-on-pride-flag-and-other-flags-at-installations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DOD restricted what flags could and couldn't be flown on military installations last July. The Pentagon considered making a special case for Pride Month, but decided against the exception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli security chief warns of Jan. 6-type ahead of Bibi departure...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israeli-security-warns-january-6-violence-8142e896-7d01-4b72-81de-c68b07722bdc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Shin Bet director raised concerns about “serious radicalization in incitement and discourse on social media.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL JAZEERA: Reporter forcefully detained...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-d5902739395b065a2023b6214664d0e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli police arrested a Palestinian protest leader in the contested Sheikh Jarrah neighborhood of Jerusalem on Sunday, a day after forcefully detaining a prominent Al Jazeera journalist covering the campaign by Jewish settlers to evict dozens of Palestinian families from the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back on stage, Trump airs conspiracies and flirts with '24 run...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210606-back-on-stage-trump-airs-conspiracies-and-flirts-with-2024-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back on stage, Trump airs conspiracies and flirts with 2024 run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm ejected from PGA tournament with 6 shot lead because he tested positive for Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/sportsnews/article-9656133/Heartbroken-Jon-Rahm-forced-WITHDRAW-Memorial-Tournament-testing-positive-Covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Spaniard had hit an incredible 64 to put himself in pole position to take home the £1.2million prize money but his test result means he now has to pull out of the competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada law bans racially discriminatory school mascots, 'sundown sirens'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/05/us/nevada-law-racially-discriminatory-school-mascots-ban-sundown-siren/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Nevada is banning "racially discriminatory" school mascots after legislation was signed into law on Friday, as well as banning town sirens historically used to discriminate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fire in Phoenix spurs 'largest response' in Fire Dept history...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/phoenix-breaking/2021/06/05/firefighters-battle-fifth-alarm-fire-west-phoenix-recycling-yards/7565565002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire started near 35th Avenue and Lincoln Street, the Phoenix Fire Department said. 35th Avenue from Buckeye Road to Van Buren Street were closed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm told he has Covid on live TV - while leading PGA event...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jun/06/not-again-jon-rahm-told-he-has-covid-on-live-tv-while-leading-us-pga-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Spaniard was forced to withdraw with a six-shot lead and close to joining Tiger Woods as the only repeat winners of the Memorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS sending out 4th stimulus check by mistake?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3024520/irs-sent-extra-stimulus-by-mistake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILLIONS of Americans have received their third stimulus checks, but some fourth relief payments have been sent out by mistake. The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) mistakenly sent out some additiona…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico votes with AMLO's 'transformation' at stake...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210606-mexico-votes-with-amlo-s-transformation-at-stake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico votes with AMLO's 'transformation' at stake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends Naomi Wolf after anti-vax tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-57374241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American author tweeted a wide-range of unfounded theories about vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOCTORS FEAR HUGE STD SPIKE...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/neoscope/doctors-fear-huge-spike-in-stis-after-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We might be headed towards a "summer of sex."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's running for mayor of Mexican city. He's also wanted by DEA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/he-e2-80-99s-running-for-mayor-of-his-mexican-city-he-e2-80-99s-also-wanted-by-the-dea/ar-AAKIiF1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador won the presidency on promises to fight corruption. But as his party has grown, so have its own scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ANONYMOUS' threatens Musk for manipulating Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9655941/Hacking-group-Anonymous-issues-warning-Elon-Musk-claiming-power-influence-Bitcoin-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'hacktivist' group Anonymous have recorded a message aimed at Elon Musk. The group express their frustration with the Tesla CEO over his 'cavalier attitude' to cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  School principal made employee take raunchy pics...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/05/school-principal-made-employee-take-racy-pictures-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gisselle Vasquez, a 35-year-old single mom, was hired as a Spanish-speaking secretary for Principal Evelina Medina at the Robert C. Dodson School.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Once Diminished and Dominating, Trump Prepares for His Next Act...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/05/at-once-diminished-and-dominating-trump-prepares-for-his-next-act/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Donald J. Trump, the former president of the United States, commutes to New York City from his New</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sugar worker, 86, fatally shoots boss after firing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fl-state-wire-police-shootings-business-7f6e7290652b8d569aba8f6d3538f2c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELLE GLADE, Fla. (AP) — An 86-year-old sugar mill worker with 31 years on the job fatally shot his boss after he was refused another year at the mill, authorities said Saturday. The Palm Beach Sheriff's Office said in a news release that Felix Cabrera was jailed without bail on a first-degree murder charge following the Friday morning shooting at the Sugar Cane Growers Cooperative in Belle Glade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's running for mayor of Mexican city. He's also wanted by DEA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/he-e2-80-99s-running-for-mayor-of-his-mexican-city-he-e2-80-99s-also-wanted-by-the-dea/ar-AAKIiF1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans re-emerge after isolation: 'Like end of Prohibition'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/americans-re-emerge-after-pandemic-isolation-e2-80-98like-the-end-of-prohibition-e2-80-99/ar-AAKJuHw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memorial Day kicked off a return to normalcy across the nation as many of the remaining coronavirus restrictions were lifted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK PUMPS UP ADULT-THEMED CRYPTO PRICE AFTER TWEETING EXPLICIT EMOJI...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/elon-musk-cumrocket-crypto-price-b1860208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CumRocket cryptocurrency rose from $0.06 to $0.28 on Saturday after tech billionaire’s tweet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mysterious Brain Syndrome Grips Canada...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mysterious-brain-syndrome-grips-canada-141709582.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTREAL — Forty-eight people from the same small Canadian province struck with a baffling mix of symptoms including insomnia, impaired motor function and hallucinations such as nightmarish visions of the dead. A quixotic neurologist working 12-hour days to decipher the clues. Swirling conspiracy theories blaming the illness on cellphone towers, fracking or even COVID-19 vaccines. Sign up for The Morning newsletter from the New York Times These are just some plotlines of a mystery that has stump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meadows Pressed DOJ to Investigate Election Fraud Claims...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/05/meadows-pressed-justice-dept-to-investigate-election-fraud-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In Donald J. Trump’s final weeks in office, Mark Meadows, his chief of staff, repeatedly pushed the Justice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinkholes, Collapsing Canal Walls, Rickety Bridges: Amsterdam Crumbling...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/05/sinkholes-collapsing-canal-walls-rickety-bridges-amsterdam-is-crumbling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a rainy evening in April when Marlies Pinksterboer, an Amsterdam-based jewelry designer, was startled by a loud, rumbling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants turn to on-demand hiring apps during labor squeeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/05/restaurants-turn-to-on-demand-hiring-apps-during-the-labor-squeeze.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As restaurants struggle to find workers, some managers are turning to on-demand hiring apps to cover temporary staffing needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware attacks closing schools, delaying chemotherapy, derailing everyday life...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ransomware-attacks-are-closing-schools-delaying-chemotherapy-and-derailing-everyday-life/ar-AAKJbek</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of warnings, the impact of ransomware finally hits home for regular people.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
