<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dems' Latest Political Misstep on Immigration:  Cut the Number of Beds!</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/15/opinion/democrats-immigrants-ice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cutting the number of beds in ICE facilities will just make things worse for immigrant detainees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT LIKELY TO DIE IN PRISON... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mueller-investigation-paul-manafort-sentence-7e78d54d-ed73-43a2-a671-d697f78b5d39.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It would essentially be a life sentence for the 69-year-old former Trump campaign manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland summons Israeli ambassador to clarify Netanyahu comments on Poles in Holocaust...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190215154840-mltfi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLAND/ (PIX):Poland summons Israeli ambassador to clarify Netanyahu comments on Poles in Holocaust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Short exercise bursts better than lengthy gym session for shedding pounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/02/14/short-bursts-intensive-exercise-better-lengthy-gym-sessions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bursts of intense exercise for just 23 minutes are better for weight loss than spending twice as long in the gym, research suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website instantly generates fake human faces using artificial intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/website-generate-fake-faces-ai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller says has comms of Roger with WIKILEAKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/15/politics/roger-stone-wikileaks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors said for the first time that they have evidence of Roger Stone communicating with WikiLeaks, according to a new court filing from special counsel prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International 'fake news' commission demands Zuck, Bezos, Schmidt testify...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/international-fake-news-investigation-to-demand-testimony-mark-zuckerberg-sheryl-sandberg-jeff-bezos-tim-cook-sundar-pichai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "International Grand Committee" wants to hear from Mark Zuckerberg, Sheryl Sandberg, Jeff Bezos, Tim Cook, Sundar Pichai, and other industry giants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPROAR FROM ALL SIDES...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/c5398086611a42149817c8d74ae2bdd3/trump-declaration-faces-uncertain-fate-coming-court-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Let the lawsuits begin.President Donald Trump declared a national emergency along the southern border Friday and predicted his administration would end up defending it all the way to the Supreme Court.That might have been the only thing Trump said Friday that produced near-universal agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Said attackers were white but two suspects are black...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/3fa6965cdc104028a4c8879ca49689a6/chicago-police-fox-dispute-reports-about-smollett-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The investigation into black actor Jussie Smollett's account of being beaten in a racist, anti-gay attack took a sharp turn Friday when police announced the arrest of two black men they believe assaulted the "Empire" cast member.At least one of the men worked on the TV show, police said.Police spokesman Anthony Guglielmi said authorities had probable cause to believe the suspects committed assault and battery against Smollett. But they had not been charged as of Friday afternoon.Guglielmi would not comment on a possible motive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacks, Nudes, Breaches: Rough Times for Romance Apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ok-cupid-dating-apps-hacks-breaches-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trouble at OkCupid, Coffee Meets Bagel, and Jack'd have made February a bad stretch for romantics online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Faces: These People DO NOT EXIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/tldr/2019/2/15/18226005/ai-generated-fake-people-portraits-thispersondoesnotexist-stylegan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hit refresh to lock eyes with another imaginary stranger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slo-mo orgies, battles royale: Seal colony dominates CA beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/abcarian/la-me-abcarian-seals-20190215-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The elephant seal colony at Piedras Blancas Beach, just north of San Simeon and Hearst Castle on California's Central Coast, is a spectacular show of nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academy Reverses, Will Air OSCARS Categories Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/academy-reverses-decision-will-air-all-oscars-categories-live-1187338</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cinematography, film editing, live-action shorts and makeup and hairstyling categories will be seen during the telecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How space station feed was cut after 21 anomalies appeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1087688/nasa-news-iss-feed-cut-anomalies-discovery-mission-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA cut the International Space Station live feed during their Discovery mission in what has been dubbed “the most important UFO footage ever” by a conspiracy theorist speaking in a documentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year in orbit puts astronaut disease defenses on alert...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8dbeac4e9b8d48c197e73f6c929e6b38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nearly a year in space put astronaut Scott Kelly's immune system on high alert and changed the activity of some of his genes compared to his Earth-bound identical twin, researchers said Friday. Scientists don't know if the changes were good or bad but results from a unique NASA twins study are raising new questions for doctors as the space agency aims to send people to Mars. Tests of the genetic doubles gave scientists a never-before opportunity to track details of human biology, such as how an astronaut's genes turn on and off in space differently than at home. One puzzling change announced Friday at a science conference: Kelly's immune system was hyperactivated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creepy tech conjures portraits out of thin air...</title>
      <link>https://thenextweb.com/artificial-intelligence/2019/02/13/thispersondoesnotexist-com-is-face-generating-ai-at-its-creepiest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenextweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nvidia's incredible people-creating AI is now available online. Now you can create startling images of people who do not exist, to your heart's content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Biggest, Most Expensive Superyacht Ever Designed...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com.au/lifestyle/travel/take-a-tour-of-the-biggest-most-expensive-superyacht-ever-designed/image-gallery/b013fc1c423a031c02607d299e1c1ab6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For now simply named 'Project Valkyrie.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake adds to jewel collection with $400,000 custom iPhone case...</title>
      <link>https://hypebeast.com/2019/2/drake-jason-of-beverly-hills-custom-iphone-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hypebeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When your case is 500x more than your phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Prosecutor, Kamala Packed Prisons With Pot Peddlers...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/kamala-harris-packed-california-prisons-for-peddling-pot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris admitted in an interview this week to using marijuana, an act that landed thousands in prison while she was California's Attorney General.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick settles collusion case against NFL...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/26004715/colin-kaepernick-eric-reid-settle-grievance-case-nfl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL, Colin Kaepernick and Eric Reid issued a joint statement Friday saying they have resolved the collusion grievances filed by the players against the league.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promised to 'Build That Wall,' Then Ran Out of Time and Options...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-promised-to-build-that-wall-then-ran-out-of-time-and-options-11550262854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s declaration of a national emergency to fund a southern border barrier comes after divisions and competing priorities in the White House allowed the project to languish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Authorities Relocate Hundreds of Migrants From Border City...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mexican-authorities-relocate-hundreds-of-migrants-from-border-city-11550262962</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Central American migrants encamped in Mexico’s border city of Piedras Negras, across from Eagle Pass, Texas, are being relocated to other cities after a group of migrants rioted earlier this week and attempted to leave an abandoned factory where they were being held.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE reaped millions of tax breaks as it secretly expanded real estate footprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/google-reaped-millions-of-tax-breaks-as-it-secretly-expanded-its-real-estate-footprint-across-the-us/2019/02/15/7912e10e-3136-11e9-813a-0ab2f17e305b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidentiality agreements and shell companies make it nearly impossible for some communities to know, let alone protest or debate, who is using their land, resources and tax dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: Trump 'total capitulation on immigration'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/why-trump-doesnt-like-ann-coulter-anymore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump cares what Ann Coulter thinks, and he proved it Friday by pretending he doesn’t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Said attackers were white but two suspects are black...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/jussie-smollett-said-attackers-were-white-but-the-two-suspects-are-black</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Chicago have arrested two Nigerian brothers in connection with an alleged racist and homophobic attack on black actor Jussie Smollett last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'basic income' become the California norm? Town starts $500 no-strings payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article226280230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSUS BATTLE MOVES TO SUPREME COURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6710371/Supreme-Court-decide-2020-Census-ask-people-theyre-U-S-citizens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The justices will hear an appeal in late April and decide whether to overturn a lower federal court ruling that barred the Trump administration from asking about citizenship on Census forms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow jumps 400 points; Stock Market's 8th Straight Weekly Gain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/15/stocks-trump-speech-us-china-trade-and-earnings-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks surged on Friday amid increasing hopes for a U.S.-China trade deal as equities posted another solid weekly gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Woman Throws Profanity-Laced Tirade On JETBLUE Flight After Being Seated Next To Child...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/02/15/woman-removed-jetblue-flight-profanity-laced-outbursts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman's trip to Las Vegas on Valentine's Day was cut short after she reportedly got unruly on a plane and had to be taken off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Traveling 128 MPH Nearly Splits SUV In Half; Blows Through Red Light In Miami Beach...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/02/15/cbs4-exclusive-speeding-tesla-near-rips-suv-half/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tesla that police say was going nearly 130 miles per hour plowed into a black Infiniti SUV on the MacArthur Causeway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Cop Shot In Ambush Suing FACEBOOKGOOGLETWITTER Alleging Companies Radicalized Gunman...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/02/14/dart-officer-sues-social-media-giants-downtown-police-ambush/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DART officer Jesus Retana was shot in the arm by a short fired from the second floor of El Cento College in July 2016. He blames social media companies for playing a role in the violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inaugural receives NJ civil subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-inaugural-receives-civil-subpoena-jersey-state-attorney/story?id=61106438</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's inaugural committee has now received a second subpoena as questions grow about the fundraising and expenditures around the inaugural festivities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly votes to require businesses to accept cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/02/15/philadelphia-law-would-require-retailers-accept-cash/2879664002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia's city council voted to require most local businesses to accept cash as payment, pushing back on a growing trend that asks for cards only</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Men's Porn Habits Fuel Women's Eating Disorders...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-mens-porn-habits-linked-womens-risk-eating-disorders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women may be more likely to suffer from an eating disorder if their boyfriend or husband watches porn often, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California to sue...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article226333740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media companies to become sports-gambling companies?</title>
      <link>https://www.recode.net/2019/2/15/18226227/sports-gambling-media-att-randall-stephenson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.recode.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sooner than you think. But AT&amp;T, which owns HBO, TNT, and CNN, says they won’t be taking your bets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Roger Stone gagged...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/15/judge-hits-roger-stone-with-gag-order-1172114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Friday ordered Roger Stone, his attorneys and special counsel Robert Mueller to stop talking publicly about their case involving charges the longtime Donald Trump associate lied to Congress and obstructed its Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe writes book about confronting white nationalism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/430255-former-virginia-gov-mcauliffe-writes-book-about-confronting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe (D) has written a book examining the Charlottesville "Unite the Right" rally in 2017 that dissolved into riots and resulted in the death of a counter-protester and two state troopers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space junk harpooned like whale in orbit-cleanup test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/066f28f2c2d04fd89ec15f7d43c99d88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A harpoon flung from a satellite has successfully captured a piece of pretend space junk, like a whale. The British-led experiment is part of an effort to clean up debris in orbit, hundreds of miles above Earth. The University of Surrey's Guglielmo Aglietti said Friday that the steel-tipped harpoon scored a bull's-eye last Friday. The harpoon — no bigger than a writing pen — pierced an aluminum panel the size of a table tennis racket attached to the end of a satellite boom. The distance was just 5 feet (1.5 meters), but researchers were delighted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Push Back on Hoax Claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/police-push-back-against-claim-that-attack-on-empire-star-was-a-hoax-11550255540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Police said they have arrested two possible suspects in an attack reported last month by “Empire” television star Jussie Smollett and pushed back against a media report that the attack was staged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College dating classes proliferate...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/failing-at-love-maybe-its-time-for-classes-11550253394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In South Korea, college-level dating courses are proliferating. They quickly fill up, as young people accustomed to spending their whole day in school make romance one more thing they need to study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: McCabe Walks Back Ousting Trump Via 25th Amendment Talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/mccabe-spox-walks-back-remarks-on-talks-to-oust-trump-via-25th-amendment-taken-out-of-context/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick settles collusion case against NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/15/colin-kaepernick-reaches-settlement-in-collusion-case-against-nfl-lawyer-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL and lawyers for players Colin Kaepernick and Eric Reid jointly announced Friday that they have settled a complaint of collusion by the players, who claimed football team owners blackballed them because they knelt during the National Anthem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Dodges 2020 Question...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/hillary-clinton-dodges-2020-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mountains Bigger Than Everest May Lie Deep Inside Earth...</title>
      <link>https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/3kgvpw/mountains-bigger-than-everest-may-lie-deep-inside-earth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;motherboard.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists used the second largest earthquake on record to glimpse the terrain 410 miles under our planet's surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F: Just 1-in-4 AMERICANS pass US citizenship test...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/doh-only-1-state-passes-us-citizenship-test-dc-fails-big</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority in every state except Vermont has failed the U.S. Citizenship test, the latest sign that Americans aren’t very good history students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 potential suspects under arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/culture/story/jussie-smollett-case-detectives-probable-men-surveillance-video-61099330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goodmorningamerica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men have been arrested in the atack on "Empire" star Jussie Smollett, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Denies Putting Boyfriend on Payroll...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/did-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-put-her-boyfriend-on-the-public-payroll-rumors-swirl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's the guy on the far right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain to get 3rd govt in 4 years amid fragmenting politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2615b904b41f4325b2390c4ce3e900c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain will elect its third government in less than four years after Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez's fragile socialist government acknowledged Friday its support had evaporated and called an early general election. Sanchez's eight-month-old administration met its end after failing to get parliament's approval for its 2019 budget proposal earlier this week, adding to the political uncertainty that has dogged Spain in recent years. "Between doing nothing and continuing without a budget, or giving the chance for Spaniards to speak, Spain should continue looking ahead," Sanchez said in a televised appearance from the Moncloa Palace, the seat of government, after an urgent Cabinet meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 cities go to war with feds over 5G expansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/14/fcc-rules-5g-cellphone-upgrade-spark-antenna-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A turf war between federal regulators and local jurisdictions is brewing over the installation of hundreds of thousands of cellphone towers to upgrade to 5G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA has 1,000 ISIS detainees -- unsure what to do with them...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2019/02/14/us-forces-have-1000-isis-detainees-and-dont-know-what-to-do-with-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“[It’s] a huge area of concern for us, especially because they’re being detained by the non-nation state that’s otherwise known as the Syrian Democratic Forces,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Lauds Hannity, Rush...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-fires-back-at-ann-coulter-taunts-i-like-her-but-shes-off-the-reservation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Amendment 'auditor' injured during argument at LA synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article226317205.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi, Schumer Threaten...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6709767/Pelosi-Schumer-Border-emergency-unlawful-declaration-crisis-does-not-exist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer claimed in a joint statement that there is no 'crisis' on the U.S.-Mexico border and threatened to sue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top investigator in Green Beret murder case charged with stolen valor...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2019/02/14/lead-investigator-in-green-beret-murder-case-faces-charges-of-stolen-valor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelation could have major impact on the Army's case against the major facing a murder charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYPASSES CONGRESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-set-to-declare-national-emergency-at-border-sign-legislation-to-fund-government-11550241799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump declared a national emergency to bolster his border-wall plans, supplementing the funding contained in a spending bill passed by Congress with billions diverted from elsewhere in government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In ROUNDUP Case, Science Will Go on Trial First...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-roundup-case-the-science-will-go-on-trial-first-11550246311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge in a Roundup cancer trial later this month has divided the case so jurors can focus first solely on the science and then, only if they find the plaintiff’s claims valid, on the question of negligence. The results could change the way the courts handle cases that hinge on complex science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg back at Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/430168-ginsburg-back-at-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was back at the court on Friday for the justices’ private conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT DECLARES BORDER EMERGENCY...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-sign-border-bill-declare-national-emergency-wall/story?id=61088949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump announced that he's declaring a national emergency to get funding for his proposed border wall that congressional Democrats refused to give him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LIVE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FFIcGqjkORk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin floored by woman during judo session -- then 'covers up' photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8435517/woman-floors-putin-in-judo-sparring-session-forcing-him-to-get-real-but-you-didnt-see-pics-due-to-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN floored Russian president Vladimir Putin in a judo sparring session, forcing him to “get real”. After the 2016 Olympic bronze medal winner Natalia Kuzyutina, 29, tackled the strongman, he g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY MUTINY: Humiliated after losing ANOTHER Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/feb/14/theresa-may-defeated-on-brexit-again-as-erg-tories-abstain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PM defeated by 303 votes to 258, plunging hopes of uniting her party around renegotiated deal into chaos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK facing record MULTI-BILLION dollar fine over privacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-Facebook-negotiating-record-13617614.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Trade Commission and Facebook are negotiating over a multibillion-dollar fine that would settle the agency's investigation into the social media giant's privacy practices, according to two people familiar with the probe. The fine would be the largest the agency has ever imposed on a technology company, but the two sides have not yet agreed on an exact amount. Facebook has expressed initial concern with the FTC's demands, one of the people said. If talks break down, the FTC could take the matter to court in what would likely be a bruising legal fight. Facebook confirmed it is in discussions with the agency but declined to comment further. The FTC declined to comment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre 'robot marriage-hunting parties' let flirt through machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/bizarre-robot-marriage-hunting-parties-14002469</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For singletons in Japan, the worry of speaking to a date is taken out of the equation - thanks to robots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPENDING BINGE WORSE THAN UNDER OBAMA, BUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/bipartisan-spending-binge-now-worse-bush-o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ve gone into deep debt for everything except the core function of the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez, Castro Plan Bill to Block...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/ocasio-cortez-plans-bill-to-block-trump-s-emergency-declaration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez,Â Joaquin CastroÂ PlanÂ Bill to Block Trump's Emergency Declaration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. Skyscraper Shown Exploding in New ISIS Threat...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/l-a-skyscraper-shown-exploding-in-new-isis-promise-fulfilled-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though ISIS backers operating under a number of media alliances regularly craft and circulate threats, Los Angeles is rarely featured as a target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu widespread in USA with 15.2 million cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/02/15/flu-season-15-m-cases-widespread-puerto-rico-47-states-cdc-says/2868271002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More people have received flu shots this year than last. The overall hospitalization rate so far this season is 20.1 per 100,000 people compared toÂ 30.5 per 100,000 at this period last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eerie 'witch symbols' found scratched into 'cave to hell'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8433075/witch-symbols-scratched-cave-hell-sherwood-forrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNDREDS of spooky “witch marks” have been discovered in a cave once believed to lead to hell. The eerie etchings were carved into the stone walls of Creswell Crags near Sherwood Forest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fringe YouTuber Shot While Filming Guard Outside Synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fringe-youtuber-shot-while-filming-guard-outside-la-synagogue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The YouTube personality known as Furry Potato has a long track record of confrontational ‘auditing’ videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as dogs to be killed for dental implant experiment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/outrage-six-dogs-killed-part-14002623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The six Labradors have already had more than a third of their teeth removed as part of the experiment which is taking place in Sweden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant herd refuses to leave spot where calf died in tense stand-off with locals...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/elephant-herd-refuses-leave-spot-14003625 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: DISTRESSING CONTENT. The animals didn't want to leave the one-year-old who was still alive but unable to get out of the deep pit in India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese protest in Madrid against mass bank account freeze...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/chinese-protest-madrid-against-mass-bank-account-freeze-133110617--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Chinese citizens staged a rare protest Friday at an office of Spain's BBVA bank in Madrid, angrily denouncing that their personal accounts had been frozen without prior warning. Waving Chinese and Spanish flags, the protesters shouted "racist BBVA" and "we want justice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man explains how he killed mountain lion with bare hands...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/02/14/travis-kauffman-mountain-lion-attack-horsetooth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who fought back when a mountain lion was attacking him while he was running on a trail at Horsetooth Mountain says he wasn't sure at first whether he would win that battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE director resigns over photos evoking slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/feb/15/vogue-brazil-director-resigns-over-birthday-photos-evoking-slavery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images show Donata Meirelles, who is white, sitting on a throne-like seat flanked by four black women dressed in white</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam mayor slams tourists who 'humiliate' sex workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/451515-sex-workers-not-tourist-attractions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amsterdam's mayor has stepped up her campaign to change the city's seedy image, scolding visitors who make the pilgrimage to its red-light district for treating sex workers like a tourist attraction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Weld launches GOP presidential exploratory committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/02/15/bill-weld-launches-gop-presidential-exploratory-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Massachusetts Gov. William F. Weld is launching a presidential exploratory committee to challenge President Trump in the Republican primaries, saying the country is “in grave peril&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Taylor Swift showed scary future of facial recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/feb/15/how-taylor-swift-showed-us-the-scary-future-of-facial-recognition </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance at concerts is just the beginning, as fears grow around an unregulated, billion-dollar industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGAL WAR LOOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/14/trump-national-emergency-legal-challenges-1170936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers, activists and state officials are planning to challenge what they say is a presidential end-run around the Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widow, 81, sole resident of remote island disputed by SKorea, Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/14/asia/south-korea-japan-disputed-islands-one-resident-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1991, Kim Sin-yeol and her husband made the unusual decision to move to a lonely set of islands at the heart of a long-standing territorial dispute between Japan and South Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brewing STARBUCKS Protest Could Hit Coffee Giant in Blue America...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/brewing-starbucks-protest-could-hit-coffee-giant-in-blue-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brewing Starbucks Protest Could Hit Coffee Giant in Blue America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furor over Omar puts spotlight on AIPAC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/business-a-lobbying/430054-furor-over-omar-puts-spotlight-on-aipac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week’s controversial tweets by Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), one of the first two Muslim women to serve in Congress, has put the spotlight on the American Israel Public Affairs Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns of 'backsliding' in measles fight as cases soar...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/warns-backsliding-measles-fight-cases-soar-161416903.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization warned Thursday that efforts to halt the spread of measles were "backsliding", with case numbers worldwide surging around 50 percent last year. The UN health agency pointed to preliminary data showing that the disturbing trend of resurgent measles cases was happening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar organizers struggle to keep show relevant...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/oscar-organizers-struggle-keep-show-relevant-015231766.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar organizers are struggling to keep Hollywood's biggest night relevant while dealing with a string of messy controversies. With less than two weeks to go before the February 24 gala, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences has been weathering the latest debacle over four awards to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man explains how he killed mountain lion with bare hands...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/14/travis-kauffman-explains-how-he-killed-a-mountain-lion-with-his-bare-hands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado man who survived a mountain lion attack while out for a run in the woods recalled thinking “this would be a crappy way to die” during his fight for survival with the animal. Travis Kau…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
