<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RECORD TURN OUT?</title>
      <link>https://www.unionleader.com/news/politics/voters/after-years-two-dozen-hopefuls-nh-primary-finally-arrives/article_d9d5d272-4cde-517f-bbba-75fd684cf696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHUA — The 10 major Democratic presidential hopefuls raced through more than 30 events on the eve of Tuesday’s first-in-the-nation primary, which remains too close to call and could well</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Journey to Mars Begins in South Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/02/space-x-texas-village-boca-chica/606382/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The residents of Boca Chica didn’t ask Elon Musk to move in, and now his company wants them out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macaulay Culkin Exonerates Michael Jackson in New Interview: 'Never did anything to me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/02/11/macaulay-culkin-exonerates-michael-jackson-in-new-interview-right-now-is-a-good-time-to-speak-up-he-never-did-anything-to-me</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macaulay Culkin exonerates Michael Jackson from all rumors concerning possible or alleged child molestation in the new issue of Esquire. Bravo to the magazine in the first place for putting Mack on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG #2 IN BETS</title>
      <link>https://www.predictit.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.predictit.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARDON ME:  President slams sentencing recommendation for Roger Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-stirs-pardon-speculation-with-condemnation-of-dojs-roger-stone-treatment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's fiery reaction to the Justice Department's sentencing recommendation for Roger Stone is stoking renewed speculation that he could end up pardoning his former associate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah considers decriminalizing polygamy...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/polygamists-may-not-face-jail-time-under-utah-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Utah state lawmaker says it’s time to remove the threat of jail time for otherwise law-abiding polygamists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren's last stand?</title>
      <link>https://www.concordmonitor.com/Is-New-Hampshire-Elizabeth-Warren-s-last-stand-32614716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.concordmonitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, N.H. – It was not supposed to be this way for Elizabeth Warren, slogging through the snow and bitter cold as she struggles to salvage her once-soaring campaign.She had policy plans – tons of them – a strong political operation that had her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Unloads $4.1 Billion Worth of AMAZON Shares in Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/11/jeff-bezos-sold-4point1-billion-worth-of-amazon-shares-in-past-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In total, Bezos sold 2 million shares, worth about $4.1 billion, SEC filings show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC anchor to challenge Ocasio-Cortez in primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/482499-cnbc-anchor-caruso-cabrera-to-challenge-ocasio-cortez-in-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CNBC anchor Michelle Caruso-Cabrera announced on Tuesday that she will challenge Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Deletes Tweet Calling Bloomberg 'TOTAL RACIST' Over Stop &amp; Frisk...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-deletes-tweet-calling-bloomberg-total-racist-over-very-same-stop-frisk-policy-he-backed-in-2016/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump decided to join with the political observers dogpiling Michael Bloomberg in light of his uncovered remarks about stop and frisk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>44% of adults admit to keeping money secrets from partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/11/44percent-of-adults-admit-to-keeping-money-secrets-from-a-partner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether they are spending more money than they are letting on, stashing a secret credit card or hiding debt, nearly half of those in a relationship admit to committing some sort of financial infidelity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Every Democrat is depressed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/theyre-voting-in-new-hampshire-but-this-democrat-just-wants-to-jump-off-a-bridge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not just Sanders and the electability question. The whole field, while all of them seem like good, dedicated people, has disappointed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK: Last Call in Miami Beach Might Be Little Earlier...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/article240181943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise Ship Rejected by Five Ports Runs Out of Options...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/482480-carnival-cruise-ship-refused-entry-by-fifth-port-due-to-coronavirus-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Carnival cruise ship on Tuesday was refused entry to Thailand over fears of coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing set in stone in Granite State...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/482428-nothing-is-set-in-stone-in-the-granite-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t go to bed Tuesday night right after the networks announce the winner. Knowing the identity of the runner-up is almost as important.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise and fall of Merkel 'mini-me'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rise-fall-merkels-mini-002112035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barely a year after replacing her mentor as head of Germany's CDU party, Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer has thrown in the towel -- unexpectedly upending Chancellor Angela Merkel's succession plans. Kramp-Karrenbauer, best known by her initials "AKK", said she was standing down as CDU leader</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA secretly owned top encryption supplier; Read communications of allies, adversaries...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2020/02/11/cia-secretly-owned-worlds-to.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than half a century, governments all over the world trusted a single company to keep the communications of their spies, soldiers and diplomats secret. That company was secretly run by the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead birds posing as cat food confiscated at Dulles airport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6a1688e85a66f065136fbe084ae0855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHANTILLY, Va. (AP) — A package of tiny dead birds passed off as pet food was confiscated by Customs agents at a Virginia airport. U.S. Customs and Border Protection says the package came...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big question as Weinstein trial winds down: Will he testify?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/986c0a99e757d187cfcb4e8c5578ef6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Harvey Weinstein’s lawyers are set to rest their defense case Tuesday, but not before answering the big question looming over his New York City rape trial: Will he take the risk...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/947b78053ef5b284f69c99009a68f6a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. (AP) — The Latest on the 2020 Democratic presidential contest and the New Hampshire primary (all times local): 9 a.m. Pete Buttigieg says he's feeling “very good”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer told to 'tone down' gayness settles suit for $10.25M...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/90ad95f5a81966f4cb74fad039caa655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLAYTON, Mo. (AP) — St. Louis County has agreed to a $10.25 million settlement with a gay police lieutenant who says he was passed over for promotion 23 times and was told to “tone down” his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In heart of Mexico's violence, disillusion grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/859a336e1b94e0360f42575245d58317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;URUAPAN, MEXICO (AP) — Alejandra Uvilla fled her home city of Apatzingan because of overwhelming violence, moving 65 miles (105 km) north to bustling, mountain-nestled Uruapan in the avocado belt...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MILITARY HAS MASS QUARANTINE CAMPS SET UP IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/department-of-defense-the-military-has-mass-quarantine-camps-set-up-in-the-u-s_02102020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected patient mistakenly released from San Diego hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/10/health/evacuee-wuhan-coronavirus-mistakenly-released/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first US evacuee from China known to be infected with the Wuhan coronavirus was mistakenly released from a San Diego hospital after an initial test found the person had not been infected, local health officials said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Analysts Outwit Humans on Investment Picks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/robot-analysts-outwit-humans-in-study-of-profit-from-stock-calls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot Analysts Outwit Humans on Investment Picks, Study Shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise Ship Rejected by Five Ports Runs Out of Options...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-11/cruise-ship-rejected-by-four-nations-runs-out-of-options</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange Russian Spacecraft STILL Shadowing U.S. Spy Satellite; 'Disturbing'...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5779315/russian-spacecraft-spy-satellite-space-force/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We view this behavior as unusual and disturbing"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-rare snowfall carpets Baghdad...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ultra-rare-snowfall-carpets-baghdad-082753629.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Baghdad rushed to have snowball fights or take photographs Tuesday as the Iraqi capital woke carpeted in white by only its second snowfall in a century. The last recorded snowfall in the city was in 2008, but it was a quick and mostly slushy affair -- and prior to that, it had been a century</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven years after stepping down, Benedict fuels 'two popes' headache...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/seven-years-stepping-down-benedict-fuels-two-popes-040116183.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven years after his surprise resignation, Benedict XVI -- weakened by age but still intellectually spry -- appears unable to remain in the shadow of his Argentinean successor Francis, creating the appearance of "two popes" at odds. On February 11, 2013, at the age of 85, the German intellectual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having optimistic partner may stave off dementia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/having-optimistic-partner-may-stave-off-dementia-study-113659893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New U.S. research has found that having an optimistic partner could help you live a healthier life. Carried out by researchers from Michigan State University and the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health, the new study looked at nearly 4,457 retired heterosexual couples over the age of 50 who had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte to Scrap U.S. Military Agreement in Rebuke of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/duterte-says-trump-wants-save-232947041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Philippines has notified the U.S. that it’s terminating a 22-year-old military agreement, which can be ended with 180-days notice, just hours after President Rodrigo Duterte said President Donald Trump was trying to save the deal.The notice to terminate the 1998 Visiting Forces Agreement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Over, Pot: Psychedelic Companies About to Go Public...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/move-over-pot-psychedelic-companies-110000647.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The first companies developing medical treatments from psychedelic drugs like LSD, ketamine and the active ingredient in magic mushrooms are gearing up to list on Canadian stock exchanges.Mind Medicine Inc., which is undertaking clinical trials of psychedelic-based drugs, intends to list</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Experts Worry as Germ-Phobic Trump Confronts Growing Epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/10/some-experts-worry-as-a-germ-phobic-trump-confronts-a-growing-epidemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — When an outbreak of the Ebola virus touched the United States’ shores in mid-2014, Donald J. Trump was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online censors tighten grip...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200211103909-l7kr0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/CENSORSHIP (PIX):China's online censors tighten grip after brief coronavirus respite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food fears grow; Troops deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/10/food-fears-grow-as-swarms-of-locusts-reach-uganda-and-tanzania</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outbreak in east Africa has already devastated crops across a swath of Kenya and Somalia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar leads midnight vote in New Hampshire...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/10/politics/dixville-notch-new-hampshire-primary/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Sen. Amy Klobuchar won the most votes when a little more than two dozen New Hampshire residents in three tiny townships cast their ballots shortly after midnight in Tuesday's first-in-the-nation primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors group breaks from health care industry with support for 'Medicare for All'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/482437-doctors-group-breaks-from-health-care-industry-with-support-for-medicare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost the entire health care industry is lined up against “Medicare for All.” Hospitals oppose it. Insurance companies oppose it. Drug companies oppose it.But not the American College of Physicians (ACP). That group made waves last month when it broke with other leading health players to endorse Medicare for All, along with an optional government plan, as a way to get to universal coverage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Write-ins score Bloomberg win in tiny town...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9369eb84718260ccd834737d36267d7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DIXVILLE NOTCH, N.H. (AP) — Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg won the votes of a tiny New Hampshire community that barely hung onto its tradition of being among the first to cast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus storytellers challenge China's official narrative...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8455474af114e6b298cec8cd5da65b65</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — After nearly a week of roaming China's epidemic-struck city, filming the dead and the sickened in overwhelmed hospitals, the strain of being hounded by both the new virus and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: UN warns of 'major shock' as locust outbreak spreads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3062a16869436a7eeb2b5596c7d04278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Uganda scrambled to respond to the arrival of the biggest locust outbreak that parts of East Africa have seen in decades, while the United Nations warned Monday that “we simply...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump mocks Pelosi and crowd chants 'lock her up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/385386/trump-mocks-pelosi-new-hampshire-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump mocked “mumbling” Nancy Pelosi at his New Hampshire rally, saying Democrats are “losing their minds” ahead of tomorrow’s primary. During the Manchester ra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans say  current economy is best since 1990s...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Americans-say-they-feel-the-current-economy-is-15045620.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Americans increasingly rate this as the best economy since the late 1990s, with a recent surge in optimism, even though many economic metrics show striking similarities to the final years of the Obama administration.  Fifty-nine percent of Americans say they are better off financially today than they were a year ago, the highest since 1999, according to a Gallup survey released last week. And nearly three-quarters predict they will do better a year from now, the most optimistic reading that Gallup's annual "Mood of the Nation" survey has ever recorded.  Other polls and surveys aren't quite as ebullient, but nearly all show that Americans are far less worried about the economy and their personal financial situations than they were during the last presidential election.  Upbeat sentiment is critical for the U.S. economy because it motivates consumer spending, the most important driver of U.S. economic growth. And President Donald Trump is counting on a strong economy to motivate voters to turn out at the polls and reelect him.  Bryan DeHenau runs a roofing business in Macomb County, Michigan, just outside Detroit. Around the time of the last presidential election, he had enough jobs to keep one crew busy, but some of the gigs were barely profitable. Today he can keep three crews busy during the spring and summer months, and he has been able to raise prices, regularly giving people estimates of $20,000 to totally redo a roof and finding that "they don't even bat an eye about it anymore."  "I'm driving a brand-new 2019 Ford F-250. I've got work coming out the ying-yang. I'm doing OK," DeHenau said. "Four years ago, I couldn't sleep at night. That's a pretty big turnaround."  Some of the biggest recent increases in consumer confidence have come from independent voters and less affluent households, according to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PAL BARRACK GUSHES OVER BIDEN, BLOOMBERG...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/10/democrats-including-biden-and-bloomberg-can-beat-trump-in-2020-tom-barrack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's former inaugural committee chairman sees Joe Biden and Michael Bloomberg as formidable contenders for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds add hacktivists, social media manipulators to top intel threats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-adds-hacktivists-social-media-manipulators-top-intel-203119738.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US counter-spy agency said Monday that cyber and surveillance technology advances have multiplied the intelligence threat to the country, putting hacktivists and online manipulators on a par with venerable foe Russia. The biennial National Counterintelligence Strategy for the first time singled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-a-million insect species face extinction: scientists...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/half-million-insect-species-face-extinction-scientists-183339666.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of the one million animal and plant species on Earth facing extinction are insects, and their disappearance could be catastrophic for humankind, scientists have said in a "warning to humanity". "The current insect extinction crisis is deeply worrying," said Pedro Cardoso, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Called Him 'Spiritual Soul Mate'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/accuser-called-weinstein-spiritual-soul-203513628.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Former friends of two Harvey Weinstein accusers assailed their credibility at Weinstein’s sexual assault trial, with one saying that prosecution witness Jessica Mann once referred to the movie producer as her “soul mate.”Testifying on Monday for the defense, Talita Maia, a Brazilian actor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  More than 100 US troops suffered traumatic brain injuries in Iran strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/384961/us-troops-traumatic-brain-injuries-iran-strike-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE than 100 US troops reportedly suffered traumatic brain injuries in Iran’s missile strike  – after Trump said no one “seriously hurt.” The US military experienced over a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOTERS STILL CAN'T MAKE UP THEIR MINDS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/just-hours-to-go-new-hampshire-primary-voters-still-cant-make-up-their-minds/ar-BBZRff2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARDON ME:  Feds seek 7 to 9 years in prison for Roger Stone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/de461beece23fa061f58ccf21ee547dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal prosecutors are asking a judge to sentence President Donald Trump's Trump confidant Roger Stone to serve between 7 and 9 years in prison after his conviction on witness...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCAR RATINGS FALL TO ALL-TIME LOW...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dbbb0d2390675493374a4ee68f55d1e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Without a host or a great deal of pizzazz, ABC's telecast of the Academy Awards reached its smallest audience ever of 23.6 million viewers. The Nielsen company said Sunday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW HAMPSHIRE CLIFFHANGER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d2bf61a0f36f7bfee0420c75ac9523e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCHESTER, N.H. (AP) — In the waning hours before New Hampshire’s first-in-the-nation primary voting begins, Democratic presidential candidates took varied approaches to the expectations game...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitcher sues ASTROS, says cheating changed career...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/columnist/nancy-armour/2020/02/10/mike-bolsinger-sues-houston-astros-says-cheating-changed-his-career/4712164002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bolsinger faced eight batters and got one out vs. the Astros in 2017. He hasn't pitched in the majors since. On Monday, he sued the team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commissioner: Kaepernick salary demands too high...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/football-xfl-luck-kaepernick-idUSKBN20429W?taid=5e41d84f0f91f60001a289f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick could have played in the reborn XFL, but his salary demands wer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot hits Times Square...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200210220118-ciakz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/ROBOT (TV):Robot with coronavirus advice hits Times Square</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man admits plotting attack on Vegas synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/courts/man-admits-plotting-attack-on-las-vegas-synagogue-1954788/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man pleaded guilty Monday to a federal weapons charge for planning violent attacks against the Anti-Defamation League, a Las Vegas synagogue and a Fremont Street bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB plotting playoff expansion with reality TV twist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/10/mlb-plotting-playoff-expansion-with-reality-tv-twist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine a team picking its playoff opponent. Think about Brian Cashman and the Yankees deciding whether to face the Red Sox or avoid them in the first round of the postseason. All on live TV. Well,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War On Sitting: Educators Urged To Let Students Stand Up, Walk Around During Class...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/new-school-educators-must-take-stand-against-prolonged-sitting-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study urges students to spend more time upright, such as taking hourly breaks to stand up and stretch during classes to offset the harms of sitting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie takes top spot in national poll...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/10/joe-biden-national-poll-113302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Quinnipiac survey also shows Bloomberg surging 7 points to third place and eating into Biden's support among black voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President floats 'powerful death penalty' for drug dealers...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/895056/trump-floats-death-penalty-drug-dealers--big-twist-from-criminal-justice-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's latest comments about China would be ironic if they weren't so disturbing. Trump hosted governors from around the country on Monday and gave a wide-ranging speech where he complained about the European Union's apparent bullying and then totally reversed his stance on criminal justice reform. While Trump touted clemency for drug offenders as recently as in his Super Bowl ad, he complimented China's 'maximum penalty' for 'drug dealers' and how it's led to the country having 'very little drug problem.' Trump first complimented what's going on in the authoritarian government of China, and then praised some of the governors in front of him. 'States with a very powerful death penalty on drug dealers don't have a drug problem,' Trump said, though he added 'I don't know if our country is ready for that.' Trump suggests he'd like to model American criminal law on drug dealing on authoritarian systems like China, where dealers are executed: 'Countries with a powerful death penalty, with a fair but quick trial, they have very little if any drug problem. That includes China.' pic.twitter.com/9WprysjJAX â€” Aaron Rupar (@atrupar) February 10, 2020 In contrast, Trump's Super Bowl ad featured Alice Marie Johnson thanking the president for granting her clemency after she'd been in prison for more than 20 years on drug-related charges. The ad was reportedly Trump's son-in-law Jared Kushner's way of appealing to black voters. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore's First 'Ceasefire Weekend' Of 2020 Ends With 14 Shot, 3 Fatally...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/02/09/baltimore-first-ceasefire-weekend-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though this weekend was the first Baltimore Ceasefire Weekend of 2020, the city still saw violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40,000 virus cases may be 'tip of iceberg'; Death toll nears 1,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/02/10/coronavirus-40-000-cases-may-tip-iceberg-death-toll-nears-1-000/4711497002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese health officials said 97 more deaths were reported Sunday, a spike after days of decline, that put the global toll at 910.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of Biden's black supporters abandon him...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/quinnipiac-nearly-half-of-bidens-african-american-supporters-have-abandoned-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden has been counting on South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg rises...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/national/release-detail?ReleaseID=3655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanders Takes Top Spot In Dem Primary As Biden Falls, Quinnipiac University National Poll Finds; Bloomberg Rises In Primary, Runs Strong Against Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 UK medics test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10903354/coronavirus-gp-practice-brighton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO medics are among four people who were diagnosed with coronavirus today – as a GP surgery was placed in lockdown. The County Oak Medical Centre in Brighton, East Sussex, was closed while s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivers leaving CHARGERS; Paving way for Brady?</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/chargers/news/philip-rivers-test-free-agency-leave-chargers-16-seasons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philip Rivers will not return to the Chargers in 2020 and instead test free agency as he continues his NFL career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar Hits Her Stride...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/amy-klobuchar-hits-her-stride-in-new-hampshire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Granite State voters could breathe new life into the Minnesota senator’s campaign tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATINGS FALL TO ALL-TIME LOW</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/oscars-hit-all-time-low-tv-ratings-sunday-feb-9-2020-1278364</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC's broadcast comes in about 3 million viewers behind the previous low in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPAC: Romney uninvited because 'physical safety' would be at risk...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/10/cpac-chair-says-romney-was-uninvited-because-physical-safety-would-be-at-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organizer of the Conservative Political Action Conference defended his decision to uninvite Sen. Mitt Romney — saying the Utah Republican’s vote for more witnesses and documents in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster Of Great White Sharks Off Carolinas Baffles Experts...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/02/10/cluster-massive-great-white-sharks-off-carolina-coast-mystery-ocearch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are trying to figure out why great white sharks are clustering off the coasts of South and North Carolina, as indicated by satellite tracking data shared Saturday on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FADING 23M VIEWERS</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/oscar-ratings-new-all-time-low-viewership-1202854581/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a historic 92nd Academy Awards with a first Best Picture recipient not in the English language in Parasite adding an element of surprise to a largely predictable winners list. There was some…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Arkansas cops wounded in WALMART shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/arkansas-walmart-shooting-police-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting at an eastern Arkansas Walmart Monday injured at least three people, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire sale: The Iran plant making US flags protesters burn...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/235580c14a77045fc7647562a2ac1d33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KHOMEIN, Iran (AP) — Near the hometown of the late Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini, workers at a small Iranian factory diligently add all 50 stars and 13 red-and-white bars to what are supposed to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirk Douglas' Last Words Were About Bloomberg?</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/2020/02/08/actor-michael-douglas-former-mayor-gary-indiana-stump-bloomberg/4701357002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Michael Douglas helped open Bloomberg's Madison office. Ex-Gary Mayor Karen Freeman-Wilson, in Milwaukee, touted Bloomberg's plan to close the black-white wealth gap.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
