<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Film crew present for Proud Boys, Oath Keepers Jan 5 meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/14/film-crew-january-5-meeting-proud-boys-oath-keepers-00017107</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The details provide new evidence of the encounter between the two groups, whose leaders played a key role in the breach of the Capitol the following day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHEVRON set to trade Venezuelan oil...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/money/topstories/exclusive-chevron-set-to-trade-venezuelan-oil-if-us-relaxes-sanctions-sources/ar-AAV2YVq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive-Chevron set to trade Venezuelan oil if U.S. relaxes sanctions -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos of Bayraktar drones blowing up armor cement heroic status...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraine-posts-videos-it-says-show-bayraktar-drones-blowing-up-russian-armor-further-cementing-their-heroic-status/ar-AAV2TZR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears British ex-special forces troops killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/russia-attack-british-troops-feared-dead-b2035555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens died in missile strike close to Ukrainian border with Nato member Poland on Sunday in most westerly attack yet by Russian forces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deep concerns' on 'alignment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220314-us-expresses-deep-concerns-on-russia-china-alignment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has "deep concerns" about "alignment" between Russia and China, a senior US official said Monday after high-ranking US and Chinese officials met for seven hours on the Ukraine war a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestor interrupts state broadcast shouting 'No War'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/anti-war-protestor-interrupts-russian-state-broadcast-shouting-no-war/ar-AAV3aFe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists flying planes into clouds to make it snow more...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/14/weather/cloud-seeding-weather-modification-wxn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 61% of the contiguous US in drought, wouldn't it be nice if we could just "make it rain" or just "make more snow?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US holds 'intense' 7-hour talks with China...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/14/us-holds-intense-7-hour-talks-with-china-amid-russias-war-in-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US and Chinese officials met on Monday to discuss a range of challenges, including Russia's ongoing war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Presidential Library Has Thousands of Files on UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/jgmnqd/obamas-presidential-library-has-thousands-of-files-on-ufos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A response to a FOIA request has revealed the Library is setting on a possible treasure trove of documents about UFOs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy flashes recession warning sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/14/economy/yield-curve-bonds-recession/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surging oil and gas prices have raised recession alarm bells around the world. But another economic indicator is starting to look ominous: The yield curve is flattening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st German Catholic diocese allows women to perform baptisms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/germany-europe-essen-religion-48dc90e8ce37f0bd1bce6c490637ac49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The Roman Catholic Diocese of Essen has become the first in Germany to allow women to perform baptisms, citing a lack of priests. The diocese said in a statement Monday that Bishop Franz-Josef Overbeck tasked 18 lay ministers —17 of them women — with conferring the sacrament of admission into the Church at a ceremony over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX reporter injured near Kyiv... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/breaking-fox-news-reporter-wounded-in-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News journalist was injured outside of Kyiv, reported Fox News anchor John Roberts on Monday. Roberts did not give the name of the journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Goes for the Zelensky Look...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10611433/Is-Macron-copying-Zelensky-French-leader-displays-stubble-jeans-hoodie-war-room-pics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French have long been known purveyors of fine fashion, but it appears Emmanuel Macron (pictured) has been taking style tips from Europe's most in-vogue leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First NATO country calls for 'no-fly zone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/russia-ukraine-nato-country-estonia-calls-for-immediate-establishment-of-no-fly-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Parliament of Estonia on Monday called for UN member states to “take immediate steps to establish a no-fly zone” over Ukraine to prevent further civilian casualties as Russia’s multi-front war against the country rages on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India looks to bail out Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10611333/India-looks-bail-Russia-considers-taking-Moscows-offer-buy-crude-oil-discount.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India, which imports 80 per cent of its oil needs, usually buys only about 2-3 per cent from Russia. But following price increases, New Delhi is looking at how it can reduce its energy bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange denied permission to challenge extradition...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-60743322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Supreme Court spokesman says the Wikileaks founder failed to raise "an arguable point of law".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON relocating workers from Seattle office due to crime...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/amazon-temporarily-relocating-workers-from-office-at-3rd-and-pine-due-to-crime-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citing an increase in violent crime, Amazon announced Friday it would temporarily relocate its workers from the company&amp;rsquo;s office space at 3rd Ave and Pine St in downtown Seattle. According to Amazon, roughly 1,800 employees are assigned to the 300 Pine St building but note many are still working remotely. KOMO News was sent the following statement regarding the move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN EMBASSY TOUTS CANDACE OWENS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/russian-embassy-retweets-candace-owens-accusing-american-government-of-appalling-treatment-of-russians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian Embassy in the United States retweeted pro-Trump commentator Candace Owens accusing Americans of “appalling” treatment of Russians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin to buy dozens of US fighter jets in spending spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220314-germany-to-buy-dozens-of-us-fighter-jets-in-spending-spree</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany plans to buy up to 35 US-made F-35 fighter jets and 15 Eurofighter jets, a parliamentary source said Monday, as part of a major push to modernise the armed forces in response to Russia's inva…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Kremlin Memo: It Is 'Essential' to Feature FOX Tucker Carlson...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2022/03/exclusive-kremlin-putin-russia-ukraine-war-memo-tucker-carlson-fox/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian government has pressed outlets to highlight the Fox host's Putin-helping broadcasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA SAYS IT CAPTURED NSA SPY TOOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4888350/china-claims-captured-us-nsa-spy-tool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA claims to have captured a US National Security Agency spy tool dubbed Trojan house that can allegedly control global internet equipment and steal information. The alleged NSA spy tool is capa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Davidson blasting off to space next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-comedian-pete-davidson-blasting-off-to-space-next-week/ar-AAV2vX3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk challenges Putin to fight, with Ukraine as prize...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/elon-musk-challenges-putin-to-fight-with-ukraine-as-the-prize/ar-AAV2A4K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Put up your dukes, Vlad. Elon Musk, the world's richest man, on Monday challenged Russian President Vladimir Putin to a fight, with nothing less than the fate of Ukraine, scene of Moscow's brutal invasion, at stake. The eccentric billionaire and founder of aerospace company SpaceX took to Twitter, where his messages are notoriously erratic, to see whether the Russian leader would test his mettle in person rather than through his country's forces...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alien Drone Swarm' Freaks Out Austin with Giant Hovering QR Code...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/halo-sxsw-drones-1235110882/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I got scared and ran inside": Texas locals were variously freaked out, annoyed and impressed by a 600-foot-wide drone swarm marketing stunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you be healed by a sound frequency?</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2648299?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — In 2015 the Grammy-nominated music producer, songwriter and rapper Maejor, 33, was living every artist’s dream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 3 MILLION million flee Ukraine war...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/more-2-8-million-flee-141549176.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of refugees who have fled Ukraine since the Russian invasion began on February 24 has topped 2.8 million, the United Nations said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deltacron' Danger...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deltacron-hybrid-delta-omicron-variants-173858119.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Deltacron' is a hybrid of Delta and Omicron. How worried should California be?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO SENDS 50 WARSHIPS TO RUSSIAN BORDER</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4890360/nato-masses-troops-warships-war-games-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO has amassed 30,000 troops and 50 warships near Russia’s border for military exercises risking Mad Vlad’s rage. The drill named Cold Response has kicked off today in Norway amid esc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For competition addicts, there will always be unfinished business...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/for-competition-addicts-like-tom-brady-there-will-always-be-unfinished-business/ar-AAV1MHT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persian Gulf monarchies hedging their bets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-ukraine-conflict-has-persian-gulf-monarchies-hedging-their-bets/ar-AAV1TbD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KREMLIN CHAOS; CRACKS IN REGIME</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-kremlin-chaos-amid-cracks-26462804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has so far lost a number of Russian generals, with General Andrei Kolesnikov, of the 29th Combined Arms Army, killed in fighting on Friday - a top Putin's ally has admitted the war is progressing slower than expected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle top destination for students...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/exclusive-poll-where-college-students-want-to-move-seattle-9418efc8-df61-4569-9de4-d7511b62caaa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It feels like a young-person city."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS:  Woman stabs date during sex as revenge for killing of Iranian commander...</title>
      <link>https://www.8newsnow.com/crime/police-woman-stabs-date-in-las-vegas-area-hotel-room-in-relation-for-u-s-drone-strike-that-killed-iranian-leader/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.8newsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman is accused of stabbing her date she had met online in retaliation for the 2020 death of an Iranian leader killed in an American drone strike, police wrote in court documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to make virtual address to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/598081-zelensky-to-make-virtual-address-us-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky will speak virtually to members of Congress on Wednesday, Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) and Senate Majority Leader Charles Schumer (D-N.Y.) announced in a joint letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Challenges Putin to 'Single Combat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/news/world/elon-musk-challenges-vladimir-putin-to-single-combat-ukraine-is-on-stake-11647259706363.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk had last week said that Starlink, a satellite internet constellation operated by SpaceX, was the only non-Russian communications system still working in some parts of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Credits Affair With AI Girlfriend For Saving Marriage...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/ai-girlfriend-wife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polyamory is one thing, but one man who claims falling in love with his AI girlfriend saved his marriage to his flesh-and-blood wife is certainly another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow threatens to pay foreign debts in rubles...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/598069-russia-threatens-to-pay-foreign-debts-in-rubles-following-sanctions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is threatening to pay foreign debts in rubles after a number of Moscow’s top banks were sanctioned in response to the country's invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan again warns Chinese aircraft in its air defense zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-taiwan-defence-china/taiwan-again-warns-chinese-aircraft-in-its-air-defence-zone-idUSKCN2LB14S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan's air force scrambled again on Monday to warn away 13 Chinese aircraft that entered its air defence zone, Taiwan's defence ministry said, in the latest uptick in tensions across the Taiwan Strait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New wave of inflation, disruptions hits factory floors...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/ukraine-crisis-usa-disruption/new-wave-of-inflation-and-disruptions-hits-u-s-factory-floors-idUSKCN2LB0VM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surging inflation is disrupting everything from carpools to the ability to quote prices on new business at already-strained U.S. factories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: High-Protein Diets Lower Men's Testosterone Levels; Can Lead To ED?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/high-protein-diet-testosterone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a high-protein diet may reduce men's testosterone levels, which can lead to erectile dysfunction and low sperm counts, say scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Sees at Least One Winner Emerging: China...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/14/china-sees-at-least-one-winner-emerging-from-ukraine-war-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The war in Ukraine is far from over, but a consensus is forming in Chinese policy circles that one country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway Singing Coach, 87, Has Brain Injury After Street Attack...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/13/broadway-singing-coach-87-has-brain-injury-after-street-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A highly regarded 87-year-old singing coach has a traumatic brain injury after a woman pushed her to the ground just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO nonalignment creates risk for Finland, Sweden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/amid-russian-aggression-nato-nonalignment-creates-risk-for-finland-and-sweden/ar-AAV0UjQ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians cross Mexico border to seek US asylum...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russians-cross-mexico-border-seek-050154594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 8,600 Russians have sought refuge in the U.S. on the Mexican border in recent months. Many fly from Moscow to Cancun, entering Mexico as tourists, and go to Tijuana, where they pool money to buy cars. (March 14)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sought in homeless killings in NYC, DC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-city-new-york-shootings-b0cdeff465d2ab4003db26986635885a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Police in New York City were searching for a man who authorities say shot and killed one homeless person and wounded another in separate street attacks. The shootings occurred early Saturday morning, according to the NYPD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most-fit 33% less likely to develop Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/the-most-fit-are-33-percent-less-likely-to-develop-alzheimer-s-report-says/ar-AAV0CKr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel grapples with fate of oligarchs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-viktor-vekselberg-mikhail-fridman-europe-7744b07a6fb0d2321aabe958cb952dd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel is grappling with how to deal with dozens of Jewish Russian oligarchs as Western nations step up sanctions on businesspeople with ties to Russian President Vladimir Putin. A worried Israeli government has formed a high-level committee to see how the country can maintain its status as a haven for any Jew without running afoul of the biting sanctions targeting Putin’s inner circle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US view of Putin: Angry, frustrated, likely to escalate war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-nato-william-burns-europe-1271f76008b3e639df6ff21e3644e339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — More than two weeks into a war he expected to dominate in two days, Vladimir Putin is projecting anger, frustration at his military’s failures and a willingness to cause even more violence and destruction in Ukraine, in the assessment of U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant woman, baby die after maternity ward bombed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-health-europe-c0f2f859296f9f02be24fc9edfca1085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned. Images of the woman being rushed to an ambulance on a stretcher had circled the world, epitomizing the horror of an attack on humanity’s most innocent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China battles multiple outbreaks, driven by stealth omicron...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-china-taiwan-d2d2a0e6635a90270cfd746854cdd856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — China banned most people from leaving a coronavirus-hit northeastern province and mobilized military reservists Monday as the fast-spreading “stealth omicron” variant fuels the country's biggest outbreak since the start of the pandemic two years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Republicans lining up for 2024 shadow primary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-larry-hogan-adam-kinzinger-donald-trump-liz-cheney-b62ae9bb1ee38bf3ec18da59352bf3dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Maryland Gov. Larry Hogan is planning trips to Iowa and New Hampshire. Rep. Adam Kinzinger, R-Ill., is considering a rough timeline for a potential presidential announcement. And allies of Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had been diagnosed with terminal prostate cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/03/13/william-hurt-actor-dead-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran character actor's death was announced Sunday by his son, who said his father had passed from natural causes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My place is still on the field'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/03/13/tom-brady-announces-nfl-comeback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is not retiring after all -- the superstar Tampa Bay QB just announced his return for a 23rd NFL season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNRETIREMENT:   Brady announces 'I'm coming back' for 23rd season 'in Tampa'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/buccaneers-qb-tom-brady-announces-i-m-coming-back-for-23rd-season-in-tampa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly two months after announcing his retirement, quarterback ﻿Tom Brady﻿ announced Sunday he will return to play for his 23rd season and do so "in Tampa."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan calls ramp up on Biden to give Ukraine jets, weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Bipartisan-calls-ramp-up-on-Biden-to-give-Ukraine-16998825.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A growing number of U.S. lawmakers ratcheted up pressure on President Joe...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
