<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Invades the Swamp as DC Catches Antitrust Fever...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/06/facebook-google-amazon-apple-hire-lobbyists-as-dc-catches-antitrust-fever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, Google, Facebook, and Apple are preparing for all-out war with Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Dems Learned Wrong Lesson From Clinton Impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/06/did-clintons-impeachment-actually-hurt-republicans/591175/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It didn’t actually cost the GOP all that much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murders, cellphones, drugs: Feds strike at Aryan Brotherhood CA prison gang...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article231253023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contempt resolution for Barr, McGahn introduced...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/447318-dems-officially-introduce-contempt-resolution-for-barr-mcgahn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats have officially introduced a resolution to hold Attorney General William Barr and former White House counsel Don McGahn in contempt of Congress for failing to comply with congressional subpoenas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of 'arson' fires across Israel...</title>
      <link>http://www.israelnationalnews.com/News/News.aspx/264287</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.israelnationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erratic sleep linked to higher health risks...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/health/irregular-sleep-routine-linked-higher-health-risks-study-finds-t155636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having an erratic sleep schedule can do a number on your health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Gone Wild: High Drama Inside DC's Most Elite Private School...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/education/archive/2019/06/sidwell-friends-college-admissions-varsity-blues/591124/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Sidwell Friends, the high school of Chelsea Clinton and the Obama children, college counselors find themselves besieged by Ivy-obsessed families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas Ink SPOTIFY Deal to Produce, Host Podcasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/obamas-ink-deal-spotify-produce-host-podcasts-1216253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through Higher Ground Audio, Barack and Michelle Obama will develop, produce and lend their voices to audio shows for the music streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN STATE Bans From Playoffs...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/06/06/golden-state-warriors-fan-ejected-confrontation-toronto-raptors-kyle-lowry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Golden State Warriors minority owner, who was ejected from Game 3 of the NBA Finals after shoving Toronto's Kyle Lowry, will not be attending any more NBA Finals games at Oracle Arena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London getting 'world's first' 360-degree infinity pool...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/infinity-pool-london-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London might soon get a 55-story building topped with a 600,000-liter, 360-degree infinity pool, which the designers say would be a world first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Trump shelves politics at anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-dday-anniversary-macron-trump/hugs-not-macho-handshakes-trump-shelves-politics-at-d-day-anniversary-idUSKCN1T71TM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump briefly set aside politics and his testy relationship wit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY lands podcast deal with Obamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/spotify-lands-exclusive-podcast-deal-barack-michelle-obama-n1014536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landing the former first couple is a major win as the podcast industry grows and the fight for rights to premium shows and creators becomes more contentious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela now a top source of asylum claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/venezuela-now-a-top-source-of-us-asylum-claims-poses-a-challenge-for-trump/ar-AACsEQa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems don't have a majority for impeachment, but support is growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.libertyheadlines.com/democrats-dont-have-majority-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.libertyheadlines.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When House Speaker Nancy Pelosi spoke last weekend at the California Democratic Party convention, she was greeted with cries of “Impeach! Impeach!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private border wall -- not working...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/salvadorhernandez/border-wall-gofundme-sunland-park-residents-migrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Regardless of what they build, they’re still coming in,” one resident said. “This is just political crap.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge of African migrants continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/06/06/500-african-migrants-apprehended-since-may-30-in-single-border-patrol-sector/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Del Rio Sector Border Patrol agents apprehended more than 500 migrants from the continent of Africa since May 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PART OWNER SHOVES RAPTORS PLAYER...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-warriors-fan-who-shoved-raptors-player-is-a-part-owner-5e2a1ded-9f3a-4ca0-9f52-3a008b644284.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Stevens is a venture capitalist and part owner of the Warriors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German nurse who murdered 87 patients given life sentence...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/02efea20c2cb468c98ec10ca36afcdb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Stabbed Self Three Times Because 'Tired Of Living In Trump's Country'...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/donald-trump/palmetto-stabbing-941685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman told police that she stabbed herself in the stomach with a kitchen knife because, “I’m tired of living in Trump’s country, I’m tired of Trump being president.” Cops found the 46-yea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA allowing illegals to fly without proper documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/tsa-allowing-illegal-migrants-to-fly-without-proper-documents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas — The federal agency tasked with overseeing security at transportation hubs has been violating its own policy by allowing migrants who have been released from federal custody onto flights despite not having required documents, according to several Department of Homeland Security…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Army Soldiers Have Worse Heart Health Then Civilians...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/soldiers-us-army-worse-heart-health-than-civilians-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One might think that the rigorous training and expectation to maintain good health would mean active Army soldiers have healthier hearts than the average civilian, but a shocking new study released by the American Heart Association reveals the opposite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Point cadet killed, 22 injured in training rollover...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/20-west-point-cadets-involved-vehicle-rollover-crash-n1014456?F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The accident happened Thursday morning near the Camp Natural Bridge training site, the U.S. Military Academy said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAKE TROLLS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/06/drake-instantly-trolls-warriors-klay-thompson-with-questionable-photo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA Finals are quickly becoming the Drake vs. Klay show — and Wednesday night went to the famed rapper. Drake trolled Warriors star Klay Thompson after his Raptors steamrolled Golden Stat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Bat Inside NYC Subway Car Spooks Passangers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/06/05/bat-on-subway-f-train-mta-new-york-city-bat-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Somehow, a bat made its way onto a subway over the weekend, startling the people inside. One straphanger recorded the incident on his cellphone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Nightmare: Finals Ratings Crash To 12-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/06/kawhi-leonard-raptors-win-nba-finals-ratings-crash-game-3-steph-curry-warriors-abc-1202628013/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anyone thought the Toronto Raptors were going to go extinct against the Golden State Warriors once the 2019 NBA Finals moved to back to America, last night’s Game 3 tore that theory apart. A res…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash Over Boston 'Straight Pride Parade'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/06/05/straight-pride-parade-boston-group-planned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before Boston's Pride parade fills city streets, celebrating the LGBTQ community, another parade proposal is causing an uproar on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontrunner Biden campaigning for president on his terms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2c57969955c4ed8bee6fb64bad9faae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Massive migrant mob WALKS AROUND border wall...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-massive-migrant-mob-walks-around-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a big beautiful border wall in Arizona, and the illegal immigrants who walk right around it are gladly turning themselves in to Border Patrol agents to begin their new life in the land of opportunity. Video of a large group of 134 Central Americans walking around the end of the border wall in Sasabe …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STD INFECTIONS SPREAD TO 1 MILLION -- DAILY...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/wake-up-call-1-million-new-std-infections-daily</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1 million new cases of sexually transmitted diseases pop up across the world every day, a figure that shows health officials have made little progress in curbing infections over the course of about five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Exchange for Movies?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/members/2019/06/05/ryan-kavanaugh-proxima-media-stock-exchange-for-movies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Missing link' in human evolution found after 30,000-year-old remains dug up...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9233938/missing-link-ancient-siberians-native-americans-evolution/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWLY discovered ancient teeth dating back 31,000 years are evidence of a new ethnic group in human history – and could change everything we know about the first American settlers. Living in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI WANTS TRUMP IN PRISON</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/05/pelosi-impeachment-1355435</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She also clashed with Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerry Nadler, who pressed her to begin impeachment proceedings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extinct Volcano Wakes; Could Unleash 'Pompeii-Size' Destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/russia-extinct-volcano-woken-pompeii-eruption-1442479</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clooney secret battle to protect family from ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/inside-amal-george-clooneys-secret-16268250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International human rights lawyer Amal Clooney is battling ISIS in the courtroom - and George Clooney is pulling out all the stops to keep their twins safe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto urged to abandon 'smart city' project...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/jun/06/toronto-smart-city-google-project-privacy-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project with Google’s Sidewalk Labs comes under increasing scrutiny amid concerns over privacy and data harvesting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alliance for 21st century...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/opinion/article/As-allies-remember-D-Day-Putin-and-Xi-look-ahead-13948643.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, Western allies are gathering in Britain and France to commemorate the largest seaborne invasion in history. But far from the English Channel, another significant gathering is taking place that aims to cement a new alliance for this century.  Leaders from countries including the United States, Britain and France met Wednesday in Portsmouth, England, on the 75th anniversary of the D-Day landings, the Allied invasion of Normandy during World War II. On Thursday, those leaders headed to Normandy to commemorate the assault on Nazi-occupied France in June 1944.  Representatives of the countries that formed that World War II alliance were slated to be in attendance, as well as envoys from Germany.  The leaders of Russia and China, two countries that made their own sacrifices to the Allied war effort, will not be present, however. They are meeting on their own, beyond the eastern edge of Europe.  Russian President Vladimir Putin welcomed Chinese President Xi Jinping to Moscow on Wednesday for the start of his three-day visit to Russia. An event on Wednesday marked the 70 years of diplomatic relations between Moscow and Beijing, and both sides claim the relationship is better than ever. Putin "is my best and bosom friend," Xi told Russian state news agency Tass ahead of his visit.  The two international gatherings stand in stark contrast: old and new, East and West, democratic and autocratic. But these differences weren't always so obvious. The Russian president first attended D-Day ceremonies in 2004. Although Moscow was not directly involved in the invasion, Soviet soldiers played the most significant role in defeating Nazi Germany, on the Eastern Front, and paid a deadly cost for it.  Putin's later presence at D-Day commemorations in 2014 was tense and came amid attempts by world leaders to isolate Moscow after its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Least 20 Cadets Involved in Major West Point Crash; Military Describes 'Chaotic' Situation... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/West-Point-New-York-Major-Car-Crash-Orange-County-Emergency-510906491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major emergency response is underway after a crash involving at least 20 cadets near the U.S. Military Academy in New York's Orange County early Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Flippers Cashing Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-home-flippers-are-cashing-out-before-profits-get-slimmer-1.1269342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stressed out? Your dog may feel it too, study suggests...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cd654537064a40adb97fe7bd1c63ba3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot baristas latest automation push...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ccb243ac19c64c0cbf22cd9c8dd99e5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover Video Shows Employees Brutally Beating Dairy Cows At Indiana Farm...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/06/05/disturbing-undercover-video-shows-animal-cruelty-fair-oaks-farms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's tribute to immortals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9233542/dday-anniversary-piper-beach-normandy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world today paid tribute to the “ultimate sacrifice” made by the soldiers who stormed the beaches of Normandy on D-Day 75 years ago. Some of the last surviving heroes from the Allied invasion o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Chipping Away at Bernie Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/i-have-a-plan-warren-gains-on-sanders-with-policy-focus-1.1269417</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi praises 'best friend' Putin during Russia visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-48537663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr Xi has also unveiled two pandas for the Moscow Zoo as part of his three-day visit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dora Maar shakes off Picasso's shadow in new Paris show...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dora-maar-shakes-off-picassos-shadow-paris-show-113723786.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She has gone down in his history as the muse who was almost Picasso's match, but a new show in Paris tries to drag Dora Maar out from under his shadow. The huge retrospective at the Pompidou Centre -- which will transfer to London's Tate Modern in November -- portrays Maar as a leading surrealist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ice pirate' to steal 3,000-foot iceberg; Tow across ocean, melt down to drink...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9234307/iceberg-tow-antarctica-melt-drink-water/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COLD, BOLD plot to hijack an iceberg and tow it from Antarctica to South Africa could take place this year. “Ice pirate” Nicholas Sloane wants to cart a 125million-ton ‘berg acr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Have Revered Crocodiles of Island Nation Suddenly Started Killing People?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/06/world/asia/east-timor-crocodile-attacks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two scientists traveled to East Timor to help solve a national murder mystery. The culprits, they say, might be migrants from Australia with a taste for blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-Day 75...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/567d5642eef242119ff75aeda3a2371c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA:  I PREFERRED LIFE BEFORE PHONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/05/magazine/madonna-madame-x.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The original queen of pop on aging, inspiration and why she refuses to cede control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico blocks new caravan of Central American migrants... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/caravan-1-200-migrants-enters-mexico-192344686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuxtla Gutiérrez (Mexico) (AFP) - Authorities blocked a new caravan of Central American migrants Wednesday after they entered Mexico bound for the United States, as the government scrambled to dodge President Donald Trump's threat to impose tariffs over undocumented immigration. Soldiers and police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Paso Immigration Center Dangerously Overcrowded...</title>
      <link>https://www.elpasotimes.com/story/news/immigration/2019/05/31/el-paso-migrant-processing-center-overcrowded-dhs-border-patrol-ice/1300160001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.elpasotimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Department of Homeland Security inspection found 900 detainees at the 125-migrant capacity Paso Del Norte International Bridge Processing Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military personnel ordered to paint border barriers?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/447215-us-military-personnel-ordered-to-paint-border-barriers-to-improve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United States military personnel deployed near the U.S.-Mexico border have reportedly been assigned to paint certain barrier structures to strengthen their “aesthetic appearance.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feud over abortion adds to questions about Joe's vulnerabilities... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dem-rivals-rebuke-biden-not-184058345.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is under fire from his Democratic presidential rivals and women's rights advocates for his defense of a decades-old prohibition on federal money paying for abortions. Most Democratic White House hopefuls reflect their party's latest platform calling for the outright repeal of the Hyde</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text messages reveal anguish of underage NXIVM 'sex slave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-cult-text-messages-girl-nxivm-20190605-4e65rjhhzfhppojogkmme47k5u-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twisted texts between Keith Raniere and the underage ‘sex slave’ at the heart of trafficking and conspiracy charges against the NXIVM “cult” leader reveal a level of control prosecutors said he used to keep his conquests in line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Poisonous thorns': The times Abraham Lincoln got really mad at CHICAGO TRIB...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/poisonous-thorns-the-times-abraham-lincoln-got-mad-like-really/article_1594e55a-d0be-5113-a441-e84796e36e61.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Abraham Lincoln was mad. Really mad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN +4 IN TEXAS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/images/polling/tx/tx06052019_tgye56.pdf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  3 Americans die at same Dominican Republic resort just days apart...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/5354804/u-s-tourists-dead-dominican-republic-resort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In all three cases, the cause of death was listed as respiratory failure and pulmonary edema, a condition caused by excess fluid in the lungs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads revoked from Steven Crowder channel...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/6/5/18654196/steven-crowder-demonetized-carlos-maza-youtube-homophobic-language-ads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘A pattern of egregious actions has harmed the broader community,’ a spokesperson said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic number of illegals flood southern border...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/record-number-undocumented-immigrants-flooded-southern-border-may-n1014186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are in a full-blown emergency, and I cannot say this stronger: The system is broken," said acting CBP Commissioner John Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firework display explosion near Roswell airport; Numerous injuries...</title>
      <link>https://www.koat.com/article/firework-display-set-up-results-in-explosion-near-roswell-airport/27758335</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.koat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Mexico State police are reporting a explosion with possible fatalities at the Roswell Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Suit for Stroke Victims Gets FDA Nod...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/small-cap-rewalk-triples-on-fda-nod-for-robotic-suit-for-stroke</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robotic Suit for Stroke Gets FDA Nod, Rocketing ReWalk Stock</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of NYC ice cream trucks seized over ticket scam...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/05/dozens-of-nyc-ice-cream-trucks-seized-over-multimillion-dollar-ticket-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freeze! More than 40 ice-cream trucks were seized by the city in Long Island City Wednesday over a multimillion-dollar ticket-avoidance scam. The trucks, most of which brandish the New York Ice Cre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors On Edge As Man Displays Giant Swastika On Front Yard...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/06/04/neighbors-on-edge-as-el-sobrante-man-displays-giant-swastika-on-front-yard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A community in Contra Costa County is on edge after a man displayed a giant cement swastika on his front yard. He denied it was a swastika, calling it a "Tibetan symbol."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>+12 IN NC...</title>
      <link>https://emersonpolling.reportablenews.com/pr/north-carolina-2020-biden-with-early-lead-on-trump-and-democratic-primary-field</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;emersonpolling.reportablenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON delivering by drones 'in months'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91506a8d547a4c48be3cc7c6e357bc1c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
