<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Swiss ambassador to U.S. assaulted by intruder in DC home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/mar/30/swiss-ambassador-us-assaulted-intruder-dc-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Swiss ambassador to the U.S. was assaulted inside his home, attached to his nation’s embassy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX high-speed rail could be first in line for funding...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/texas-high-speed-rail-could-be-first-in-line-for-funding-from-biden-congress/ar-BB1f9up4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas — The federal government is serious about spending money on high-speed rail, and Texas could be among the first beneficiaries. The recent interest in investing in bullet trains capable of going 200 mph or faster comes at a time when many Texans — after hearing promises about high-speed rail for the past 12 years — are skeptical that such a project will ever come to fruition. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACK IN THE DOG HOUSE:  MAJOR BITES AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/30/politics/major-biden-dog-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bidens' dog Major has been involved in another biting incident that required medical attention, two people with knowledge of the incident tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even as debt soars, Biden faces few spending constraints...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-era-even-debt-100056598.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal debt has swelled to levels rarely seen, but shifts in politics and economic concerns mean Biden has relatively few spending constraints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100 fully vaccinated people contract COVID in Washington state...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/100-fully-vaccinated-people-contract-covid-19-washington/story?id=76784838</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 100 people in Washington state have tested positive for COVID-19 more than two weeks after becoming fully vaccinated against the disease, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'humanzees' to super viruses. China Frankenstein experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14442711/china-dumping-ground-frankenstein-research-pandemic-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has been accused of becoming the global dumping for Frankenstein-style experiments which create hybrid animals and risk unleashing viruses even more deadly than Covid. The warning was made by…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graffiti or homage? Hi-tech imaging sheds light on Holy Sepulchre crosses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-religion-easter-holy-sepulchre-crosse-idUSKBN2BN0YP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crosses etched in mysterious abundance across the walls of Christianity's most sacred church were long assumed to be graffiti, but they may be the work of mediaeval masons paid to carve them by pilgrims, research suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealed: Number of friends needed to be successful...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-9420995/Psychologist-Robin-Dunbar-reveals-exact-number-friends-need-successful.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British anthropologist and 'mathematician of relationships' Robin Dunbar believes we can only maintain a certain number of human connections at any one time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORPORATE HIKE...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/03/31/president-joe-biden-proposes-2-trillion-infrastructure-jobs-plan/4809290001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is comparing President Joe Biden's infrastructure proposal to the construction of interstate highways and the Space Race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looks for infrastructure win where Obama, Trump failed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/31/biden-infrastructure-plan-unveiling-478684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president will unveil a sweeping $2 trillion plan Wednesday focused on clean infrastructure and creating millions of jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buildup of forces near Ukraine border 'concerning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-troops-ukraine-border-concerning-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian troops have been assembling near the border with Ukraine as tension rises almost 7 years after Russia's annexation of Crimea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Trust in tech craters...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/edelman-trust-barometer-tech-5787acea-8ef5-4d0b-9694-6e4f8eb006c4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Edelman Trust Barometer surveyed 31,000 people in 27 countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naval Officer Busted Selling NATO Secrets to Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italian-navy-officer-nabbed-while-095633065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Max Rossi via Reuters ROME—Italian secret service agents backed by Carabinieri military police swooped in on a clandestine meeting in a Roman parking garage early Wednesday morning just as an Italian navy officer was handing a secret dossier of Italian state secrets and classified NATO documents to a Russian spy who had a reportedly paltry sum of €5,000 ($5,863) in cash ready to swap for the documents.Top NATO Scientist With Security Clearance Busted Spying for ChinaThe Italian, who was the captain of a navy frigate, was taken into custody on charges of espionage and endangering state security. The Russian, who has diplomatic status, was released to the Russian embassy in Rome and will be expelled from the country. On Tuesday, Italy’s foreign ministry summoned Russian ambassador Sergey Razov to get to the bottom of the matter. The foreign minister’s office later announced that Italy had expelled two Russian diplomats tied to the arrest, but did not elaborate who the second Russian was or what role he or she may have played. The Russian embassy in Rome confirmed the events and released a short statement, saying it was “verifying” details, and hoped the inconvenient series of events would not compromise relations between the two nations. “For now, we consider it inappropriate to comment on what happened,” the statement said. “In any event, we hope that what happened is not reflected on the bilateral relationship between Russia and Italy.”Russian president Vladimir Putin’s obsession with the destruction of NATO, which was to a large extent backed by former President Donald Trump, is not yet confirmed as the motive behind the sale of these documents. There are six NATO bases in Italy, all joint operations with the U.S. and Italian military. It is yet unknown which of those bases the alleged Italian spy worked on.NATO officials did not immediately return requests for information, but this is the second event involving classified NATO documents in recent weeks. In mid March, an Estonian researcher with NATO clearance was arrested for spying for China. Top NATO Scientist With Security Clearance Busted Spying for ChinaThe two had been under surveillance for more than two months in an investigation led by Italian secret service chief Mario Parente. They were arrested as they passed the dossier for a wad of cash, according to local media based on unnamed sources. Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy metal star takes on Poland's anti-blasphemy law...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/heavy-metal-star-takes-polands-095752575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his Warsaw apartment decorated with occult imagery, heavy metal star Adam Darski from the band Behemoth told AFP he has had enough of being prosecuted under Poland's anti-blasphemy law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Military Preparing for U.S. Intervention in Taiwan Strait...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/chinas-military-preparing-us-intervention-taiwan-strait-1579788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts in Beijing and Taipei said the Chinese military's pincer movement around Taiwan on Monday was the PLA's way of showing it could isolate the island in the event of a conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron under pressure to lock down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/31/europe/france-macron-lockdown-coronavirus-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron is expected to tighten coronavirus restrictions on Wednesday as case numbers and admissions to intensive care units soar across France, where the government has been resisting a third nationwide lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Empty Amsterdam, Reconsidering Tourism...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/31/in-empty-amsterdam-reconsidering-tourism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When international travel came to a halt last year, Amsterdam — like cities everywhere — was drained of tourists almost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brisk Walking Good for Aging Brain...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/31/brisk-walking-is-good-for-the-aging-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brisk walking improves brain health and thinking in aging people with memory impairments, according to a new, yearlong study of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD: MILLION MIGRANTS COULD CROSS BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-border/more-than-a-million-migrants-expected-at-us-mexico-border-this-year-us-official-idUSKBN2BM3FN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top U.S. border official said on Tuesday he expects more than a million migrants will arrive at the U.S.-Mexico border this year, a sign of a growing humanitarian challenge for President Joe Biden on the southwest border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden $2.25 Trillion Investment Plan to Rival Space Race... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/biden-to-lay-out-us-economic-renewal-in-rejuvenated-pittsburgh/ar-BB1f8zAk </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's First' Animal Jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2021/03/31/worlds-first-animal-covid-19-vaccine-registered-in-russia--heres-what-that-means/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of mink were culled due to widespread outbreaks of Covid-19, sparking fears for the future of the fur industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's girlfriend 'ready to die on Mars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/elon-musks-girlfriend-ready-die-23826057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Elon Musk's girlfriend Grimes, whose real name is Claire Elise Boucher and is a Canadian musician, has said on Instagram that she is willing to die on the red planet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER says shot 100% effective in kids 12 to 15...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/31/covid-vaccine-pfizer-says-shot-is-100percent-effective-in-kids-ages-12-to-15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer plans to submit the new vaccine data to the FDA "as soon as possible," CEO Albert Bourla said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle rages over 'passports'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/545670-battle-rages-over-vaccine-passports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are up in arms over the possibility that businesses and local governments may require vaccine passports for people to get access to certain activities, buildings or events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 3 GEORGE FLOYD CASE: Firefighter blocked from helping returns to stand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trials-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-minneapolis-us-news-00cfa62f9b1c12076316845c100d6b97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A Minneapolis firefighter who voiced frustration at being prevented from using her EMT training to help George Floyd will be back on the stand Wednesday in the trial of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G GORDON LIDDY DEAD AT 90...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/g-gordon-liddy-undercover-operative-convicted-in-watergate-scandal-dies-at-90/ar-BB1f8CKT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His can-do ruthlessness, loyalty to Nixon and ends-justify-the-means philosophy made him a natural fit in a White House determined to get even with its political enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgue workers accused of stealing from the dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/2-medical-examiners-accused-of-stealing-thousands-of-dollars-from-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two mortuary technicians in the New York City medical examiner’s office are accused of using credit and debit cards belonging to the dead to steal thousands of dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor's wife plotted his murder amid love triangle, authorities say...</title>
      <link>https://kfor.com/news/local/court-documents-giving-further-details-into-alleged-love-triangle-involving-murdered-ada-pastor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kfor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two arrests were made in the murder of Ada pastor David Evans. The Oklahoma State Bureau of Investigation tells KFOR his wife, Kristie Evans, was arrested Wednesday after confessing to his murder a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE WAS 17?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9420481/Rep-Matt-Gaetz-investigation-sex-trafficking-teenage-girl-17.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican congressman fired out a series of tweets Tuesday claiming a former DOJ employee was trying to extort $25 million from him and slamming the allegations as 'lies.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Actor Shares Homophobic DMs from NBA Superstar Kevin Durant...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2938918-michael-rapaport-shares-homophobic-misogynistic-dms-from-kevin-durant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Michael Rapaport posted screenshots Tuesday of a conversation between himself and Kevin Durant , in which the Brooklyn Nets star used homophobic, misogynistic and profane ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA COVID NUMBERS GET NEW SCRUTINY; RESEARCH FINDS 5,000 MORE DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-covid-numbers-face-new-scrutiny-090058319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research published earlier this month in the American Journal of Public Health argues that Florida is undercounting the number of people who have died from COVID-19 by thousands of cases, casting new doubt on claims that Gov. Ron DeSantis navigated the pandemic successfully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skin 'peeled off' in rare reaction to JOHNSON &amp; JOHNSON...</title>
      <link>https://www.wric.com/news/local-news/goochland-county-man-suffers-rare-severe-reaction-to-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wric.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC IMAGES Richard Terrell was released from the hospital and is now sharing his vaccination story as he recovers. He tells 8News that he’s still very weak and that it will take …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People's Expensive NFTs Keep Vanishing...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkdj79/peoples-expensive-nfts-keep-vanishing-this-is-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There was no history of my ever purchasing it, or ever owning it,” said one confused NFT buyer. “Now there’s nothing. My money’s gone.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINUTES' TOP SHOW IN PRIMETIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.viacomcbspressexpress.com/cbs-news/releases/view?id=57259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.viacomcbspressexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50%  in UK now have antibodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/30/about-50-of-people-in-uk-have-antibodies-against-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study by Office for National Statistics based on data from blood test results across four nations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidency is over. So are many relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/03/trump-friend-family-relationships/618457/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden wants the country to heal from its political divisions. But some people say they aren’t ready to reconnect with their estranged friends and family members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake's mansion stormed by knife-wielding woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/2610995/drake-toronto-home-stormed-knife-wielding-woman-arrested-striking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAKE’S Toronto mansion was stormed by a knife-wielding woman who allegedly “struck a security guard with a pipe.”  Law enforcement confirmed to The Sun that an adult female who was carrying a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which world leader has worst pandemic record? Competition is fierce...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/Which-world-leader-has-the-worst-pandemic-record-16064411.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A catastrophic pandemic and a calamitous presidency combined to give the United States...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents of 5 killed by falling redwood...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/Jessica-Jake-Woodruff-falling-redwood-death-199-16061157.php?IPID=SFGate-HP-CP-Spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials called it a very unusual tragic accident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  17% SAY WAS 'GREAT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2021/03/29/a-partisan-chasm-in-views-of-trumps-legacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans and Democrats offer starkly different assessments of Donald Trump’s presidential legacy, a new survey finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather Service internet systems crumbling as key platforms are taxed and fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Weather-Service-internet-systems-crumbling-as-key-16064001.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service experienced a major, systemwide internet failure Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite NYC Hospital Charges $3,358 for Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/it-felt-like-deception-an-elite-nyc-hospital-charges-huge-covid-test-fees/ar-BB1f83i0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lenox Hill Hospital in Manhattan advertised its “Covid-19 Testing” on a large blue and white banner outside its Greenwich Village division’s emergency room. The banner said nothing about cost. But cost turned out to be the testing’s most noteworthy feature. Lenox Hill, one of the city’s oldest and best-known hospitals, repeatedly billed patients more than $3,000 for the routine nasal swab test, about 30 times the test’s typical cost. “It was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Epstein forced real estate broker to have sex with judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-lawsuit-names-jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-and-alleges-actions-sinister-even-by-his-standards/ar-BB1f8u9x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — In early 2008, as financier Jeffrey Epstein’s lawyers were waging what would become a successful campaign to get the Justice Department to drop its sex trafficking case against their client, Epstein and his purported madam, Ghislaine Maxwell, were allegedly raping a 26-year-old South Florida real estate broker who claims in a lawsuit filed last week that Epstein trafficked her to other ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers giving in-person instruction to migrant kids -- but not own students?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/psaki-migrant-kids-teachers-in-person-instruction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: White House press secretary Jen Psaki on Tuesday was grilled about San Diego public school teachers volunteering to teach migrant children in-person before returning to the classroom to teach the students in their own district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO scrambles jets 10 times to track Russian military planes across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/30/politics/nato-russia-jets/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO scrambled fighter jets 10 times Monday to track and intercept an unusually "rare peak" of Russian bombers and fighters flying over the North Sea, Black Sea and Baltic Sea, according to a NATO official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 Senate Dems urge recurring stimulus checks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/30/stimulus-check-update-senators-push-biden-to-send-recurring-payments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden is set to unveil his infrastructure and recovery plan, and some Democrats want it to include emergency economic aid like stimulus payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil rocked by political turmoil as pandemic outlook darkens...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Brazil-is-rocked-by-political-turmoil-as-pandemic-16064821.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO - Six cabinet members are out. The military's top leaders are also gone....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police bust 'world's biggest' video-game-cheat operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56579449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese police seize a collection of luxury sports cars in the raid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOUSEWIVES' star busted for alleged fraud, money laundering...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/03/30/real-housewives-star-jen-shah-busted-for-alleged-fraud-money-laundering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embattled “Real Housewives of Salt Lake City” cast member Jen Shah was arrested by the feds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands held in cramped Texas tent facility...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/30/more-than-4000-migrants-many-children-packed-in-texas-facility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US government’s main border detention facility for migrant children is an overcrowded tent structure currently packed with more than 4,000 people, despite a 250 person capacity, it was re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$4 TRILLION spending plan...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/30/biden-to-announce-up-to-4-trillion-infrastructure-plan-with-tax-hike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will outline his massive $3 to 4 trillion infrastructure plan Wednesday, which will create four tax increases worth around $1.8 trillion, the White House revealed. Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Company's Bid to Buy Military Tech Firm Raises National Security Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://insidesources.com/singapore-companys-bid-to-buy-military-tech-firm-raises-national-security-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;insidesources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A buyout bid from a Singapore-based aerospace and defense company for Cubic Corp. of San Diego is the latest flashpoint in a fundamental debate about the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAETZ IN SEX PROBE</title>
      <link>https://axios.com/matt-gaetz-sexual-misconduct-investigation-2755fd4f-f72e-4283-b8ac-9233c952b914.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The allegations against me are as searing as they are false," Gaetz said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big tech, Nevada repair shops clash over 'right to repair'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/legislature-nevada-coronavirus-pandemic-cd337d1335c7f27aea8f5a82e94bead3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARSON CITY, Nev. (AP) — Trade groups representing big tech companies faced off with independent repair shop owners Monday during a committee hearing in the Nevada Legislature over a proposal that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON vote may spark more union pushes... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-amazoncom-inc-alabama-health-coronavirus-pandemic-747ea42198655bfbca000c2e0665c3ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happens inside a warehouse in Bessemer, Alabama, could have major implications not just for the country's second-largest employer but the labor movement at large. Organizers are pushing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heir to O? Drew Barrymore launches lifestyle mag...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2021/mar/30/drew-barrymore-launches-quarterly-us-lifestyle-magazine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor and talkshow host will also pen an agony aunt column for Drew, to be published by Bauer Media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARPA Developing Giant Flying Aircraft Carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2606638/usa-darpa-flying-aircraft-carrier-nick-fury-avengers-ship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON is planning to change the face of warfare with the development of flying aircraft carriers. The experimental planes would take the form of a mothership that deploys drones instead of f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to restore Jewish names to phonetic alphabet...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/germany-to-restore-jewish-names-to-phonetic-alphabet-663581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA double-charged some customers for new cars, leaving them desperate for refunds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/29/tesla-double-charged-some-customers-for-new-cars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla double-charged some customers for new cars. Now those customers are trying to get refunds for the added charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey reimposes restrictions after sharp rise in infections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/turkey-coronavirus-pandemic-recep-tayyip-erdogan-ankara-europe-22adbf45d3773d1e84f05788ec73dae5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Turkey is re-introducing weekend lockdowns in most of its provinces and will also impose restrictions over the Muslim holy month of Ramadan following a sharp increase in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 2  George Floyd case: 'I witnessed a murder'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/derek-chauvin-trial-latest-updates-bba19d0f75c2cd71c135eed69f5e8200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A man who was among the onlookers shouting at a Minneapolis police officer to get off George Floyd last May testified Tuesday that he called 911 after paramedics took Floyd...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUIR'S 'WORLD NEWS' #1 ACROSS ALL BROADCAST AND CABLE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/647095514870988800/for-first-time-in-25-years-world-news-tonight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAST WEEK MARKS ONE YEAR STRAIGHT WITH ‘WORLD NEWS TONIGHT’ WINNING IN TOTAL VIEWERS, ADULTS 25-54 AND ADULTS 18-49 ‘World News Tonight’ Is Delivering Largest Season Viewership in 16 Years 1st Quarter...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
