<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: COVID In Penile Tissue, May Lead To Erectile Dysfunction...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/virility-the-virus-covid-found-in-penile-tissue-may-even-lead-to-erectile-dysfunction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have, for the first time ever, discovered traces of COVID-19 within penile tissue. They say it may even lead to erectile dysfunction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-liner Ahmadinejad again seeks to be Iran president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-2b0497dfd2773eaa39c719cc91d10bbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's former hard-line President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad registered Wednesday to run again for the Islamic Republic's presidency, raising the possibility that the populist leader who rapidly advanced Tehran's nuclear program to challenge the West could return to the country's top civilian post...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS TOPS $3/GALLON</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/national-average-for-gasoline-tops-3-a-gallon-amid-pipeline-shutdown-rush-to-buy-in-southeast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colonial Pipeline is expected to make a full restart decision by the end of the day on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION SURGES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/consumer-price-index-april-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAKE: No greater offense than honesty in today's GOP...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/553034-flake-no-greater-offense-than-honesty-in-todays-republican-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Sen. Jeff Flake (R-Ariz.) is calling out GOP lawmakers for their plan to oust Rep. Liz Cheney (R-Wy.) from the party’s leadership in the House, arguing that “today there is no greater offense than honesty” among Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Republicans threaten to form new party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/553037-dozens-of-influential-republicans-threaten-to-form-new-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of Republicans are planning to call for reforms amid escalating divisions within their party, and threaten to form a separate group if GOP members do not break away from former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami appoints chief heat officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/facing-rising-temperatures-miami-appoints-chief-heat-officer/ar-BB1gDUd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Gilbert, the city’s new chief heat officer, says she will put together a task force of experts to address the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLONIAL Faces Deadline to Decide on Hacked Pipeline Restart...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gas-stations-run-dry-pipeline-100859225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Colonial Pipeline Co. told federal officials it will know by late Wednesday whether it’s safe to restart gasoline and diesel flows that have been on hold since criminal hackers targeted the company last week.The promise comes as frustration grows among political leaders over scant details about when the biggest North American fuel pipeline will recover, while fuel shortages spread rapidly across the South and East. U.S. Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm said that even if Colonial can restart on Wednesday, it’ll take days longer to “ramp up operations.” With a full restoration of the pipeline system potentially taking weeks, U.S. retail gasoline jumped to the politically sensitive level of $3 a gallon for the first time in six years.Facing increasing pressure, the White House announced several measures Tuesday to blunt the growing crisis that threatens to hobble the post-pandemic economic recovery. The Biden administration will give a House briefing on the cyberattack at 6 p.m. Washington time on Wednesday.“This is something that demands really serious federal attention,” Florida Governor Ron DeSantis said on Tuesday, prior to declaring a state of emergency. “The U.S. government needs to be involved, they need to help mitigate this. My fear is, you have these gas shortages, it’s going to cause a lot of problems for people.”The Colonial pipeline is the most important conduit for distributing gasoline, diesel and jet fuel in the U.S., connecting Gulf Coast refineries to population centers from Atlanta to New York and beyond. Each day, it ships about 2.5 million barrels (105 million gallons), an amount that exceeds the entire oil consumption of Germany.The national average retail gasoline price rose to $3.008 a gallon, the first time it’s exceeded $3 since October 2014, according to auto club AAA data on Wednesday. The premium for wholesale gasoline in the New York area reached its widest in three months.The vital economic lifeline has been shut since late Friday, prompting a run on filling stations by panicked motorists in several states. In addition to Florida, Virginia and North Carolina are under states of emergency. U.S. average retail gasoline prices have risen to their highest since late 2014 due to the disruption, almost touching $3 a gallon. That could add to broader inflationary pressures as commodity prices from timber to copper also surge.The situation across the southeastern states is “rapidly deteriorating,” Brad Jenkins, a senior vice president at truck-stop owner Pilot, said in an email.The White House relaxed some environmental rules across 12 states and Washington D.C. to help bring in more fuel, even as some Gulf Coast refiners were forced to curtail output to cope with logjams of fuel they can’t send to eastern markets. The Department of Transportation also announced initial steps that could permit foreign tankers to transport gasoline and diesel to East Coast ports.The Wednesday deadline on a decision over the pipeline’s restart was given by Colonial Chief Executive Officer Joe Blount to Granholm. The energy secretary said she’s been in regular contact with the CEO in recent days to track the company’s progress in neutralizing the ransomware attack.“By the end of business tomorrow, Colonial will be in a position to make the full restart decision,” she said.“We have been providing daily and sometimes twice daily updates to our shippers, and have been in close contact with law enforcement and federal agencies to relay information on our restoration efforts,” Colonial’s media relations office said earlier in the day. “We will continue to keep all of our stakeholders informed and appreciate the outpouring of support we have received throughout the industry.”Even when the pipeline is restored to full service, however, it’ll take about two weeks for gasoline stored in Houston to reach East Coast filling stations, according to the most recent schedule sent to shippers. For diesel and jet fuel, the transit time is even longer -- about 19 days -- because they are heavier and move more slowly.More than four days into the crisis, Colonial has only managed to restart a small segment of the pipeline as a stopgap measure. Meanwhile, fuel shortages continued to worsen. In Atlanta, 20% of filling stations were dry by Tuesday afternoon, according to retail-fuel tracker GasBuddy.Two of the nation’s largest truck-stop owners --- Love’s Travel Stops &amp; Country Stores Inc. and TravelCenters of America Inc. -- confirmed that fuel is scarce is some states. Both companies said they’re taking extraordinary measures to replenish tanks.The Biden administration issued an order on Sunday extending the amount of time truck drivers can spend behind the wheel when transporting fuel across 17 states and the District of Columbia. On Tuesday evening, the Transportation Department said 10 states could allow heavier-than-normal truck loads of gasoline and other fuels.Federal transportation regulators also took the first step toward waiving the 101-year-old Jones Act that prohibits foreign-flagged and -staffed ships from hauling products from one U.S. port to another. Fuel traders have so far redirected at least one international cargo of gasoline, and another of diesel, toward the U.S. East Coast, according to shipping data compiled by Bloomberg.Gasoline isn’t the only oil-derived product under threat. In an effort to bolster jet-fuel inventories, Southwest Airlines Co. has begun flying supplies to Nashville, Tennessee, and other cities. So far, no Southwest flights have been affected by the pipeline closure; rather, the airline said it’s “actively managing” fuel stockpiles.United Airlines Holdings Inc. loaded extra fuel on flights to preserve local supplies in places like Baltimore and Greenville-Spartanburg, South Carolina. Problems are “relatively minor so far,” however, Chief Executive Officer Scott Kirby said at the Resources for the Future Forum.What BloombergNEF Is SayingBloombergNEF expects additional supply this week to come primarily from storage inventories, increased East Coast refinery run, other pipelines and shipments from Canada. Cargoes from Europe could also help alleviate lingering shortages next week.-- Anastacia Dialynas, BNEF analystRead the full report here.The Environmental Protection Agency moved to allow the sale of gasoline that doesn’t satisfy requirements meant to help combat smog in certain areas. An initial order allowed the sale of conventional gasoline in areas where reformulated gasoline is required across Maryland, Pennsylvania, Virginia and the District of Columbia. A second order went further by waiving low-volatility requirements governing conventional and reformulated gasoline in those areas, as well as nine other states.Emergency shipments of gasoline and diesel from Texas are already on the way to Atlanta and other southeastern cities via trucks, and at least two Gulf Coast refineries began trimming output amid expectations that supplies will begin backing up in the nation’s oil-refining nexus.(Updates with vessel diversions in 17th paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Used Male Doll in Joke. Now Accused of Sexual Harassment...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/12/she-used-a-male-doll-in-a-joke-now-shes-accused-of-sexual-harassment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Park Na-rae, a comedian, grabbed a male doll, placed its plastic arm between its legs and made a suggestive remark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man and Woman Brawl Over Line-Cutting at Packed Gas Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/man-and-woman-brawl-over-line-cutting-at-packed-north-carolina-gas-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pipeline shutdown in the Southeast has caused long lines at the pump—and even a physical fight over line etiquette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Untold Story of NFT Boom...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/12/the-untold-story-of-the-nft-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. “It’s at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Reversal, Retirements Increased During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/12/in-reversal-retirements-increased-during-the-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After decades in which it decreased, the retirement rate rose during the pandemic, according to the latest government data. This</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Exercise May Help Us Flourish...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/12/how-exercise-may-help-us-flourish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our exercise habits may influence our sense of purpose in life and our sense of purpose may affect how much</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embraces Downfall in Defiant Speech...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/12/cheney-embraces-her-downfall-warning-g-o-p-of-trump-in-a-fiery-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In the hours before facing a vote that will almost certainly purge her from House Republican leadership, Representative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecaped leopard eluding captors. Hundreds of drones sent to find...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-escaped-leopard-is-eluding-its-would-be-captors-in-china-now-officials-are-deploying-hundreds-of-drones-to-find-it/ar-BB1gDIOk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the three big cats that escaped from a safari park in April have been recaptured, but one remains on the loose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opposition to recall grows as Jenner, Republicans generate little support...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/opposition-to-newsom-recall-grows-as-jenner-gop-generate-little-support-poll-finds/ar-BB1gBEvi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic voters polled by the UC Berkeley Institute of Governmental Studies also overwhelmingly favored having a prominent Democratic replacement candidate on the recall ballot in case Newsom is ousted from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Basquiat Painting Sells for $93.1 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/a-basquiat-painting-just-sold-for-24931-million-at-christie-e2-80-99s/ar-BB1gCOGW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 1983 piece, titled “In This Case,” smashed its estimate of $50 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's fattest island becomes first to jab 100% of adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-fattest-island-becomes-first-24090659</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Due to a statistical quirk Nauru, north-east of Australia, has technically given 108% of the adult population the coronavirus vaccine, because its most recent census hasn't caught up with the actual population level</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinated Comparing Adverse Reactions on REDDIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/vaccinated-people-are-comparing-adverse-reactions-in-a-reddit-subgroup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaxxed Reddit users are networking with other vaccine-damaged individuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28-year-old posed as student to sneak into high school. Her goal: INSTAGRAM follows...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-28-year-old-posed-as-a-student-to-sneak-into-16170558.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a backpack slung over her shoulders, a painting under one arm and a skateboard under...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds in Orange County protest passports: 'Not going to brand us'...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/hundreds-in-orange-county-protest-covid-19-vaccine-passports-you-re-not-going-to-brand/article_670a09e6-3d07-524c-8ded-bc1f15d2659e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA ANA, Calif. — On the same day that Orange County recorded some of its most positive coronavirus statistics to date — nearing the least restrictive yellow tier in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snow has fallen in Mile High City 9 straight months, spanning 245 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Snow-has-fallen-in-the-Mile-High-City-in-9-16168729.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seemingly endless snow season has befallen Denver, where flakes first flew in early...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden works to present calm contrast to turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Biden-works-to-present-calm-contrast-to-GOP-16170582.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is seizing on this week's dramatic moment of Republican discord by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000+ ROCKETS HIT ISRAEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/four-dead-from-latest-wave-of-rockets-aimed-at-central-israel-667902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Israelis were killed overnight in rocket barrages, bringing the death toll in Israel to five.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riots shake Jewish-Arab city...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/border-police-officers-diverted-to-lod-amid-violent-protests-667894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu: "If this isn't an emergency situation, I don't know what is. We're talking about life and death here" • Arab man shot dead during riots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OF 'FULL-SCALE WAR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9569675/Israel-heading-scale-WAR-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barrages levelled tower blocks in Gaza last night as the death toll rose to 43 Palestinians, including 13 children and three women, health officials in the territory said. Another 233 people were wounded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATES DECLARE EMERGENCY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9568339/Virginia-declares-state-emergency-Atlanta-gas-pumps-run-amid-Colonial-Pipeline-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst shortages were in North Carolina, where 9.7% of all stations were without fuel, according to Gas Buddy Tracker. Virginia was second hardest-hit, followed by Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGET TEL AVIV...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-57066275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Militants attack the Israeli city after an air strike brings down a tower block in Gaza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney set to be ousted from Republican leadership...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-liz-cheney-house-elections-election-2020-government-and-politics-db885d0a6b28f12d733da54dbae617fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Republicans seem ready to toss Rep. Liz Cheney from her leadership post after she repeatedly rebuked former President Donald Trump for his false claims of election fraud and his role in fomenting the Jan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China offers digital yuan as alternative...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/china-digital-yuan-bring-surveillance-state-at-expense-of-us-dollar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's emerging digital currency could enhance the yuan’s importance in the international financial system at the expense of the U.S. dollar and extend the Chinese surveillance state into wallets around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Biden billboard angers locals who are demanding removal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/anti-biden-sign-maryland-angers-locals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pro-Trump sign in Maryland is causing a stir in the community due to its graphic language and has some calling for its removal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military AI can detect sarcasm on socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2020/05/how-ai-will-soon-change-special-operations/165487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new SOCOM office is pursuing tools to understand and influence populations, clear rooms with robots, and spot new forms of jamming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major rioting and chaos erupt...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-may-11-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergency declared in city, Border Police forces rushed in as synagogues, stores burned by Arab mobs; PM: terror groups will pay after unprecedented rocket fire on central Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dosed YANKEES Coach Tests Positive, Others Pending...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/yankees-dealing-with-covid-issues-on-coaching-staff-but-expect-to-play-series-opener-vs-rays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team announced third-base coach Phil Nevin tested positive on Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE OF EMERGENCY IN VA</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/virginia-gov-ralph-northam-issues-state-of-emergency-to-address-gasoline-supply-disruptions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Governor Ralph Northam has signed an executive order declaring a state of emergency in the state to address gasoline supply disruptions throughout the Commonwealth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000+ GAS STATIONS RUN OUT OF FUEL</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-stations-run-out-of-fuel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 gas stations in the Southeast reported running out of fuel, primarily because of what analysts say is unwarranted panic-buying among drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University president caught plagiarizing speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.fitsnews.com/2021/05/11/usc-president-resigned-after-plagiarized-speech-scandal-but-board-didnt-accept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fitsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debacle at USC deepens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD GET WORSE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/11/colonial-spot-gas-shortages-may-worsen-if-pipeline-doesnt-reopen-soon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the Colonial Pipeline is not back in business by the weekend, prices could continue to rise at the pump and there will be broader localized fuel shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Man killed 6, self at Colorado party after not being invited...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/colorado-shootings-e66fa3c58eaff7671e6ba4d691f32a80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLORADO SPRINGS, Colo. (AP) — A gunman who killed six people at a Colorado birthday party held by his girlfriend's family over the weekend opened fire because he had not been invited and then killed himself, police said Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE HIT</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-energy-pipeline-hit-gaza-rocket-attack-israels-channel-12-tv-2021-05-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pipeline belonging to an Israeli state-owned energy company was hit in a rocket attack from Gaza late on Tuesday, an Israeli government official and an energy sector official told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New book portrays Secret Service riven by scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-book-portrays-a-secret-service-riven-by-scandal-and-growing-pains/ar-BB1gCogj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Zero Fail’ depicts missteps, successes and evolution of the agency tasked with protecting the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD GET WORSE...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comould worse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comould worse&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses NRA bankruptcy in victory for New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-bankruptcy-judge-rejects-nra-bid-reorganize-texas-2021-05-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association cannot use bankruptcy to reorganize in gun-friendly Texas, a federal judge in Dallas ruled on Tuesday, handing a defeat to the influential firearms rights group that is facing an effort to dissolve it in New York state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL RACE PREAKNESS...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/05/11/medina-spirit-permitted-to-enter-preakness-maryland-jockey-club-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a failed drug test after the Kentucky Derby, Medina Spirit will be able to run the Preakness in Baltimore Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Morrison's fall from eccentric genius to conspiracy theorist...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/happened-van-morrison-fall-eccentric-215325922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On his new album, 'Latest Record Project, Vol. 1,' Van Morrison shocked fans by espousing an array of conspiracy theories. The seeds were always there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 3 More Cars Report Windows Blown Out On SoCal Freeways...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/10/car-windows-shot-out-in-riverside-county-as-flurry-of-southland-freeway-shootings-continue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They're the latest in a series of such shootings which have taken place on multiple Southland freeways over the past several weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inheritance tax poised for comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.crainsnewyork.com/politics/inheritance-tax-poised-comeback-post-covid-era</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.crainsnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis company growing weed in Colombia goes public in US...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/11/investing/flora-growth-cannabis-ipo/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most cannabis companies that list their stocks in the United States grow their products in indoor greenhouses, often in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN GURION AIRPORT CLOSED</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/israel-hamas-launches-rocket-attack-on-tel-aviv-12303773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terrorist group said it had fired 130 rockets towards Tel Aviv and its suburbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland A's to start looking at relocating elsewhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/31427293/oakland-athletics-start-looking-relocating-elsewhere-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The A's, who have played in Oakland since 1968, will look into relocating elsewhere, sources told ESPN, after years of failed plans for a new stadium. The team has asked the city council to vote on a new site prior to its late-July recess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts say CDC exaggerating outdoor transmission rate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/11/cdc-exaggerates-outdoor-transmission-rate-covid-19-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At issue is the research cited by the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention in touting its outdoor transmission statistic, which put the figure at a murky and allegedly too high “less …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoarding fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.starnewsonline.com/story/news/2021/05/11/colonial-pipeline-shutdown-lead-gas-lines-shortages-wilmington/5036048001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.starnewsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Leland, the Citgo station had a long line early Tuesday, and the Scotchman on River Road in Belville was already out of gas by 10 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gang begins leaking DC police data...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/babuk-ransomware-dc-police-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of cybercriminals leaked internal files after Washington, D.C.'s police department was targeted with ransomware last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Baffert admits betamethasone ointment on Medina Spirit...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/sports/horses/horse-racing/2021/05/11/bob-baffert-says-ointment-used-medina-spirit-includes-betamethasone/5019077001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trainer Bob Baffert says Otomax could be the source of the drug that has put Medina Spirit's victory in Kentucky Derby in jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario to give mixed doses due to ASTRAZENECA shortage...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/ontario-likely-to-mix-1st-and-2nd-vaccine-doses-amid-lack-of-astrazeneca-supply</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES forced to add stops on long flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2866153/american-airlines-long-haul-flights-colonial-pipeline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN Airlines is adding extra stops to two long-haul flights so planes can refuel as a result of the cyberattack on the Colonial Pipeline.  The airline was forced to alter the schedule …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's president rallying base -- so he can expand his power...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-president-is-rallying-his-base-e2-80-94-so-that-he-can-expand-his-power/ar-BB1gBnJl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our research finds that voters may encourage democratically elected leaders to undermine democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Denies Involvement in Pipeline Hacking...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-05-11/russia-denies-involvement-in-darkside-attack-on-colonial-pipeline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials believe Russian cybercriminals were behind a ransomware attack that shut down a major artery of America’s fuel supply, portending similar attacks on U.S. infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's blog isn't lighting up internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/trumps-blog-isnt-lighting-internet-rcna890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president’s blog has drawn a considerably smaller audience than his once-powerful social media accounts, according to engagement data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci Battles With Rand Paul...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/you-are-entirely-and-completely-incorrect-watch-faucis-epic-throwdown-with-rand-paul-on-wuhan-lab-covid-theory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci and Senator Rand Paul engaged in an epic battle over the origins of the deadly Covid-19 contagion that has thus far led to the deaths of almost 600,000 Americans. There are two competing theories of its origins: one is that it emanated from wet markets in Wuhan, China that sold civets, which […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gang threatens release of DC police records...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ransomware-gang-threatens-release-of-washington-dc-police-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian-speaking ransomware syndicate that stole data from the Washington, D.C., police department says negotiations over payment have broken down and it will release sensitive information that could put lives at risk if more money is not offered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUCKENMILLER:  Fed endangering dollar's reserve status with endless pumping...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/11/stanley-druckenmiller-says-the-fed-is-endangering-the-dollars-global-reserve-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed policies could end up threatening the long-term health of the U.S. dollar, investing magnate Stanley Druckenmiller told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Didn't Even Vote In 2020...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/05/11/caitlyn-jenner-cnn-interview-trump-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner is attempting to defy ideological definition as she runs to unseat Gov. Gavin Newsom in California's all-but-certain recall election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS QUEEN:  WASH POST names Buzbee executive editor!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ks-state-wire-sally-buzbee-donald-trump-middle-east-health-1ee82d121623381c1afad6306d892744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sally Buzbee, senior vice president and executive editor of The Associated Press, was named Tuesday as executive editor of The Washington Post, succeeding the recently retired Marty Baron...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot customers demand 'angel' model with wings...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-customers-demand-angel-24085045</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RealDoll teased its followers with a picture of a female mannequin with wings and a halo. The company produces a range of sex robots, some of which have incredible capabilites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average daily U.S. Covid cases fall below 40,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/11/covid-19-cases-deaths-vaccinations-daily-update.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rate of average new Covid cases in the U.S. fell to 38,800 per day Monday, the first time daily case counts have been below 40,000 since September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Feeling Younger Slows Aging, Protects Against Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/feel-younger-protects-stress-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adults with a youthful outlook displayed stronger cognitive abilities, less inflammation, and even lived longer compared to adults who "feel old."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST names Sally Buzbee executive editor; First woman to lead newsroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/washington-post-executive-editor-c3e7a229-b2ec-44ad-9cc7-5ed09e00bf21.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She will be the first woman to lead the newsroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Home Prices Surge Most on Record in Buying Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-home-prices-surge-most-141744748.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The median price for a single-family home in the U.S. rose the most on record in the first quarter, as buyers fought over a dearth of inventory, according to the National Association of Realtors.Prices jumped 16.2% from a year earlier to a record high of $319,200. The growth eclipsed the 14.8% rate in the fourth quarter, which was the highest in data going back to 1989, the group said in a report Tuesday.Americans are taking advantage of low mortgage rates to buy homes in the suburbs and in less-costly cities across the country, where supplies are tight and bidding wars are common.“The record-high home prices are happening across nearly all markets, big and small, even in those metros that have long been considered off-the-radar in prior years for many home-seekers,” said Lawrence Yun, the group’s chief economist.The metropolitan area with the largest increase from a year earlier was Kingston, New York, a picturesque Hudson Valley town about 90 miles (145 kilometers) north of Manhattan. Prices there soared 35.5%. Fairfield County, Connecticut -- home to Greenwich -- followed, with 34.3%.Of the 183 metro areas measured by the group, 163 had double-digit price gains, up from 161 in the fourth quarter. Springfield, Illinois, was the only area where prices fell.(Updates with Fairfield County price gain in fifth paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST names Sally Buzbee executive editor; First woman to lead newsroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/media/sally-buzbee-washington-post-editor/2021/05/11/63491212-b25d-11eb-ab43-bebddc5a0f65_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longtime journalist has led the news service since 2017, serving as Washington bureau chief before that. She succeeds Martin Baron, who retired in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAIN IMPLANT MADE MICE IMMEDIATELY BECOME FRIENDS...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/brain-implant-mice-friends</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We didn't actually think this would work."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
