<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pence's Motorcade Involved In Crash With Dump Truck...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/07/30/vice-president-mike-pence-bus-crash-greensburg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists in VP Pence's motorcade are reporting separate accidents with a minor crash involving a bus in the motorcade, and later, an accident involving two motorbike escorts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami-Dade ICUs Hit 146% Capacity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-dade-ic-us-at-146-percent-capacity-with-coronavirus-patients-151222876.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals in the Miami area have been so overwhelmed by coronavirus patients that intensive care units are now operating well beyond full capacity, according to a federal pandemic update obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins Doc Says End Of 2021 Realistic Timeline For 'Wide Distribution' Of Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/johns-hopkins-press-conference-coronavirus-pandemic-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johns Hopkins public health experts laid out challenges in distributing and administering coronavirus vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lewis issues call to action in posthumous op-ed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/76a63a9d89f53018f9347206b98ae9a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — John Lewis was mourned, revered and celebrated on Thursday at Atlanta's Ebenezer Baptist Church, a sacred place for many of those who helped to shape civil rights history. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key West couple jailed for violating quarantine orders...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/couple-jailed-violating-quarantine-730259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 30--A Florida couple was arrested yesterday for defying quarantine orders issued after they each tested positive for COVID-19, police report. Cops last night busted Yohana Gonzalez, 26, and Jose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift Fans Doxx and Harass Music Critic Over Review...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/taylor-swift-remains-silent-as-fans-doxx-and-harass-music-critic-over-folkore-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans tweeted a Pitchfork editor’s address and phone numbers—and even photos of her and her home—all over a review some zealous Swifties decided was not positive enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Tech Companies Already Won...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2020/07/antitrust-hearing-tech-pandemic-inescapable/614749/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antitrust could break up the big players. It wouldn’t change everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*ck' and 'sorry': New sounds of baseball season...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/30/astros-josh-reddick-screams-f-k-after-popup-against-dodgers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This won’t be the last “f–k” of the baseball season. Astros outfielder Josh Reddick screamed the curse in anger after popping out during his team’s 4-2, 13-inning loss…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA SINGLE DAY RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730134919-dqydg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-RECORDS (URGENT):Florida reports record increase in COVID-19 deaths for third day in a row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nazi Hunter Taking On Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-nazi-hunter-taking-on-mark-zuckerberg-and-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serge Klarsfeld has spent his life pursuing Nazis. Now, he’s teamed up with a number of other Holocaust activists and survivors to combat Facebook’s support of Holocaust denialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW GOVTS USE GEOLOCATION DATA TO IDENTIFY EVERYONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/how-government-entities-use-geolocation-data-to-identify-everyone_07302020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA is 'Satan,' Israel 'Chained Dog' --  But TWITTER Gives Ayatollah Pass...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/international/patrick-goodenough/us-satan-israel-its-chained-dog-twitter-gives-ayatollahs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s supreme leader, in a tweet Wednesday that was not flagged, restricted, or blocked by Twitter, called the United States “Satan,” labeled Israel America’s “chained dog,” drawing fresh attention to questions about the platform’s content policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Woman Catches UBER EATS Driver -- Eating Her Chicken Wings! </title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/its-called-uber-eats-not-uber-eats-my-food-austin-neighborhood-man-catches-delivery-driver-eating-his-wing-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Austin neighborhood resident said his Uber Eats delivery driver liked his food so much that the driver ate some of it himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordics brush off mouth covers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-country-face-masks-nordics-brush-off-mouth-095007454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As most of the world either orders or recommends the use of face masks, with even US president Donald Trump seen wearing one, Nordic nations are the remaining holdouts. In supermarkets, on buses, and along the streets of capitals -- such as Stockholm, Copenhagen, Oslo, Helsinki and Reykjavik -- face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/ci39322287/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA launches to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fcc3d442fe0cb4e640b0eae05d3e71c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The biggest, most sophisticated Mars rover ever built — a car-size vehicle bristling with cameras, microphones, drills and lasers — blasted off for the red planet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lewis issues call to action in posthumous op-ed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/30/opinion/john-lewis-civil-rights-america.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though I may not be here with you, I urge you to answer the highest calling of your heart and stand up for what you truly believe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Secrets, From Sex to Pets to Celeb Bad Behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/private-jet-secrets-from-sex-to-pets-to-celebrity-bad-behavior</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight Shocking Secrets I Learned While Working on Private Jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS TOO...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/texas-reports-single-day-record-coronavirus-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas passed the 6,000 deaths mark the same day the U.S. passed 150,000 deaths, the most of any country in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA launches to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df83e06ae963e63a1ec3b525df4ae50e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The summer’s third and final mission to Mars — featuring NASA's most elaborate life-hunting rover — is on the verge of liftoff. The rover Perseverance will follow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP: 4.2 MAG QUAKE SHAKES SOCAL...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/preliminary-45-quake-hits-near-san-fernando-area/6342317/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 4.2-magnitude earthquake hit the Pacoima area early Thursday morning, according to the U.S. Geological Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Night Mysterious Drone Swarm Descended On Palo Verde Nuke Plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/34800/the-night-a-drone-swarm-descended-on-palo-verde-nuclear-power-plant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious case of mass drone incursions over America's most powerful nuclear power plant that only resulted in more questions and no changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Unleashes on Trump Privately as He Raises $24 Million for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/30/obama-unleashes-on-trump-privately-as-he-raises-24-million-for-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At fund-raising events where he has pulled in more than $24 million for Joseph R. Biden Jr.’s campaign in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Could Free 20% of Prisoners to Avoid Infection...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/30/about-20-of-n-j-prisoners-could-be-freed-to-avoid-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey lawmakers seemed close to supporting legislation on Thursday that could free more than 3,000 prisoners — about 20</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First dog to test positive in USA dies...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/first-dog-with-covid-pets-coronavirus-buddy-german-shepherd/6341615/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mahoneys say, Buddy, their 6-year-old German Shepherd, started having trouble breathing in mid-April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governors' approval ratings drop as cases mount...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/509722-governors-approval-ratings-drop-as-covid-19-cases-mount</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters growing weary after months of the coronavirus pandemic are increasingly critical of their governors, especially in states where those governors raced to reopen the economy and are now suffering a surge in new cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama to deliver eulogy at John Lewis funeral where Presidents Bush and Clinton will attend...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1223604/obama-eulogy-john-lewiss-funeral-bush-clinton-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARACK Obama is reportedly going to deliver the eulogy at Rep. John Lewis’ funeral. Former US Presidents George W. Bush and Bill Clinton will also be at the Thursday funeral – but Trump will …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico's power grid fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/puerto-ricos-power-grid-fails-hours-ahead-of-potential-arrival-of-tropical-storm/ar-BB17l0tN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA'S DEADLIEST DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-reports-217-more-people-have-died-from-covid-19-the-highest-of-pandemic/ar-BB17l3VS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man fires gun in Miami hotel because people weren't social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/man-fires-gun-in-miami-hotel-because-people-weren-t-social-distancing-police-say/ar-BB17lylv?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 30 Million in USA Didn't Have Enough to Eat Last Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/almost-30-million-in-us-didn-e2-80-99t-have-enough-to-eat-last-week/ar-BB17ldBN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born-again fiscal conservatives are sign of Trump's weakening hand in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Born-again-fiscal-conservatives-are-sign-of-15443923.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A growing number of Senate conservatives have provided the latest sign of President Donald Trump's weakening hand on Capitol Hill.  From the presidentially ambitious Sens. Ted Cruz, R-Tex., and Josh Hawley, R-Mo., to onetime deficit hawks like Sen. Patrick J. Toomey, R-Pa., conservatives are abandoning the president as his top aides struggle with negotiations on a pandemic relief bill that is Trump's last, best chance to pass legislation that could help his floundering reelection bid.  Ignoring their own record of support for adding trillions of dollars to the national debt, these conservatives have signaled that they think, in a post-Trump Republican Party, that deficits will return to the forefront just as they did in the first years of the Obama administration.  "We can't just waste money. So I'm very concerned about the amount of money we're talking about," Sen. Rick Scott, R-Fla., told reporters Tuesday after leaving a GOP huddle with White House Chief of Staff Mark Meadows and Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin.  Those Trump advisers negotiated with Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., for a week until they rolled out proposals that totaled $1 trillion, a figure that left Scott stumped.  "A lot of money," he said.  Others washed their hands of the negotiations and said that Trump's advisers would negotiate an even larger compromise with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., whose initial offering two months ago cost $3 trillion.  "It's a mess. I can't figure out what this bill's about," Hawley said leaving the same meeting Tuesday. "This is not going to be the bill. They're going to go negotiate with Pelosi. We have no idea what the final bill will be, and we'll be the last to know."  And Sen. Ben Sasse, R-Neb., fresh off winning his primary, with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baghdad soars to 125&amp;#8457;, its highest recorded temp... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/temperature-soars-124-ancient-desert-204217413.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record high temperatures will continue to be challenged across the Middle East this week as blistering heat and dry conditions remain over the region.The week got off to a blazing start in Baghdad, Iraq, with a temperature reading of 50.6 C (123.1 F) on Monday. But on Tuesday, the temperature climbed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE A MINUTE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200730001802-03zgs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-CASUALTIES (UPDATE 2, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 2-U.S. records a coronavirus death every minute as total surpasses 150,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona leads multi-state probe into older iPhones slowing, shutting down...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200729181342-8fnch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE-PROBE/ (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Arizona leads multi-state probe into older iPhones slowing, shutting down</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci suggests wearing goggles or eye shields... </title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/dr-fauci-wear-goggles-eye-shields-prevent-spread/story?id=72059055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Fauci says in order to best prevent spreading or catching COVID-19, you should consider using goggles or a face shield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump TWITTER doc says Jesus will destroy FACEBOOK if doesn't put vid back...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1223386/doctor-says-jesus-will-destroy-facebook-over-covid-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HOUSTON doctor who went viral because of a now-deleted video where she touted hydroxychloroquine as a “cure” for COVID-19 has said Jesus Christ will destroy Facebook’s servers if the footage is n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to Unveil Ugliest GDP Report Ever Recorded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-is-about-to-unveil-the-ugliest-gdp-report-ever-recorded/ar-BB17jsXO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil reopens to foreigners...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/brazil-lifts-four-month-ban-on-foreigners-arriving-by-air-despite-virus-surge-decree-jhb-ch-01596075904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil reopened Wednesday to foreign visitors arriving by plane, hoping to revive its lockdown-devastated tourism industry despite the rapid spread of the new coronavirus in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST DEATHS SINCE MAY</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1288603954985578498?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top exec sees $200 million windfall...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/29/kodaks-top-exec-sees-200-million-windfall-on-stock-frenzy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The net worth of Kodak’s top executive has skyrocketed on the company’s transformation from an ailing camera maker to cutting-edge pharmaceutical start-up — thanks in part to some timely share purc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg  undergoes bile duct procedure in hospital...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-supreme-court-justice-ginsburg-000443552.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg is resting comfortably after undergoing a non-surgical medical procedure on a bile duct stent on Wednesday at a New York City hospital, the court said. Ginsburg, at 87 the oldest member of the Supreme Court and its senior liberal justice, expects to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Consider PAYING Infected To Self-Quarantine!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/29/la-los-angeles-covid-city-council-positive-test-pay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles City Council is considering plans to pay Angelenos who test positive for COVID-19 to stay home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos can't promise employees don't access independent seller data...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/7/29/21347083/jeff-bezos-amazon-tech-antitrust-hearing-jayapal-questioning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He says Amazon is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark goes off script to blast APPLE, GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/zuckerberg-goes-off-script-blasts-apple-and-google-in-testimony/ar-BB17l2K9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Hearing Explodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fireworks-house-hearing-explodes-after-dem-rep-calls-out-jim-jordan-for-fringe-conspiracy-theories-about-google/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House antitrust hearing went off the rails Wednesday afternoon following one Democrat swiping at Jim Jordan for his line of questioning to Google CEO Sundar Pichai.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust questions bruise but don't break Big Tech CEOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/amazon-apple-facebook-and-google-ceos-get-grilled-by-house-members-in-historic-antitrust-hearing-2020-07-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a bruising day tech’s biggest names on Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK threatened to clone INSTA before buying...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitaltrends.com/news/pramila-jayapal-accuses-facebook-of-threatening-to-clone-instagram-before-buying-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitaltrends.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Wednesday's antitrust hearing, Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg was grilled about his company's decision to acquire Instagram in 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KODAK deal with government sends stock to moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/29/investing/kodak-stock-rally-defense-protection-act/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The enormous rally in Kodak shares has no end in sight, after the Trump administration announced the company will be transformed into a pharmaceutical producer under the Defense Production Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Zeroes In On GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/congress-zeroes-in-on-google-during-historic-tech-antitrust-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEO Sundar Pichai takes intense heat from lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious trading activity raises questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/20/07/16814320/kodak-had-some-very-suspicious-trading-activity-ahead-of-drug-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.benzinga.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eastman Kodak Company (NYSE: KODK) shares skyrocketed 222% on Tuesday after the company announced it's pivoting to drug ingredient development and announced a large government...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How lockdowns change personalities...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200728-how-lockdown-may-have-changed-your-personality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our personalities are shaped by our experiences and social interactions, so how might the months spent isolated from friends, family and colleagues have altered us?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confused Rep. Quizzes Zuckerberg -- About TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/house-antitrust-hearing-mark-zuckerberg-donald-trump-jr-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Congressman, well, first to be clear, I think what you might be referring to happened on Twitter, so it's hard for me to speak to that."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zimbabwe signs billion-dollar deal to repay white farmers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cca5777366726c485510f4efc48bd367</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARARE, Zimbabwe (AP) — Zimbabwe’s government on Wednesday signed a deal with former white farmers to pay them billions of dollars in compensation roughly two decades after they lost their land in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$377 million West Wing remodel in virus bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Administration-wants-West-Wing-remodel-money-in-15443513.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration wants $377 million in the next coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA China academies abusive, investigation finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/29553829/espn-investigation-finds-coaches-nba-china-academies-complained-player-abuse-lack-schooling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with ESPN about its findings, an NBA official said the league is "reevaluating" the China academies after concluding it had insufficient oversight over the program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow campaign to stop her...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/29/biden-allies-move-to-stop-kamala-harris-from-becoming-vice-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's allies are waging a campaign behind the scenes to stop Kamala Harris from becoming vice president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly NAACP Pres Facing Calls To Resign Over Anti-Semitic FACEBOOK Post...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/07/28/pennsylvania-leaders-join-calls-for-philadelphia-naacp-president-to-resign-over-anti-semitic-facebook-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pennsylvania Gov. Tom Wolf and Attorney General Josh Shapiro are joining others in calling for Philadelphia NAACP President Minster Rodney Muhammad to resign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVES' player returns weeks after opting out of season...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a15e403edf87a0fc9474d84d2f24720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Nick Markakis is returning to the Atlanta Braves, three weeks after announcing he was opting out of the season due to his concerns about the coronavirus pandemic. Markakis,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Scene from hell'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/29/us/tempe-arizona-train-derailment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person was treated for smoke inhalation after a Union Pacific train derailed and caught fire on a bridge over Tempe Town Lake in Arizona, officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squid teeth secret to 'self-healing' robots? Army thinks so...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2020/07/29/are-squid-teeth-the-secret-to-building-self-healing-robots-the-army-thinks-so/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protein in squid teeth could hold the solution for self-healing materials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon warns of 'false alarm' nuke launches...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/928200/pentagon-wants-new-nuke-because-might-fire-old-ones-by-mistake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Department and the Energy Department's National Nuclear Security Administration in May argued in a previously undisclosed memo to Congress that the United States needs a new, more powerful nuclear warhead program because of risks and vulnerabilities in the current one, Roll Call reports. The argument is 'groundbreaking,' per Roll Call, because the government rarely, if ever, acknowledges the arsenal's weaknesses. Among the issues the departments address in the 'closely held' document are what they consider to be an over-reliance on one type of submarine-launched warhead that apparently isn't destructive enough and could suffer from technical problems, as well concerns about land-based intercontinental ballistic missiles that are set in a 'launch under attack posture.' That means the weapons are ready to launch within minutes of a reported enemy attack, which increases the risk of firing in the wake of a false alarm. And when ICBMS are launched, they cannot be returned to their silos. The Pentagon usually downplays the possibility of reacting to a false report, Roll Call reports, but the memo uses it to justify a new weapon that supposedly wouldn't carry the same risks. Critics think developing the new sub-launched weapon, known as a W93, is unnecessary (they believe the current warheads are plenty forceful), too expensive, and could harm global non-proliferation efforts. It remains to be seen if the Pentagon and the NNSA will be able to convince Congress and whoever wins the 2020 presidential election with their arguments, but the debate will likely gain more attention going forward. Read more at Roll Call. Tim O'Donnell Whatever one thinks of the administration's arguments, they are extraordinary &amp; groundbreaking. This new weapon has received scant public debate. Just $53 million is on the line this year for design work. But after that, this will become a bigger issue in Washington. / END â€” John M. Donnelly (@johnmdonnelly) July 29, 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK govt invests in sex-party startup amid pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/29/uk-government-invests-in-sex-party-startup-killing-kittens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK government is dipping its toe into the booming sex business amid the coronavirus pandemic – investing more than $220,000 in a company that runs adult parties in London and New York, accordin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peace agreement to begin withdrawing from Portland?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/07/29/federal-agents-to-leave-portland-governor/5536136002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents will remain in Portland to protect the federal courthouse but will rely on state police to deal with protesters outside the fence line, Homeland Security said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer snagged up to $350K in federal cash...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/28/influencer-arielle-charnas-snagged-up-to-350k-in-ppp-loan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent funding round for the brand valued it at $45 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train derails in Arizona causing massive fire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/train-derails-arizona-causing-massive-fire-180307545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freight train derailed and caught fire on a bridge in Arizona on Wednesday, but there were no reports of injuries in what a witness described as a &amp;quot;scene from hell.&amp;quot; The accident near Phoenix took place at around 6:15 a.m., prompting a massive fire visible for miles and sending some 100</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India uses arrival of new fighter jets to warn China...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-uses-arrival-fighter-jets-warn-china-000018890.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first five Rafale fighter jets bought from France in a multi-billion-dollar deal landed in India on Wednesday, and the defence minister used their arrival to launch a veiled warning to neighbouring China over territorial tensions. A water-cannon guard of honour greeted the five jets when they landed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage after NYPD hustles protester into unmarked van...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/80b30e504bcdf4107ed408c366db6645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The New York Police Department’s use of plainclothes officers and an unmarked minivan to haul away a vandalism suspect during a protest Tuesday created confusion and drew outrage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB players may not be paid for missed games...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/columnist/bob-nightengale/2020/07/29/marlins-covid-19-investigation-players-paid/5536625002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MLB has opened an investigation involving the Marlins’ coronavirus outbreak, trying to determine the cause of 18 positive tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agents deploying to Detroit, Cleveland, Milwaukee...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/07/29/operation-legend-doj-to-send-officers-to-detroit-cleveland-milwaukee/5535490002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration's Operation Legend is now launching in six cities in what the Justice Department calls an effort to quell violent crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDE: Berated Staffers for Taking Precautions...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm/2020/07/29/why-the-capitol-needs-testing-489917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Republicans aim for a short-term extension of some Covid relief priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/29/tech-ceo-antitrust-hearing-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is CNBC's live blog of the House Antitrust Subcommittee hearing featuring testimony from the CEOs of Amazon, Apple, Facebook and Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For TV heads and viewers, conventions largely a mystery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/32361acc69f4b5256d4d2b8f5245b6fb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Weeks before political conventions, television networks would typically be confirming hotel reservations, booking experts and pounding the last nails in temporary studios for their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Manhattan fashion exec killed in Maine shark attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/she-had-a-great-career-she-had-it-all-says-friend-of-retired-manhattan-fashion-exec-killed-in-maine-shark-attack/ar-BB17krl6?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO accidentally reports Kamala...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/politico-biden-vp-kamala-harris-running-mate-mistake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politico appears to have jumped the gun on reporting that Kamala Harris was chosen to be Joe Biden's running mate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O podcast sounds suspiciously like stump speech...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/928117/michelle-obamas-podcast-sounds-suspiciously-like-stump-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Michelle Obama has officially joined the ranks of Snooki, Snoop Dogg, and your old college roommate by starting her own podcast. In a sense, The Michelle Obama Podcast was inevitable: the Obamas pivoted from being politicians to celebrities after leaving the White House, and a requirement of being a famous person in 2020 is talking into a microphone for fans who may or may not exist. Since handing over the keys to 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue to the Trumps, the Obamas have fully embraced their celebrity status, signing a $65 million joint book deal, landing a massive, multi-year producing gig with Netflix, and, most recently, booking Obama's podcast (Spotify, which has the exclusive, inked similar deals around the same time with Kim Kardashian West, Joe Rogan, and DC Comics). Though Michelle Obama isn't hawking vagina candles or posting FabFitFun sponcon on Instagram, the Obamas aren't exactly following the Jimmy Carter model of living modestly while quietly building thousands of homes for Habitat for Humanity, either. Perhaps most frustrating for their supporters, the couple's pivot into celebritydom has seemed accompanied by a reluctance to speak out about politics in any meaningful way. The debut episode of the podcast, though, also highlights Michelle's innate gift for spinning her biography into political issues and advocacy â€” a talent that is hard to come by (Hillary Clinton struggled with it) but practically a golden ticket for a politician. Obama, for example, discusses her Leave It to Beaver-esque childhood, smoothly evoking the unifying vision her husband sold: 'You are guided by the principle that we are each other's brother's and sister's keepers,' Michelle tells Barack. 'And that's how I was raised!' Obama says her podcast is intended to explore 'relationships' by digging into her own. But it quickly becomes clear that there's a bigger picture: 'We weren't built to do this thing called life in a vacuum. It is much more hopeful, it is much more gratifying, much more effective to live this life as a 'we,'' she stresses. It's a good line â€” she should have saved it for the convention speech. Jeva Lange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH RECKONING?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/25a4d18ae3989402f0ad23f38d8cfa23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Four Big Tech CEOs — Facebook’s Mark Zuckerberg, Amazon’s Jeff Bezos, Sundar Pichai of Google and Tim Cook of Apple — are set to answer for their companies’ practices before...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/storminfo/09L_tracks_latest.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tropicaltidbits.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE reveals concept AirPods that 'vibrate music through your skull'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1218894/apple-airpods-vibrate-music-skull-patent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE is working on a new device that would use the bones in your head to vibrate music through your skull. This is according to a patent filed by the tech giant showing designs for a headset that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical teams feel 'helpless'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-usa-miami/miami-medical-teams-feel-helpless-as-covid-19-devastates-south-florida-idUSKCN24S27J?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus ravages Florida, healthcare workers in Miami hospitals are struggling to cope with the emotional and physical impact of treating a crushing wave of COVID-19 patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline bailout coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-airlines/majority-of-u-s-house-backs-new-bailout-for-u-s-passenger-airlines-idUSKCN24S2PE?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority U.S. House of Representatives lawmakers signed a letter made public on Monday calling for a six-month extension of a $32 billion payroll aid program that they argue is crucial to keeping hundreds of thousands of aviation workers employed through March 31.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Gohmert refused to wear mask, tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/29/louis-gohmert-who-refused-to-wear-a-mask-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-386076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Republican received the diagnosis during a pre-screening procedure at the White House on Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA IN FORECAST CONE FOR TROPICAL STORM..</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/refresh/AL092020_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/150024_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENTRALIZED INTERNET THREATENS US ALL</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2020/07/so-much-decentralized-internet/167281/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETBLUE deploys ultraviolet cleaning robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/jetblue-deploys-ultraviolet-cleaning-robot-at-jfk-airport-in-fight-against-coronavirus/2540269/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a device that looks like a blend between a beverage cart and a robot, but it is meant to help continue the fight against coronavirus. On Wednesday, JetBlue has become the first airline in the country to use new cutting-edge UV light technology in its cleaning efforts as a means to fight the coronavirus. JFK Airport in New York,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man given 1% chance of surviving makes it out of hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-known-as-patient-zero-in-burbank-hospital-recovers-from-coronavirus-most-fingers-amputated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One California man will undergo reconstructive surgery after most of his fingers were amputated during a two-month hospital stay for coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority now support kneeling during anthem...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kneeling-athletes-anthem-opinion-poll-28-07-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Views on this are divided by political party and race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Floyd Hologram Displayed At Former Sites Of Confederate Statues...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2020/07/28/george-floyd-hologram.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The image will be projected in historically significant locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago's New Deputy Police Chief Dies By Suicide...</title>
      <link>https://wbbm780.radio.com/articles/chicago-cop-found-shot-dead-in-apparent-suicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wbbm780.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago Police Department’s new deputy chief was found shot dead Tuesday in an apparent suicide at the Homan Square police facility on the West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO developing drama about vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/covid-19-vaccine-drama-in-development-at-hbo-adam-mckay-to-produce-1234717497/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO has optioned a book proposal about the hunt for a COVID-19 vaccine with Adam McKay onboard as an executive producer, Variety has confirmed. The potential limited series is based on the book pro…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
