<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Republicans have post-Trump identity crisis on horizon...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/the-gop-identity-crisis-on-the-horizon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether it's a few months or six years from now, what will being Republican mean after Donald Trump is no longer president?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anita Hill 'Deeply Unsatisfied' After Apology...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/25/us/politics/joe-biden-anita-hill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. called Anita Hill this month to express his regret over “what she endured” testifying against Justice Clarence Thomas in 1991.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Preps Armageddon With Simulation Exercises...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/nasa-prepares-asteroid-armageddon-simulation-exercises-2787802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA, Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) and its international partners are conducting planetary defense exercises for a potential asteroid impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto: I Won't Deport Like Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/25/robert-beto-orourke-pledges-ice-will-not-deport-like-trump-and-obama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential hopeful Robert “Beto” O’Rourke said Wednesday his presidency won't use ICE to deport people like presidents Trump and Obama did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloves off as Biden eyes Trump knockout in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gloves-off-biden-eyes-trump-knockout-2020-144325918.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was with these words that Donald Trump earlier this month summarily dismissed the challenge posed by the former vice president, who on Thursday announced his long-expected decision to run for the Democratic nomination in 2020. Julian Zelizer, a professor at Princeton University, told AFP: "In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom arrested on FRONTIER flight after complaining about seat vomit...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/travel/durham-woman-arrested-on-frontier-flight-after-complaint-about-vomit-in-seat/5269018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Durham woman is facing charges after a confrontation on a Frontier Airlines flight that landed her in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endangered Amazon tribe vow to take up bows and arrows against Brazilian govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8936896/brazil-arara-tribe-bows-arrows-government-forces-invading-rainforest-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN isolated Brazilian tribe hidden deep in the Amazon rainforest has vowed to “take up bows and arrows” against government forces threatening their territory with deforestation. The Ara…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opens in 25 markets before USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/box-office-avengers-endgame-roars-record-169m-overseas-1204650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That includes $107 million in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Snow Expected in Detroit...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/weather/2019/04/25/metro-detroit-weather-rain-snow/3571372002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Weather Service predicted "intermittent" rain showers and colder temperatures dropping to the 50s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full film leaks online after recorded in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/25/full-avengers-endgame-film-leaks-online-ahead-of-us-opening.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite attempts to prevent pirated versions of "Avengers: Endgame" from reaching fans ahead of the film's release, a 1.2-gigabyte torrent of the movie recorded in a Chinese theater has found its way online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early focus on Pennsylvania...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/25/biden-makes-early-play-for-pennsylvania-as-he-joins-race-to-beat-trump-in-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden already has a number of advantages over his opponents in the swing state, which holds 20 votes in the electoral college.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden spotted on Amtrak train hours after announcing White House bid...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/440626-hours-after-announcing-2020-campaign-biden-spotted-on-amtrak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A photo of former Vice President Joe Biden sitting casually on an Amtrak train just hours after announcing his 2020 presidential campaign is making the rounds on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Dropping Child Porn Cases to Avoid Revealing Surveillance Systems Info...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/04/24/the-feds-are-dropping-child-porn-cases-instead-of-revealing-info-on-their-surveillance-systems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human Rights Watch and other groups say these systems draw serious concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron offers tax cut to quell anger...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frances-macron-vows-tax-cuts-months-protests-171510343.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Emmanuel Macron Thursday promised significant tax cuts but also a return to public order in France as he revealed his long-awaited response to nearly half a year of street protests. In the first formal domestic news conference of his entire presidency, Macron steered clear of bombshell announcements</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asked Obama Not to Endorse...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/biden-i-asked-obama-not-to-endorse-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden said Thursday he had asked former President Barack Obama "not" to endorse him as he formally entered the 2020 race for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders holds press briefing --  for kids...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f41725f673994a96b0fc508540ca2ce9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — White House press secretary Sarah Sanders held her first briefing in more than a month Thursday, but still didn't field questions from working journalists. Instead, Sanders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE PLAYS COMMON MAN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0da41bc7243c434b8d6522cc344c61bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden spent a hot August day at his lakefront Delaware home watching hatred on display in Charlottesville, Virginia, where torch-wielding white supremacists had marched through town. A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCLA, Cal State LA To Quarantine Students Who Cannot Prove They Had Measles Vaccination...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/04/25/measles-quarantine-ucla-cal-state-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials at UCLA and Cal State LA are working with county health officials to issue quarantine orders for students who cannot provide evidence of measles immunizations, officials announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge charged for helping suspect evade ICE arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www2.bostonglobe.com/metro/2019/04/25/federal-prosecutors-charge-mass-judge-with-obstructing-justice/XuNadgoVjMjlRkc9cjPH0L/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Newton judge and a now-retired state court officer face obstruction of justice charges for allegedly helping an undocumented immigrant evade ICE custody last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brent touches $75 per barrel...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-oil/brent-touches-75-per-barrel-after-europe-halts-russian-crude-imports-idUSKCN1S1021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brent crude hit $75 per barrel on Thursday for the first time in nearly six mont...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans Hollywood fundraiser with Katzenbergs, Eric Schmidt, Rob Reiner...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/politics/news/joe-biden-hollywood-backers-1203197957/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has lined up a long list of co-hosts for his first Hollywood-centric fundraising event, including a number of industry figures who were active in President Barack Obama’s presidenti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Mayor Arrested For Trying To Rig Own Election...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/04/25/texas-mayor-richard-molina-arrested-trying-rig-own-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas mayor has been arrested on charges of trying to rig his own 2017 election victory, prosecutors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Suspect Who Plowed Into 8 -- On Way To Bible Study...</title>
      <link>http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/04/25/sunnyvale-rampage-pedestrians-isaiah-peoples/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 34-year-old Sunnyvale man picked up food for his bible study group and was on his way to the gathering when police say he intentionally veered his car into eight pedestrians on a Sunnyvale street, authorities said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger mauls wildlife sanctuary founder...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/bengal-tiger-attacks-ex-las-vegas-illusionist-sanctuary-founder-1649101/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Las Vegas Strip entertainer was injured Monday when he was bitten by a Bengal tiger in Valentine, Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI raids Baltimore City Hall, home of Mayor...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-baltimore-20190424-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agents are raiding Baltimore’s City Hall and the home of Mayor Catherine Pugh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens accused of taking e-scooters at gunpoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/police-track-down-teens-accused-taking-scooters-gunpoint-midtown/Ml5srvpO84jJ7ihQfSHm4J/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 13-year-old and a 17-year-old are facing charges after police said a group of teens stole electric...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron offers tax cut to French workers to quell anger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f4cb6de554247d5b400c3cdd3f0c276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French President Emmanuel Macron announced tax cuts for middle-class workers and a more representative parliament on Thursday to quell five months of yellow vest protests that have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince estate to drop new work...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190425-prince-estate-release-new-album-featuring-unreleased-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince estate to release new album featuring unreleased work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army cuts power for thousands to test 'real-world reactions' to cyber-attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article229662514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost 'CLOCKWORK ORANGE' sequel discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-48036694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unfinished follow-up to Anthony Burgess's Clockwork Orange novel is unearthed in his archive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CA Dem Chair Forcibly Gave Oral Sex to Male Staffer, Suit Says...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/former-calif-dem-chair-forcibly-gave-oral-sex-to-male-staffer-lawsuit-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former chairman of the California Democratic Party is accused in a lawsuit of forcibly performing oral sex on a male subordinate and threatening him to keep quiet, the Sacramento Bee reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver Cited For Watching 'LAW &amp; ORDER' While Driving...</title>
      <link>http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/04/25/driver-cited-for-watching-law-order-while-driving-state-patrol-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier in the month, Gov. Tim Walz signed into law a "hands free" bill to combat distracted driving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Risk of dying higher in back seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/04/25/car-crashes-iihs-study-rear-seat-less-safe/3552964002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sitting in the back seat? You could be at more risk of dying in a head-on collision than someone sitting in the front, according to IIHS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country Too Fractured to Be Funny...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/04/white-house-correspondents-dinner-shows-death-humor/587872/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House Correspondents’ Dinner suggests that stand-up joke telling is an art form whose moment has passed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Promise of Mayor Pete...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/04/pete-buttigieg-model-bourgeois-gay-domesticity/587779/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He can deliver us from a scandal-plagued presidency and transform the relationship between gay and straight America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ammonia spill near Chicago sends 32 to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-beach-park-hazmat-spill-20190425-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ammonia spill in north suburban Beach Park sent at least 31 people to hospitals and prompted school closings and warnings from Lake County sheriff’s officials for residents of the area to stay inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to Slash Red Meat Consumption to Fight 'Climate Change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/24/new-yorks-green-new-deal-will-slash-red-meat-in-city-facilities-by-50/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City plans to reduce the amount of red meat served in municipally-run facilities by half to combat climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILVER: Media Underestimating...</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/how-joe-biden-could-win-the-2020-democratic-nomination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Barack Obama’s two-term vice president, he’s the most familiar brand in the field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hires Key Bernie Advisor...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/entertainment/biden-hires-strategist-symone-sanders-adds-diversity-to-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden has hired Symone Sanders, a prominent African American political strategist, as a senior adviser to his newly launched presidential campaign. The move adds a younger, diverse voice to Biden's cadre of top advisers, which has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan creates first artificial crater on asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190425-japan-creates-first-artificial-crater-asteroid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan creates first artificial crater on asteroid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimpanzee uses iPhone...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6959633/King-swipers-Chimpanzee-uses-iPhone-scroll-videos-photographs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JD Durkin from Queens, New York admitted that the chimpanzee developing technology skills is worrying for society in general, claiming it could be 'the end for us idiots'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE 22-Year Tax Break Part of Billions in CA Bounty...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report-state/apples-22-year-tax-break-part-of-billions-in-california-bounty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. was on the brink of bankruptcy in 1997 when it cut a deal with the city of Cupertino, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN: NKorea ready to denuclearize -- for guarantees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fbe1a8e788aa444481ef8d3f638f834f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIVOSTOK, Russia (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin said North Korean leader Kim Jong Un confirmed during their first summit Thursday he is willing to give up his nuclear weapons — but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia put crucified body on public display after 37 executions...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/saudi-arabia-put-crucified-body-14579574</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amnesty International say teenagers are among those killed by the oil-rich state who has been accused of targeting the Shi'ite minority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coachella: Huge Spike In Herpes Reported On Festival Grounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.hotnewhiphop.com/coachella-2019-a-huge-spike-in-herpes-reported-on-festival-grounds-news.78249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotnewhiphop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coachella 2019 was an unforgettable experience for some of the more active participants. According to TMZ, the 2019 edition of Coachella has incited a nasty outbreak of herpes. Initially reported by HerpAlert, the internet's number one resource in diagnosing the STD, the outbreak was caused by, you ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students appalled by 'creepy' touching...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=12141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"That's definitely excessive..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen readies Western-style album...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f95c785e2f564a909d1e4d32e8fb5472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fresh off his Broadway run, New Jersey's Bruce Springsteen looked West for inspiration on a new album he's planning to release on June 14. The 13-song disc is his first new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside decision to run one more time...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0da41bc7243c434b8d6522cc344c61bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden spent a hot August day at his lakefront Delaware home watching hatred on display in Charlottesville, Virginia, where, days earlier, torch-wielding white supremacists had marched through...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Campaign going to be parody of self...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/836978/joe-bidens-campaign-going-parody-itself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get your bingo cards ready for the debates, folks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sloppy launch may cost him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/440603-bidens-sloppy-launch-may-cost-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden better finish strong, because the start couldn't be going much worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President taunts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/440598-trump-mocks-sleepy-joe-after-biden-jumps-into-2020-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday mocked Joe Biden after the former vice president launched his campaign for the Democratic presidential nomination in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON tops 'dirty dozen' list of most dangerous workplaces...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comAMAZON tops 'dirty dozen' list of most dangerous workplaces...</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comAMAZON tops 'dirty dozen' list of most dangerous workplaces...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says Never Asked McGahn to Fire Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-says-he-never-asked-mcgahn-to-fire-mueller-11556196379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday contradicted a detailed account in Mr. Mueller’s report, tweeting that he never told White House Counsel Don McGahn to fire special counsel Robert Mueller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BATTLE FOR SOUL OF NATION'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/joe-biden-launches-2020-presidential-run-n998236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president enters the race polling ahead of all 19 other candidates in the Democratic field, but will it last?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY UNLOADS: 'DERANGED DONALD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/george-conway-loses-it-deranged-donald-doesnt-need-books-because-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6958783/Ex-Vice-President-Biden-launches-2020-presidential-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden formally entered the race for the presidential race Thursday in an announcement that struck directly at President Donald Trump and laid out the former vice president's vision to led the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS JUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/25/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The underlying trend continued to point to labor market strength, however.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bartiromo stock rises at FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-himi-maria-bartiromo-fox-news-20190425-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former CNBC anchor who originated live reporting from the New York Stock Exchange now anchors 17.5 hours of programming a week at Fox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans abandoning high-tax states...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/americans-high-tax-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from 2018 shows more Americans moved out of higher-tax states than into them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 16 MINUTES less sleep than need can wreck whole day...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/774372/sleep-insomnia-how-much-cant-sleep-tired-better-nights-sleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Broadcaster Under Scrutiny for Disseminating Propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-broadcaster-under-scrutiny-for-disseminating-propaganda-11556184602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials are scrutinizing the U.S. government’s Radio Free Europe / Radio Liberty news service, established to promote democratic values abroad, after complaints it has distributed foreign propaganda favorable to authoritarian regimes in Central Asia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'Narcos' Danger Zone to Rising Tourist Star: Colombia's Medellin...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/from-narcos-danger-zone-to-rising-tourist-star-colombias-medellin-11556123510 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young entrepreneurs are turning Medellín and its surroundings—former Escobar country—into one of South America’s most dynamic destinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Schizophrenia Cases Misdiagnosed; Just Anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hopkins-study-half-schizophrenia-cases-misdiagnosed-anxiety/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A significant number of people declared schizophrenic by their doctors may be misdiagnosed. A small study of patients referred to the Johns Hopkins Early Psychosis Intervention Clinic (EPIC) with diagnoses of schizophrenia found that about half didn't have the disease at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Luxury Loses Luster in Hamptons as High-End Homes Pile Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-25/luxury-loses-luster-in-the-hamptons-as-high-end-homes-pile-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials Tried to Kill American Mall. Gen Z Might Save It...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-25/are-u-s-malls-dead-not-if-gen-z-keeps-shopping-the-way-they-do </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin praises Kim efforts to improve ties with rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fbe1a8e788aa444481ef8d3f638f834f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIVOSTOK, Russia (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin said after his summit with Kim Jong Un Thursday that the North Korean leader is ready to proceed toward denuclearization — but needs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At WALMART, using AI to watch the store...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d416ba3945d64975994805db55467744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEVITTOWN, N.Y. (AP) — Inside one of Walmart's busiest Neighborhood Market grocery stores, high resolution cameras suspended from the ceiling point to a table of bananas. They can tell how ripe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven big decisions facing Joe in primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440573-seven-big-decisions-facing-biden-in-2020-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden announced his presidential candidacy on Thursday and joins the c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete draws new scrutiny, criticism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440556-buttigieg-draws-new-scrutiny-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg’s early success in the Democratic primary has prompted scrutiny and rougher treatment from his rivals and the news media, creating new challenges for the rising star and his campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN LAUNCHES</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d5c415b99a6945dbbecf60d57bcf68cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former Vice President Joe Biden formally joined the crowded Democratic presidential contest on Thursday, betting that his working-class appeal and ties to Barack Obama's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest presidential field in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/biden-entry-makes-2020-democrats-the-largest-presidential-field-in-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With former Vice President Joe Biden set to enter the 2020 fray on Thursday, the Democratic field contesting the right to challenge President Trump for the White House next year will be a record 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star on Hollywood Walk of Fame defaced by vandal -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/04/24/president-trump-putins-bitch-vandalized-hollywood-walk-of-fame-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's Walk of Fame star got a fresh coat of paint, but he ain't gonna be thrilled about it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie gets tough reception at minority women's event, signaling challenges ahead... </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Sanders-gets-tough-reception-at-minority-women-s-13793574.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON - The groans erupted halfway through Bernie Sanders' appearance Wednesday at a presidential candidates' forum sponsored by She the People, a group that aims to drive up voter participation among women of color.  Before an audience of about 1,700, many of them African-American and Hispanic women, the moderator asked Sanders, I-Vt., how he would handle the rise in white supremacy. Sanders spoke of fighting discrimination and running a campaign "to bring our people together around an agenda that speaks to all people" - then returned to a familiar message on universal health care.  For many in the audience, that was insufficient. "Come on!" a woman shouted from the back, as others began to jeer and boo.  The reception reflected Sanders' struggle to win support from minority voters, a problem that dogged his 2016 primary campaign against Hillary Clinton. Sanders has taken steps since to improve his outreach, including meeting with black leaders and talking more frequently about the difficulties facing minorities, but Wednesday's event suggested the senator still faces challenges.  Sanders at one point mentioned his long record on civil rights, but it did little to mollify the crowd.  "I was actually at the March on Washington with Dr. King back in 1963, and - as somebody who actively supported Jesse Jackson's campaign, as one of the few white elected officials to do so in '88 - I have dedicated my life to the fight against racism and sexism and discrimination of all forms," Sanders said. That prompted audible groans.  Sanders may have come into the event at a disadvantage, since many black women supported Clinton in 2016. Some Clinton backers believe Sanders did too little to help her after she won the nomination.  Sanders did eventually coax a warmer reception when he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 60: MADONNA FIGHTS FOR AIRPLAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6957033/Madonna-transforms-bride-snogs-male-suitor-licks-TOE-dramatic-video.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pop legend, 60, reveals at the beginning of the visual extravaganza that she will now only be known by the moniker Madame X, which is the name of her new album.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey mayor tells TWITTER user to call the cops on Jewish 'invaders'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/24/new-jersey-mayor-tells-twitter-user-to-call-the-cops-on-jewish-invaders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey mayor is facing mounting backlash for telling a constituent to call the cops on Jewish people for going to the beach. Brick Township Mayor John G. Ducey was responding to a flat-out an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Can't Afford to Keep Talking About Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/04/24/britain-cant-afford-to-keep-talking-about-brexit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The never-ending conversation about leaving the EU has stalled all other progress on economic policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaffolding firm says workers smoked at Paris' Notre-Dame...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424184708-qxte6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NOTREDAME/ (PIX):Scaffolding firm says workers smoked at Paris' Notre-Dame</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Temple Says Recognized as Church by IRS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/satanic-temple-tax-exempt-hail-satan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organization is the first satanic group granted tax-exempt status of other religious institutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Christie Warns: White Working-Class Trump Voters Could Hand 2020 Election to Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/chris-christie-white-working-class-trump-voters-could-hand-2020-election-to-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Playoff Ratings Sink to New Lows...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/04/24/nba-playoffs-ratings-sink-new-lows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a small rise in viewers last weekend, the NBA playoffs are still sinking in the ratings, according to the numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS RELEASING 1,400 ILLEGALS INTO USA EVERY DAY... </title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/24/dhs-releases-seven-thousand-illegal-aliens-into-u-s-in-five-days-released-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's DHS has released about 7,000 border crossers and illegal aliens into the interior of the U.S. in the last five days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57% SEE ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AS THREAT TO HUMAN RACE...</title>
      <link>https://scottrasmussen.com/57-see-artificial-intelligence-as-threat-to-human-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scottrasmussen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-seven percent (57%) of voters believe that Artificial Intelligence (A.I.) is at least somewhat of a threat to the human race. A ScottRasmussen.com national survey found that 43% disagree and do not see it as a threat.Those figures include 16% who consider A.I. is a Very Serious threat while 10% say it is not a threat at all.Concern about A.I. threatening the human race has been a regular feature of science-fiction films, including classics such as The Matrix. The number currently considering A.I. to be a threat is up three points since November. Other recent studies show a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA May Ban Schools From Suspending Students For Defiance Of Teachers...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/04/23/willful-defiance-bill-senate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California State Senate voted to ban schools and principals from suspending students for "willful defiance" of teachers, staff, and administrators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' Stars Demand FOXDISNEY Bring Smollett Back -- Or Else...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/empire-cast-crew-letter-jussie-smolett-return-fox-disney-1202601208/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Empire co-creator Lee Daniels told a New York City morning show Wednesday that the fate of Jussie Smollett on the Fox hit is “in discussions” right now, but Taraji P. Henson, Terrence Ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles cases hit highest level since eradication in 2000...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190425000013-u7mcf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEASLES/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. measles cases hit highest level since eradication in 2000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel chair accuses President of 'massive' obstruction...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424233941-6j2nq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/ (UPDATE 7, PIX):UPDATE 7-House panel chair accuses Trump of 'massive' obstruction; Trump vows to fight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC tickets 12 people for defying measles vaccination order...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424194017-a9z9p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEASLES/:New York City tickets 12 people for defying measles vaccination order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader of armed militia group attacked in jail...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424190640-j4n8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MILITIA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Leader of self-styled U.S. citizen border patrol attacked in jail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated pilots get Navy to stop dismissing UFO sightings...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/unidentified-flying-objects-ufos-navy-document-encounters-20190424.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent uptick in sightings of unidentified flying objects - or, as the military calls them, "unexplained aerial phenomena" - prompted the U.S. Navy to draft formal procedures for pilots to document encounters, a corrective measure that former officials say is long overdue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULTRA music stressed fish more than chase by predator...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/article229610019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interstate blocked as 30,000 pounds of TV dinners spill off big rig...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/04/24/gold-run-tv-dinner-big-rig-fire-i-80/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A truckload of TV dinners caught fire and blocked Interstate 80 in the Sierra Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked pics of China 11,509-mph HYPERSONIC rocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8933644/leaked-china-secret-hypersonic-nuke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILLING photos have been leaked onto the internet which some fear show China’s top secret 11,509mph hypersonic rocket system aimed at dodging US defences. Images of the impressive Jia Geng N…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW: 80% of tweets come from small minority of accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewinternet.org/2019/04/24/sizing-up-twitter-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewinternet.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter users are younger, more likely to identify as Democrats, more highly educated and have higher incomes than U.S. adults overall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FIGHTING ALL SUBPOENAS'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/trump-blasts-house-oversight-probes-says-white-house-fighting-all-n998046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump called himself the "most transparent president ever" amid blocking officials from appearing before Congress and suing to keep financial documents secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama staying on sidelines as VP set to launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/obama-staying-on-the-sidelines-as-biden-gets-ready-to-launch-his-2020-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden’s expected to declare his candidacy for president on Thursday. But when he does, don’t expect his running mate – former President Barack Obama – to speak out in support of his bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIEBER DENIES COACHELLA LIP SYNC -- SORTA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/justin-bieber-ariana-grande-address-coachella-lip-synch-controversy-1203197026/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Justin Bieber joined Ariana Grande on stage at the Coachella Festival Sunday night to perform his hit “Sorry,” there was little doubt in anyone’s mind about whether it was co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: STARTS WITH EDGE OVER TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/04/24/joe-biden-is-the-front-runner-over-democrats-and-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As former Vice President Joe Biden prepares to enter the race for the Democratic presidential nomination, he’s doing so as the front-runner, polling ahead of both fellow Democrats and President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Police!' Lookout parrot trained to alert drug dealers keeps beak shut after arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/24/brazil-drug-parrot-trained-as-lookout-for-dealers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bird was taught to alert criminals to officers’ presence, according to reports: ‘As soon as the police got close he started shouting’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacked LIME Scooters Shout Sexual Messages at Riders...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lime-scooters-hacked-to-say-sexual-things-to-riders-in-1834264534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight Lime e-scooters have been pulled from the streets of Brisbane, Australia this week after they were hacked to say sexual and otherwise offensive things. Lime calls the hack “disappointing.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT HITS TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/24/microsoft-q3-2019-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft kicked off tech earnings season and the stock jumped after revenue topped estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beset by infighting, NRA faces toughest foe: Own members...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bda97817dabf492e9be8099bdd1a4cd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association is used to battling forces that criticize its fiery and unbending efforts to protect gun rights. But as the group gathers for its annual convention this week, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds probe claims Governor removed mansion toilets to get tax break...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2019/04/24/report-feds-investigating-claims-pritzkers-removed-mansions-toilets-to-get-tax-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — The so-called "toilet fiasco" that dogged Gov. J.B. Pritzker during his campaign has not gone away, as new reports indicate the matter is currently the subject of a federal investigation. During the same week Pritzker marks 100 days in office,  WBEZ reports investigators are looking into whether he and his wife broke the law by removing toilets from their Gold Coast mansion to get a tax break.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
