<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone Volcano Eruption Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/yellowstone-volcano-eruption-fears-california-earthquake-1448193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Many feeling vulnerable despite economic gains...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3aec63de0dce4f558dd20fee6127b35c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines arrested for smuggling illegals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/09/marines-arrested-for-smuggling-illegal-immigrants-near-southern-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Marines were busted last week in California for allegedly smuggling a trio of illegal immigrants near the US-Mexico border. Marines Bryon Darnell Law II and David Javier Salazar-Quintero were c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTROS Pitcher Claims MLB Juicing Baseballs To Goose Up Offense...</title>
      <link>https://deadspin.com/justin-verlander-says-mlb-is-juicing-baseballs-to-goose-1836199057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadspin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astros pitcher and American League All-Star Justin Verlander is convinced that baseball’s ongoing surge of home runs is not only the result of a more aerodynamic baseball, but is the result of a baseball that has been intentionally juiced during manufacturing in order to produce more offense. Verlander told ESPN on Monday that the ball is “a fucking joke” and “it’s not coincidence” that the ball is flying farther now that its manufacturer is owned by Major League Baseball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dentist accused of illegally killing THOUSAND jaguars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7227439/Dentist-accused-illegally-killing-thousand-jaguars-Brazil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longest serving member of the gang and the most prolific was said to be Temistocles Barbosa Freire, a dentist who is believed to have illegally killed over 1,000 jaguars since 1987.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTS WITHIN YEAR</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/09/virgin-galactic-says-space-tourism-flights-to-begin-in-a-year-company-will-be-profitable-in-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic expects to be profitable two years after it begins publicly-trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Marine launches Dem challenge to McConnell...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/452117-kentucky-democrat-announces-challenge-to-mcconnell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Marine and previous Democratic congressional candidate Amy McGrath on Tuesday announced that she is launching a 2020 challenge against Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R) in Kentucky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Alien Hunters to Storm Area 51 for ET Proof...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/us/201907091076190763-alien-hunters-storm-us-area-51/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The truth hunters, however, have made no secret of their daring plans to seek extraterrestrial guests in an area of Edwards Air Force base that is classified and heavily guarded. They’ve even invited everyone willing to join on Facebook. An earlier attempt to breach the area ended in the death of a trespasser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. appeals court to take up constitutionality of Obamacare...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-obamacare/u-s-appeals-court-to-take-up-constitutionality-of-obamacare-idUSKCN1U40ZU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of Obamacare could be at stake on Tuesday when a coalition of Democra...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE ANNOUNCES 'ECO-TAX' FOR ALL FLIGHTS LEAVING COUNTRY...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/france-eco-tax-flights-tickets-airlines-planes-climate-change-a8996741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Nazis to hippies: End of road for VOLKSWAGEN BEETLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/53243665f30f4d97a2a292e3c7e76a41</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida high school principal removed after comments about Holocaust...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/schools/fl-ne-william-latson-comments-20190708-cm5wzlw4lrayrl5y2r3vljxhnu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;William Latson, principal of Spanish River High in Boca Raton, told a parent in an email that "I can't say the Holocaust is a factual, historical event because I am not in a position to do so as a school district employee." On Monday, he was removed as the school's principal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thief used 'Jaws of Life' to pry open ATMs... </title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/breaking-news/hc-br-southington-atm-thief-arrest-20190708-25yep76xbzf7tglsuea2jvqenq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southington police say they have arrested a man who police said used a “Jaws of Life” hydraulic tool to break into ATMs around the state, stealing up to $300,000 in cash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAMP FLOODS</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/floods/news/2019-07-08-washington-maryland-virginia-flooding-leads-to-water-rescues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downpours have created commuting nightmares in and around the Washington D.C. area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 60 million Hispanics in USA, 52% of population growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/record-60-million-hispanics-in-us-52-of-population-growth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Hispanic population surged another 1.2 million last year and now is a record 59.9 million, according to newly released U.S. Census Bureau population estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vows to ghost UK ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jul/08/donald-trump-we-will-no-longer-deal-with-the-british-ambassador</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In latest tweets, US president also attacks Theresa May for making a mess of Brexit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRONES ON TRAFFIC PATROL TO HELP CATCH DANGEROUS DRIVERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/07/08/speeding-dangerous-drivers-targeted-britains-first-traffic-drone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speeding and dangerous drivers are to be targeted by Britain&amp;rsquo;s first traffic drone which was previously used on the battlefield and against terrorists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Purell Presidency: White House aides learn real red line...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/07/donald-trump-germaphobe-1399258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A self-described germaphobe, the 45th president is strictly enforcing proper hygiene inside the White House — and wherever else he goes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson Seeks Political Asylum in America, Says He Will Be Murdered in UK Prison... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/tommy-robinsons-desperate-plea-to-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spread this urgent message to get the word out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial intelligence monitors  behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90373578/instagram-tool-alerts-bullies-about-hurtful-comments-before-they-post</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook-owned Instagram wants to weed out hateful comments before they appear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter Accuses Editor Graydon Carter of Cover Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.democracynow.org/2019/7/8/jeffrey_epstein_a_billionaire_friend_of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.democracynow.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire hedge fund manager Jeffrey Epstein, who has been accused of sexually assaulting underage girls for more than a decade, will appear in federal court today in Manhattan on sex trafficking charges. He was arrested on Saturday for allegedly running a sex trafficking operation by luring underage girls as young as 14 years old to his mansion in Manhattan. Epstein was previously accused of molesting and trafficking dozens of underage girls in Florida, but he ended up serving just 13 months in county jail after the U.S. prosecutor in Florida, Alexander Acosta, cut what’s been described as “one of the most lenient deals for a serial child sex offender in history.” The plea deal allowed Epstein to avoid a federal trial and possible life in prison, and effectively ended an FBI probe into the case. Acosta is now Donald Trump’s labor secretary. Epstein has counted Presidents Donald Trump and Bill Clinton among his friends. We speak with Vicky Ward, an investigative journalist who profiled Jeffrey Epstein for Vanity Fair in 2003 in a piece headlined “The Talented Mr. Epstein.” The magazine’s editor at the time, Graydon Carter, cut out the testimonies of two young women Epstein allegedly molested who had spoken to Ward on the record. Ward later wrote about the incident for The Daily Beast in an article headlined “I Tried to Warn You About Sleazy Billionaire Jeffrey Epstein in 2003.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95,500 apprehensions in June...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/plummet-border-numbers-still-well-level-system-wide-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New normal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuser invokes Fifth Amendment... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/08/kevin-spacey-groping-accuser-invokes-5th-judge-bars-testimony.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spacey's defense attorney, Alan Jackson, also said that the accuser's mother, Heather Unruh, may have been watching live coverage of her son's testimony on TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O GETS PERSONAL: YES, I SUPPORT... GREAT SEX AT EVERY AGE!</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-michelle-obama-gets-personal-yes-i-support-great-sex-every-a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Yes, Gayle, the answer is yes’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Rape Trial Set For September...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/07/harvey-weinstein-new-lawyers-new-york-rape-trial-date-remains-1202640490/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Despite being on the job for barely over a week, Harvey Weinstein’s newest and latest defense lawyers won’t be asking a New York state judge for another delay in the start of the O…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dancing parrot stuns scientists with 14 separate moves to 80s classics...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/07/08/snowball-dancing-parrot-stuns-scientists-14-separate-moves-eighties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans may have more in common with parrots than chimpanzees due to a shared natural ability to dance, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE co-founder Wozniak: 'Get Off FACEBOOK'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7225593/Apple-founder-Steve-Wozniak-says-Facebook.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a brief run-in with TMZ, Wozniak warned people often assume they have more privacy online than they really do, and said he's now 'worried about everything' when it comes to potential eavesdropping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran threatens to enrich uranium to 20% purity as tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iran-says-could-enrich-uranium-100610706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Iran said it had already begun enriching uranium beyond the cap set in the landmark 2015 nuclear deal and threatened to boost enrichment to 20% purity, escalating tensions with European partners who are struggling to salvage the accord in the face of tightening U.S. sanctions.Iran announced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What did famous friends know and see?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d0490c6774048dc8a5f4fe80d0cf71f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMVs become part of unprecedented surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fbi-ice-find-state-drivers-license-photos-are-a-gold-mine-for-facial-recognition-searches/ar-AADZk0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWALWELL OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/democrat-eric-swalwell-drops-out-of-presidential-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swalwell had fallen from the 1% he was polling at early in his short campaign, and he was at high risk of being bumped from the second debate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Music festival scraps charging white people DOUBLE to attend...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/festival-scraps-cheaper-people-of-colour-tickets-after-white-supremacist-threats-11758953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early bird tickets for AfroFuture Fest had started at $10 for "people of colour" and $20 for "non-people of colour".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT:  County cannot ban invocations by atheists...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190708191331-hjpbv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLORIDA-INVOCATIONS/:Florida county cannot ban invocations by atheists -U.S. appeals court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stays in Jail -- for Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-case-billionaire-pleads-not-guilty-to-sex-trafficking-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His lawyers claim the new charges are an improper ‘do-over’ of a decade-old case that ended with a sweetheart plea deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Londoners being tracked on the Tube using WiFi...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2019/07/08/tfl-begins-tracking-london-underground-commuters-using-wi-fi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crushing queues at rush hour, station closures and squeezing on to packed carriages are familiar experiences for London's commuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM to warn users before posting 'mean' comment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/instagram-s-anti-bullying-feature-warns-users-if-they-re-n1027521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Mosseri, the head of Facebook-owned Instagram, said the company is willing to make decisions that keep its users safe from online bullying, even if it leads to decreased usage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stricken Russian Nuke Sub Crew Prevented 'Planetary Catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/stricken-russian-nuke-sub-crew-prevented-planetary-catastrophe/ar-AAE1Fn5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr sees legal path for census citizenship query...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3455cd57e744af08c5690fe1f0517ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE LEAKING</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/07/08/donald-trumps-white-house-leaking-literally-media/1672287001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not totally unique: The press basement is below ground level, and frequently absorbs water after heavy rains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots, Not Humans: The New Space Explorers...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/07/08/733714689/robots-not-humans-are-the-new-space-explorers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landing a man on the moon captures the public's imagination. But in the decades after the Apollo program, robots have also generated public excitement about space exploration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to 'no longer deal' with UK ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/452024-trump-says-he-will-no-longer-deal-with-the-uks-ambassador-to-the-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday said he would “no longer deal with” the U.K.’s ambassador to the U.S. after leaked cables revealed the diplomat’s blunt assessment of the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Spacey Accuser Pleads Fifth After Failing To Provide Cell Phone As Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/07/08/kevin-nantucket-spacey-sexual-assault-trial-cell-phone-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case against actor Kevin Spacey returned to a Nantucket courtroom on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipe bomb explosions damage SC courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article232397052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren rakes in $19 million despite no fundraisers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/08/warren-rakes-in-19-million-despite-no-fundraisers-1400058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator far exceeded expectations, outpacing her rival on the left, Bernie Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem field readies for BIG shrink...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/08/2020-democratic-candidates-1399458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The winnowing process is about to begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pleads not guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/08/jeffrey-epstein-pleads-not-guilty-in-child-sex-trafficking-case.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy financier Jeffrey Epstein pleaded not guilty Monday to charges of sex trafficking dozens of underage girls more than a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag Show Starring Kids Draws Protesters, Heavy Police Presence...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/07/08/drag-show-mile-high-comics-protests-denver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters were kept behind a fence with a strong police presence outside an all ages drag show in Denver on Sunday. About a dozen young people participated in the show which caused some controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bible shortage? Publishers say tariffs could cause it...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/35b3c523466d4cc58db5507e6e1190ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS HITS CAPITAL</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/heavy-rain-slams-dmv-causes-flooding-road-closures-and-chaos/65-d0e9e375-3bde-4c87-891b-c150a2478449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Flash Flood Emergency prompted massive flooding across the DMV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIES TO CLINTON...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-jeffrey-epstein/us-financier-epstein-lured-underage-girls-to-his-mansions-for-sex-acts-prosecutors-idUSKCN1U3136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American financier Jeffrey Epstein was charged with sex trafficking on Monday, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAMP FLOODS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/weather/stories/Weather-Alert-Flash-Flood-Watch-in-Effect-Heavy-Rain-Possible-512404832.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy rain drenched the D.C. area Monday, leading to dangerous flash flooding, stranding drivers in vehicles, felling trees and even leaking into some Metro stations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand gun owners are refusing to turn over their firearms to the government...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/07/08/noncompliance-kneecaps-new-zealands-gun-control-scheme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of last week, only around 700 weapons had been turned over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern District of New York  Strikes Again!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-shouldnt-expect-to-wiggle-free-again-with-sdny-sex-trafficking-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feds in Florida cut an infamous sweetheart deal with the confessed billionaire sex predator. The ‘sovereign’ district of New York isn’t likely to do that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Workers Plan Prime Day Strike Despite $15-an-Hour Pledge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/amp/news/articles/2019-07-08/amazon-workers-plan-prime-day-strike-despite-15-an-hour-pledge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threats bring MORE to border?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/why-the-migrant-crisis-is-happening-now-eb2d38ee-8765-4a5f-a4ac-4c5ec36a868f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Droughts, political instability, a booming U.S. economy, technological advancements and asylum backlogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATINGS TOP MEN'S CHAMPIONSHIP GAME...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/07/megan-rapinoe-us-womens-world-cup-final-ratings-netherlands-team-usa-fox-1202642953/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are going to win, win big and conclusively, and that’s exactly what Team USA did yesterday at the 2019 Women’s World Cup, both on the pitch and in the ratings. Snaring their second consecuti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein charged with sex trafficking crimes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f995d90cbfd943169f74a0dbb3b1eadc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE WATCH: Is 'Big One' coming?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5a88585528b4243905700913471e9b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked secret cables...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8be524e9acc549f991f67ccc999b499a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATINGS TOP MEN'S CHAMPIONSHIP GAME...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/womens-world-cup-final-jumps-20-in-early-ratings-above-mens-2018-championship-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Women's World Cup trophy is coming back home to America -- again. Team USA made Fox Sports a winner on Sunday as well</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  FOXNEWS OVER CNN; DRUDGE OVER DAILYMAIL; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY moves in on Trump's tax returns... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/ny-gov-cuomo-signs-bill-allowing-congress-access-trump-s-n1027396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The measure ensures that "no one is above the law," the governor said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coco Gauff Wimbledon fairytale ends...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/tennis/coco-gauffs-wimbledon-2019-fairytale-17510854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 15-year-old was beaten in straight sets as Halep advanced to the quarter-finals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAMP FLOODS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/flood-the-swamp-d-c-gets-pelted-by-furious-rainstorm-and-the-videos-are-just-bonkers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's an extremely rainy Monday in Washington D.C. today, and commuters are reporting that the water levels have gotten so intense that multiple stops on the Metro rail are getting flooded at an a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer's Sad, Stale State of Movies: A New Low In Creativity?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/todd-mccarthy-summer-2019s-sad-stale-state-movies-1221932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aside from 'Toy Story 4,' this season looks to go down as a landmark low in major studio creativity — but how do the years that closed out the previous five decades measure up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailer: Zellweger as Judy Garland in Her Final Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/judy-trailer-renee-zellweger-plays-judy-garland-her-final-days-1222493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jessie Buckley, Finn Wittrock, Rufus Sewell and Michael Gambon round out the cast of the Rupert Goold-directed film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive crack opens in earth...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/before-and-after-ground-splits-open-after-ridgecrest-earthquake/5383181/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before-and-after aerial photographs are showing how a massive crack opened in the desert floor after the 7.1 Ridgecrest earthquake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE software engineer injures 8 in drug-induced Fourth of July rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/07/07/youtube-software-engineer-injures-lsd-rampage-police/1669362001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Betai Koffi's alleged drug-induced rampageÂ in Bodega Bay brought a violent end to eightÂ people's Fourth of July, authorities in California said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAST NETWORK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-charged-with-sex-trafficking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire allegedly built a trafficking pyramid scheme that involved girls as young as 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein charged with federal sex trafficking crimes involving minors...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-epstein-charged-20190708-2iqrv6w4wfdhjm32yxl7ighq6y-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multimillionaire sex offender Jeffrey Epstein couldn't dodge justice forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy arms destroyers with new high-powered laser, changes war tactics...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/navy-arms-destroyers-with-new-high-powered-laser-changes-war-tactics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If swarms of enemy small attack boats armed with guns and explosives approached a Navy ship, alongside missile-armed drones and helicopters closing into strike range, ship commanders would instantly begin weighing defensive options - to include interceptor missiles, electronic warfare, deck-mounted guns or area weapons such as Close-in-Weapons System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/6184408-U-S-v-Jeffrey-Epstein-Indictment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.documentcloud.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Source document contributed to DocumentCloud by Tom Namako (BuzzFeed).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I was 14. I had braces'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7224539/Jeffrey-Epstein-victims-recall-pedophile-forced-perform-sex-acts-ahead-bail-hearing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the women who accused Jeffrey Epstein of molesting them when they were minors will be in attendance for his court appearance on Monday in Manhattan for his bail hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC SOAKED!</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/weather-news/2019/07/flash-flood-risk-continues-for-dc-region-on-monday-morning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police across the region are urging drivers to stay off the roads as the National Weather Service has issued a flash flood emergency for the immediate D.C. metropolitan area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun Valley '19: Content Arms Race, Streaming Wars Center Stage After Turbulent Year...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/sun-valley-2019-content-streaming-allen-co-conference-1203260796/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUN VALLEY, Idaho — The art and commerce of the content business will surely be center stage this year as media moguls gather once again in this mountain resort for Allen &amp; Co.’s annual confere…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents so rattled -- they're sleeping outside...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/06/after-powerful-quakes-rock-the-ridgecrest-area-many-would-rather-stay-outdoors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many said they didn't want anything over their heads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Violent brawl breaks out at DISNEYLAND as children watch...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/2019/07/08/caught-on-video-fight-breaks-out-at-disneyland-as-children-watch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video posted to YouTube on Sunday captured a violent fight that broke out at Disneyland.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
