<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT INFECTED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-marcelo-ebrard-mexico-coronavirus-pandemic-vladimir-putin-7cf4feae9e363d519d5c336202be0ae6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador said Sunday he has tested positive for COVID-19 and that the symptoms are mild. Mexico's president, who has been criticized...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85% diversity...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-personnel-team-opm-7df87473-3fd3-4ff7-9289-c89994e50879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 85% of Biden's new political appointees to the Office of Personnel Management identify as people of color, women or LGBTQ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada Worries About Biden's 'Buy American'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/canada-worries-biden-buy-american-201549916.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Canada is uneasy about President Joe Biden’s planned “Buy American” provisions and will press the case against moves that would harm the countries’ $725 billion trade relationship, according to Canada’s top diplomat. Biden is expected to sign an executive order this week urging federal agencies to buy goods and services from U.S. companies. Marc Garneau, Canada’s foreign minister, said he expects the new administration will discuss the measures with Justin Trudeau’s government. “President Biden is aware of it and the Prime Minister made that very clear that we are concerned about Buy American policies, because it actually harms our bilateral trading relationship which is so tightly integrated,” Garneau said in a television interview with CBC News.The U.S. and Canada exchanged nearly $2 billion a day in goods and services in 2019, making it “the world’s most comprehensive trading relationship,” according to the State Department. Some industries, such as the automotive sector, have highly-connected supply chains that span the border.“Sometimes, some of the products that we sell to the United States already have American components in them. And those are messages that we carried a lot during the Nafta 2 negotiations” with the Trump administration, Garneau added.The minister’s remarks come after Biden dealt Trudeau a blow on inauguration day by revoking the permit for the Keystone XL pipeline that would have taken more than 800,000 barrels a day of crude from western Canada to Nebraska. Read More: For Trudeau, Life After Trump Is Off to a Rocky StartFor more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy SEAL sentenced to 10 years in Green Beret hazing death...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/military/dp-nw-seal-dedolph-20210124-sgmqqd2is5c6pnt553h5khemgm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEAL Team 6 member Tony DeDolph pleaded guilty earlier this month to involuntary manslaughter, acknowledging he applied the chokehold that killed Army Staff Sgt. Logan Melgar while trying to haze him in 2017 in Mali, West Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Get out Bolsonaro!' say ex-supporters in Brazil as pandemic weighs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210124201036-6e7xm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/ (PIX, TV):'Get out Bolsonaro!' say ex-supporters in Brazil as COVID-19, vaccines weigh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish woman who 'died' of covid returned 10 days later!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210124163449-51tpd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN:Spanish woman who 'died' of COVID returned 10 days later-newspaper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel closes skies to air travel, again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-fearing-virus-mutations-to-close-its-only-international-airport/ar-BB1d3gvl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Gurion International Airport will be shuttered for at least a week as country races to vaccinate more of the population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of vaccine supply could hinder distribution...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccine-supply-hinders-expanding-beyond-100-million-shots-goal-biden-health-official-says/ar-BB1d3bLN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony S. Fauci, the government’s senior infectious-disease expert, also said he now believes the coronavirus variant first detected in the United Kingdom is more deadly and spreads faster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic problems overwhelm global supply lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/pandemic-aftershocks-overwhelm-global-supply-lines/ar-BB1d3lz8?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One year after the coronavirus pandemic first disrupted global supply chains by closing Chinese factories, fresh shipping headaches are delaying U.S. farm exports, crimping domestic manufacturing and threatening higher prices for American consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico enters darkest days of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-enters-darkest-days-covid-110030753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's vaccination plan has been delayed after Pfizer said it would be shipping fewer doses of the shots than originally planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'California miracle' dissolved into a winter  nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-miracle-dissolved-winter-coronavirus-140021007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say California's brutal winter COVID-19 surge is largely driven by complacency on masking and distancing. One calls it 'COVID resentment.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to repeal Trump ban on transg joining military...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210124193701-se85e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ban brought in by Trump in 2017 on transgender people serving in the U.S. military could be lifted as early as Monday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to impose South Africa travel ban to combat new variant...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210124190027-ocgou</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAVEL (EXCLUSIVE, URGENT, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Biden to impose South Africa travel ban to combat new COVID-19 variant -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could homegrown strain be partly to blame for surge?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/could-homegrown-coronavirus-strain-partly-130053205.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California scientists have discovered a new coronavirus strain that appears to be propagating faster than any other variant in the Golden State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago teachers vote to teach from home, defying district...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-teaching-coronavirus-pandemic-chicago-d51f2ebe1504cfe36eb5ea8467567389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The Chicago Teachers Union said Sunday that its members voted to defy an order to return to the classroom over concerns about COVID-19, setting up a showdown with district officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ailing pope, reducing appearances, prays for homeless dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/rome-europe-pope-francis-vatican-city-43a81f536f871789979626e421dbd9fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Ailing Pope Francis, who this week is making limited public appearances due to persistent pain, has drawn attention to the plight of homeless people in winter, including a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel targets flights, religious scofflaws, as virus rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-israel-coronavirus-pandemic-religious-communities-jerusalem-c83aec91d6ed9935921f6109a161a409</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Sunday said Israel will be closing its international airport to nearly all flights, while Israeli police clashed with ultra-Orthodox...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHURCH SUNDAY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-pope-francis-jen-psaki-42db004ea67e67350c1a563adbece683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden attended Mass for the first time since taking office, worshipping Sunday at the church he frequented when he was vice president. Biden, the nation’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing number of Republican senators oppose impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-cabinets-trials-impeachments-82c0a1035ee55e6a8bda4d289943c641</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A growing number of Republican senators say they oppose holding an impeachment trial, a sign of the dimming chances that former President Donald Trump will be convicted on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. carrier group enters South China Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southchinasea-usa/us-carrier-group-enters-south-china-sea-amid-taiwan-tensions-idUSKBN29T05J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. aircraft carrier group led by the USS Theodore Roosevelt has entered the South China Sea to promote "freedom of the seas", the U.S. military said on Sunday, at a time when tensions between China and Taiwan have raised concern in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration plan may be risky for Dems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-politics-race-and-ethnicity-health-care-reform-7c0584e2e7a795e24aa3c829b98dde08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is confronting the political risk that comes with grand ambition. As one of his first acts, Biden offered a sweeping immigration overhaul last week that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan reports 2nd day of incursions by Chinese air force...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210124091524-55023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/SECURITY (URGENT):Taiwan reports second day of incursions by Chinese air force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten People Fighting the Forever War...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2021/01/america-forever-war-afghanistan/617776/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A devastating incident in Afghanistan shows the perils of relying on Special Operations alone to fight the nation’s battles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia's 'El Chapo' arrested in Amsterdam...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-55784104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia believes Tse Chi Lop's syndicate controls up to 70% of narcotics entering the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge of Student Suicides Pushes Vegas Schools to Reopen...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/24/surge-of-student-suicides-pushes-las-vegas-schools-to-reopen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reminders of pandemic-driven suffering among students in Clark County, Nev., have come in droves. Since schools shut their doors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb thrown into CA church criticized for extremist views on gay people...</title>
      <link>https://www.sgvtribune.com/2021/01/23/bomb-damages-el-monte-church-that-opposes-gay-marriage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sgvtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pastor of the First Works Baptist Church had filed a police report after an online threat was made. The FBI is investigating the attack and trying to close in on the motive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17-year-old in ICU after receiving second dose...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/17-year-old-in-icu-after-receiving-second-coronavirus-dose-656527</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man used $2M bailout for BENTLEY, TESLA, Vegas condos...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/24/man-used-2m-in-covid-relief-for-a-bentley-tesla-las-vegas-condos-feds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Las Vegas man allegedly stole about $2 million in federal COVID-19 relief funds meant for small businesses — all so he could buy luxury cars and homes, prosecutors said. Jorge Abramovs has …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MALIBU SNOW: Winter storm brings rare sight to SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/weather/winter-storm-brings-rare-snowfall-to-malibu/9958516/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malibu Canyon saw a rare snowfall on Saturday, just a week after seeing temperatures in the 80s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioting youths in Netherlands torch testing center...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/netherlands-health-coronavirus-pandemic-riots-amsterdam-550ce0c260d45131181727fbf41e8340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;URK, Netherlands (AP) — Rioting youths protesting on the first night of a Dutch curfew torched a coronavirus testing facility and threw fireworks at police in a Dutch fishing village. Police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wastes no time in first 100 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/24/joe-biden-president-100-hours-trump-legacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democrat has kicked off his presidency with a blitz of executive orders and measures – here are the key themes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests of leadership comes quickly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/tests-of-biden-e2-80-99s-leadership-and-gop-e2-80-99s-willingness-to-cooperate-come-quickly/ar-BB1d1NFv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president hopes to show government can work effectively to combat the pandemic and revive the economy while trying to change the political climate in the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will USA deploy Iron Dome to protect bases in Gulf?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/will-us-deploy-iron-dome-to-protect-bases-in-the-gulf-656516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"the system will assist the US Army in protecting American troops from ballistic and airborne threats as well as from developing threats in the areas where US troops are deployed on various missions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
