<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Stress test finds some banks could be stressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/25/fed-puts-restrictions-on-bank-dividends-after-test-finds-some-banks-could-be-stressed-in-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move signals that the unprecedented nature of the coronavirus pandemic, and the difficulty in forecasting what the future holds for banks, is making the Fed cautious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA TOO</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-06-25/florida-s-desantis-doesn-t-plan-to-move-to-next-phase-of-opening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to offer more 'context' on virus posts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-seeks-offer-more-context-virus-posts-193736510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook said Thursday it was looking to add notifications about the source of coronavirus-related posts and will warn users when they share stories that are more than 90 days old. Facebook Vice President John Hegeman said in a blog post the social media giant would be seeking to direct people to "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy investigating LSD ring...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/navy-warns-of-increase-in-personnel-taking-lsd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy disclosed on Thursday that it has seen an increase in its personnel purchasing, using, and distributing the hallucinogenic drug LSD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan prosecutor pick ducks questions about Barr's job offer...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/25/jay-clayton-sdny-bill-barr-339888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay Clayton — the chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission — made the remarks in a congressional hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobbyist Jack Abramoff Charged in Crypto-Currency Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/amp/news/articles/2020-06-25/lobbyist-abramoff-charged-in-crypto-currency-case-u-s-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORAD intercepts 2 Russian aircraft near Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://wpta21.com/2020/06/25/norad-intercepts-2-russian-aircraft-that-came-near-alaska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wpta21.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNEAU, Alaska (AP) — Military officials say two Russian aircraft were intercepted after they came within 50 miles of Unimak Island along Alaska’s Aleutian chain. The commander of the North American Aerospace Defense Command says Wednesday’s incident marked the fifth time this month that such an intercept has taken place. NORAD says the Russian aircraft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precinct commander quits in protest...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/25/bronx-nypd-precinct-commander-is-quitting-in-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Brea, a Bronx NYPD precinct commander, is quitting in protest of how the department is handling police reform, The Post has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong-un death rumors resurface; Japan reveals 'suspicions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11954967/kim-jong-un-dead-rumours-japan-suspicions-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN has revealed it has “some suspicions” about the health of the periodically missing North Korean dictator Kim Jong-un.   The country’s defence minister made the bombshell comment at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON buys Seattle arena naming rights, will call it 'Climate Pledge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/sports/hockey/amazon-buys-naming-rights-to-keyarena-will-call-it-climate-pledge-arena/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arena, home to the city’s incoming NHL franchise and WNBA's Storm, will be powered 100% by renewable electricity and seek to achieve a zero carbon footprint. NHL Seattle CEO Tod Leiweke said the arena aims to produce zero waste,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trumps LOSE attempt to gag Mary Trump from publishing tell-all book...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8460807/Trumps-LOSE-attempt-gag-Mary-Trump-judge-dismisses-petition-protective-order.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump family have lost their attempt to gag their niece from writing a tell-all book about them. A judge ruled that their application to stop Mary was 'fatally defective' and dismissed it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY changing 'Splash Mountain' ride tied to Jim Crow film...</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/entertainment/2020/06/25/disney-changing-splash-mountain-ride-tied-to-jim-crow-film/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid calls to change the Splash Mountain theme park ride because of its ties with “Song of the South,” the 1946 movie many view as racist, Disney officials said Thursday it was recasting the ride to make it based on “The Princess and the Frog,” the 2009 Disney film with an African American female lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan: 1 in 3 pilots have fake licenses...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/06/25/business/pakistan-fake-pilot-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 30% of civilian pilots in Pakistan have fake licenses and are not qualified to fly, the country's aviation minister revealed Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing, Tracking Still Plagued by Delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2020-06-25/virus-testing-tracking-still-plagued-by-reporting-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Used Missile With Long Blades to Kill Qaeda Leader in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-s-used-missile-with-long-blades-to-kill-qaeda-leader-in-syria/ar-BB15WcHZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe coronavirus resurgences alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53175459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If left unchecked the resurgences will "push health systems to the brink once again", the WHO warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to secure virus 'red zone' in southern Italy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thepeninsulaqatar.com/article/25/06/2020/Army-to-secure-virus-red-zone-in-southern-Italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepeninsulaqatar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The army was being sent in to secure a virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone footage catches huge great white lurking below surfers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1030159/footage-white-shark-prowling-six-surfers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS chilling footage shows a great white shark prowling just feet away from six oblivious surfers as they wait to catch a wave.  The drone footage, filmed by a local teenager, shows the fears…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNEAKY:  Your iPhone has hidden map of EVERYWHERE you go...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1035842/iphone-map-location-tracking-significant-settings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOUR iPhone keeps track of your real-world movements – which you can view on a map. The little-known feature is buried deep within your iPhone settings, and shows your exact movements over the past…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS PAUSES REOPENING</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/texas-governor-pauses-state-s-reopening-due-spike-new-covid-n1232118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The last thing we want to do as a state is go backwards and close down businesses," Gov. Greg Abbott said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Weigh Scrapping Football Season...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/ncaafb/colleges-weigh-scrapping-football-season-in-threat-to-a-cash-cow/ar-BB15XkPj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare red rainbow forms...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/red-rainbow-forms-over-birmingham-22249706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A red rainbow formed over Birmingham this month, with sky-watchers claiming the beautiful dome is so rare you are lucky if you witness it first-hand just once in your lifetime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece woos tourists with pledge of 'maximum' safety...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/greece-woos-tourists-pledge-maximum-virus-safety-153554991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece has taken every possible care to shield tourists from COVID-19 as it prepares to open additional airports to travellers on July 1, Prime Minister Kyriakos Mitsotakis said Thursday. With a quarter of the nation's economy dependent on tourism, the government faces an urgent challenge to reassure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury sent $1.4 BILLION in payments to DEAD PEOPLE...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report/botched-testing-1-200-for-the-dead-watchdog-audits-virus-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government’s quick action to issue stimulus payments in the wake of the coronavirus crisis led to more than a billion dollars of fraudulent payments, while slow action to address the health risks might have worsened the outbreak, according to a report by a government watchdog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incessant Fireworks Keeping Minneapolis Residents On Edge Amid Gun Violence...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/06/24/incessant-fireworks-keeping-minneapolis-residents-on-edge-amid-gun-violence-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a time when gun violence is becoming more common across Minneapolis, the consistent sound of fireworks is increasing fear and anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston facing 'apocalyptic' July 4...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/houston-facing-apocalyptic-july-4-134936261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Houston’s Covid-19 outbreak is accelerating at an exponential pace that will swamp the fourth-largest U.S. city’s medical infrastructure by the Independence Day holiday, less than two weeks away, a leading disease specialist warned.Even as Houston-area intensive-care wards approach full</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTBREAK:  TEXAS GETS REALITY CHECK...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/covid-19-gives-texas-reality-143042609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The Texas Medical Center in Houston is the largest health care complex in the world, so vast it describes itself, accurately, as a “medical city.” About 106,000 people work there, traversing 50 million square feet of property. If TMC were a stand-alone business district, it would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China could get coronavirus bailout from by U.S. taxpayers?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/how-scarce-us-taxpayer-money-could-wind-up-in-chinas-coffers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American taxpayer dollars intended to help countries weather the global downturn could flow into Chinese Communist Party coffers, U.S. officials and analysts fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/24/us-hits-highest-single-day-of-coronavirus-cases-at-36358-breaking-april-record.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grim milestone reported on Wednesday surpasses the peak that was hit in late April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED STATES OF INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-surge-map-7714f8d1-5ba1-46f8-9bf3-5d59938f2c95.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the grimmest map since Axios began tracking the weekly changes in coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 store  opens at Miami mall...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/covid-19-essentials-pop-up-offers-in-demand-supplies-for-pandemic-in-one-place/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 essentials. No, we’re not about to list off a bunch of items. COVID-19 Essential is the name of a new pop-up store in Aventura....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: World putting America in quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/921833/world-putting-america-quarantine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus is making the U.S. a pariah state and reshuffling the international order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WON'T FOLLOW NJ MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/06/24/president-trump-wont-follow-new-jersey-quarantine-mandate-during-upcoming-trip-white-house-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump recently traveled to Arizona, one of the states designated by New Jersey as a hotspot requiring quarantine. Trump will visit his Bedminster golf club this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Sexual Abuse Epidemic Rocking Gaming World...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-wild-west-of-twitch-video-game-streaming-where-sexual-abuse-runs-rampant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple women come forward to The Daily Beast to share their stories of sexual harassment and abuse on the popular video game-streaming platform, where victims have no recourse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops' use of military-grade speakers at protests prompts backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-orlando-george-floyd-protests-lrad-opd-20200625-vke7xwiggbg23llwetr4eggsz4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often described by critics as an acoustic weapon, the LRAD device was created for the military after the attack on USS Cole in 2000. It has since been marketed to domestic law enforcement and public safety agencies as a super-powered bullhorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saharan Dust Turns Skies Gray from Gulf Coast to Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/african-dust-turns-skies-gray-from-the-gulf-coast-to-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;African Dust Turns Skies Gray from the Gulf Coast to Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC Cops Caught on Tape Talking About 'Slaughtering' Black People...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/504454-3-north-carolina-police-officers-fired-after-conversation-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three police officers in North Carolina have been fired after they were heard on camera making racist comments, including the use of racial epithets and references to “slaughtering” Black people, police said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court 2020: Major rulings on abortion, Trump's tax returns still to come...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/supreme-court-2020-major-rulings-152456132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at the major Supreme Court rulings of 2020 and the pending cases yet to be decided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Adults Than Ever Live With Parents or Grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/25/more-adults-than-ever-live-with-parents-or-grandparents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record 32 million American adults were living with their parents or grandparents in April, according to the latest American</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo artist sees bump in desire to erase hateful skin art...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ca3686e2f5113a82a065626d2a07e86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELLOWS FALLS, Vt. (AP) — A Vermont tattoo artist who has long offered free removal or covering of hateful skin art like swastikas, SS lightning bolts or the words “white power” says he’s seen an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiorina for Joe...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/06/carly-fiorina-vote-biden/613474/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Republican presidential candidate Carly Fiorina tells The Ticket that she plans to vote for Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strangers To Selves: Only 35% Know Blood Type; One In Three Know 98.6 Is Avg Temp...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/strangers-to-ourselves-survey-reveals-how-little-americans-know-about-the-human-body/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey asked 2,000 Americans about their understanding of the human body and 35% couldn't even name their blood type.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prostitution, Substance Abuse, Spying: Inside Hollywood's Nastiest Producer Feud...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/allegations-prostitution-more-hollywoods-nastiest-producer-feud-1299878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the promising partnership between 'The Departed' and 'It' producer Roy Lee and tobacco heir John Middleton imploded amid "very public mudslinging."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Bizarre Events Happening All Over Globe...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/really-bizarre-things-are-happening-all-over-the-globe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just when you think that 2020 has been filled with enough trouble, even more stuff starts happening.  Coming into this week, we were already dealing with a new COVID-19 surge which has pushed the number of daily cases to the highest levels we have seen so far, a global economy which is in the proces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$60 million painting will test art market's resilience...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/25/60-million-painting-marks-biggest-test-for-art-market-during-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday's auction marks the first real test of the global art market since the coronavirus pandemic and is a bold experiment in bidding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Weigh Scrapping Football Season in Threat to Cash Cow...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/colleges-that-live-for-football-hope-to-play-through-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colleges Weigh Scrapping Football Season in Threat to a Cash Cow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Biohacker's Improbable Bid to Make DIY Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-06-25/one-biohacker-s-improbable-bid-to-make-a-diy-covid-19-vaccine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist to Peform First Ever-Walk Space Walk...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/202006251079718465-first-ever-contract-for-tourist-walk-in-outer-space-signed-russian-space-corporation-reveals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roscosmos and Space Adventures have been cooperating in space tourism since 2001, when the first space tourist, Dennis Tito, went into orbit. Since then, a total of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows abusive taming of baby elephant for Thai tourism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/video-shows-abusive-taming-baby-elephant-thai-tourism-023654200.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of a distressed baby elephant jabbed by bullhooks at a Thai camp to tame it before joining the tourist industry has been released by conservationists in an appeal to end the practice. The footage, taken on a hidden camera last year and published Wednesday by UK-based animal rights group World</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oz tech titans to build world's tallest 'hybrid timber' tower...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oz-tech-titans-build-worlds-tallest-hybrid-timber-072153271.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global software giant Atlassian will build the world's tallest "hybrid timber" building for its new headquarters in Sydney, the company said Thursday. The 40-storey structure, coming in at 180 metres (590 ft), will be constructed with timber mass -- layers of softwoods pressed together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Sagging Popularity Drags Down Republican Senate Candidates...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/25/trumps-sagging-popularity-drags-down-republican-senate-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Trump’s erratic performance in office and his deteriorating standing in the polls is posing a grave threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ Overwhelmed With Demand for Tests as U.S. System Shows Strain...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/25/arizona-overwhelmed-with-demand-for-tests-as-u-s-system-shows-strain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People seeking drive-up coronavirus tests in Phoenix faced a three-mile-long car line last weekend. On Friday, Arizona’s largest laboratory received</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Faces of conquerors': Trump trip to Rushmore draws fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/50f6bdb9e2fd2349bb39b99c1250b093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — President Donald Trump’s plans to kick off Independence Day with a showy display at Mount Rushmore are drawing sharp criticism from Native Americans who view the monument...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron Gets $100 Million Investment to Build Media Empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/lebron-james-maverick-carter-s-springhill-to-be-a-media-empire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James Gets $100 Million Investment to Build Media Empire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls for slave reparations gain steam...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200624170052-dt00z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has never gotten far on whether or how to compensate African Americans for slavery, now support is growing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census shows white decline, nonwhite majority among youngest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a3600edf620ccf2759080d00f154c069</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — For the generation of Americans not yet old enough to drive, the demographic future has arrived. For the first time, nonwhites and Hispanics were a majority of people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  U.S. Marshals to help protect monuments nationwide... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/U-S-Marshals-told-to-prepare-to-help-protect-15364721.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - U.S. Marshals have been told they should prepare to help protect national monuments across the country, according to an email directive viewed by The Washington Post, as President Donald Trump has vowed stern punishment for those who vandalize or destroy such structures as part of police violence protests.  In an email, Marshals Assistant Director Andrew Smith wrote that the service "has been asked to immediately prepare to provide federal law enforcement support to protect national monuments (throughout the country)."  "This is a challenging assignment due to the breadth of possible targets for criminal activity," Smith wrote. He said the Marshals Incident Management Team would start a Joint Operations Center in Springfield, Va., to coordinate, and every deputy in the Special Operations Group would be made available to help as soon as Thursday. He also asked other districts and divisions to identify people they might be able to lend to the effort until July 8.  On Monday, protesters attempted to topple a statue of President Andrew Jackson in a park next to the White House, though police in riot gear intervened and stopped them. That night, Trump tweeted his dismay, and the next morning he wrote that he had "authorized the Federal Government to arrest anyone who vandalizes or destroys any monument, statue or other such Federal property in the U.S. with up to 10 years in prison, per the Veteran's Memorial Preservation Act, or such other laws that may be pertinent....."  Earlier Wednesday, defense officials said that the Army activated about 400 unarmed members of the District of Columbia National Guard to "prevent any defacing or destruction" of monuments.  Jackson, a former general in the U.S. Army, was known for his harsh treatment of Native Americans as president. He signed the Indian Removal Act, which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  KUNG FLU FIGHTING</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-elicits-backlash-over-racist-language-15364474.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's first public use of the phrase "kung flu" - during a campaign rally in Tulsa, Okla., last weekend - drew broad political backlash as a racist slur against Asian Americans.  Within three days, however, it was also something else: a rallying cry for his supporters.  Trump's appearance before a crowd of several thousand enthusiastic young people at the Dream City Church in Phoenix on Tuesday showed how his casual use of a demeaning phrase - one that even some White House aides rejected three months ago - has swiftly morphed into a staple of his reelection message amid tumbling poll numbers.  The president hadn't even used the words in Phoenix before audience members, presumably primed from having heard his riff on the "many names" of the coronavirus at the Tulsa rally, beat him to the punchline and began shouting out "kung flu" - prompting Trump, with a grin, to repeat it.  "Kung flu - yeah," Trump said, eliciting cheers. "Kung flu."  The episode laid bare how, despite attempts from White House aides to justify Trump's rhetoric as a way to pin the blame for the coronavirus pandemic on China, where it originated, the president appears more interested in juicing his conservative base.  "The fact that he got the crowd so riled up was just chilling," said Chris Lu, a Chinese American who served as cabinet secretary in the Obama administration. "In that really primal desire to get a rise out of the crowd and get that affirmation he wants, he went to this place that has such bad consequences for Asian Americans broadly and for Asian American kids in particular. It's a joke to him but not to us."  Lu was among a number of prominent Asian Americans, including actor George Takei, former U.S. attorney Preet Bharara and tech entrepreneur Andrew Yang,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL IN THE FAMILY:  President's Brother Was in ICU Just Before Filing Suit Over Book...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumps-brother-robert-was-in-icu-just-before-filing-suit-over-niece-marys-tell-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Trump, Donald’s younger brother, spent at least 10 days in a neuro intensive care unit just before launching legal action to stop the publication of his niece’s book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET SERVICE QUARANTINE AFTER RALLY</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Dozens-of-Secret-Service-officers-and-agents-told-15364507.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Dozens of Secret Service officers and agents who were on site for President Donald Trump's rally in Tulsa, Okla., last week were ordered to self-quarantine after two of their colleagues tested positive for the novel coronavirus, part of the fallout from Trump's insistence on holding the mass gathering over the objections of public health officials.  The Secret Service instructed employees who worked the Tulsa event to stay at home for 14 days when they returned from the weekend trip, according to two people familiar with the agency's decision.  The order came in the wake of the discovery - hours before the president's Saturday evening rally - that at least six advance staffers who helped organize the trip had tested positive for the virus, including two Secret Service employees. Another two advance staffers tested positive after Trump returned to Washington on Sunday.  On Tuesday, the Secret Service field office in Tulsa arranged for a special testing session at a hospital to determine if local agents had contracted the virus while assisting with the rally, according to two other people with knowledge of the testing. As part of the arrangement, doctors administered the test to both agents and some local officials in parked cars outside the hospital.  Among those who got tested was U.S. Attorney Trent Shores of the Northern District of Oklahoma, who had attended both pre-planning meetings with advance staff and the rally in case any legal issues arose, according to spokeswoman Lennea Montandon. Shores tested negative, she said.  It is still unknown how the rally may have impacted Tulsa's count of coronavirus cases, which are rising swiftly. Tulsa County hit a record Wednesday, with 259 new confirmed cases, part of "steep upward trends" seen across Oklahoma, said Bruce Dart, the director of Tulsa's health...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Department of Justice broadens case against Julian Assange...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Department-of-Justice-broadens-case-against-15364689.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Department of Justice outlined new evidence Wednesday to bolster its case against Julian Assange, in an updated indictment that accuses the WikiLeaks founder of soliciting hackers to break into the Icelandic government's computers to steal information that could be leaked to embarrass the government.  FBI agents and prosecutors in Manhattan were close to making a criminal hacking case against WikiLeaks based on these allegations in 2011, but were blocked by senior officials, who wanted to focus on an espionage case against Assange in Virginia, according to people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity because they were not authorized to speak publicly about an investigation.  The Obama administration ultimately decided not to pursue the espionage case because of First Amendment concerns; it was revived under President Donald Trump, over the objections of some prosecutors involved.  The superseding indictment does not add to the 18 charges accusing Assange of working with former Army private Chelsea Manning in 2010 to steal classified documents from the U.S. government. The statute of limitations for the new allegations has expired. But the document adds evidence to the government's assertions that Assange is not a publisher or journalist but a hacker.  Assange is currently fighting extradition from the United Kingdom.  The new indictment in federal court in Alexandria, Va., alleges that Assange asked a teenager to illegally obtain recordings of phone conversations between politicians in a foreign country. The description matches that of Sigurdur Thordarson, an Icelandic hacker who was interviewed by prosecutors last year. Assange and Thordarson made a "joint attempt" to decrypt a file stolen from an Icelandic bank, according to the indictment.  Assange was evidently angry at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  KUNG FLU FIGHTING</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-elicits-backlash-over-racist-language-15364474.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's first public use of the phrase "kung flu" - during a campaign rally in Tulsa, Okla., last weekend - drew broad political backlash as a racist slur against Asian Americans.  Within three days, however, it was also something else: a rallying cry for his supporters.  Trump's appearance before a crowd of several thousand enthusiastic young people at the Dream City Church in Phoenix on Tuesday showed how his casual use of a demeaning phrase - one that even some White House aides rejected three months ago - has swiftly morphed into a staple of his reelection message amid tumbling poll numbers.  The president hadn't even used the words in Phoenix before audience members, presumably primed from having heard his riff on the "many names" of the coronavirus at the Tulsa rally, beat him to the punchline and began shouting out "kung flu" - prompting Trump, with a grin, to repeat it.  "Kung flu - yeah," Trump said, eliciting cheers. "Kung flu."  The episode laid bare how, despite attempts from White House aides to justify Trump's rhetoric as a way to pin the blame for the coronavirus pandemic on China, where it originated, the president appears more interested in juicing his conservative base.  "The fact that he got the crowd so riled up was just chilling," said Chris Lu, a Chinese American who served as cabinet secretary in the Obama administration. "In that really primal desire to get a rise out of the crowd and get that affirmation he wants, he went to this place that has such bad consequences for Asian Americans broadly and for Asian American kids in particular. It's a joke to him but not to us."  Lu was among a number of prominent Asian Americans, including actor George Takei, former U.S. attorney Preet Bharara and tech entrepreneur Andrew Yang,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Multiple Teams' Interested In Kaepernick...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/multiple-teams-interested-in-colin-kaepernick-could-set-up-workouts-closer-to-training-camp-per/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ongoing pandemic could be the main holdup in teams organizing workouts for the QB</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Has to Demolish His $50 Million Mega-Mansion Because of 'Racism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2020/06/mohamed-hadid-mansion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He called the California Supreme Court ruling a “political lynching.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES top editor says won't step down amid newsroom diversity criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/norman-pearlstine-la-times-executive-editor-will-not-resign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norman Pearlstine spoke with staffers at a nearly five-hour town hall on the newsroom's failures to recruit and support non-white journalists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEYLAND DELAYS REOPENING</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disneyland-delays-theme-park-resort-reopening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Park was set to reopen on July 17, but no new date was announced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD INFECTIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Coronavirus-deaths-lag-behind-surging-infections-15364490.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With novel coronavirus infections setting a single-day national record Wednesday, health experts are taking little solace from one of the few bright spots in the current resurgence: deaths are not rising in lockstep with caseloads.  But that may be just a matter of time.  "Deaths always lag considerably behind cases," Anthony Fauci, the nation's top infectious-disease specialist, told Congress at a hearing Tuesday. In the weeks to come, he and others said, the death toll is likely to rise commensurately.  Which means Arizona, Texas and Florida, states that reopened early and now are experiencing runaway infection rates, are likely to be burying more dead in July.  "As long as there is a fair amount of testing going on, if there is an uptick in covid-19 infections, then we are likely to see that in the confirmed case data before we see it in the death data," said Nicholas Reich, associate professor of biostatistics at the University of Massachusetts at Amherst, in an email.  He predicted "rises in covid-19 deaths over the next month in many of the states that are seeing upticks in cases, like Texas, California, Florida and others, even though the deaths have been either steady or declining in recent weeks."  The virus has come surging back in recent days, with 38,115 U.S. infections Wednesday, more than any previous day in the pandemic, including the catastrophic days of April. This time, the increases are mainly in the South and West, while New York and New Jersey, which were nearly overwhelmed in the spring and have been slow to reopen, are seeing declining cases.  California, which shut down early and has taken a slow approach toward reopening, nevertheless reported more than 7,000 new cases Wednesday, easily surpassing its record of 5,019 set Tuesday. Oklahoma - where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delegates to stay home...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-tell-convention-delegates-to-stay-home-during-pandemic/ar-BB15VI0i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expand the battleground map or play it safe?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article243720022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California voters to decide if restoring affirmative action... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-voters-asked-restore-affirmative-215427910.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California voters will be asked in November whether to erase Proposition 209, which banned the use of race and gender as consideration for government contracts and in college admissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucson Police Chief Offers Resignation Over Death of Hispanic Man in Custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/tucson-police-chief-chris-magnus-offers-resignation-over-horrible-death-of-carlos-ingram-lopez-in-custody</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A disturbing video released Wednesday shows Carlos Ingram-Lopez begging for water and complaining that he can’t breathe while being restrained by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange charges expanded...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1034838/julian-assange-prosecutors-charges-wikileaks-anonymous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Department of Justice “broadened” charges against WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange on Wednesday – claiming he conspired with hackers linked to the shady web activist group Ano…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA JUMPS 70% IN 48 HRS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1034237/covid-cases-california-70percent-jump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW coronavirus cases in California rose to almost 70 percent in a period of just two days. California Governor Gavin Newsom shared the grim statistics and added that he may reinstate strict rules …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT, NJ, NY implement mandatory 14-day quarantine for travelers from hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/tri-state-to-require-visitors-from-covid-hotspots-to-quarantine/2482284/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governors of New York, New Jersey and Connecticut said Wednesday they will implement a mandatory quarantine on visitors to their states from viral hotspots, part of a coordinated effort to sustain low local infection rates as coronavirus cases surge to two-month highs across nearly half of the country. The order, which goes into effect at 11:59 p.m. ET Wednesday,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  BIDEN 14 POINT LEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/biden-takes-dominant-lead-in-poll-as-voters-reject-trump-on-virus-and-race/ar-BB15U5LL?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handcuffed, left face-down on ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/tucson-police-chief-chris-magnus-offers-resignation-after-mans-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucson, Arizona, police chief offers resignation after man’s death in custody comes to light; three officers quit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard to protect DC monuments...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/24/politics/dc-national-guard-protests/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DC National Guard will provide unarmed guard members to assist with additional security for monuments in Washington, DC, the National Guard Bureau said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLYNN FREE: Appeals court orders judge to dismiss charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/24/us-appeals-court-orders-judge-to-dismiss-case-against-michael-flynn.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court ordered a judge to dismiss the criminal case against Michael Flynn, who briefly served as President Trump's first national security advisor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://tucson.com/news/local/watch-now-police-body-cam-video-of-tucson-man-s-in-custody-death-graphic-content/video_1553fe89-235f-5dbc-93f8-96a37203b387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tucson.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: RAW, GRAPHIC VIDEO. Body-camera video of Tucson Police officers trying to restrain Carlos Ingram-Lopez, 27, on April 21, 2020. Ingram-Lopez died in policy custody. Video by Tucson Police Department</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Openly gay candidates poised to make historic wins in NY...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200624223947-3oi3i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-LGBT/ELECTION:Openly gay candidates poised to make historic wins in New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THREATENS $1,000 FINE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200624193836-mxc3f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 4, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 4-New forecast predicts 180,000 U.S. deaths from COVID-19 by October</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ supports legal challenge to Hawaii traveler quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/88809cda9ae98da5c32fcea616dc2f85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — A quarantine imposed on travelers arriving to Hawaii discriminates against out-of-state residents, the U.S. Department of Justice said in support of a lawsuit challenging the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASES SURGE AMONG YOUNG</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/753ed7dc88ec5ce8906967f268d78b99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) — Coronavirus cases are climbing rapidly among young adults in a number of states where bars, stores and restaurants have reopened — a disturbing generational shift that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confederate store in Branson, Missouri, at protests' center...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/13bb9ea2bee3e25c38eaa730b18e20a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRANSON, Mo. (AP) — Branson, Missouri, may be known for its country music shows and wholesome entertainment, but the tourist hot spot now finds itself at the center of a standoff over Confederate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems plan virtual convention...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/09785e274676e46351c70644d2b77215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats will hold an almost entirely virtual presidential nominating convention Aug. 17-20 in Milwaukee using live broadcasts and online streaming, party officials said Wednesday. Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning signs keep mounting...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/warning-signs-keep-mounting-for-trump-from-polls-to-primaries/ar-BB15UEhj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes can't sue TWITTER over statements by fake cow, judge rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/nation-world/national/article243664982.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BET founder mocks crowds pulling down statues, calls them 'borderline anarchists'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/bet-founder-mocks-crowds-statues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BET founder Robert Johnson, in an interview Wednesday with Fox News, blasted those who are toppling Confederate and other statues across the nation as "borderline anarchists" -- while challenging the notion that black Americans support this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Lost Control. Then The Agency Disappeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/danvergano/cdc-coronavirus-containment-redfield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s premier health agency pushed a flawed coronavirus containment strategy — until it disappeared from public view one day before the outbreak was declared a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarce medical oxygen worldwide leaves many gasping for life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df97326ec00fb7cc4abf5b3821ace984</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONAKRY, Guinea (AP) — Guinea’s best hope for coronavirus patients lies inside a neglected yellow shed on the grounds of its main hospital: an oxygen plant that has never been turned on....</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
