<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>One-in-three chance of 'massive' disaster worse than COVID-19, says DEUTSCHE BANK...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/theres-a-one-in-three-chance-of-a-massive-disaster-that-could-be-worse-than-covid-19-says-deutsche-bank-2020-06-17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank says there is at least a one-in-three chance that at least one of four major tail risks will occur within the next decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive spying on users of GOOGLE CHROME shows new security weakness...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-alphabet-google-chrome-exclusive-idUKKBN23P0JM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A newly discovered spyware effort attacked users through 32 million downloads of extensions to Google's market-leading Chrome web browser, researchers at Awake Security told Reuters, highlighting the tech industry's failure to protect browsers as they are used more for email, payroll and other sensitive functions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV nets hire PI to probe stars' socials for racism...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/06/17/tv-networks-hire-pi-to-scope-stars-social-media-for-racism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California-based firm Edward Myers &amp; Associates will be conducting the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON: Trump Said Journalists Should Be 'Executed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/white-house-chaos-and-personal-favors-to-dictators-11-insane-revelations-from-reports-on-boltons-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new series of report have provided a sneak peek into John Bolton's upcoming book, and it reveals several shocking anecdotes about what the former White House national security adviser observed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'White Lives Matter' Spray Painted On Arthur Ashe Memorial...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/06/17/white-lives-matter-sprayed-on-arthur-ashe-memorial-in-virginia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statue of African American tennis legend Arthur Ashe on Richmond, Virginia's, Monument Avenue has been vandalized with the words "White Lives Matter."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard soldiers activated for Trump rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jun/17/national-guard-soldiers-activated-donald-trump-ral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 250 Oklahoma Army National Guard soldiers are being activated to help provide security during President Donald Trump’s campaign rally Saturday in Tulsa, authorities said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>592-page memoir!</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Trump-asked-China-s-Xi-to-help-him-win-15347229.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump asked Chinese President Xi Jinping to help him win the 2020 U.S. election, telling Xi during a summit dinner last year that increased agricultural purchases by Beijing from American farmers would aid his electoral prospects, according to a damning new account of life inside the Trump administration by former national security adviser John Bolton.  During a one-on-one meeting at the June 2019 Group of 20 summit in Japan, Xi complained to Trump about China critics in the United States. But Bolton writes in a book scheduled to be released next week that "Trump immediately assumed Xi meant the Democrats. Trump said approvingly that there was great hostility among the Democrats.  "He then, stunningly, turned the conversation to the coming U.S. presidential election, alluding to China's economic capability to affect the ongoing campaigns, pleading with Xi to ensure he'd win," Bolton writes. "He stressed the importance of farmers, and increased Chinese purchases of soybeans and wheat in the electoral outcome. I would print Trump's exact words but the government's prepublication review process has decided otherwise."  At the same meeting, Xi also defended China's construction of camps housing as many as 1 million Uighur Muslims in Xinjiang - and Trump signaled his approval.  "According to our interpreter," Bolton writes, "Trump said that Xi should go ahead with building the camps, which Trump thought was exactly the right thing to do."  The episode described by Bolton in his book, "The Room Where It Happened: A White House Memoir," bears striking similarities to the actions that resulted in Trump's impeachment after he sought to pressure the Ukrainian president to help dig up dirt on Democratic rival Joe Biden in exchange for military assistance. The China allegation also comes amid ongoing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW CHINA OUTBREAK RAISES FEARS FOR WORLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/local/beijing-outbreak-raises-coronavirus-fears-for-rest-of-the-world/ar-BB15C6Im</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON: Trump Said Journalists Should Be 'Executed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/trump-said-scumbag-journalists-should-be-executed-bolton-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He also describes a summer 2019 meeting in New Jersey where Trump says journalists should be jailed so they have to divulge their sources: 'These people should be executed. They are scumbag</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden calls revelations 'morally repugnant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Joe-Biden-reacts-to-allegations-against-Trump-in-15348038.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former vice president Joe Biden released a scathing statement Wednesday, describing President Donald Trump's actions as alleged in former national security adviser John Bolton's new book as "morally repugnant" and accusing the president of ignoring the coronavirus threat to keep his trade deal with China alive.  Biden, the presumptive Democratic nominee to challenge Trump in November, reacted to Bolton's claim that Trump tried to convince Chinese President Xi to increase imports from American farmers because it would be good for his reelection prospects.  "He was willing to trade away our most cherished democratic values for the empty promise of a flimsy trade deal that bailed him out of his disastrous tariff war that did so much damage to our farmers, manufacturers, and consumers," Biden said in a statement. "If these accounts are true, it's not only morally repugnant, it's a violation of Donald Trump's sacred duty to the American people to protect America's interests and defend our values."  Biden then linked Trump's handling of the coronavirus pandemic to his desire for a finished trade deal with Xi for political leverage. It's why, Biden posits, that Trump continued to praise the Chinese government and downplay the threat even as the coronavirus began to spread.  America has "been hurt far worse because of Donald Trump's inability to lead and his failure to meet the crisis." Biden said. "Today we learned more about the depth and nature of that failure," Biden added.  Missing from his lengthy statement is reaction to Bolton essentially confirming the charges leveled by Democrats against Trump during the impeachment inquiry. Biden unwittingly became a central figure in that probe as it centered around Trump freezing military aid to Ukraine to pressure that country to launch an investigation into Biden and his son,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot surgeon sews you up...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/intel-uc-berkeley-motion2vec-ai-robot-surgery-203003829.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UC Berkeley team, led by Dr. Ajay Tanwani, has developed a semi-supervised AI deep-learning system, dubbed Motion2Vec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Buffalo protester pushed by cops has fractured skull, cannot walk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/16/us/martin-gugino-protester-skull/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Gugino, the 75-year-old protester who was pushed by two Buffalo, New York, police officers earlier this month, has a fractured skull and is not able to walk, his lawyer said in a statement provided to CNN on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Now Predicts 200,000 U.S. Deaths by October...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-white-house-model-prediction-200000-deaths-october/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prediction went up by more than 30,000 since last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than Third of Americans Think Civil War 'Likely'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/06/16/poll-34-of-american-voters-think-second-civil-war-is-likely/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in three voters believes that the United States could face another civil war soon, as unrest rages across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three months later, Prince Charles's sense of smell, taste still not back...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-53026903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prince discusses his experience with Covid-19 as the royals return to public engagements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators unveil bill to limit Big Tech protections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/4-us-senators-unveil-bill-limit-big-tech-175644647.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four Republican senators introduced a bill Wednesday aimed at limiting legal protections of Big Tech platforms if they "selectively" suppress certain content, stepping up a political battle with social media. Senator Josh Hawley said his measure, if enacted, "gives users the right to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trillions in Bailout Go Unchecked With Watchdogs Kept Toothless...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/coronavirus/trillions-in-stimulus-go-unchecked-with-watchdogs-kept-toothless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has spent more than half of $3 trillion in economic rescue funds passed by Congress -- with little of the oversight intended to ensure the money goes to the right places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Danny Masterson charged with raping 3 women...</title>
      <link>https://hollywoodreporter.com/news/70s-show-star-danny-masterson-charged-raping-three-women-1299061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged separate incidents occurred between 2001 and 2003, according to authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASK DEBATE DIVIDING AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/necessary-or-needless-three-months-pandemic-americans-are-divided-wearing-n1231191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From "caution fatigue" to confusing advice, some are questioning whether they should still take safety measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov: 'White people need to listen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msnbc.com/craig-melvin/watch/virginia-governor-says-he-s-learned-a-lot-with-more-he-can-do-on-racial-justice-85236293785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geoff Bennett sat down with Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam to talk about racial justice, where the governor says the burden of educating people on racism "needs to shift from people of color to people who look like me."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA rushing to complete Mars launch before planet moves out of range...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/nasa-rushing-to-complete-mars-launch-before-planet-moves-out-of-range-mission-to-include-first-ever-helicopter-exploration/ar-BB15CUYw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Matter protester sucker-punched as bikers overwhelm rally...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/17/black-lives-matter-protester-sucker-punched-as-bikers-overwhelm-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small Black Lives Matter rally in an Ohio village was overwhelmed by hundreds of armed bikers, disturbing video shows. “Take the black lives s–t and shove it up your ass!” one o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danny Masterson charged with raping 3 women...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/that-70s-show-actor-danny-masterson-charged-with-raping-3-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Danny Masterson, known for his roles in “That ’70s Show” and “The Ranch,” has been charged with forcibly raping three women in separate incidents in his Hollywoo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacKenzie Bezos partners with Melinda Gates...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90518094/mackenzie-bezos-unveils-her-first-public-philanthropic-effort-with-a-famous-partner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MacKenzie Bezos and Melinda Gates are teaming up for a philanthropic effort to help women gain more power and influence by 2030.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Nude suspect spent night atop railroad sign, punched out K-9 dog...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/police-nude-suspect-spent-night-atop-railroad-sign-punched-out-k-9-dog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUGENE, Ore. (KVAL) &amp;mdash; Eugene police said a man who spent the night perched nude atop a railroad crossing sign attempted to run from police after more than 12 hours on the pole. K9 police dog Cwyk caught up with the suspect, who "was actively fighting" the police dog when officers got to them. Police said the suspect put the dog in a headlock and punched it several times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodward's new book coming in Sept...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/17/politics/bob-woodward-donald-trump-new-book/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is about to get the Bob Woodward treatment again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNCLE BEN to Change 'Brand Identity'...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/06/17/virginia-based-mars-says-its-planning-to-evolve-uncle-bens-rice-hours-after-aunt-jemima-brand-retired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uncle Ben's owner Mars is planning to change the rice maker's "brand identity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONG ROAD AHEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/06/17/rising-covid-19-cases-hospitalization-long-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is confronting the reality that the coronavirus will be with us for many months, and lapses in vigilance will lead to more sickness and death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas hospitalizations surge 11% in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/17/texas-coronavirus-hospitalizations-surge-11percent-in-a-single-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people sickened with Covid-19 across Texas' hospitals hit a new high Wednesday, surging about 11% in a single day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson in fender-bender after protester rushes car...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0312394beb38c2be0ac5129e9ab0cff1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson was in a minor car crash on Wednesday after a protester ran in front of the vehicle as it left Parliament. No one was hurt.  Footage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top DOJ official announces resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/top-doj-official-announces-resignation-hours-after-appearing-in-lawsuit-over-bolton-book  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT 'LIAR' IN FIRST TV CLIP...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8429083/Bill-Barrs-DOJ-sues-John-Bolton-try-block-bombshell-book-working-Donald-Trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States government sued former National Security Advisor John Bolton, accusing him of breach of contract and claiming publication of his book would put out classified information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE  Racially Profiles Via Artificial Intelligence, Algorithms?</title>
      <link>https://hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/youtube-alleged-racially-profile-artificial-intelligence-algorithms-1298926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit taking direct aim at Section 230 of the Communications Decency Act says the site applies "restricted mode" to videos tagged "Black Lives Matter," among other names, words, and phrases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGS should socially distance from other pets to avoid catching...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11882671/keep-your-dog-socially-distanced-coronavirus-fda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOG walkers should make sure their pets observe social distancing so they don’t catch coronavirus, a US health agency has warned. The Food and Drug Administration issued new guidance saying p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHAKY', 'WEAK': LINCOLN PROJECT questions Trump's health in new ad...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/920460/new-lincoln-project-ad-controversially-questions-trumps-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lincoln Project released its latest ad against President Trump on Tuesday, a 45 second spot focusing on his health that begins with a woman intoning, 'Something's wrong with Donald Trump.' The Lincoln Project is a political action committee formed by current and ex-Republicans who don't want to see Trump re-elected. Their previous ads have broached topics Trump is sensitive about, including the crowd size at his inauguration and how he 'dodged the draft' during the Vietnam War. This new ad delivers the deepest gut punch yet. Titled '#TrumpIsNotWell,' it features a montage of Trump seemingly struggling with drinking a glass of water and walking down a ramp, as well as footage of him going up the stairs to Air Force One with what appears to be toilet paper under his shoe. The narrator calls Trump 'shaky' and 'weak,' and says White House reporters should be covering Trump's 'secretive midnight run to Walter Reed Medical Center.' It's clear to everyone, the ad concludes, that now is the time 'we talk about this: Trump is not well.' Some people have argued that because Trump has mocked a disabled reporter and calls former Vice President Joe Biden 'Sleepy Joe,' frequently intimating he is cognitively impaired, Trump's own health is fair game and people should speculate away. Rebecca Cokley, director of the Disability Justice Initiative at the liberal Center for American Progress, disagrees. In an op-ed for The Washington Post published Tuesday, Cokley wrote that when people who do not have medical degrees diagnose Trump with various health issues, it hurts those who are actually disabled. 'Every single professional with a disability I know has been questioned privately and publicly about whether their 'condition' hinders their ability to do their job,' Cokley said. 'This is a universal truth and fear for any individual across physical, mental, intellectual, sensory, and chronic illness communities.' A person's ability to 'use a ramp or drink from a glass of water has no bearing on whether someone can fulfill the essential functions of a job,' she added, and instead, the focus should be on Trump's policies and actions while in office. 'The ableism that pervades society makes it easy to argue that someone is a failure because they're disabled, not because they're evil, unethical, and unqualified,' Cokley said. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NON-WHITES ACCOUNT FOR 64% OF COVID CASES...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/people-of-color-account-for-majority-of-coronavirus-infections-new-cdc-study-says-214850885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;African-Americans and Latinos are vastly overrepresented when it comes to coronavirus infections, according to an analysis released by the Centers for Disease Control on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarborough Rips Zuckerberg for 'Promoting Extremism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/joe-scarborough-morning-joe-facebook-promotes-extremism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Morning Joe" host says Facebook pushes users to extremist sites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: I WOULDN'T GO TO TRUMP RALLY</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/of-course-not-dr-fauci-says-he-definitely-wouldnt-attend-trumps-tulsa-rally-warns-we-havent-gotten-out-of-our-first-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Of course not': Dr. Fauci says he definitely wouldn't attend Trump's Tulsa rally, warns 'we haven't gotten out of our first wave' of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia requiring all visitors to pay $3,000 deposit to cover possible costs...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/920508/cambodia-requiring-all-visitors-pay-3000-deposit-cover-possible-coronavirus-costs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're thinking about traveling to Cambodia anytime soon, you should probably be aware of the country's recent announcement that all visitors â€” in light of the coronavirus pandemic â€” are required to pay a $3,000 deposit upon arrival at the airport. Cambodian officials have said the mandatory deposit is refundable after fees are deducted for COVID-19 tests or quarantine and medical costs. Every visitor will have to at least pay for transportation to a testing center, the test itself, a one-night stay in a hotel while waiting for a result, and three meals during the mini-quarantine, which comes out to a more manageable $165. But if one passenger on a plane tests positive, every other person on the aircraft must quarantine for 14 days and take a second test, bringing the total up to $1,276, and the number nearly triples, vaulting past the original deposit, for anyone who tests positive. Finally, should a visitor die from the coronavirus while in the country, $1,500 will reportedly be taken out of the deposit for cremation purposes. Cambodia has staved off the coronavirus quite successfully thanks to a quick response (although some measures have drawn criticism from human rights groups) â€” as of early June, there have officially been 126 cases since the pandemic began, and 124 recoveries. The perception of safety might tempt some people with the itch to travel to set their sights on the Southeast Asian nation, but the deposit seems likely to be an effective deterrent. Read more at Frommer's. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPULAR MECHANICS publishes how-to guide to take down statues...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/503121-popular-mechanics-publishes-how-to-guide-to-take-down-statues-without-anyone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Popular Mechanics magazine published an instruction piece on Tuesday that tells readers how to take down statues "without anyone getting hurt."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NBA Is Coming Back. There Are 113 Pages of New Rules...</title>
      <link>https://postofasia.com/the-n-b-a-is-coming-back-there-are-113-pages-of-new-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;postofasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An nameless tip line to report rules violations. Preapproved golf outings. Protocols for methods to correctly disinfect basketballs. Ping-Pong video games allowed — however singles, no doubles. The N.B.A. on Tuesday evening detailed its elaborate plan for resuming play this summer time by sending a 113-page handbook to workforce personnel, with a heavy emphasis on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French composer Jarre to perform world's first 'Matrix avatar' concert...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-composer-jarre-perform-worlds-first-matrix-avatar-131430032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French electronic music legend Jean-Michel Jarre told AFP Wednesday that he is going to perform the world's first "avatar" concert -- "like in the Matrix". The veteran star will play live on Sunday in a virtual universe created for the French midsummer Festival of Music where</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fists, stones, clubs: Brutal high altitude, low-tech clash...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fists-stones-clubs-china-indias-brutal-high-altitude-143504194.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India and China's militaries have some of the world's most sophisticated modern weaponry, but their deadliest scrap in over 50 years was fought using fists, rocks wrapped in barbed wire and clubs studded with nails. Colonel Babu was seriously injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midwest challenges escalate as Iowa goes from sure-bet to swing state...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/trump-midwest-challenges-escalate-as-iowa-goes-from-sure-bet-to-swing-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iowa is back on the map as a top-tier battleground, with President Trump moving to rebuff surging presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden with early television advertising and campaign appearances by Vice President Mike Pence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson in car crash outside Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2020/06/17/boris-johnson-car-crash-outside-parliament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson was in a car leaving the Houses of Parliament and onto Parliament Square in Westminster when a protester ran out into the road</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President turns to establishment players...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/17/trump-2020-karl-rove-324914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing worrisome polls, Trump is turning to establishment figures to supplement his own 2020 instincts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this double-decker seat future of jet travel?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/zephyr-seat-double-decker-airplane/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zephyr Seat, a design that reconfigures airplane cabins with double-decker lie-flat seats in premium economy, is being touted as a possible solution for fliers looking for more protection from the spread of Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 states report record-high jumps in cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-cases-rise-records-states-reopen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States may be at a crucial point in the coronavirus​ pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Friends Test Positive After Night Out At Florida Bar...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/06/17/16-friends-coronavirus-florida-bar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of 16 friends all tested positive for coronavirus after a night out at a recently reopened Florida bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS: REGIONAL CONFLICTS THREATEN TO ERUPT...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/rumors-of-wars-china-india-north-korea-south-korea-israel-and-turkey-all-move-toward-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As if we didn't have enough already going on in 2020, now we are facing the possibility that several regional wars may erupt.  China and India had both been pouring troops into a disputed border region, and now there has been an incident where they were actually killing each other.  On the Korean pe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to build floating spaceports for hypersonic flights around Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/spacex-build-floating-spaceports-hypersonic-085957470.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s SpaceX is building floating spaceports at sea to launch rockets into space and hypersonic flights around Earth. In a tweet, Musk confirmed that the development of “floating, superheavy-class” spaceports was underway on offshore sites, in preparation for “hypersonic travel” as well as trips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modi Warns of 'Befitting Reply' if Tensions Worsen...</title>
      <link>https://www.theusaexpress.com/index.php/2020/06/17/modi-warns-of-befitting-reply-from-india-if-china-tensions-worsen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theusaexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Narendra Modi of India broke his silence on Wednesday over the 20 Indian troopers killed this week by Chinese language forces alongside the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man in KKK outfit walks dog, waves to neighbors...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/993262/wisconsin-man-kkk-robe-hood-walks-dog-drinks-beer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN wearing a Ku Klux Klan hood and robe was seen casually walking his dog near a freeway, prompting multiple phone calls to the police. Officials with the Vilas County Sheriff’s Office sai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ultimate covid-19 mystery: Why does it spare some and kill others? </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/The-ultimate-covid-19-mystery-Why-does-it-spare-15345984.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The novel coronavirus can be a killer - or no big deal. It can put a person in the intensive care unit on a ventilator, isolated from family, facing a lonely death - or it can come and go without leaving a mark, a ghost pathogen, more rumor than reality.  Six months into a pandemic that has killed more than 400,000 people globally, scientists are still trying to understand the wildly variable nature of covid-19, the disease caused by the virus.  Among their lines of inquiry: Are distinct strains of the coronavirus more dangerous? Does a patient's blood type affect the severity of the illness? Do other genetic factors play a role? Are some people partially protected from covid-19 because they've had recent exposure to other coronaviruses?  Much of the research remains provisional or ambiguous, and for now scientists can't do much better than say that covid-19 is more likely to be worse for older people - often described as over the age of 60 - and for those with chronic conditions such as hypertension, diabetes, lung disease and heart disease.  That describes tens of millions of people in the United States alone. It also isn't much of an explanation: The link between chronic disease and the severity of covid-19 is more in the category of correlation than causation. The "why" of the matter remains unclear.  The issue of disease variability "is the most critical question about covid," said Edward Behrens, chief of the rheumatology division at Children's Hospital of Philadelphia.  "Why do some people get sick? Why do some people have no problem at all?" he said.  Social and demographic factors, including sex, race, ethnicity, income and access to quality health care, play major roles in how this pandemic affects people and who suffers the most. The ultimate goal of many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amputee says AMERICAN AIRLINES crew told her to 'scoot' down aisle to use bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/airlines/2020/06/16/amputee-says-american-airlines-crew-told-her-to-scoot-down-airplane-aisle-to-use-bathroom/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican operatives launch pro-Biden super PAC...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republicans-pro-biden-super-pac-e48b415a-7fc3-44e4-b02e-11a105239811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Right Side PAC" will identify and target former Trump supporters across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite winner, US will face very turbulent period after election...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/502984-despite-winner-us-will-face-a-very-turbulent-period-after-the-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this climate, Trump can no longer use the booming economy for his reelection, and he is now opting for a tough-guy approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUIBBLE: Katzenberg resorting to unusual tactics to avoid lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/16/jeffrey-katzenberg-resorting-to-unusual-tactics-to-avoid-quibi-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood mogul Jeffrey Katzenberg is resorting to unusual tactics to fend off a lawsuit against his struggling video startup Quibi, The Post has learned. Despite publicly blasting patent infringem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots: Allies during crisis, enemies later?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/robots-allies-during-virus-crisis-enemies-later-032623080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The moment there is a threat for humans, you should send a robot," said Cyril Kabbara, co-founder of the French start-up Sharks Robotics. "This crisis has demonstrated that you have to have a capacity to continue activity even when a health or another type of crisis strikes," said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is racial,' protesters insist after hanging death of black man...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/racial-us-protesters-insist-hanging-death-black-man-054546975.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Shawna Green and many other residents of Palmdale, a city in California's Mojave Desert, there is no question that Robert Fuller's death was racially motivated. "In a word, this is a cover-up," said Green, 46, commenting about the 24-year-old black man who was found dead hanging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans can tell what chimps are saying?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/humans-tell-chimps-saying-sort-112647386.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We demonstrate for the first time that humans can accurately map other species vocalisations to specific behavioural contexts," Roza Kamiloglu, a researcher at the University of Amsterdam and lead study author, told AFP. Kamiloglu and the team asked close to 3,500 participants to listen to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan warns off intruding Chinese aircraft for fourth time in nine days...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-taiwan-china-defence/taiwan-warns-off-intruding-chinese-aircraft-for-fourth-time-in-nine-days-idUSKBN23O1QQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan jets on Wednesday again had to warn off Chinese air force aircraft that approached the island, Taiwan's military said, the fourth such encounter in nine days as China steps up its activity near the Chinese-claimed island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKER to remove AUNT JEMIMA from brand; 'Based on racial stereotype'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/aunt-jemima-brand-will-change-name-remove-image-quaker-says-n1231260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We recognize Aunt Jemima’s origins are based on a racial stereotype," Quaker Oats said, adding that the move is an effort "toward progress on racial equality."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence in Travel Slides With Less Than Half Willing to Fly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/confidence-in-travel-slides-with-less-than-half-willing-to-fly/ar-BB15zavJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trillions in Stimulus Go Unchecked With Watchdogs Kept Toothless...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/trillions-in-stimulus-go-unchecked-with-watchdogs-kept-toothless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trillions in Stimulus Go Unchecked With Watchdogs Kept Toothless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJs, ping pong, pedicures: Inside NBA plan to restart...</title>
      <link>https://nesn.com/2020/06/heres-what-will-life-be-like-for-nba-players-quarantined-at-disney-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nesn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA is closing in on its return, and and given the leagues strict limitations for players leaving the quarantine…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW OUTBREAK AT CHINA MARKET</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/54374ff841dfd84323a1fb86d1e93180</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China raised its emergency warning to its second highest level and canceled more than 60% of the flights to Beijing on Wednesday amid a new coronavirus outbreak in the capital — a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High court decision spotlights Republican divide over LGBT rights...</title>
      <link>/https://apnews.com/0412f42b9709c5b0eaa080ff805b3448</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
