<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The Peculiar Life of the Man in the 'BIG LEBOWSKI' House: Wild L.A. Mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/inside-nba-superfan-james-goldsteins-wild-la-party-mansion-1283516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Goldstein, the city's most unapologetic 80-year-old bon  vivant (and Lakers fixture), throws parties with models and Leonardo DiCaprio as he rushes to finish his architectural legacy: "The villains always live in the modern houses."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civility, or civil war?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/486819-civility-or-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may take a new generation to restore common courtesy and decency to American politics once again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man knew had virus, flew from JFK to Palm Beach anyway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/12/coronavirus-in-ny-passenger-on-jetblue-flight-from-jfk-tests-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger on a JetBlue flight from JFK Airport has tested positive for the coronavirus after landing in Palm Beach, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate staffer tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/11/us-senate-staffer-tests-positive-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer for US Senator Maria Cantwell has tested positive for coronavirus – the first known congressional worker to catch the virus, her office said Wednesday. The unidentified patient, who…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It caused mass panic': Rush to get back...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200312095943-wmvg5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/EUROPE-AIRPORT (TV, PIX):"It caused a mass panic": travellers in Europe rush to get back to US after Trump order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sit, stay forever: Americans willing to pay top dollar to keep old dogs alive...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200312092305-1g7b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DOGS/ (TV, PIX):Sit, stay forever: Americans willing to pay top dollar to keep old dogs alive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World walls off as leaders warn pandemic will worsen...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a123df57403757910e63ca01fde2f322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Sweeping travel bans accelerated across the globe on Thursday, walling regions apart, keeping people inside their homes and slowing the engines of commerce in an effort to stem the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems smell blood in Texas after sky-high primary turnout...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/12/democrats-texas-primary-126651</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party is targeting another half-dozen House seats in the Lone Star State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A no-savings generation is cashing in its sneaker collections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/a-no-savings-generation-is-cashing-in-its-sneaker-collections/ar-BB10Zo24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUTURES HIT LIMIT DOWN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/11/futures-are-steady-wednesday-night-after-dow-closes-in-bear-market-traders-await-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came after yet another wild session on Wall Street and the demise of the Dow's record-setting bull market run that began in March 2009.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals brace for onslaught...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/487151-hospitals-brace-for-coronavirus-onslaught</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals are bracing for an onslaught of patients as the coronavirus spreads in the United States, with experts warning that a spike in cases could overwhelm the health care system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macho men more likely to suffer health, social issues in old age...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/11/macho-men-more-likely-to-suffer-health-social-issues-in-old-age/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toxic masculinity may literally be hazardous to men’s health. While movies may make the macho lifestyle seem alluring, a new study has found that hypermasculine males could suffer from a host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Re-election Chances Suddenly Look Shakier...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/12/trumps-re-election-chances-suddenly-look-shakier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump faces the biggest challenge yet to his prospects of being re-elected, with his advisers’ two major assumptions for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Going To Die, Might as Well Do It At DISNEY WORLD'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/12/if-im-going-to-get-sick-and-die-i-might-as-well-do-it-at-disney-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Vice President Mike Pence was asked, earlier this month, if he would feel comfortable taking his children and grandchildren</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looks to beef up his campaign team...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Biden-scaling-up-campaign-as-primary-focus-turns-15124577.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after winning another string of dominant victories that moved him closer to the Democratic presidential nomination, Joe Biden's campaign was working to reboot amid broad concerns within the party that his current operation is ill-equipped to match President Donald Trump's behemoth reelection effort.  Biden pulled off the most stunningly swift turnaround in modern political history with a relatively small staff, underwhelming fundraising and a campaign occasionally marked by dysfunction and turmoil.  After finishing fifth just four weeks ago in New Hampshire, there were questions over how his campaign could gracefully end. But Biden now has won at least 15 of the last 21 voting states, making him the candidate likeliest to face Trump in a highly polarized, extremely expensive general election.  Biden's advisers are taking steps to expand virtually all parts of his shoestring campaign operation, from finance, field and communications departments to the senior leadership team, answering the concerns of senior Democrats who are bracing for a new wave of assaults from Trump.  That effort will occur even as Biden continues to battle for delegates with Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., who announced Wednesday that he would stay in the race as he issued policy demands to Biden on issues like health care.  "We will be building out every team here," Biden senior adviser Anita Dunn said Wednesday, after making clear that the primary mission of the campaign remains acquiring enough delegates to win the nomination. She suggested that would be done at least in part by embracing aides to former candidates, many of whom have endorsed Biden in recent days.  "We are seeing an enormous amount of talent from people on other campaigns. We would hope that we would be able to have some of those...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fury at Fed! Explosive tirade...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/Trump-urged-Mnuchin-to-pressure-Fed-s-Powell-on-15124246.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump, in an explosive tirade on Monday, urged Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin to encourage Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell to do more to stimulate the economy, two officials familiar with the exchange said, revealing the president's mounting fury as his administration struggles to corral economic fallout from the novel coronavirus.  Trump has frequently complained about the Fed in public for at least two years, but his latest effort to pressure Mnuchin to privately push for action has not been previously reported.  During that tense Monday meeting in the Oval Office, Trump fumed that Powell never should have been appointed and is damaging the nation and his presidency.  He then told Mnuchin, who had encouraged Trump to nominate Powell in 2017, to engage with the chair and urge him to take more dramatic steps to arrest the stock market's plummet, according to three White House officials and a senior Republican. The people spoke on the condition of anonymity because they weren't authorized to reveal the exchange.  Mnuchin has not commented publicly on this meeting, but he has said recently that he is in daily contact with Powell during the coronavirus crisis. Trump initially tried to brush aside concerns about the coronavirus' impact on the economy, saying it would be short-lived, but the Oval Office meeting struck some of his advisers because it showed how furious he had become.  The stock market has fallen precipitously since mid-February because global supply chains are seizing up, consumers are pulling back sharply on spending, and companies are retrenching as they wait to see what the impact of the coronavirus will be. Interest rates are already very low, and they are typically lowered in an effort to spur more borrowing and spending. This time, however, many businesses and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-rich jet off to disaster bunkers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/11/disease-dodging-worried-wealthy-jet-off-to-disaster-bunkers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Self isolate’ for some of world’s richest means Covid-19 tests abroad, personal medics and subterranean hide-outs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Manning fighting for life after attempting suicide; Refuses to testify in WIKILEAKS probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/525558/chelsea-manning-us-army-intelligence-wikileaks-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHELSEA Manning attempted suicide in a Virgina jail cell on Wednesday after refusing to testify in a WikiLeaks probe, her lawyers say. The ex-army intelligence analyst – who leaked 700,000 cl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive 'David' statue topples at cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-11/massive-david-statue-a-replica-of-michelangelos-work-topples-at-glendale-cemetery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The full-size marble reproduction of the Renaissance artist's statue falls over and breaks into pieces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hordes of starving monkeys seen storming empty streets as tourists stay away...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/hordes-starving-monkeys-seen-storming-21676062</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The normally well-fed primates had no food after coronavirus fears left the normally busy streets in Thailand completely empty of tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA SUSPENDS SEASON</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/12/coronavirus-nba-suspends-season-after-player-tests-positive.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Basketball Association has suspended its season after a Utah Jazz player tested positive for COVID-19 coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BANS ALL TRAVEL FROM EUROPE FOR 30 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-makes-statement-on-coronavirus-wednesday-evening-watch-live-stream-today-2020-03-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ban will exclude the United Kingdom, the president said Wednesday night in a brief address to the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Devil Assails Christians with Vanity and Rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/faith/2020/03/11/pope-francis-devil-assails-christians-vanity-rage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The devil always goes to extremes, Pope Francis said, either through the soft-sell of worldly glory or the violence of enraged persecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests indicate coronavirus can survive in air...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/487110-tests-indicate-coronavirus-can-survive-in-the-air</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federally funded tests conducted by scientists from several major institutions indicated that the novel form of coronavirus behind a worldwide outbreak can survive in the air for several hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In divided America, misery looking for company...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/487061-in-a-divided-america-misery-is-looking-for-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For conflicts to be resolved, people in opposition must meet a mutual level of misery and belief that there's a possible solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOM HANKS TESTS POSITIVE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/tom-hanks-rita-wilson-test-positive-coronavirus-elvis-presley-movie-1202880431/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: We have just received word that Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson were tested positive for the coronavirus. Both were down in Australia for the pre-production of Baz Luhrmann’s untitled El…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businesses see plummeting sales; Job losses have begun...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/the-first-us-layoffs-from-the-coronavirus-are-here-1.622069</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Americans have lost jobs over the past week, as the coronavirus outbreak begins to take a deeper toll on the U.S. economy and brings more industries to a standstill, according to interviews with two dozen companies and workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of cancellations as virus spreads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f46e3914fac402e673c0a564b3325913</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Seven weeks after the first case of COVID-19 was confirmed in the U.S., the outbreak is now classified as a pandemic and it's doing widespread damage to critical economic sectors...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears China is harvesting their organs from muslim prisoners...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/522114/fears-china-is-executing-muslim-prisoners-and-harvesting-their-organs-to-treat-coronavirus-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE are growing fears China is executing muslim prisoners so they can harvest their organs to treat dying coronavirus patients. The concerns come after Beijing boasted it had performed a successf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran and Russian Media Push Bioweapon Conspiracies...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2020/03/iran-and-russian-media-push-bioweapon-conspiracies-amid-covid19-outbreak/163669/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disinformation about the coronavirus is spreading as vast as the virus, thanks to the usual players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Taxes and Spending Set New Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-and-spending-set-records-through-february</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set records for both the amount of taxes it collected and the amount of money it spent in the first five months of fiscal 2020 (October through February), according to data released today in the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVEY GETS 23 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/11/harvey-weinstein-fell-asleep-during-his-trial-his-sentence-should-wake-everyone-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein will, as his defense team admitted in a Hail Mary plea this week, die in prison. Until then, may he rot. As Justice James Burke said to Weinstein at sentencing: “This is your first…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist Links 2 State Outbreaks With Genetic Fingerprints...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2020-03-11/scientist-links-2-state-outbreaks-with-genetic-fingerprints</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODELL'S closing remaining stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/business/nation/story/2020-03-11/sporting-goods-chain-modells-to-close-its-remaining-stores</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modell's Sporting Goods, the century-old family-owned sporting goods chain, has filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy and is closing its remaining 100-plus stores</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department to suspend non-essential travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-usa-diplomats/exclusive-u-s-state-department-to-suspend-non-essential-travel-sources-idUSKBN20Y34N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. State Department has decided to suspend non-essential travel because of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULLS EMERGENCY DECLARATION</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/11/trump-emergency-declaration-coronavirus-message-125902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is concerned that declaring an emergency would hamper his narrative that the coronavirus is similar to the seasonal flu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor pleads for help; Trapped with sister's dead body for 36 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8100479/Gomorra-actor-pleads-help-trapped-sisters-dead-body.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luca Franzese, who appeared on the TV show Gomorrah, has released a series of videos, appealing for funeral services to pick up the corpse of his sister after she tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARCH SADNESS: NCAA tournament to be fan free...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/ncaa-march-madness-closed-general-public-210705563--nba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NCAA officials closed the US national college basketball tournament to paying fans on Wednesday in an unprecedented move due to the coronavirus outbreak. National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) president Mark Emmert said the move, made after consultations with public health officials, would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy expands shutdown to nearly all stores...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/57d413557858077d861f846670ca3515</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on the coronavirus outbreak sweeping the globe: Italy's premier is urging people not to hoard food, saying they don't need to because stores where they can buy it will remain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCAA March Madness to be fan free...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/11/ncaa-march-madness-basketball-games-will-be-closed-to-public-spectators.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NCAA president Mark Emmert announced the Division I men's and women's basketball tournament will be played without fans due to the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC declares state of emergency...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2020/03/coronavirus-update-dc-st-patricks-day-parade-postponed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The St. Patrick’s Parade in D.C. has been postponed amid a growing number of coronavirus cases in the broader D.C. area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEATTLE SCHOOLS CLOSE</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/education/seattle-public-schools-to-close-for-two-weeks-in-light-of-coronavirus-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement comes after the district's early efforts to stay open, in an effort to make sure children don't suddenly see a loss in services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books plagiarized from news outlets dominate AMAZON search results...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/coronavirus-books-plagiarized-news-outlets-dominate-amazon-search-results-n1155641</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The listings highlight the challenge that Amazon has faced as consumers have turned to the company for a variety of goods and information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TO ADDRESS NATION</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8101591/Donald-Trump-tweets-plea-calm-White-House-emergency-meeting-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump defended his administration's response to the coronavirus and said his team was 'putting into policy a plan to prevent, detect, treat and create a vaccine.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds arrests 600 alleged Mexican cartel members...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/487064-feds-arrests-over-600-alleged-mexican-cartel-members</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice (DOJ) and Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) announced Wednesday that more than 600 arrests have been made as a result of an interagency operation cracking down on Mexican cartel activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA weighs limits on travelers from Europe...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200311185424-flcls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-U.S. weighs limits on travelers from Europe as coronavirus hits home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gronkowski Signs With WWE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/rob-gronkowski-wwe-gronk-signs-friday-night-smackdown-fox-new-england-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's scheduled to appear at next month's WrestleMania 36 in Tampa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA game to go fan-less...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/sports/article/San-Francisco-bans-large-events-for-two-weeks-due-15123281.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco Mayor London Breed will announce a ban on all events larger than 1,000 people across the city Wednesday, the San Francisco Chronicle first reported . The ban will apply to all events at Chase Center, including Golden State Warriors games, the mayor is reportedly set to announce.  "San Francisco will officially ban large events over 1000 people, including Warriors games. Effective tomorrow, the ban will last at least 2 weeks," San Francisco Supervisor Matt Haney tweeted . "Other counties and states have taken similar steps. Public health must be first priority."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED PUMPS $175 BILLION IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/11/fed-boosts-money-its-providing-to-banks-in-overnight-repo-lending-to-175-billion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed aimed to 'support smooth functioning of funding markets' in response to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETBLUE CEO: Impact On Airline 'Probably Worse' Than 9/11...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-jetblue-ceo-robin-airline-industry-demand-after-911/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is the sort of event in the airline industry we only tend to see about once every ten years," Hayes said on "CBS This Morning" Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia to isolate patients at Hard Labor Creek State Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-news/georgia-preparing-park-for-isolating-patients-exposed-coronavirus/qtEDELBUm8Xo0TqlCRhPgI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials are preparing Hard Labor Creek State Park in Morgan County for isolating and monitor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE: Will take 140 years to deport illegals from border surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/11/ice-says-it-will-take-140-years-deport-illegals-bo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICE’s chief said Wednesday that at current deportation rates it would take 140 years to remove all the illegal immigrants who came in during the border surge of the past two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House told federal health agency to classify deliberations...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-secrecy-exclusive/exclusive-white-house-told-federal-health-agency-to-classify-coronavirus-deliberations-sources-idUSKBN20Y2LM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has ordered federal health officials to treat top-level coronavi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Bernie to press on...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/sanders-campaign-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders, after a drubbing in the latest round of primaries, vowed Wednesday to press on with his presidential campaign -- touting the appeal of his progressive message and suggesting front-runner Joe Biden has not attracted a sufficient following among young voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO Blasts 'Alarming' Inaction...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/coronavirus-pandemic-world-health-organization-stocks-51583947289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization has made the call that the Covid-19 outbreak is a global pandemic, news that deepened the slide in stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds wiretap former DEA supervisor in leak probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6b2787ff1ccb15aefb57f01024821d52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Federal investigators took the unusual step of wiretapping a retired supervisor in the U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration’s Miami office as part of an inquiry into whether sensitive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP DOC: Virus 10 TIMES more lethal than flu...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/901470/coronavirus-10-times-more-lethal-than-seasonal-flu-trumps-task-force-immunologist-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, told lawmakers during a House Oversight Committee hearing Wednesday that COVID-19 â€” the disease caused by the novel coronavirus â€” is probably about 10 times more lethal than the seasonal flu. President Trump has often compared COVID-19 to the flu, which affects tens of thousands of Americans each year, in an effort to calm people down, but Fauci clearly wasn't trying to downplay the seriousness of the virus' spread. Fauci is a member of the White House's coronavirus task force. At the same time, he did clarify that 10 times figure actually brings the new coronavirus' fatality rate lower than official estimates, which hover around 3 percent. The flu has a mortality rate of about 0.1 percent, so, when considering the likelihood that there are many asymptomatic or very mild cases that have gone undiagnosed, Fauci places the new coronavirus' lethality rate at somewhere around 1 percent. While that's a good deal lower than the current data suggests, it still would lead to significant numbers of fatalities, and makes the flu comparisons seem pretty questionable. Tim O'Donnell Q: How does COVID-19 compare to other previous health situations â€” SARS, H1N1? Dr. Fauci: '...It is 10 times more lethal than the seasonal flu. I think that's something that people can get their arms around and understand.' pic.twitter.com/yjLrcFSOxR â€” Erick Fernandez (@ErickFernandez) March 11, 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormons to hold major confab without attendees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b0f429fc9c1c751ea6755ec35d9218a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints announced Wednesday that it will hold a major conference in April that features speeches by top leaders without any attendees...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Bernie defiant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/950629c702d5b089c1209dec5ff3874b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURLINGTON, Vt. (AP) — Bernie Sanders says he's moving ahead with his Democratic presidential campaign. He told reporters in Burlington, Vermont, on Wednesday that he's not quitting despite...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry says Trump has 'blood on his hands' over climate change...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/521820/prince-harry-says-president-donald-trump-has-climate-blood-on-his-hands-in-call-with-russian-hoaxers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Harry said President Donald Trump’s support for the coal industry means he has ‘blood on his hands’ as part of a call with hoaxers who apparently duped the duke. Speaking on the phone with R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five earthquakes rattle Northeast in four days...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article241056321.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SMITH</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/ben-smith</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Smith is the media columnist. He joined The New York Times in 2020 after eight years as founding editor in chief of BuzzFeed News. Before that, he covered politics for Politico, The New York Daily News, The New York Observer and The New York Sun. Email: ben.smith@nytimes.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-rays show terrifying damage in lungs of victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-x-rays-show-terrifying-21672219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CT scans and x-rays of coronavirus sufferers' lungs - taken after they came down with symptoms such as a fever and cough - show a pattern of abnormalities similar to SARS and MERS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naomi Campbell wears full hazmat suit and mask at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/coronavirus-naomi-campbell-wears-full-21671373</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supermodel, 49, also donned goggles and plastic gloves, as she turns her hygiene routine into a major fashion moment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  PRESIDENT'S APPROVAL HOLDS AT 40%...</title>
      <link>https://www.ipsos.com/en-us/news-polls/reuters-ipsos-data-core-political-2020-03-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ipsos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's overall approval rating remains stable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme tattooist inks entire body to turn himself blue...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/worlds-most-extreme-tattooist-inks-21669320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donnie Snider, 26, has become an online sensation for slowly tattooing his entire body blue. The extreme tattooist started his craze back in 2017</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ HIT HARD BY OUTBREAK...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/biz/news/hollywood-coronavirus-entertainment-industry-movies-festivals-1203529795/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cancellation of SXSW on March 6 due to the coronavirus epidemic sent shockwaves through the entertainment industry. But in truth it was the culmination of weeks of mounting anxiety — in executi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVEY GETS 23 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/harvey-weinstein-awaits-sentencing-for-sex-assault-rape-convictions-in-nyc/2321293/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein was sentenced in a Manhattan criminal courtroom Wednesday to 23 years for sexually assaulting a former production assistant and raping an aspiring actress — a landmark sentencing in the #MeToo era. A jury made up of five women and seven men found the 67-year-old movie producer guilty last month of raping aspiring actress Jessica Mann in 2013 and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCKSTAR SELLS FOR $4 BILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kristinstoller/2020/03/11/rockstar-energy-drink-founder-cashing-out-for-nearly-4-billion-says-the-american-dream-is-alive-and-well/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Russ Weiner says the deal will make Rockstar a “global powerhouse.” It will also add a lot of cash to his wallet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: Infections and deaths 'totally dependent upon how we respond'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/11/top-federal-health-official-says-coronavirus-outbreak-is-going-to-get-worse-in-the-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare white giraffes killed by poachers in Kenya...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-51816083</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rangers found the carcasses of a female and her calf in a village in north-eastern Kenya.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rape Accusers Fill Two Rows In Courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/harvey-weinstein-prison-sentence-jail-rape-sexual-assault-1202878583/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein, his handcuffs temporarily removed and likening himself to Hollywood’s blacklisted Dalton Trumbo, was sentenced to 23 years in prison today, with New York Supreme Court Judge…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casino To Take Temperatures Of Guests, Employees...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/03/11/coronavirus-encore-boston-harbor-casino-taking-temperatures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Encore Boston Harbor is taking new steps in response to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had Enough? Californians Turn Down Higher Taxes, Debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2020-03-11/had-enough-californians-turn-down-higher-taxes-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans Will Likely Be Exposed to Coronavirus, Republicans Told...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/most-americans-will-likely-be-exposed-to-coronavirus-republicans-told</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of Congress who attended the closed-door briefing where the assessment was made called the prediction “sobering.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why TV Is So Worried About Free Will...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2020/03/devs-and-westworld-mine-data-dystopia/607771/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Garland’s new show "Devs" and Season 3 of "Westworld" find dystopia in determinism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grief In The Wild: Baboon Mothers Carry Their Dead Infants For Up To 10 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/grief-in-the-wild-baboon-mothers-carry-their-dead-infants-for-up-to-10-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new heartbreaking study finds that baboon mothers have an incredibly hard time saying goodbye when they lose a child, carrying their bodies for 10 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of fingerprint files exposed in unsecured database, research finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/thousands-of-fingerprint-files-exposed-in-unsecured-database-research-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: The data reveals important distinguishing characteristics of 76,000 fingerprints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus conference canceled -- because of coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/11/coronavirus-conference-canceled-in-new-york-because-of-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Council of Foreign Relations was due to hold a roundtable titled “Doing Business Under Coronavirus” on Friday, but decided to cancel it amid fears that it could lead to a spread of the deadly b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health officials called to 'emergency meeting' at White House...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200311132631-apjw9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-MEETING (URGENT):Health officials called to 'emergency meeting' at White House- Rep. Maloney</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
