<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TMZ sold to FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/13/media/tmz-sold-fox-entertainment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TMZ will now be a part of Fox Entertainment, the companies announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US budget deficit rises to $2.71 trillion through August...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-7a2fc48cf977988d3cd580ac84a51de5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. budget deficit rose to $2.71 trillion through August, on track to be the second largest shortfall in history due to trillions of dollars in COVID relief. In its monthly budget report, the Treasury Department said Monday that the deficit for the first 11 months of this budget year is 9.9% less than the imbalance during the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharon Osbourne reveals months of ketamine therapy after 'constant death threats'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9978409/Sharon-Osbourne-betrayed-hosts-following-secret-pact-underwent-ketamine-therapy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharon Osbourne sat down exclusively with DailyMailTV for her first in-depth interview since her shock exit from The Talk this year amid controversy over purported racist comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC broadens antitrust suit against AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/572008-dc-broadens-antitrust-lawsuit-against-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;District of Columbia Attorney General Karl Racine (D) on Monday expanded the antitrust lawsuit he filed against Amazon in May, accusing the e-commerce giant of locking first-party sellers into anti-competitive agreements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS' test data left on open web...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22623871/walgreens-covid-test-site-data-vulnerability</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people got Covid-19 tests through Walgreens. Their information wasn’t adequately protected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French far-right pundit edges closer to presidential bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210913-french-far-right-pundit-edges-closer-to-presidential-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French far-right pundit edges closer to presidential bid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban scientists reject 'Havana Syndrome' claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210913-cuban-scientists-reject-havana-syndrome-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban scientists reject 'Havana Syndrome' claims</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani denies being drunk during rambling 9/11 speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9985471/Rudy-Giuliani-says-NOT-drunk-rambling-September-11th-speech-Cipriani.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Mayor Rudy Giuliani denied accusations he was drunk during a speech at Cipriani on the anniversary of 9/11 where he mimicked the British accent of the Queen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Keefe says hackers scammed PROJECT VERITAS out of $165,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/project-of-veritas-says-hackers-scammed-it-out-of-165000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project Veritas announced on Monday that it was scammed out of $165,000 after being targeted by hackers who impersonated lawyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Sign of Presidency Becoming Monarchy...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/13/bidens-vaccine-mandate-is-the-latest-sign-of-the-presidency-becoming-a-monarchy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidency has always been inclined to unilateral power—and many Americans like it that way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA National Guard Activated -- Over School Bus Driver Shortage!</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/13/massachusetts-national-guard-activated-school-bus-driver-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts National Guard has been activated to help with the state's shortage of school bus drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected Reason AZ Mask Mandate Ban May Be Unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/13/1036455622/the-unexpected-reason-arizonas-mask-mandate-ban-may-be-unconstitutional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaf through the most recent Arizona budget, and you'll find everything from a mask mandate ban to voting restrictions. A new lawsuit says those aren't budget items; they are political horse-trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Syrian War Criminal, Double Agent Disappeared in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/09/20/how-a-syrian-war-criminal-and-double-agent-disappeared-in-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the bloody civil war, Khaled al-Halabi switched sides. But what country does he really serve?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Former aide sees Melania as doomed French queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook/2021/09/13/grisham-dishes-on-melania-494293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Democrats eye big tax increases as they move ahead on reconciliation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What next 6 months of pandemic will bring...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/here-e2-80-99s-what-the-next-six-months-of-the-pandemic-will-bring/ar-AAOmGL2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race between vaccinations and new variant strains won’t end until Covid-19 has touched almost everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Social media making polarization worse...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/571747-social-media-making-political-polarization-worse-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report recommends that the federal government prioritize plans to enact stronger transparency requirements and other measures for tech platforms in an effort to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to rally...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/09/13/biden-sacramento-newsom-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden arrives in Sacramento on Monday, and he'll be here to campaign with Gov. Gavin Newsom on the eve of the California Recall Election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across Latin America, abortion restrictions are being loosened...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/across-latin-america-abortion-restrictions-100006019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A court ruling in Mexico is latest victory for abortion rights advocates in Latin America. But legal abortion still remains unavailable for most women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 63:  Madonna shows off bare bottom at MTV...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3648428/mtv-vmas-red-carpet-megan-fox-kourtney-travis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGAN Fox showed off her bare butt and thong in a sheer dress with Machine Gun Kelly and pals Travis Barker and Kourtney Kardashian at the MTV VMAs. The Jennifer’s Body actress left little to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Stern Roasts Rogan For Taking Horse Pills...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/howard-stern-roasts-joe-rogan-for-taking-ivermectin-instead-of-cure-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howard Stern took a shot at Joe Rogan for crediting ivermectin for his recovery from the coronavirus when he could've just gotten vaccinated instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon UFO whistleblower to reveal intel in new book...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lifestyle/arts/luis-elizondo-ufo-book-1235012266/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former head of the U.S. government’s secretive UFO program will pen a book for HarperCollins that includes "profound implications for humanity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enforcement patrols hit NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-pandemic-rules-for-nyc-restuarants-police-schools-go-into-effect-monday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enforcement of New York City's indoor vaccination mandate has started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$79 BILLION FOR MORE IRS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/13/house-democrats-propose-tax-increases-in-3point5-trillion-budget-bill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats proposed a 26.5% top corporate tax rate and 39.6% top individual rate as they try to pay for a $3.5 trillion bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ineffective Rodgers Benched As PACKERS Blown Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/packers-bench-aaron-rodgers-for-jordan-love-as-jameis-winston-torches-green-bay-in-week-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So much for a dominant start to Rodgers' potential farewell tour</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  Dems See Trump Supporters and Unvaccinated As Biggest Threats Facing Nation...</title>
      <link>https://scottrasmussen.com/democrats-see-trump-supporters-and-the-unvaccinated-as-biggest-threat-to-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scottrasmussen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-seven percent (57%) of Democratic voters believe supporters of Donald Trump are a serious threat to the nation. A Scott Rasmussen national survey found that 56% of those in President Biden's party also consider the unvaccinated a serious threat. That's a higher level of concern than Democrats express about the Taliban (44% see it as a serious threat); China (44%), or Russia (37%). These results help explain the tone and actions taken recently by President Biden. Republicans and Independents have a much different view of the threats facing the nation. For Republicans, the top concerns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci supports mandated air travel vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/13/fauci-says-he-would-support-vaccine-requirement-for-air-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci has expressed his support for COVID-19 vaccination requirements for air travel – as the Biden administration did not rule it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with 'machete' in truck graffitied with swastikas arrested near Dem HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3652029/swastika-graffiti-truck-arrested-democratic-national-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN who allegedly had multiple knives including a machete was arrested near the Democratic National Committee headquarters. Donald Craighead, 44, was arrested for possession of prohibited weapons…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS TAX RATE HIGHER THAN COMMUNIST CHINA</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/dems-propose-3-trillion-tax-hike-working-families-and-small-businesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are proposing almost $3 trillion ($3,000,000,000,000) in tax increases including tax increases on small businesses and working families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Company With Wild Mission: Bring Back Woolly Mammoth...</title>
      <link>https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/384478</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.entrepreneur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We've found a way to harness CRISPR's power for species de-extinction."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrett says Supreme Court 'not a bunch of partisan hacks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/13/politics/amy-coney-barrett-supreme-court-not-partisan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Amy Coney Barrett on Sunday rejected claims that decisions by the high court are driven by political views at a speech at the University of Louisville's McConnell Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO CON: Litecoin tumbles after fake WALMART press release...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/13/walmart-to-accept-payments-with-cryptocurrencies-using-litecoin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency litecoin gave up a 20% gain and tumbled back to earth following a suspicious press release sent out by GlobeNewswire that referenced a partnership with Walmart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweaty, Sticky, Triumphant Return of Sex Parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kvjwg/the-return-of-sex-parties-after-covid-pandemic-lockdown-v28n3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 15 long months of everyone being their own safest sex partner, what do sex parties look like now?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 1 In 7 Have Dumped Friends Over Shot Stance...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-vaccine-stance-friendships/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of those who ended a friendship during the pandemic, 66 percent are vaccinated and 17 percent don’t ever plan to receive the shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Dems' Answer to James O'Keefe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/meet-lauren-windsor-the-democrats-answer-to-james-okeefe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Windsor’s group has caught Republicans like Senators Ron Johnson and Tommy Tuberville saying the quiet part out loud on camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will women save him?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/13/california-women-newsom-511303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor successfully warded off any viable Democrats from entering the race, and the GOP failed to offer a top-polling female candidate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top earning NYers could face 61.2% rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/13/top-earning-new-yorkers-could-face-61point2percent-combined-tax-rate-under-house-plan-californians-may-face-59percent-rate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposals include a 3% surtax on taxpayers earning more than $5 million a year. They would also raise the top marginal income tax rate to 39.6%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have Canadians wearied of Trudeau's vapid wokeness?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/have-canadians-wearied-of-trudeaus-vapid-wokeness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will the world’s wokest leader be reelected? When Justin Trudeau called the election to Canada’s 44th Parliament at the end of August, he was comfortably ahead in the polls. Crises bolster all but the most obviously useless incumbents, and Canada has had, as measured by deaths, vaccine rollout, and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon prepped Epstein for CBS interview, Wolff claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2021/sep/13/steve-bannon-jeffrey-epstein-cbs-interview-michael-wolff-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Trump strategist told financier to ‘stick to his message, which is that he is not a paedophile’, New York Times reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions mount over boosters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/13/cdc-biden-health-team-vaccine-boosters-511529</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior officials from the White House and the FDA say the CDC is withholding critical data needed to develop the booster plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They could be your neighbors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/they-could-be-your-neighbors-and-they-re-going-to-space-spacex-gets-ready-to-fly-the-inspiration4-crew/ar-AAOo1E7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;None of the crew has been to space before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh China outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/13/china/fujian-covid-outbreak-mic-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who completed 21 days of mandatory quarantine upon returning to China from overseas has been identified as the likely source of a new outbreak, raising questions over the sustainability of the country's stringent zero-Covid strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for $3.5 trillion spending plan...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/571905-democrats-brace-for-battle-on-bidens-35-spending-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are bracing for battle as they try to unify their slim majorities behind a sweeping social spending package at the heart of President Biden’s economic and political agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Former aide sees Melania as doomed French queen...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/571925-former-aide-sees-melania-trump-as-doomed-french-queen-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former top aide reportedly describes former first lady Melania Trump as "the doomed French queen" in a new book set to be released next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to launch private, all-civilian crew into Earth orbit...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-09-spacex-private-all-civilian-crew-earth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX is set to launch four people into space Wednesday on a three-day mission that is the first to orbit the Earth with exclusively private citizens on board, as Elon Musk's company enters the space tourism fray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McGregor, Machine Gun Kelly fight on VMAs red carpet...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/12/conor-mcgregor-and-machine-gun-kelly-get-into-fight-on-vmas-red-carpet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spy told Page Six that McGregor and Machine Gun Kelly “got into a fight at the top of the carpet” and “had to be pulled apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seriously ill COVID patients double in vax pace-setter Singapore...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210913112754-w5k94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SINGAPORE:Seriously ill COVID-19 patients double in vaccine pace-setter Singapore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Long-Range Missile Test as Arms Race Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/13/north-korea-reports-long-range-cruise-missile-test-as-arms-race-intensifies-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL — North Korea said on Monday it​ had successfully launched newly developed long-range cruise missiles, its first missile test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Ford wraps NY Fashion Week with a show of disco glam...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-fashion-0fbba01be4ffaf8aed48437680820d6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Champagne was cold and the front row star studded Sunday night as Tom Ford closed New York Fashion Week at Lincoln Center with a spring-summer collection of hopeful, glitzy glam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol rally seeks to rewrite Jan. 6 by exalting rioters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-d2fb23af3f01387412a1a00b4eac531c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — First, some blamed the deadly Jan. 6 attack at the U.S. Capitol  on left-wing antifa antagonists, a theory quickly debunked. Then came comparisons of the rioters to peaceful protesters or even tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allegations fly as recall vote looms for Newsom...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-california-los-angeles-gavin-newsom-long-beach-00e1180f98406e85439616f822f6ba18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — In a blitz of TV ads and a last-minute rally, California Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom urged voters Sunday to turn back a looming recall vote that could remove him from office, while leading Republican Larry Elder broadly criticized the media for what he described as double standards that insulated Newsom from criticism and scrutiny throughout the contest.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
