<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Freeway project unearths a time when camels roamed San Diego!</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/science/story/2020-07-17/fossil-find-ancient-camels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paleontologists dig up fossils thought to be at least 15 million years old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  The Founding Fathers Would've Been Pro-Face Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-founding-fathers-wouldve-been-pro-face-mask/ar-BB16U9Uh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AOC's Anti-Billionaire Crusaders Are Spreading in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/aocs-anti-billionaire-crusaders-are-spreading-in-new-york-city/ar-BB16U2IN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of coordination leaves states spiraling...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/coronavirus/us-coronavirus-testing-mired-in-another-round-of-failures-worsening-outbreaks-20200717.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What has the U.S. learned from ramping up diagnostic testing? Not enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK:  Woman pretended to have cancer for years to scam people for donations...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/crime/article244319752.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank pays extra for change due to growing coin shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/coin-shortage-prompts-bank-to-pay-you-for-spare-change-it-has-never-happened-before</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you have a jar of coins in your house? Maybe you have been saving for a special occasion? Well, a local bank says they will pay you for what’s inside that jar — plus interest!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona back in lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/barcelona-back-under-lockdown-virus-cases-surge-171832241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barcelona's streets were largely empty on Saturday, with millions of people instructed to stay at home as new coronavirus restrictions came into effect following a spike in the number of infections in the region over the past week. "It's a disaster," wails Maria Quintana, looking at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 1918 flu hammered this Arizona mining town. Now a new scourge looms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/1918-flu-hammered-arizona-mining-130015845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This southeastern Arizona town, once a tourist haven, is struggling during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthy 13-Year-Old Boy Dies Days After Experiencing Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/17/claremont-13-year-old-dies-covid-19-symptoms-maxx-cheng/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An autopsy report to determine Maxx Cheng's cause of death, and whether he had COVID-19, is expected in the coming days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85 Babies Test Positive In One TX County!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/07/18/texas-county-reports-85-babies-positive-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eighty-five infants under age 1 have tested positive for coronavirus in one Texas county.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARTEL FLEX: Mexico video shows dozens of uniformed gunmen, armored cars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb2a8b66ba6d281c2f61290c4ea21cda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico's top security official said Saturday that authorities are investigating a video showing dozens of combat-uniformed gunmen posing with military-grade weapons and armored...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bet crisis would fade away proved wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/inside-the-trump-administration-s-rush-to-abandon-leadership-role-on-the-virus/571821141/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the Trump administration's rush to abandon leadership role on the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson suspected as fire ravages medieval cathedral in French city...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/arson-suspected-fire-ravages-medieval-cathedral-french-city-nantes-n1234287</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze comes just over a year after a massive fire at the historic Notre-Dame Cathedral in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin seeks to block money for testing, tracing, CDC in upcoming relief bill... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-administration-pushing-to-block-new-money-for-testing-tracing-and-cdc-in-upcoming-coronavirus-relief-bill/ar-BB16UnyK?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Star, Web Founder Team Up on Tech for Humans to Communicate With Animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/rock-star-and-web-founder-teaming-up-on-technology/ar-BB16Slqf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot sells for $100,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-sold-80000-after-22373765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Whitney Cummings last year had a sex robot based on her after it was produced by RealDoll. The company says it is the most expensive doll it has ever sold</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW PEAK NOW:  USA 71,558 INFECTIONS PAST 24 HOURS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/18/us-reports-more-than-70000-new-coronavirus-infections-for-second-day-in-a-row.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Saturday, the 7-day average has seen a 18.34% increase in new cases compared to one week ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CONTINUES TO DISRUPT DAILY LIFE</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Coronavirus-updates-Halfway-through-the-year-15418121.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Halfway through the year - and halfway through the summer season when officials once hoped warmer weather might speed the coronavirus's retreat - the pandemic is only intensifying in much of the country.  Major school districts are bucking federal pressure to say they won't reopen classrooms in the fall. Infections have been reaching record heights in the South, West and Midwest. More than 20 states are reporting seven-day averages in coronavirus-related deaths higher than at the end of June, underscoring the turnaround since May and June when deaths declined nationally - a development President Donald Trump had touted as a sign of progress.  Here are some other significant developments:  The Trump administration is trying to block billions of dollars for states to conduct testing and contact tracing in an upcoming coronavirus relief bill, people involved in the talks said Saturday. The administration is also trying to block billions that GOP senators want to allocate for the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the people said.  Arizona on Saturday reported a single-day high in new deaths, another sign that the surge in fatalities health officials had warned about is underway. And North Carolina, Georgia, Kentucky, Wisconsin and Missouri announced record-high new cases.  A study from South Korea could bolster those who argue reopening classrooms in much of the United States is too risky, suggesting that, while children under 10 years old are less likely to spread the coronavirus, young people between 10 and 19 years old will spread it similarly to adults.  Health authorities are seeking to conduct testing faster while conserving resources. The Food and Drug Administration on Saturday reissued an emergency use authorization to Quest Diagnostics for a coronavirus test to be used in pool testing, which involves...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Cannon Sparks Concern With Troubling Tweet About Leaving Planet...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2020/07/17/fans-express-concern-for-nick-cannon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans are worried about Nick Cannon after he posted a tweet amid his podcast scandal, saying: "Y’all can have this planet. I’m out!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis protest against Netanyahu, gov't handling...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200718193022-cm1pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-PROTESTS (TV, PIX):Israelis protest against Netanyahu, gov't handling of COVID-19 crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam discourages red light district visits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f595fc278431a2e6c5b165d8b468a4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands — Authorities in Amsterdam are urging people not to visit the city’s famous red light district and have closed off some of the historic district’s narrow streets because...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions raised after fatal motorcycle crash listed as COVID-19 death...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox35orlando.com/news/fox-35-investigates-questions-raised-after-fatal-motorcycle-crash-listed-as-covid-19-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox35orlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person who died in a motorcycle accident was added to Florida’s COVID-19 death count, according to a state health official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Woman Urinates On Floor After Refusing To Leave VERIZON Store For Not Covering Up...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/07/17/roseville-urination-verizon-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities responding to reports of a disturbance at a Verizon store arrested a woman who is accused of refusing to wear a mask, urinating in the store and was linked to a theft at a nearby business, the Roseville Police Department said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber can subpoena TWITTER to turn over sexual assault accusers, judge rules...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/18/will-justin-bieber-subpoena-twitter-to-turn-over-sexual-assault-accusers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women who used Twitter to anonymously accuse Justin Bieber of sexual assault may be identified after a judge ruled that the star is allowed to subpoena the social media platform for the info.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Inside Trump Failure: Rush to Abandon Leadership Role on Virus...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/18/inside-trumps-failure-the-rush-to-abandon-leadership-role-on-the-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Each morning at 8 as the coronavirus crisis was raging in April, Mark Meadows, the White House chief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Florida relock?</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/miami-dade/fl-ne-more-shutdowns-could-be-coming-soon-20200718-myxkzk726ndtjpkafcc34a7ovu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The question now is whether limited restrictions like masks and curfews can reverse the coronavirus wave. Many people think not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Doctor Versus Denier...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/18/opinion/fauci-trump-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci’s at the pool, but Donald Trump’s in deep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting on Athlete's Heart Rate During Game Coming to Broadcasting?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/is-betting-an-athletes-heart-rate-a-game-coming-broadcasting-guest-column-1303582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's now possible to measure in real time biometric data like an athlete’s respiration, temperature, blood pressure, and more. Can sports content partners let people gamble on these metrics?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young people increasingly driving spread...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/507905-young-people-are-increasingly-driving-covid-19s-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Younger Americans eager to get back to their social lives are increasingly responsible for the spread of the coronavirus, risking their own health and that of their family and friends under what health experts say is the misguided impression that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola cases rise in new outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ebola-cases-rise-dr-congo-outbreak-153320535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ebola outbreak in the DR Congo's northwest is growing, according to health officials, sounding the alarm weeks after the country officially declared an end to a separate Ebola epidemic which claimed over 2,000 lives. There have been 54 confirmed cases since June 1 in Mbandaka, a transport hub</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients swamp ERs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b41b3eae4574d3630d6904261ad88871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-rising rising tide of new coronavirus cases is flooding emergency rooms in parts of the United States, with some patients moved into hallways and nurses working extra shifts to keep up with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trouble in suburbs key to suddenly competitive Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a4f8eaa5a1401cc6371c5d76dba03c6a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI (AP) — During a background briefing with reporters in December, President Donald Trump's reelection campaign team gave only passing mention of Ohio. Certainly no one suggested a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas dog makes 50-mile trek to her old home in Missouri...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/507e69b87d79fb48c42dca1ef77daac7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAWSON, Mo. (AP) — A dog named Cleo who disappeared from her home in Kansas earlier this month turned up a few days later at her old home in Missouri, about 50 miles (80 kilometers)...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Be Most Powerful in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/07/joe-bidens-vice-president-powerful-history/614161/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’d need to maintain a healthy partnership with his deputy—without worrying that she’ll outshine him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters clash with police in violent encounter at Chicago's Columbus statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/07/18/chicago-protest-columbus-statue-18-police-wounded-12-arrested/5464162002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of protesters attempting to topple the city's Christopher Columbus statute faced off with dozens of Chicago police Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Creepy Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/its-spooky-right-now-inside-the-creepy-federal-crackdown-on-portland-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Customs and Border Protection joined the protest crackdown in D.C., they were made into U.S. Marshals. In Portland, they’re using new powers provided by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Low-Budget Horror Is Thriving This Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2020/07/why-low-budget-horror-thriving-summer/614344/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These dirt-cheap productions are making money, finding eager audiences, and garnering critical praise during a largely dead box-office season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lollapalooza co-founder predicts no concerts until 2022...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/507946-lollapalooza-co-founder-predicts-no-concerts-until-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lollapalooza co-founder Marc Geiger predicts there may not be concerts or festivals in the U.S. until 2022 due to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground parties continue to dismiss social distancing rules...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/18/underground-parties-continue-to-dismiss-social-distancing-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clubs continue to be called out for packed parties that don’t follow social distancing rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trusted employee arrested in grisly murder of tech CEO... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/17/tyrese-haspil-charged-with-murdering-tech-ceo-fahim-saleh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trusted employee of tech CEO and investor Fahim Saleh was arrested on Friday in his boss’ slaying and dismemberment on the Lower East Side — with sources saying the motive involved a broken promi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China city enters 'wartime mode'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200718112239-8lt36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/CHINA-CASES (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-China's western city Urumqi enters 'wartime mode' after reporting 16 coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising Opposition...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/18/federal-officers-in-portland-face-rising-opposition-on-streets-and-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. — An aggressive federal campaign to suppress unrest in Portland appears to have instead rejuvenated the city’s movement,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Star, Web Founder Team Up on Tech for Humans to Communicate With Animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/rock-star-and-internet-founder-team-up-on-dr-dolittle-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rock Star and Internet Founder Team Up on Dr Dolittle Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor who survived bewildered by public disregard...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3f548ec32bf6b7dd198f26c90b8cff2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIRMINGHAM, Ala. (AP) — Dr. Michael Saag spends much of his time treating patients fighting for their lives and working with colleagues who are overwhelmed and exhausted by the relentless battle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP senators sound alarm as cases surge in home states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/507924-gop-senators-sound-alarm-as-coronavirus-surges-in-home-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are raising the alarm over the country's rapidly growing number of coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistrust Could Imperil Widespread Immunity...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/18/mistrust-of-a-coronavirus-vaccine-could-imperil-widespread-immunity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost daily, President Trump and leaders worldwide say they are racing to develop a coronavirus vaccine, in perhaps the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathtaking virus numbers show normal life still far away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c0d1e01ffd786d510a37951d758a996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — South Africa was poised on Saturday to join the top five countries most affected by the coronavirus, while breathtaking numbers around the world were a reminder that a return...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to launch mini space station as military takes to stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/pentagon-launch-mini-space-station-22366865 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bermuda Pitches Island Life as Escape From Pandemic Madness...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/bermuda-pitches-island-life-as-escape-from-pandemic-madness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For anyone tired of dodging coronavirus Bermuda has an offer: a year at the beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal Case Launched After 15th Century Cathedral in Nantes Catches on Fire...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/europe/202007181079921473-cathedral-in-nantes-france-catches-on-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Roman Catholic church located in Nantes, Pays de la Loire, France has caught fire a year after a devastating blaze hit the Notre-Dame cathedral in Paris, partially...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surging Dems expand Senate targets to Republican states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/269c5a18f098ec93e8a63fc460a78e0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It's come to this for Republicans straining to defend their Senate majority in November's elections: They're air-dropping millions of dollars into races in Alabama, Kentucky and...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
