<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Beggar asks for cash on board plane...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5861269/Beggar-asks-cash-board-PASSENGER-PLANE.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The middle-aged man held out a plastic pouch and pleaded for help onboard a Qatar Airways flight from Doha to Shiraz, ignoring repeated requests from staff to sit down - reports Daily Pakistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOTTI' fires back at critics: 'Trolls behind keyboard'...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/movies/2018/06/19/gotti-slams-movie-critics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst reviewed movie of the year is firing back at film critics. The official Twitter feed for Gotti released an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies destroy ISIS drug lab making 'Jihadi Pills'...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/2018/06/18/us-led-coalition-destroys-islamic-state-narcotics-cache-including-300000-so-called-jihadi-pills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The international coalition to defeat the Islamic State of Iraq and Syria destroyed a large drug cache on June 12 that was previously controlled by the militant group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Invasion of West...</title>
      <link>https://www.chroniclesmagazine.org/trump-and-the-invasion-of-the-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chroniclesmagazine.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[St]riking down the policy will leave America's immigration crisis still unresolved. Consider. Since 2016, some 110,000 children have entered the U.S. illegally and been released, along with 200,000 Central American families caught sneaking across the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER under fire after mistaking ICE worker tattoo for Nazi symbol...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/19/new-yorker-fact-checker-under-fire-after-mistaking-ice-workers-tattoo-for-nazi-symbol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Harvard-educated fact-checker for the New Yorker is being excoriated by the Immigration and Customs Enforcement agency for “baselessly slandering” a Marine veteran — by falsely accusing him…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders consider camps outside bloc to process refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/regional-disembarkation-platforms-eu-leaders-consider-camps-outside-bloc-to-process-refugees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Nets Flood Broadcasts With 176 Minutes of Separated Kids Coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/geoffrey-dickens/2018/06/19/six-days-june-nets-flood-broadcasts-176-minutes-separated-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outraged anchors and correspondents at ABC, CBS and NBC attacked the Trump administration for separating children from parents at the border as they overwhelmed their Monday morning and evening news programs with a massive 94 minutes of coverage on the detainment policy. Overall, in just six days of coverage (June 13 through June 18) the nets have flooded their broadcasts with almost three hours (176 minutes) of emotional segments that included pictures of crying children and accompanying anger from correspondents and pundits alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Invasion of The West...</title>
      <link>http://www.unionleader.com/article/20180614/OPINION02/180619646/0/NEWS07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the G-7 summit in Canada, President Donald Trump described America as “the piggy bank that everybody is robbing.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DOUBLES DOWN:  Dems want illegals to 'infest our country'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/392977-trump-dems-want-illegal-immigrants-to-infest-our-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday restated his support for his administration's policy of separating migrant families at the U.S. border, calling Democrats "the problem."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: DNA Tests Reveal Species Of Mystery Animal Shot In Montana...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/dna-test-reveals-identity-of-mysterious-wolf-creature-shot-in-montana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About a month after the animal turned up on a Montana ranch, a DNA test has come back with its true identity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE HEATS UP CAMPAIGNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.gjsentinel.com/breaking/border-separations-ripple-through-midterm-campaigns/article_7d7e46da-73c6-11e8-9e4a-03bd699ad789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gjsentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wrenching scenes of migrant children being separated from their parents at the southern border are roiling campaigns ahead of midterm elections, emboldening Democrats on the often-fraught issue of immigration while</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVS PLANS DRUG DELIVERIES NATIONWIDE...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyjournal.net/2018/06/19/us-cvs-prescription-deliveries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyjournal.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CVS Health is making prescription deliveries nationwide to accommodate the heightened expectations of convenience from consumers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Trump and the Invasion of The West...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/06/trump-and-the-invasion-of-the-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is cruel. It is immoral. And it breaks my heart,” says former first lady Laura Bush of the Trump administration policy of “zero tolerance,” under which the children of illegal migrants are being detained apart from their parents. “Disgraceful,” adds Dr. Franklin Graham. “We need to be … a country that governs with a […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicted own death?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6569196/xxxtentacion-dead-rapper-predicted-own-death-video-miami-shooting-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAPPER XXXTentacion predicted his own death in a chilling Instagram video he filmed before he was fatally shot in Florida yesterday. The 20-year-old was gunned down as he left a motorcycle dealersh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson Broadway Musical Planned...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/19/michael-jackson-broadway-musical-planned-but-its-not-so-easy-as-abc-1-2-3-to-tell-his-life-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Michael Jackson Estate is said to be producing a Broadway musical about the King of Pop. Pulitzer Prize winning playwright Lynn Nottage is writing the book. Tony Award winning choreographer Chr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems rising star admits -- he's a Trump supporter!</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/392945-dem-house-candidate-in-west-virginia-voted-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Ojeda backed Donald Trump for president, but the West Virginia state senator is now running as a Democrat for the House as his party seeks to wrest control of Congress from Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk alleges extensive sabotage by employee...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/elon-musk-email-employee-conducted-extensive-and-damaging-sabotage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk sent an e-mail to all employees late on Sunday night alleging a saboteur within the company's ranks had tweaked code on internal products and sent company data out without authorization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderate drinking teaches heart cells how to toughen up...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5860471/How-alcohol-protects-heart-Scientists-discover-moderate-drinking-toughens-heart-cells.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of São Paulo discovered the body's reaction to drinking alcohol is similar to its reaction during a heart attack, so alcohol could help the body learn to protect itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets Begin to Take Threat of Trade War Seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/markets-begin-to-take-threat-of-trade-war-seriously-1529411543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese stocks logged their steepest declines since trade tensions between the U.S. and China began, a turning point in the reaction to an escalating trade war. Dow futures pointed to a more than 300-point decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared meets Jordan's Abdullah about Israeli-Palestinian peace...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180619133252-9t8jz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-JORDAN/ (URGENT):White House says Kushner met Jordan's Abdullah about Israeli-Palestinian peace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Officials Approve Plan to Build Largest Mall...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/florida-officials-approve-plan-to-build-largest-u-s-mall-1529406001 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a time when store closures are accelerating and struggling malls pockmark the country, county commissioners in Florida have approved a plan to build what would be the largest mall in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange health fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/976425/julian-assange-health-update-wikileaks-anniversary-ecuador-embassy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULIAN Assange’s lawyers hit out at the UK and the WikiLeaks founder is being forced to make an “impossible choice” between his health and his safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent Fight Caught On Video At Hollywood Homeless Camp; Residents Fed Up...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/06/18/homeless-camp-fights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent fight at a homeless camp in Hollywood was caught on camera. Residents say it happens all the time and they are fed up and fighting back. Tom Wait reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Chart-topping Rapper shot and killed in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f42d12c851a4ba18f7adf6d154f41b4/No-motive,-arrests-in-fatal-shooting-of-rapper-XXXTentacion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEERFIELD BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Troubled rapper-singer XXXTentacion was shot and killed Monday in Florida in what police called an apparent robbery attempt. Investigators don't have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tops Germany as country with most new asylum requests...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/asylum-requests-us-tops-germany-as-country-with-most-new/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home price insanity: $2.6 million for 900 square feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/home-price-insanity-2-6-million-for-900-square-feet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A two-bedroom, one-bathroom cottage in Palo Alto, Calif., is the latest example of skyrocketing home prices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going gluten-free linked to unhealthy weight loss...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/18/going-gluten-free-linked-to-unhealthy-weight-loss-behaviors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gluten-free eating has a dark side. A new study led by researchers at the University of Minnesota found that young adults aged 25 to 36 who regularly consumed gluten-free foods were also more likel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable News: 22 Comparisons of Immigration Policy to Holocaust, Slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/bill-dagostino/2018/06/18/cable-news-22-comparisons-immigration-policy-holocaust-slavery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pundit class have lost their minds over the Trump administration’s zero-tolerance border enforcement policy. Since Friday, the collective breakdown has yielded a total of 22 instances in which cable news commentators compared the separation of parents and children illegally entering the country to World War II-era war crimes and human rights violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Man beat neighbor over lawn mowing job...</title>
      <link>http://www.gwcommonwealth.com/state_news/article_015b6bb4-3a9a-537d-b49b-5b1fcd2aa4f3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gwcommonwealth.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENWOOD, Miss. (AP) — A Mississippi man is accused of beating a neighbor with a hammer and an ax handle for hiring someone else to mow their lawn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man convicted over Nazi salute in Austria...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/croatian-man-convicted-over-nazi-salute-austria-104844616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A Croatian man has been handed a 15-month suspended sentence for giving a Nazi salute at an annual commemoration in Austria of a 1945 massacre of pro-Nazi Croats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Abusive Emo 'Sex Cult'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-an-alleged-abusive-emo-sex-cult-none-of-these-poor-girls-could-say-no </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple women claim that musician William Control is the leader of a violent ‘sex cult,’ branding women with his initials and forcing them to obey his every terrifying demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERIK PRINCE: I 'Cooperated' With Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/erik-prince-i-cooperated-with-mueller </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trumpworld insider is under scrutiny for his alleged backchanneling with Russia, his work for China, and his plans for Afghanistan. He defends it all in a new interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacred snappers: Village where crocodiles welcome...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/sacred-snappers-village-where-crocodiles-welcome-031753245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bazoulé (Burkina Faso) (AFP) - Crocodiles may be one of the deadliest hunters in the animal kingdom, but in a small village in Burkina Faso it is not unusual to see someone sitting atop one of the fearsome reptiles. People in Bazoule, around 30 kilometres (20 miles) from the capital Ouagadougou, share</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's 'millionaires,' the new poor...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuelas-millionaires-poor-051601973.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Torres is outraged, but as a Venezuelan she takes the affront in her stride. "We are a country of millionaires," she says ironically, eyeing a carton of eggs in the market. "You are a millionaire because you have to pay that much, and for that you get 36 eggs, but the minimum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigarette smoking reaches new low...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-cigarette-smoking-reaches-low-study-042628548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's National Center for Health Statistics refer to adult cigarette smokers in 2017. A previous CDC report using 2016 data found that 15.5 percent of adults smoked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Denmark? Faroese weigh pulling free of Danish grip...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/goodbye-denmark-faroese-weigh-pulling-free-danish-grip-031544917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tórshavn (Denmark) (AFP) - Enough is enough: for the Faroese sailor Birgir Enni, having spent more than half a millennium under Danish rule means it's about time for the North Atlantic autonomous archipelago to break away. "We've been occupied by Denmark for 600 years! That is enough and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan faces biggest challenge in tight Turkey polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-faces-biggest-challenge-tight-turkey-polls-025537089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Sunday faces the biggest ballot box challenge of his 15-year grip on Turkey, seeking to overcome a revitalised opposition against the background of an increasingly troubled economy. A self-styled heavyweight champion of campaigning, Erdogan has won successive elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian opposition leader Navalny calls for protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-opposition-leader-navalny-calls-protests-during-world-091832914.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian opposition politician Alexei Navalny called Tuesday for nationwide protests to take place across the country during the World Cup over a government plan to raise the retirement age for the first time in its modern history. Navalny said his team had so far applied for permits to hold demonstrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At $9.7 Million a Pop, Private Jets Luring Buyers Once Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/19/at-9-7-million-a-pop-private-jets-are-luring-buyers-once-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At $9.7 Million a Pop, Private Jets Are Luring Buyers Once Again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-you-can-eat offer bankrupts restaurant in just two weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/you-can-eat-restaurant-forced-12741216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese restaurant Jiamener was offering an incredible loyalty deal - but it didn't end well for the owners</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM computer debates humans -- and wins...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/an-ibm-computer-debates-humans-and-wins-in-a-new-nuanced-competition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to computational argumentation. IBM's Project Debater won a convincing victory in one debate but a human debater edged it out in another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 weeks out from midterms, Dems and GOP brace for surprises...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/392872-20-weeks-out-from-midterms-dems-and-gop-brace-for-surprises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty weeks before November’s midterm elections, Democrats and Republicans are cautiously eyeing a fluid political landscape, one that is likely to be dramatically altered by outside forces in the weeks and months ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks set to skid as Trump ratchets up pressure on China... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/19/us-stock-futures-trade-tensions-in-focus-for-investors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures slumped ahead of Tuesday’s open, after President Donald Trump threatened China with a new raft of tariffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters accused of making porn in station...</title>
      <link>http://www.cleveland19.com/story/38448345/2-akron-firefighters-accused-of-making-pornography-in-fire-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland19.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Akron Fire Department firefighters, Art Dean and Deann Eller are on paid leave pending an investigation into allegations that they created pornographic videos in an Akron fire station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing vows to FIGHT BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/trade-war-watch-china-pledges-it-will-fight-back-firmly-if-trump-publishes-list-of-new-tariffs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Commerce Ministry said on Tuesday morning that it will take counter measures if the U.S. publishes an additional tariffs list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE HEATS UP CAMPAIGNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/As-debate-shifts-GOP-decries-family-separations-13005407.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A backlash over the Trump administration's decision to separate children from their parents at the southern border has left Republican candidates scrambling to distance themselves from a policy the president sees as central to accomplishing his political goals. A shift in the dynamics of immigration politics, which Trump has long used to his advantage and some Democrats have seen as a liability, was evident Monday as the face of the debate moved from violent central American street gang members to young and bewildered children isolated by federal agents behind chain-link fences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA employee charged in major leak of agency hacking tools... </title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Ex-CIA-employee-charged-in-major-leak-of-agency-13005463.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors on Monday charged a former CIA employee with violations of the Espionage Act and related crimes in connection with the leak last year of a collection of hacking tools that the agency used for spy operations overseas. Joshua Adam Schulte, who worked for a CIA group that designs computer code to spy on foreign adversaries, was charged in a 13-count superseding indictment with illegally gathering and transmitting national defense information and other related counts in connection with what is considered to be one of the most significant leaks in CIA history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Dole's final mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Bob-Dole-s-final-mission-13005359.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each Saturday, before Bob Dole sets off on his latest vocation, he has cornflakes, a little sugar on top, and a bottle of chocolate Boost. It takes less time to get dressed now that the 94-year-old finally allows a nurse to help him, but it remains a rough half-hour on a body racked by injury and age. The blue oxford has to be maneuvered over the dead right arm and the shoulder that was blown away on an Italian hillside. The pressed khakis over the scarred thigh. A pair of North Face running shoes, the likes of which his artillery-blasted hands have been unable to tie since 1945. Then comes the hard part - getting there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Chart-topping Rapper shot and killed in Florida...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/18/xxxtentacion-shot-dead-miami/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;XXXTentacion was shot dead Monday -- TMZ has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marriage is [literally] good for heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/marriage-literally-good-heart-study-225324808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even if marriage is sometimes more a bed of nails than roses, living into old age with a partner may help ward off heart disease and stroke, researchers said Tuesday. A sweeping survey of research conducted over the last two decades covering more than two million people aged 42 to 77 found that being</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As summer travel begins, TSA says come early and be prepared...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/business/article/As-summer-travel-season-begins-TSA-says-come-13004331.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLONIE - Come early, have your bag packed properly and expect that you might need to unpack some items at the security checkpoint, more so than last summer.  That's the advice of Bart Johnson, who leads security for the Transportation Security Administration at airports across upstate, including at Albany International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homophobic chants haunt Mexican soccer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/jun/18/puto-chants-mexico-football-world-cup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Tri’s victory over Germany on Sunday was marred by alleged homophobic chanting. It’s a common trend across stadiums in the Americas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART shopper accused of making 1,000 fake returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/17/us/walmart-shopper-accused-fake-returns/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 23-year-old Walmart shopper is accused of making fraudulent returns at more than 1,000 of the chain's stores across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Dre to make Marvin Gaye biopic with rights to singer's catalogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jun/18/dr-dre-marvin-gaye-biopic-rights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper, whose film credits include Straight Outta Compton, has the singer’s family estate’s blessing to produce the biopic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Chief: Illegal Kids Have 'Playstations, Pool Tables' in Shelters... </title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/border-chief-rebukes-media-illegal-immigrant-kids-have-playstations-pool-tables-in-shelters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSM reporting that children kept in concentration camps patently false, he says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says cash handouts from govt 'necessary' if robots take jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/elon-musk-automated-jobs-could-make-ubi-cash-handouts-necessary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla and SpaceX billionaire tweeted about universal basic income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary fundraises off border 'humanitarian crisis'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/hillary-fundraises-off-border-humanitarian-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Never let a crisis go to waste,” the Clintonista Rahm Emanuel once said. Hillary Clinton is very concerned about what’s happening on the southern border, and despite not being a candidate for anything (yet), she wants Americans to give her money to do something about it. The failed Democratic candidate for president sent a fundraising …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return From Exile: Kevin Spacey Movie to Hit Theaters This Summer...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/12/kevin-spacey-film-billionaire-boys-club-coming-in-august-from-same-distributor-as-gotti-movie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vertical Entertainment may be remembered one day the as the film distributor of lost causes. The very small company with peculiar taste is going to release “Billionaire Boys Club” on Au…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Two Suitors for FOX, Murdochs Consider Next Steps... </title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/with-two-suitors-for-fox-the-murdochs-consider-next-steps/17636468/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Walt Disney Co. has agreed to buy most of 21st Century Fox’s assets in a deal worth $52.4 billion, but things got complicated last week when Comcast made a rival offer that valued the business at $65 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah Becomes One of World's 500 Richest...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/18/oprah-winfrey-just-became-one-of-the-world-s-500-richest-people </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oprah Winfrey Just Became One of the World's 500 Richest People</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Heather Locklear hospitalized after threatening to shoot self...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/18/heather-locklear-hospitalized-psych-evaluation-threatening-shoot-herself/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heather Locklear was hospitalized for a psych evaluation after threatening to harm herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP READIES $200B IN NEW CHINA TARIFFS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/donald-trump-readies-new-tariffs-for-china-1529365844</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump launched a pre-emptive strike in the trade conflict with China, directing his aides to identify $200 billion in Chinese goods for new 10% tariffs—in case Beijing retaliates against the tariffs the U.S. imposed earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zayn loves America and might want to run for office... </title>
      <link> https://www.yahoo.com/news/zayn-loves-america-might-want-run-office-193306046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return From Exile: Kevin Spacey Flick to Hit Theaters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/kevin-spaceys-billionaire-boys-club-to-hit-theaters-in-august/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is neither an easy nor insensitive decision," indie distributor Vertical Entertainment says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts court strikes down 'millionaire tax' ballot question...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/politics/index.ssf/2018/06/sjc_strikes_down_ballot_questi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain to remove Franco remains from mausoleum...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/spains-government-remove-francos-remains-mausoleum-193605593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's new Socialist government is determined to remove the remains of Francisco Franco from a vast mausoleum near Madrid and turn it into a place of "reconciliation" for a country still coming to terms with the dictator's legacy. "We don't have a date yet, but the government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves 'MISSION IMPOSSIBLE'-Style Rappel Through BEST BUY Ceiling For $100k APPLE Product Heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/north-fulton-county/burglars-make-off-with-100k-in-merchandise-after-rapelling-through-best-buy-ceiling-police-say/772298528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police compared the crime to a heist like the one in 'Mission Impossible.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Trapper rescues alligator from python's death grip!</title>
      <link>https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/local/florida-man-saves-his-third-gator-from-a-python-in-under-a-year/565179214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtsp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This wasn't Kimmel's first go around with the big snakes; in fact this was the third alligator in under a year he had successfully rescued from the grasp of a python, he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate rejects rescue of ZTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/18/senate-rejects-trumps-rescue-of-chinese-firm-zte-652459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vote is a rebuke to President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Bans Super Sperm Donor...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/why-is-israel-banning-this-u-s-jewish-super-sperm-donor-1.6179555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass. Gov Cancels National Guard Deployment To Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.wgbh.org/news/local-news/2018/06/18/baker-cancels-national-guard-deployment-to-border-citing-inhumane-treatment-of-children-and-families</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wgbh.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baker joins a growing chorus, including former First Lady Laura Bush and a coalition of Catholic Bishops, condemning the Trump Administration's decision to take children away from asylum seeking families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump warns USA could follow path of Germany on immigration...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/trump-warns-u-s-could-follow-path-of-germany-on-immigration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump appeared to defend policy of separating migrant families by saying immigration-related issues in Germany and Europe could happen here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Won't Let Become 'Migrant Camp'...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5314997/donald-trump-immigration-policy-migrant-camp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Not on my watch"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Operates On Human Eye for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/robot-assisted-eye-surgery-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bot's a bit slow, but completely effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father's Day Dinner Shock: Restaurant Receipt Instructs Cook To SPIT On Burger!</title>
      <link>http://abc7.com/food/restaurant-receipt-please-spit-in-burger/3614918/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After he already ate his burger, a New York restaurant customer saw his receipt had orders to the cook "Please spit in it too!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd yells in horror as circus bear jumps off skateboard, attacks handler...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5856227/Bear-forced-ride-SKATEBOARD-attacks-Russian-circus-handler.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children in the audience screamed as the animal turned on its keepers moments after riding down a ramp during a performance at a village in Russia's Volgograd region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Bezos Worth $141,900,000,000 -- Nearly $50B More Than Bill Gates!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/how-amazon-made-jeff-bezos-the-richest-man-alive-worth-141-billion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bezos is worth more than Bill Gates or Warren Buffett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City traffic path for people walking and texting...</title>
      <link>http://bgr.com/2018/06/15/smartphone-texting-path-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’ve never run into anyone while walking down a sidewalk texting a friend or scrolling through Instagram, you’ve probably come pretty close. As a culture, we’ve become irrevo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Wife shoots husband's testicles after trying to take air conditioner...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkbn.com/news/national-world/florida-woman-shoots-husband-in-testicles-after-he-tries-to-take-air-conditioner/1245513440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say Kimberly Dunn lost her cool when her husband and his brother went to her Lake City home to pick up an air conditioning unit she was selling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How European Opera Houses Won Over Millennials...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-europes-opera-houses-won-over-millennials-1529332646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With an escape game and networking parties, La Scala and the Paris Opera are attracting under-30 audiences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norman Pearlstine named top LATIMES editor...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-norman-pearlstine-latimes-editor-20180618-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norman Pearlstine, who has spent 50 years in journalism helping shape some of the nation’s most prominent publications — including Time Inc. magazines, Bloomberg News, Forbes and the Wall Street Journal — on Monday was named executive editor of the Los Angeles Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mechanic admits to impersonating general after chartering helicopter to impress married woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdtn.com/news/u-s-world/man-will-admit-to-impersonating-general-for-helicopter-ride/1246616778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdtn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) - A man accused of trying to impress a woman by landing a chartered helicopter at a North Carolina technology company plans to plead guilty to impersonating a three-star Army general and will concede that he was sane at the time, according to a new court filing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRONC abandoning name...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/18/tronc-finally-realizes-it-has-a-stupid-name/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tronc, one of the most lambasted corporate name changes of the digital era, is going to return to its original name, Tribune Publishing. An insider said that the name change for the parent company …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian lawmaker wants to ban 'mockery' of soccer team...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-lawmaker-wants-ban-mockery-soccer-team-172505377--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Russia (AP) — A conservative legislator in Russia says he wants to ban "mockery" of the national soccer team because the players are "fighting for the honor of our country."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia: Marines beefed-up presence in Norway an attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/06/18/russia-argues-the-corps-beefed-up-presence-in-norway-is-an-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week Russia warned there would be consequences following Norway's decision to invite 700 Marines for training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY UNDER INVESTIGATION...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/18/comey-under-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEVELOPING...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Tractor Strikes Roadside Explosive, Linked To Mysterious PA Booms...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/06/15/police-tractor-mowing-grass-strikes-device-related-to-mysterious-explosions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating another mysterious explosion in Bucks County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: WENDY'S Employee Finds Mouse, Feces In Burger Bun Bag...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/06/18/video-mouse-found-crawling-in-bag-of-wendys-hamburger-buns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It shows a mouse among the hamburger buns and feces throughout the packaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: TRUMP APPROVAL TIES HIGHEST OF PRESIDENCY...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/203207/trump-job-approval-weekly.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gallup tracks daily the percentage of Americans who approve or disapprove of the job Donald Trump is doing as president. Weekly results are based on telephone interviews with approximately 1,500 national adults, with a margin of error is ±3 percentage points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian mobster jailed for vicious attack on journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/italian-mobster-jailed-vicious-attack-journalist-172136279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A notorious Italian mobster, Roberto Spada, was sentenced Monday to six years in jail for violently assaulting a journalist during an interview in 2017, the video of which immediately went viral. The assault, which shocked Italy, occurred last November in the seaside town of Ostia, near Rome. Daniele</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia cuts Treasury holdings in half as foreigners start losing appetite for US debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/russia-cuts-treasury-holdings-in-half-as-foreigners-start-losing-appetite-for-us-debt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign governments pulled back their purchase of U.S. debt as trade tensions escalated. One of the most glaring declines has come from Russia, which sliced its holdings nearly in half from March to April, from $96.1 billion to $48.7 billion.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
