<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CA NIGHTMARE SUMMER</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/california-drought-summer-wildfire-a0e2c959-8d76-4c56-af5d-e13b1ee76e6f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Southwest is drying out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOES PUSH FOR QUICK VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-politics-netanyahu-lapid-bennett-e96cc15e2474658e271e373cd4d6aeda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s opponents pushed Thursday for a quick parliament vote to formally end his lengthy rule, hoping to head off any last-minute attempts to derail their newly announced coalition government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrinking giants: North Atlantic right whales getting tinier...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-climate-change-whales-science-environment-and-nature-e8478d8d6decf8a6cf4c9037f0c60f2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the giants of the deep is shrinking before our eyes, a new study says. The younger generation of critically endangered  North Atlantic right whales are on average about three feet (one meter) shorter than whales were 20 years, drone and aircraft data show in a study in Thursday’s journal Current Biology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-printed 'electric nose' can SNIFF out virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9648775/3D-printed-electric-nose-SNIFF-COVID-19-just-80-seconds-94-accuracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'electric nose' sits in the nostril and uses deep learning to sniff out the coronavirus, which emits specific smelling chemicals. The device produces results in just 80 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of elder care is here: Artificial intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jun/03/elder-care-artificial-intelligence-software</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Computers are increasingly guiding decisions about elder care – and tracking everything from toilet visits to whether someone has bathed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden offers to keep '17 tax cuts intact in infrastructure counteroffer ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-offers-to-keep-2017-trump-tax-cuts-intact-in-infrastructure-counteroffer-to-gop/ar-AAKFOS8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's new offer to pay for infrastructure would look to end tax loopholes for corporations but not raise the corporate tax rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity attorney F. Lee Bailey dead at 87...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ma-state-wire-f-lee-bailey-entertainment-celebrity-8cdd719dd3dbfa6c2ea30bc853f8b036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALTHAM, Mass. (AP) — F. Lee Bailey, the celebrity attorney who defended O.J. Simpson, Patricia Hearst and the alleged Boston Strangler, but whose legal career halted when he was disbarred in two states, has died, a former colleague said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Self-described 'Trump man' copped to serial pooping spree targeting home of Biden supporters...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/trump-fan-busted-for-serial-pooping-spree-547906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 3--A 70-year-old Ohio man who told cops he was a “Trump man” confessed to repeatedly urinating and defecating in front of a neighbor’s home because the residents "are Democrats and support Joe B</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation drugs track, kill cancer: 'Next big wave'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cancer-science-business-health-54e08ed1a440669a88932aba505d2e54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors are reporting improved survival in men with advanced prostate cancer from an experimental drug that delivers radiation directly to tumor cells. Few such drugs are approved now, but the approach may become a new way to treat patients with other hard-to-reach or inoperable cancers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booming Market for Woke Gurus...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/culture/what-wokes-worth-and-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early 2019, Ta-Nehisi Coates delivered the inaugural "Distinguished Diversity Lecture" at the Ohio State University. Coates’s hourlong engagement, which included a reading, a moderated conversation, and an audience Q&amp;A, cost OSU $41,500.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When Doctors Can't Tell the Truth?</title>
      <link>https://bariweiss.substack.com/p/what-happens-when-doctors-cant-speak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bariweiss.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whole areas of research are off-limits. Top physicians treat patients based on their race. An ideological 'purge' is underway in American medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bodycam Video Shows Deputies In Shootout With Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/volusia-county-florida-shootout-12-14-year-old-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Volusia County Sheriff's Office said the children shot at the deputies for more than half an hour Tuesday night, before the deputies returned fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic deaths soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210603180749-ydzgn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAFFIC (URGENT):U.S. traffic deaths soar to 38,680 in 2020; highest yearly total since 2007</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quake at underwater Hawaii volcano shakes Big Island...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hi-state-wire-hawaii-earthquakes-science-75a58084ec1b72e92a917ac0d9c2df1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — An earthquake at an active deep sea volcano off Hawaii shook the Big Island but didn't appear to have any impact on other nearby volcanoes and no significant damage was reported. The U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90% of Sharks Were Mysteriously Wiped Out, Never Recovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvzj5m/90-of-sharks-were-mysteriously-wiped-out-and-never-recovered-scientists-find</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They made it through the asteroid impacts, they've made it through global warming, global cooling, and all sorts of things. And yet this event that we didn't know about wiped out 90 percent of them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY MAIL Published Nude Photos of Katie Hill. Now She Has to Pay Them $100k...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/katie-hill-daily-mail-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge decided today that the former Congresswoman is on the hook for the tabloid's legal fees in her revenge porn lawsuit against it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sly smuggler uses Border Patrol for free trips home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/3/sly-smuggler-uses-border-patrol-free-trips-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the category of not all crooks are stupid, one accused migrant smuggler figured out an ingenious way to cut in half the time it took him to get back to Mexico from the U.S. to prepare for his next load of people: He turned himself in to the Border Patrol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuated after anonymous threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/03/europe/air-france-flight-ecavuated-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers on an Air France flight were evacuated in Paris on Thursday after an anonymous threat, the company said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  No explosive device aboard the AIR FRANCE flight...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210603163813-jmh9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-CHAD/ (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-No explosive device aboard the Air France flight from Chad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Turmoil erupts at DAILYNEWS as owner pushes buyouts...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/03/union-turmoil-erupts-at-daily-news-owner-as-hedge-fund-pushes-buyouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tribune Publishing is asking all of its full-time editorial staffers to consider voluntary buyouts at all nine major metro dailies in the chain, which is now controlled by the cost-slashing hedge f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st cruise ship sails through Venice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-entertainment-music-health-coronavirus-pandemic-52e1150bd621486282a4d677aaaf29b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOAVE, Italy (AP) — Early risers in Venice were surprised Thursday to see a cruise ship nosing down the Giudecca canal for the first time since the start of the pandemic, despite repeated government pledges to reroute such huge vessels due to safety and environmental concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE BLUNDER! New iOS system 'draining battery life FAST'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3008745/ios-update-ruins-iphone-battery-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IPHONE users have been reporting battery issues after upgrading to the Apple’s latest iOS 14.6 software. Apple’s Community Forum is full of complaints about the issue and users have also take…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA-SHAM! Influencer 'brags about flying business class', is then snapped in economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/3008218/instagram-model-pretending-fly-business-class-selfie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FRENCH Instagrammer has been caught out by fans posting a picture of herself in business class but actually flying in economy. Model and reality TV star, Oceane El Himer, 27, uploaded the Instagr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pupil Size Marker of Intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/pupil-size-is-a-marker-of-intelligence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scientificamerican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a surprising correlation between baseline pupil size and several measures of cognitive ability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone wants to debate Bannon as traitor to movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/06/03/maga-throwdown-roger-stone-wants-to-debate-steve-bannon-as-traitor-to-trump-movement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will lumbering MAGAsaurs do battle? Stone throws down "gauntlet" to "sloppy Steve" in Infowars appearance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S trials artificial intelligence drive-through system to cut waiting times...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mcdonalds-trials-artificial-intelligence-drive-24244345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology is being tested 10 branches in the US, but it has so far proven to be only 85% accurate, with the remaining 15% of orders needing to be corrected by staff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FRIENDS' Producer Stands by All-White Casting Amid Scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/tv-shows/news/friends-producer-stands-by-all-white-casting-amidst-continued-scrutiny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following the Friends reunion, producers of the popular sitcom are facing a myriad of complaints [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Attributes Meat Industry Cyberattack To Russia-Linked Op...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/06/02/greeley-jbs-cyberattack-fbi-attributes-revil-ransomware-operation-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cyberattack that disrupted operations at JBS, the world's largest meat supplier, is now attributed to a Russia-linked ransomware operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI investigating Postmaster General Louis DeJoy in connection with his political fundraising...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/FBI-investigating-Postmaster-General-Louis-DeJoy-16222392.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The FBI is investigating Postmaster General Louis DeJoy in connection with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lab-Leak Theory: Inside Fight to Uncover Origins...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/the-lab-leak-theory-inside-the-fight-to-uncover-covid-19s-origins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout 2020, the notion that the novel coronavirus leaked from a lab was off-limits. Those who dared to push for transparency say toxic politics and hidden agendas kept us in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake rattles San Jose...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/california/article251864413.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It was so big and shook my whole bed, it was very scary. Scarier than most earthquakes.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Pushes Forward With Olympics Despite Covid Crisis, Public Doubts... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tokyo-olympics-2021-move-forward-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Tokyo marked 50 days until the start of the Olympics, most of Japan is still under a COVID-19​ state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://scedc.caltech.edu/recent/Maps/122-37.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scedc.caltech.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unofficial Celine Dion Biopic Uses Singer's Songs --  But Changes Her Name to God...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/celine-dion-biopic-trailer-aline-god/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fictionalized biopic of Celine Dion playing at Cannes changes the Quebec singer's name to Aline Dieu but still uses her real songs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE AGAINST CLOCK</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/anti-netanyahu-coalition-demands-vote-replacing-knesset-speaker-669973</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yamina MK Nir Orbach said he did not support the request and asked that his signature be withdrawn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels spread terror with weaponized drones inside USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/drug-cartels-attack-enemies-spread-170948989.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like rogue militaries, Mexican drug cartels have upgraded their arsenals with weaponized drones that pose a growing threat in Mexico and the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buckingham Palace banned ethnic minorities from office roles, papers reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/jun/02/buckingham-palace-banned-ethnic-minorities-from-office-roles-papers-reveal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Documents also shed light on Queen’s ongoing exemption from race and sex discrimination laws</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Stock Craze Reaches New Heights...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/meme-stock-amc-is-offering-its-investors-popcorn-how-fitting/ar-AAKFDVb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There could be no better gift to shareholders than the alluring kernels of puffed-up nothingness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI DOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/lapid-tells-rivlin-new-government-ready-669937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennett, Abbas finalize coalition deal * New governing coalition has been formed and is prepared to replace Netanyahu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISLAMIST LEADER OUSTS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210603082133-ag1u1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/ISLAMIST-ABBAS (PIX):Arab Islamist helps clinch Israel's new anti-Netanyahu government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE AGAINST CLOCK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-health-coronavirus-pandemic-e96cc15e2474658e271e373cd4d6aeda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s opponents pushed Thursday for a quick parliament vote to formally end his lengthy rule, hoping to head off any last-minute attempts to derail their newly announced coalition government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU plans digital ID wallet for bloc's post-pandemic life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-travel-73f90d18909c595da463994e16e17348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The European Union unveiled plans Thursday for a digital ID wallet that residents could use to access services across the 27-nation bloc, part of a post-pandemic recovery strategy that involves accelerating the shift to an online world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafts may be coming from sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3008383/ufos-coming-from-space-sea-aliens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UFOs may not be coming from space – but rather from beneath the sea amid a string of strange encounters involving US warships, a former cop turned investigator has claimed. Gary Heseltine is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter Braun Hit With $200M Fraud Suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/scooter-braun-hit-with-fraud-suit-private-equity-firm-1234962451/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scooter Braun, the music industry megastar who launched Justin Bieber’s career, is now afflicted with a significant legal dispute over actions in getting a new private equity fund off the gro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Favorite Pole-Dancing Studio Undone by Emotional Exploitation, Racial Insensitivity...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/hollywood-pole-dancing-studio-s-factor-allegations-1234961498/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nadia Mitri says it was her experience on the dance floor in a Hawaii hotel ballroom with a veteran Hollywood actress that led to the darkest interlude of her life. In 2015, at a wellness retreat i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Anderson, Sean Penn to headline Cannes return...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-filmfestival-cannes-selection/wes-anderson-sean-penn-to-headline-cannes-return-idUSKCN2DF166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wes Anderson's "The French Dispatch" and Sean Penn's latest outing will be among movies vying for the top award at the Cannes Film Festival in July, as the cinema showcase plots a red carpet revival and coronavirus restrictions ease up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ investigating consulting firm tied to Hunter Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/03/blue-star-burisma-justice-department-investigation-491681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice is looking at whether Blue Star Strategies illegally lobbied on behalf of a Ukrainian company that counted Hunter Biden as a board member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying spheres spotted hurtling past ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/perfectly-spherical-ufos-mechanical-lighting-24239714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple glowing "orbs" appeared on the ISS camera and moved at a great speed in space. Graham, who recorded the footage, said it was a very "compelling" UFO sighting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'MONOPOLY' Leads To Most Fights On Game Nights...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/game-night-monopoly-banned-causes-most-fights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-two percent have banned certain games and another 22 percent have had to ban a particular player from their game nights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist Sells Invisible Sculpture for $18,000...</title>
      <link>https://hypebeast.com/2021/6/salvatore-garau-lo-sono-invisible-sculpture-18k-usd-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hypebeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Made from "air and spirit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOND Writer Fears Bezos Will Ruin Franchise: 007 Not 'Mere Commodity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/james-bond-writer-fears-amazon-will-ruin-the-franchise-007/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Logan, who wrote the James Bond movies Skyfall and Spectre, is worried about the future of the franchise in the wake of Amazon’s purchase of MGM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George P. Bush launches run for TX attorney general...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/02/politics/george-p-bush-texas-attorney-general/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Land Commissioner George P. Bush announced Wednesday night that he's running for attorney general in Texas, setting up a GOP showdown with one of the most high-profile Republican attorneys general in the country, Ken Paxton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why now?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/03/why-are-we-all-talking-about-u-f-o-s-right-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When spooky things appear in the sky, witnesses have often been reluctant to report them for fear of mockery by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10,000 volunteers drop out; Tokyo Olympics open in 50 days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tokyo-health-coronavirus-pandemic-olympic-games-2020-tokyo-olympics-e7350e3562f420ef35f51b71b558aa8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The countdown clock for the Tokyo Olympics hit 50-days-to-go on Thursday, and the day also brought another problem for the delayed games. About 10,000 of 80,000 unpaid volunteers for the Tokyo Olympics and Paralympics have told organizers they will not participate when the games open on July 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur exiles describe forced abortions, torture in Xinjiang...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-middle-east-europe-government-and-politics-76acafd6547fb7cc9ef03c0dd0156eab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Three Uyghurs who fled from China to Turkey have described forced abortions and torture by Chinese authorities in China’s far western Xinjiang region, ahead of giving testimony to a people’s tribunal in London that is investigating if Beijing’s actions against ethnic Uyghurs amount to genocide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming UFO report to Congress creating lots of buzz...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/upcoming-ufo-report-congress-creating-lots-buzz/story?id=78017649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A highly-anticipated U.S. government report on UFOs is set to come out later this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds investigating obstruction as part of Gaetz probe, sources say...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/03/politics/feds-investigating-obstruction-gaetz-probe/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is investigating potential obstruction of justice connected to the ongoing probe of Rep. Matt Gaetz and his alleged sexual relationship with a minor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bundy Gov Run Has Some Bracing for Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/far-right-vigilante-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98alarming-e2-80-99-gubernatorial-run-has-some-bracing-for-chaos/ar-AAKF2Ei </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MEAT HACK SHAKES GLOBE...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jbs-plants-limp-back-hack-223525704.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- JBS SA workers returning to a meat-processing plant in Texas on Wednesday afternoon were told to be ready to do things a bit differently than normal: Work by hand.With everything from knife sharpening to production-line speed controls relying on automation, coming back from a cyberattack that forced the world’s largest meat producer to halt operations across the globe is set to be a bumpy ride. Because the plants are coming back online without some of their systems in service, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Wants to Bring Back Supersonic Air Travel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/03/united-airlines-wants-to-bring-back-supersonic-air-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The era of supersonic commercial flights came to an end when the Concorde completed its last trip between New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought ravages CA reservoirs ahead of hot summer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-droughts-government-and-politics-science-business-76709d5854394905e0f46880ed6dab9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OROVILLE, Calif. (AP) — Each year Lake Oroville helps water a quarter of the nation’s crops, sustain endangered salmon beneath its massive earthen dam and anchor the tourism economy of a Northern California county that must rebuild seemingly every year after unrelenting wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report examines misinformation on Miami Spanish talk radio...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/up-is-down-and-down-is-up-report-examines-misinformation-on-miami-spanish-talk-radio/ar-AAKDYlb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Thousands of dead people and noncitizens voted in the 2020 presidential election. There were more votes cast than registered voters. Black Lives Matter and Antifa infiltrated the deadly storming of the U.S. Capitol. Doctors Without Borders, which closed its COVID-19 treatment center last year after three months because of low use, said it has not decided whether to reopen. Those are ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rampaging herd of elephants cause chaos as they plough through city of 7 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9647679/Rampaging-herd-15-elephants-cause-chaos-plough-Chinese-city-7-million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rampaging herd of 15 elephants have reached the outskirts of Kunming, the capital of the Yunnan province, after breaking out of a nature reserve in Xishuangbanna Dai prefecture on April 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Stock Craze Reaches New Heights...</title>
      <link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/markets/amc-stock-extends-surge-as-reddit-s-retail-frenzy-reaches-new-heights-121060300697_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.business-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie-theater chain has a market value of more than $30 billion, making it more valuable than at least half of the companies in the S&amp;P 500 Index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Prices Decade High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-food-prices-surge-highest-080152199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global food prices extended their rally to the highest in almost a decade, heightening concerns over bulging grocery bills as economies struggle to exit the Covid-19 crisis.A United Nations gauge of world food costs climbed for a 12th straight month in May, its longest stretch in a decade. The continued advance risks accelerating broader inflation, complicating central banks efforts to provide more stimulus.Drought in key Brazilian growing regions is crippling crops from corn to c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR Therapy Plunges Patients Back Into Trauma. Some Swear by It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/03/virtual-reality-therapy-plunges-patients-back-into-trauma-here-is-why-some-swear-by-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a Veterans Affairs therapist first suggested that Chris Merkle try a virtual reality simulation that would mimic his days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's largest warship catches fire, sinks in Gulf of Oman...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/persian-gulf-tensions-middle-east-iran-business-evacuations-f3e8126a8603326e1abc4705c6629fcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — The largest warship in the Iranian navy caught fire and later sank Wednesday in the Gulf of Oman under unclear circumstances, the latest calamity to strike one of the country’s vessels in recent years amid tensions with the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Covid shock has radicalized Generation Z...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/02/how-the-covid-shock-has-radicalised-generation-z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: young people’s testimonies show they are ready to draw systemic conclusions from the handling of the pandemic by political elites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microwave weapons that could cause Havana Syndrome exist, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/02/microwave-weapons-havana-syndrome-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and possibly China have developed technology capable of injuring brain and a US company made a prototype in 2004</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ends blog after 29 days, infuriated by measly readershipy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-ends-blog-after-29-days-infuriated-by-measly-readership/ar-AAKDOuj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infuriated by reports highlighting its measly viewership, Trump ordered his team Tuesday to put the blog out of its misery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts on Manchin as 'panic' sets in among Dems over voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pressure-mounts-on-Manchin-over-voting-rights-16218859.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Democratic leaders and activists are urgently stepping up pressure on Sen....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York subway system was targeted...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/556598-new-york-subway-system-was-targeted-by-chinese-linked-hackers-in-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s subway system was targeted by hackers with links to the Chinese government in April, according to an MTA document</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
