<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sees 6 more ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/16/federal-reserve-meeting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve on Wednesday approved its first interest rate increase in more than three years, and said it expects to keep raising through the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops 'shot, killed 10 people standing in bread line'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-troops-ukraine-kill-10-cherihiv-bread-line-us-embassy-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. embassy in Ukraine says "such horrific attacks must stop," and notes it is "considering all available options to ensure accountability for any atrocity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State TV hit by stream of resignations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60763494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marina Ovsyannikova's protest highlighted a growing number of journalists leaving their jobs at Kremlin-run TV channels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWIII 'MAY HAVE ALREADY STARTED'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/world-war-iii-may-already-started-russian-invasion-zelenskyy-says-rcna19967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outcome of this war has the whole of civilization at stake, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy told "NBC Nightly News" anchor Lester Holt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden sending more anti-aircraft systems, drones...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/white-house/2022/03/zelenskyy-center-stage-facing-congress-pleading-for-help-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy cited Pearl Harbor and the terror attacks of Sept. 11, 2001 on Wednesday as he appealed to the U.S. Congress to do more to help Ukraine’s fight against Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Big Tech made compromises with Kremlin in recent years...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putins-pre-war-moves-against-145840120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian agents came to the home of Google's top executive in Moscow to deliver a frightening ultimatum last September: take down an app that had drawn the ire of Russian President Vladimir Putin within 24 hours or be taken to prison. Google quickly moved the woman to a hotel where she checked in under an assumed name and might be protected by the presence of other guests and hotel security, according to people with knowledge of the matter. The same agents - believed by company officials to be fr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory fight over anonymity is future of internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/anonymous-internet-jeff-koseff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Kosseff on the technological and regulatory fight between those who want to stay anonymous and those who would unmask them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham threatened 25th Amendment to remove Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jonathan-martin-alex-burns-book-biden-sinema-94352832-b1e8-465f-ada0-521729691c73.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person likened Biden's perplexity at Sinema to his difficulty grasping TikTok.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes &amp; Covid: Scientists explore potential connection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-science-health-indiana-diabetes-e1193bc9891e45d589337f7a092f6c4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CROWN POINT, Ind. (AP) — When their 11-year-old son started losing weight and drinking lots of water, Tabitha and Bryan Balcitis chalked it up to a growth spurt and advice from his health class. But unusual crankiness and lethargy raised their concern, and tests showed his blood sugar levels were off the charts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200mph bullet train 'DERAILED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17968773/japan-earthquake-tsunami-warning-bullet-train-derailed-fukushima/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MASSIVE 7.3 earthquake has struck Fukushima nuclear plant and has shaken Tokyo for two minutes triggering a tsunami warning. The Japan Meteorological Agency has released a warning for an over 3ft…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Poaches Buck, Aikman From FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/espn-joe-buck-monday-night-football-1235109536/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buck and Aikman will be the lead play-by-play voice and analyst, respectively, for Monday Night Football.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA accuses Chinese agent of scheme to undermine congressional candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-accuses-chinese-agent-of-scheme-to-undermine-congressional-candidate/ar-AAV8xXW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buildings shake in Tokyo...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/japan-earthquake-fukushima-live-tsunami-26484274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7.3 magnitude earthquake has struck off the coast of Fukushima, leaving two million households without power as the tremor rocked buildings throughout the region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toad breaks silence after 100 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220316-ecuadoran-toad-breaks-its-silence-after-100-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuadoran biologist Jorge Brito was trekking through the forest when he heard what he thought was the chirp of a cricket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coumo Hits CNN With $125M Demand; Says Zucker Behind Everything...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/chris-cuomo-arbitration-demand-cnn-jeff-zucker-1234979631/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: After months of legal anticipation following his December 2021 firing by Jeff Zucker, Chris Cuomo has just launched the official opening salvo in what looks to be protracted battle with …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii man's body was found in bathtub filled with concrete. Police say lover killed him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-hawaii-man-e2-80-99s-body-was-found-in-a-bathtub-filled-with-concrete-his-lover-has-been-charged-with-murder/ar-AAV83bV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/at00r8udwu/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.3 mag quake hits north Japan, tsunami alert issued...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-world-news-japan-earthquakes-tsunamis-1e5f510a574d31d6c2048c8c98a3b47b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A powerful 7.3 magnitude earthquake shook off the coast of Fukushima in northern Japan on Wednesday evening, triggering a tsunami advisory. The Japan Meteorological Agency said the quake struck 60 kilometers (36 miles) below the sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunt Pilots to Trade Planes in Mid-Air for History-Making Live Special...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/plane-swap-hulu-live-special-1235111232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hulu and Red Bull are partnering on 'Plane Swap,' an extreme stunt that's precisely what it sounds like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin says West's 'attempt to have global dominance' coming to end...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10619493/Putin-says-Wests-attempt-global-dominance-coming-end.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said today that the West's 'attempt to have global dominance' is coming to an end after claiming it has used the conflict is an excuse to sanction Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: 9 dead in Texas crash involving college golf teams...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-texas-accidents-f49e5494f4f3d9ac58904be8ac0f1a56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANDREWS, Texas (AP) — Nine people died in a fiery, head-on collision in West Texas, including six students and a coach from a New Mexico university who were returning home from a golf tournament, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Variant in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/israel-records-new-coronavirus-variant-2826778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's ministry of health said Wednesday it had recorded two cases of new Covid variant, but which officials said they were not unduly worried about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Resignation May Be Accelerating...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/the-great-resignation-may-be-accelerating-microsoft-s-global-survey-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Young Workers Are Considering Leaving Your Company: Survey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWS VIDEO OF BOMBINGS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4905646/zelensky-speech-today-live-congress-biden-ukraine-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINIAN President Volodymyr Zelensky addressed Congress today in a dramatic speech calling for further help fighting back against Russia that included a graphic video. Zelensky’s live-streamed ad…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine rejects peace proposal to become 'neutral'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10618473/Russias-Lavrov-says-neutrality-Ukraine-seriously-discussed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine's chief negotiator has called for a legally binding security agreement, signed by international partners, who would 'not stand aside in the event of an attack on Ukraine, as they do today.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CLOSE THE SKY'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-16-22/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky is delivering a virtual address to the US Congress Wednesday as Russian forces inch toward the capital of Kyiv, with intensified fighting to the northeast and east of the city. Follow here for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian prisoners of war voice disquiet, shame over war...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/15/europe/ukraine-russian-prisoners-of-war-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I want to tell our commander-in-chief to stop terror acts in Ukraine because when we come back we'll rise against him."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZELENSKY ADDRESSES CONGRESS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-winston-churchill-congress-af1578f966e3e8feda02659740c8fba1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy cited Pearl Harbor and the terror attacks of Sept. 11, 2001 as he appealed to the U.S. Congress to do more to help Ukraine's fight against Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany record infections again...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-germany/germany-reports-another-record-covid-19-incidence-idUSKCN2LD0NZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany reported another record high seven-day incidence of the coronavirus on Wednesday even as the country prepares to ease restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China attempt to play both sides of Ukraine crisis starting to crack...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-e2-80-99s-attempt-to-play-both-sides-of-the-ukraine-crisis-is-starting-to-crack/ar-AAV7Xgn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVOKES PEARL HARBOR, 9/11</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/16/ukraine-president-zelenskyy-makes-speech-to-congress-on-russia-war.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelenskyy addressed Congress seeking more aid to fight against its invasion by Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $140 Billion Question: Can Russia Sell Huge Gold Pile?</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/140-billion-russia-sell-huge-084440230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia spent years building a giant stash of gold, an asset that central banks can turn to during a crisis. But any attempt to sell it will now be a challenge just when it’s needed most.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Russia Keeps Up Shelling Ahead of More TalksLuxury Cruise Ship Runs Aground While Leaving Caribbean PortRussia Is Spiraling Toward a $150 Billion Default NightmareUkraine’s Anti-Tank Missiles Could See Russia Shift War TacticsUkraine Update: China Seeks to Av</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Exposure To Even Small Amount Of Light While Sleep Bad For Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/close-curtains-light-sleep-heart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exposure to even moderate ambient lighting during sleep harms cardiovascular function and increases insulin resistance the following morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?518685-1/ukrainian-president-zelensky-addresses-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky addressed Congress about the Russian invasion of his country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail Sales Soften as Gas Prices Begin to Bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-retail-sales-soften-as-high-gasoline-costs-begin-to-bite-1.1738443</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growth in U.S. retail sales slowed in February after surging a month earlier, suggesting that consumers are pulling back spending in some categories as inflation limits purchasing power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refugee Crisis Will Test European Economy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/16/refugee-crisis-will-test-a-european-economy-under-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly everyone who crossed the Danube on the open-air ferry from Ukraine and landed in the frostbitten Romanian port city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel hit by 'largest ever' cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4902627/israel-cyberattack-iran-hackers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CYBERCRIMINALS have been targeting government websites in Israel – and one expert believes they’re from Iran. Several Israeli government networks were met with a distributed denial-of-service…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone footage shows civilian shot as he surrenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4904824/horrific-moment-russians-shoot-dead-civilian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING drone footage appears to show the horrific moment Russian soldiers shoot dead a civilian as he holds up his hands. The distressing clip, which we are choosing not to show, shows the man ge…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine rejects Moscow neutrality proposals...</title>
      <link>https://www.rte.ie/news/ukraine/2022/0316/1286704-ukraine-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rte.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine has dismissed Russian proposals to turn it into a neutral state, as the United States readied a huge package of military aid ahead of a historic address to Congress by Ukrainian president Volodymyr Zelensky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover two secret voids in Giza Pyramid that could hide mythical Pharaoh...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/scientists-discover-two-secret-voids-26480104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists have located two enormous secret voids inside the Great Pyramid of Giza that they believe could be hiding the lost tomb of the mythical Pharaoh Khufu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dentist broke patients' teeth on purpose so could fix them. He made millions...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-dentist-broke-his-patients-teeth-on-purpose-so-17005581.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Charmoli's patients' teeth were just fine, but fine wasn't making him enough...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic buying spreads in Middle East as invasion sparks fear over food and fuel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/panic-buying-spreads-in-middle-east-as-russian-invasion-sparks-fear-over-food-and-fuel/ar-AAV7cu0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: TSA has investigated 3,800 mask-related incidents since mandate went into effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tsa-has-investigated-more-than-3-800-mask-related-incidents-since-mandate-went-into-effect/ar-AAV7SUB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet ElliQ, the robot who wants to keep Grandma company...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/meet-elliq-the-robot-who-wants-to-keep-grandma-company/ar-AAV7E1n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea may be gearing up for full ICBM test, just when attention focused elsewhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/North-Korea-may-be-gearing-up-for-a-full-ICBM-17005595.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea - It's about to be a volatile few months on the Korean Peninsula and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN LOSES 4TH GENERAL</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-loses-general-7-swat-26479067</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Vladimir Putin's most decorated military veterans and 'Hero of Russia' Captain Alexander Garnaev has warned that society will be horrified by the true death toll of the war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed expected to raise rates, but unique challenges could slow pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/15/the-federal-reserve-is-expected-to-raise-rates-but-unique-challenges-could-slow-its-pace.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed is expected to raise interest rates by a quarter point, a major step in reversing the easing it put in place to help the economy through the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgues overflowing as Hong Kong suffers deadly Covid wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-close-off-beaches-065642121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers in PPE gear in Hong Kong carted the bodies of coronavirus victims into refrigerated shipping containers on Wednesday, as the city's morgues run out of space from a deadly Omicron surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European leaders return safely after Kyiv visit amid attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-kyiv-travel-czech-republic-4a8ec171baf643542a91888a225bf1d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — The prime ministers of Poland, the Czech Republic and Slovenia safely returned to Poland Wednesday after a visit to Kyiv intended to show support for Ukraine as it defends itself against the Russian military onslaught.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mariupol descends into despair...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-only-on-ap-708cb8f4a171ce3f1c1b0b8d090e38e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — The bodies of the children all lie here, dumped into this narrow trench hastily dug into the frozen earth of Mariupol to the constant drumbeat of shelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR 'exoskeleton' for sex in metaverse...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4901256/metaverse-sex-virtual-reality-exoskeleton-dreamtouch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUMANS may rely on exoskeletons to have realistic sex in the metaverse, one sex tech expert has revealed. Daniel Goldin, vice president at adult site Dreamcam, spoke to The Sun about a new exoskele…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Proud Boys leader  to remain behind bars as he faces Jan. 6 charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/miami-judge-orders-proud-boys-leader-tarrio-to-remain-behind-bars-as-he-faces-jan-6-charges/ar-AAV680j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky speech to Congress could add pressure on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/zelensky-speech-to-congress-could-add-pressure-on-biden/ar-AAV6Bhf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND GENTLEMAN TESTS POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/15/politics/doug-emhoff-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Second gentleman Doug Emhoff tested positive for Covid-19 on Tuesday, according to a statement from the vice president's office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders meet in Kyiv as capital faces fresh attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2022/03/15/european-leaders-meet-in-kyiv-as-besieged-capital-faces-fresh-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dramatic visit from top officials in the Czech Republic, Poland and Slovenia to a city that was shaken Tuesday morning by new blasts came amid a spiraling humanitarian crisis and a new push to isolate Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLIGARCHS ON THE RUN:  Abramovich's plane lands in Moscow, hours after he was spotted at Israel's airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/abramovichs-plane-lands-in-moscow-hours-after-he-was-spotted-at-israeli-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oligarch apparently touched down in Turkey before heading to Russia, after a day in Israel; UK welcomes Israel's announcement it won't allow oligarchs to bypass sanctions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Proud Boys leader  to remain behind bars as he faces Jan. 6 charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/miami-judge-orders-proud-boys-leader-tarrio-to-remain-behind-bars-as-he-faces-jan-6-charges/ar-AAV680j?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Rachel Wood Says Marilyn Manson Used a Nazi Whip to Torture Her and Made Her Drink His Blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/evan-rachel-wood-says-marilyn-manson-used-a-nazi-whip-to-torture-her-and-made-her-drink-his-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evan Rachel Wood has shared more horrifying allegations about her relationship with Marilyn Manson in the second part of HBO documentary Phoenix Rising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St Gets Reprieve From Fed Crackdown as Raskin Bows Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/wall-street-gets-reprieve-from-fed-crackdown-as-raskin-bows-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street Gets Reprieve From Fed Crackdown as Raskin Bows Out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU LEADERS COME TO KYIV</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-forces-press-kyiv-talks-162918340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of eastern European leaders met Ukraine's president in his besieged capital Tuesday, in a defiant act of solidarity as Russian forces pressed in and air strikes claimed yet more lives in the city under curfew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark mulls cigarette sale ban for next generations...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2022-03-denmark-mulls-cigarette-sale.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark unveiled plans on Tuesday to ensure that future generations are tobacco-free, and is considering banning the sale of cigarettes and other nicotine products to anyone born after 2010.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First trial of a sitting member of Congress in 21 years begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/mar/15/jeff-fortenberry-trial-begins-wednesday-first-of-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little-known Republican congressman from Nebraska will begin a high-profile trial Wednesday in California over accusations by federal prosecutors that he lied about illegal campaign contributions from a Nigerian billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Very meticulous in his planning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-gunman-caught-targeted-homeless-men-nyc-washington-dc-20220315-bviym7pczna4jd252sxe3x4up4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Early this AM, law enforcement arrested the suspect in Washington, DC,” the Metropolitan Police Department said in a tweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe getting hit by ANOTHER resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/europe-is-getting-hit-by-covid-resurgence-after-rushed-exit/ar-AAV4alQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Turned it down three or four times, I wanted no part of it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/nicolas-cage-interview-unbearable-weight-of-massive-talent-1235104433/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar winner candidly discusses his struggle to play himself in his new comedy 'The Unbearable Weight of Massive Talent,' his "mutual departure" with Hollywood, why he's become a meme favorite, and whether he'd be down for 'Face/Off 2.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Tax Files: Nine Months and Still No Answers from the IRS...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/stolen-tax-files-nine-months-and-still-no-answers-from-the-irs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine months ago it was revealed that the private tax files of “thousands” of Americans – covering a period of 15 years — had been stolen and given to a progressive news organization. The IRS and the Biden administration immediately vowed to investigate and prosecute. Yet here we are nine months later with no answers […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Spiraling Toward $150 Billion Default Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russia-spiraling-toward-150-billion-040120029.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia’s economy is fraying, its currency has collapsed, and its debt is junk. Next up is a potential default that could cost investors billions and shut the country out of most funding markets.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: China Seeks to Avoid Russia Sanctions SideswipeElon Musk Challenges Vladimir Putin to ‘Single Combat’ for UkrainePutin’s State Media News Is Interrupted: ‘They’re Lying to You’Panic Selling Grips Chinese Stocks in Biggest Plunge Since 2008U.S. Sewer D</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 FOX NEWS JOURNALISTS KILLED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-afghanistan-kyiv-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-d9eaf6c6ae19140c061e7d4b54f74bfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A veteran videographer and a 24-year-old Ukrainian journalist working for Fox News were both killed when their vehicle came under fire outside of Kyiv, the network said on Tuesday. Pierre Zakrzewski, 55, and Oleksandra “Sasha” Kuvshynova were traveling Monday with Fox News reporter Benjamin Hall, who remains hospitalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZELENSKY CENTER STAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-business-nato-congress-348b29a5b19e87cb277a8b353b93f7ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy will address the U.S. Congress on Wednesday, the actor-turned-turned-wartime leader's latest video stop as he employs the West's great legislative bodies as a global stage to orchestrate support against Russia’s crushing invasion .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER seeking OK for 4th dose...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pfizer-seeks-approval-for-fourth-covid19-booster-0f4477f4dcc5d10f36974b66eac86d6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Drugmaker Pfizer is expected to request authorization this week for an additional COVID-19 booster dose for seniors, according to a person familiar with the matter. It would add a fourth dose to the regimen — currently a primary series of two shots, followed months later by a booster dose — in an effort to provide maximum protection to the over-65 population that has been hit hardest by the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY LGBT employees plan walkout over Florida bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/disney-lgbtq-employees-plan-walkout-over-florida-bill/ar-AAV6jDc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz In Talks to Return To TV...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/dr-oz-in-talks-return-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The television doctor is running for Senate in Pennsylvania — but his numbers aren't promising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Forces Have Plans for Insurgency...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dg43z/ukraine-russia-insurgency-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Ukraine has a long history of national resistance against occupation,” a special forces soldier told VICE World News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students steer school bus to safety after driver collapses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-maine-education-b64058734fcee75156ab772397a9ea77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPSHAM, Maine (AP) — A group of Maine middle and high school students grabbed the wheel of their school bus Monday morning when their driver suffered a fatal medical condition, steering the vehicle to safety while another classmate attempted to administer first aid to the stricken driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BUZZFEED Accused of Illegally Shortchanging Employees in IPO...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/buzzfeed-accused-illegally-shortchanging-employees-192910655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The complainants are seeking compensation of at least $4.6 million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders visit capital to show support...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/leaders-eu-states-head-kyiv-attacks-intensify-83451392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime ministers of Poland, Czech Republic and Slovenia have arrived by train to Kyiv in a show of support for Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India explores opening alternate payment channels...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/politics/policy/russia-india-explore-opening-alternative-payment-channels-amid-sanctions-11647371750761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both sides are discussing accepting RuPay and MIR Cards within national payment infrastructures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate approves making Daylight Saving Time permanent...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/598314-senate-unanimously-approves-making-daylight-saving-time-permanent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate on Tuesday approved a proposal to make daylight saving time permanent, which if passed in the House and signed by President Biden, would mean Americans would never again have to set their clocks back an hour and lose an hour of afternoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostages as forces occupy hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60757133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors and patients are prevented from leaving Mariupol's main hospital, the deputy mayor says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA first lab-grown mosquitoes may take flight...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2022-03-california-lab-grown-mosquitoes-flightstirring-controversy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A biotech firm is seeking permission to release genetically modified mosquitoes into the open air of California for the first time later this year, aiming to reduce the expanding populations of invasive mosquitoes and prevent deadly disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ELVIS' to Play Cannes...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/elvis-presley-movie-cannes-film-festival-premiere-baz-luhrmann-tom-hanks-austin-butler-1234979064/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Warner Bros has firmed a splashy Cannes premiere for Elvis, the Baz Luhrmann-directed epic story about the relationship between Elvis Presley and his manager Colonel Tom Parker that shoo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cargo ship stuck in Chesapeake Bay; 'Logistical challenge'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/cargo-ship-stuck-marylands-chesapeake-bay-presenting-coast/story?id=83455048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The loaded 1,095-foot cargo ship remained stuck Tuesday morning in Maryland's Chesapeake Bay, according to the Coast Guard.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
