<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bernie looks electable -- but could be mirage...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/2/25/21152538/bernie-sanders-electability-president-moderates-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research suggests Sanders would drive swing voters to Trump — and need a youth turnout miracle to compensate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Preps 'Bachelor' Spinoff for Senior Citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/abc-offers-rose-to-senior-citizens-in-search-of-love-in-new-bachelor-spinoff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During last night's episode of "The Bachelor," ABC aired a casting call for people over the age of 65 who are looking for love.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Border Patrol Agents Provided Respirators to Deal with Chinese Immigrants Crossing from Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/report-border-patrol-agents-provided-respirators-to-deal-with-chinese-immigrants-crossing-from-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Report claims CBP has encountered 91 immigrants from China since start of 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein now in wheelchair, scared of dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8043175/Harvey-Weinsteins-lawyer-says-hes-scared-dying-bars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with DailyMail.com on Tuesday, Weinstein's attorney Donna Rotunno said he would likely not survive years in prison and was frightened about the prospect of dying there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUDLOW: USA has it contained, economy holding up nicely...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/25/larry-kudlow-says-us-has-contained-the-coronavirus-and-the-economy-is-holding-up-nicely.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Economic Council Director Larry Kudlow tried on Tuesday to assuage concerns over the cornavirus and its impact on the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Accused of Trying to Blow Up Car in Pentagon Parking Lot...</title>
      <link>https://www.arlnow.com/2020/02/25/acpd-assists-with-search-for-suspicious-man-at-arlington-national-cemetery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arlnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Updated at 1:50 p.m.) A 19-year-old man from Arkansas has been charged with trying to blow up a car in the Pentagon parking lot Monday morning. The charges, announced Tuesday afternoon, follow a multi-hour search yesterday involving numerous law enforcement agencies, including Arlington County P</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mystery Around Former DHS Whistleblower Found Dead In CA...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/02/24/philip-haney-amador-county-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Department of Homeland Security whistleblower was found shot to death in Amador County over the weekend, and contrary to previous reports, investigators haven't classified his death as a suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI, NYPD raid fashion mogul office in sex-trafficking probe...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/25/fbi-nypd-raid-peter-nygards-times-square-offices-in-sex-trafficking-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Biase, a spokesman for the US Attorney’s Office in Manhattan, confirmed to The Post that the raid was carried out but would not elaborate or provide details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy sees 45% rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6268e9441f590fbc625221c1c77cf471</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The number of people in Italy infected with the new virus from China increased 45% in the last day and the number of deaths grew to 10, civil protection officials said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says top official who played down fears is infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4fe2b4075638d59a180f354fc90caf93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The head of an Iranian government task force on the coronavirus who had urged the public not to overreact about its spread has tested positive for the illness...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPREAD IN USA 'INEVITABLE'</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/coronavirus-china-live-updates/2020/02/25/f4045570-5758-11ea-9000-f3cffee23036_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comments were made in separate briefings to lawmakers and reporters on Tuesday, marking an escalation in tone and urgency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP MOVES TO INVALDATE SUPREME COURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/feb/25/trump-supreme-court-sonia-sotomayor-ruth-bader-ginsburg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President rages at Sonia Sotomayor and Ruth Bader Ginsburg after Sotomayor criticized administration’s frequent appeals for supreme court to step in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In historically old presidential field, candidates refuse to release health records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/in-a-historically-old-presidential-field-candidates-refuse-to-release-health-records/ar-BB10jVHf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book of Revelation?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1247068/end-world-book-revelation-coronavirus-sabbath-china-wuhan-church-bible-jesus-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORONAVIRUS is preventing churches in China from honouring the Christian Sabbath, something the Book of Revelation predicted before the end of the world, according to a religious publication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herpes-riddled monkeys rampage in Florida as humans infected... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/herpes-riddled-monkeys-rampage-humans-21574956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rhesus macaques are on the rampage on the banks of the Silver River in Florida and are constantly breeding and expanding their range – bringing them into conflict with people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLY WEEK TO STOP HIM!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/484444-the-memo-democratic-rivals-have-seven-days-to-stop-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rival candidates have just a week to stop Sen. Bernie Sanders if they hope to prevent the Independent from Vermont from taking the party’s presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmer fined for punching sheep...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scottish-farmer-fined-punching-sheep-160852045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Scottish wool farmer has pleaded guilty to animal abuse after he was caught on video punching two sheep in the face, an animal welfare charity said Tuesday. William Brown, 59, was fined £550 ($715, 660 euros) under Section 19 of Scotland's Animal Health and Welfare Act 2006, after he admitted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guests in Spanish hotel locked down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hundreds-tourists-tenerife-hotel-lockdown-over-coronavirus-154330732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people were confined to a Tenerife hotel Tuesday after an Italian tourist was hospitalised in a suspected case of coronavirus, officials in Spain's Canary Islands said. "Hundreds of hotel clients are being monitored for health reasons.. but so far, we're not talking about quarantine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Doomsday vault' stocks up on 60,000 more food seeds...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/arctic-doomsday-vault-stocks-60-000-more-food-162311685.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "doomsday vault" nestled deep in the Arctic received 60,000 new seed samples on Tuesday, including Prince Charles' cowslips and Cherokee sacred corn, increasing stocks of the world's agricultural bounty in case of global catastrophe. Mounting concern over climate change and species</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAHM EMANUEL ISSUES DIRE WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/02/24/former-chicago-mayor-rahm-emanuels-dire-warning-bernie-sanders-candicacy-built-on-false-premise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel had a clear warning for Democrats: A primary victory for Bernie Sanders puts the whole future of the party at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 months to decide fate of Tokyo Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/afs:Content:8539951776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dick Pound, the longest-serving member of the IOC, estimates there's a three-month window to decide the fate of the Tokyo Olympics, which are being threatened by the fast-spreading virus from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg faces black voters wary of a gay candidate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8e2d57dc3e8c5d26017ab9413b6035da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONWAY, S.C. (AP) — South Carolina state Sen. Gerald Malloy is fine with a gay presidential candidate like Pete Buttigieg. His older male relatives are not — and that may be the defining challenge...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC TOP NEWS BROADCAST IN AMERICA; 9 MILLION VIEWERS...</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/610949995198283776/world-news-tonight-with-david-muir-is-no-1-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘World News Tonight’ Wins Both Total Viewers and Adults 25-54 for 10 Weeks in a Row, Leading in Overall Viewers for All 22 Weeks of Season ‘World News Tonight’ Outdelivers NBC by 1.24 Million Viewers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Preps Nuclear Moon Rocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pentagon-prepping-nuclear-moon-rocket-to-beat-china-into-cislunar-space</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government is working on an atomic rocket to send satellites into the vast space between Earth and the moon—before Beijing gets there with its own spacecraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-YEAR YIELD RECORD LOW</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/25/treasury-yields-climb-from-record-lows-after-coronavirus-plunge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10-year Treasury yield fell to a record low of 1.32% as coronavirus fears raised concerns about global economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPREAD ESCALATING</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/warns-pandemic-risk-virus-peaks-china-033755975.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh deaths and a surge in new coronavirus cases in Iran, Japan and South Korea on Tuesday fuelled fears of a pandemic as the disease took root in more countries. The rapid spread abroad came as the World Health Organization announced that the epidemic had peaked at its epicentre in China, where it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery over cemetery slayings sparks fear and rumors in California town...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-02-25/three-men-killed-in-perris-cemetery-a-mystery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four men walked into a small-town cemetery one morning. Only one walked out. The town wonders: random violence or cartel murders?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EL-ERIAN warns: 'This is different'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/25/mohamed-el-erian-continues-to-warn-against-buying-coronavirus-dips.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disruptions to earnings and the economy from "shock" events such as the coronavirus tend to stick around longer than more fundamental downturns, the Allianz chief economic advisor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Panic Could Soon Hit USA...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/the-extreme-panic-the-coronavirus-is-causing-elsewhere-on-the-globe-could-soon-be-coming-to-the-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. government officials are doing their best to keep the general population calm, but everyone can see what is happening in the rest of the world.  There are now empty store shelves in Italy just like there are in China.  People are waiting in extremely long lines to buy masks in South Korea just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plot Twist? Study Concludes Edgar Allen Poe Likely Didn't Kill Self...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/edgar-allen-poe-likely-didnt-kill-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many believe that Edgar Allan Poe's death was a deliberate act, but researchers at Lancaster University are challenging the notion that Poe killed himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Says He's 'Candidate for the United States Senate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/02/25/brain-freeze-joe-biden-says-hes-candidate-for-the-united-states-senate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden made yet another gaffe, saying in a campaign speech in South Carolina that he is a “candidate for the United States Senate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo show smashes LOUVRE all-time record...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/leonardo-show-smashes-louvres-time-record-140224211.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 1.1 million people flocked to see a blockbuster Leonardo da Vinci exhibition at the Louvre in Paris before it closed Monday -- an all-time record -- the museum said. "It is marvellous that an Italian Renaissance artist continues to fascinate the public," said the museum's director</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMUNISM: Independent media in firing line in Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/independent-media-firing-line-cuba-050443213.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monica Baro's investigation into cases of lead poisoning in Havana won her a prestigious Latin American journalism award but few friends in the Cuban government, which views independent media outlets like hers with growing suspicion. Baro's report for the Periodismo de Barrio website -- which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guests in Spanish hotel locked down...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200225125014-6m7k8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/SPAIN (URGENT):Guests in Spanish hotel to remain locked down for coronavirus pending tests on confirmed case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes on Greek islands in protest against migrant camp...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200225092008-bpnm6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-MIGRANTS/GREECE-PROTESTS (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Clashes on Greek islands in protest against migrant camp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opera Star Domingo Had 'Inappropriate Activity' With Women, Union Finds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1a8add4db2c4ba38420b7b8b2857ffac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — An investigation into legendary singer Plácido Domingo by the U.S. union representing opera performers found more than two dozen people who said they were sexually harassed or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body camera video shows 6-year-old girl crying, screaming as she's arrested at school...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/florida/os-ne-orlando-police-body-camera-6-year-old-arrest-20200225-rlg2ukttdvhehpoj2ki7irqe74-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body camera footage of the arrest of a 6-year-old at an Orlando charter school, released to the Sentinel, shows the girl crying for help while officers and school employees stand by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA databases are boon to police but menace to privacy, critics say...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2020/02/20/dna-databases-are-boon-to-police-but-menace-to-privacy-critics-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors rejected woman for liver transplant because of drinking. Then learned her bladder was brewing alcohol...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/doctors-rejected-woman-liver-transplant-for-drinking-bladder-brewing-alcohol-auto-brewery-upmc-20200224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors at UPMC think they've identified a new phenomenon: urinary auto-brewery syndrome or bladder fermentation syndrome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key California reservoir to be drained due to earthquake risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/key-california-reservoir-to-be-drained-due-to-earthquake-risk/article_24654552-0272-5057-80bf-033b1d3f7099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif. — In a dramatic decision that could significantly impact Silicon Valley’s water supply, federal dam regulators have ordered Anderson Reservoir, the largest reservoir in Santa Clara County,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent protests over citizenship law erupt amid Trump visit to India...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/india/484466-violent-protests-over-citizenship-law-erupt-amid-trump-visit-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violent demonstrations again broke out in New Delhi on Tuesday, just one day after at least seven people were killed and more than 100 were injured in clashes between supporters and critics of a new Indian citizenship law that favors non-Muslims,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Investor Asks For Advice on Stockpiling Food...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/02/25/top-investor-asks-for-advice-on-stockpiling-food/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus spread driving fears of shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: Man Held In County Jail For 27 Days -- With No Charges!</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/02/24/lawsuit-man-held-sacramento-jail-27-days-no-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man said he spent 27 days in the Sacramento County Jail without being charged or making a court appearance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Iranian Health Official Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-cases-top-80-000-020046679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Iran reported a total of 15 deaths from the outbreak, the most fatalities outside China, and a top health official was diagnosed with the coronavirus. Italy reported another surge in infections, Austria reported two cases, and Spanish police isolated 1,000 people at a holiday resort.U.S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piled Bodies, Overflowing Morgues: Inside America's Autopsy Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/25/piled-bodies-overflowing-morgues-inside-americas-autopsy-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Say you are found on your bathroom floor, on the grassy knoll of someone else’s front yard, in the berth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divisiveness Hits New Low...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/25/divisiveness-among-2020-democratic-hopefuls-hits-new-low/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one has tagged a rival with a bully-boy nickname like “Sleepy” or “Liddle.” But as push comes to shove</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal poll claims Bernie would sink downballot Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/25/bloomberg-internal-poll-claims-bernie-would-hurt-downballot-dems-117290</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bloomberg's campaign is shopping an internal survey that shows the liberal Vermont senator could be a millstone around the necks of vulnerable House Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosni Mubarak, Egyptian Leader Ousted in Arab Spring, Dies at 91...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/former-egyptian-president-hosni-mubarak-has-died-aged-91-n1142306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mubarak ruled Egypt with an iron fist until he was overthrown during the so-called Arab Spring uprisings that toppled leaders throughout the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baboon escapes vasectomy op at testing lab and flees with two female monkeys...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/baboon-escapes-vasectomy-op-testing-21571843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the baboons was scheduled for a vasectomy when he took two female primates in a daring escape from a New South Wales hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS STABILIZE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/24/stock-futures-are-flat-in-overnight-trading-following-the-dows-1000-point-rout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures were slightly higher Tuesday morning, giving back a more than 100 point gain following the market's worst decline in two years on coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Seeks Redemption...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloomberg-seeks-debate-redemption-while-090000450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Michael Bloomberg is trying for a do-over in Tuesday’s Democratic presidential debate, previewing that he’ll turn his focus to newly minted front-runner Bernie Sanders after a much-criticized debut at last week’s face-off.Seven Democratic candidates will meet in Charleston, South Carolina</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT: BERNIE FACES FIRE IN DEM DEBATE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6cb5e160744fc577aabc8918c60882b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) — Bernie Sanders is facing the greatest test of his presidential campaign as his Democratic rivals prepare to launch a series of attacks on the Vermont senator during what...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate to stop spread, countries limit travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/041a70e832d06dc7f09e0f724efa1321</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — Police manned checkpoints in quarantined towns, governments issued travel warnings and more flights were suspended Tuesday as officials desperately sought to stop the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stumbles over names of cricket greats...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/trump-stumbles-over-names-indian-cricket-greats-195741089--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump gave a special mention to cricket greats Sachin Tendulkar and Virat Kohli during a visit to India on Monday -- but it was probably the first time he had spoken their names. In a speech at the Sardar Patel Stadium in Ahmedabad -- the world&amp;#39;s largest cricket stadium -- Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX to rank popularity of shows in move toward transparency...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-release-top-10-feature-214019895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Gatos, California, company has guarded its viewership data for years and only recently started revealing information about how many people watch its shows. Director of Product Innovation Cameron Johnson wrote in a company blog post https://media.netflix.com/en/company-blog/see-whats-popular-on-netflix</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandalism Hits Campaign Offices Across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/blog/meet-press-blog-latest-news-analysis-data-driving-political-discussion-n988541/ncrd1141671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least seven of Mike Bloomberg’s campaign offices have been vandalized over the last two weeks, campaign officials say, in a string of incidents that the Bloomberg campaign has blamed without evidence on Bernie Sanders’ supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official clubs two poodles to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/chinese-official-clubs-two-poodles-21570035  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pets were reportedly attacked in a residential complex after the community officer and the dogs’ owner got into a heated argument</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could be catalyst for China to boost its mass surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/25/coronavirus-china-to-boost-mass-surveillance-machine-experts-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With over 75,000 coronavirus cases confirmed in China alone, the government has mobilized its surveillance machine, a move experts said could continue even after the virus has been contained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg prepares media onslaught against front-runner...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/24/mike-bloomberg-prepares-media-blitz-against-bernie-sanders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bloomberg's presidential campaign plans to unleash its cash-flush media operation against Bernie Sanders in the wake of the Vermont senator's resounding victory in the Nevada caucuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SPIRAL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a1a0f6cb7f593fc79467f4ead2aa3e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average slumped more than 1,000 points Monday in the worst day for the stock market in two years as investors worry that the spread of a viral outbreak that began in China...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden holds narrow lead in SC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/nbc-news-poll-biden-holds-narrow-lead-over-sanders-south-n1142046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden performs best among black and moderate voters, while Sanders holds lead with progressives and those under 45.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  'Under control'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/484408-trump-asserts-coronavirus-under-control-as-stocks-plunge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump asserted Monday that the coronavirus is “very much under control” in the United States, even as stock markets plunged amid concerns about the spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Political conventions could be cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/24/what-effect-will-coronavirus-have-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baseball games played to empty stands — and not just at Marlins Park. Airlines largely grounded. Restaurants empty — though Grubhub deliveries are booming as hungry people fear leaving their homes. This is the summer that quite possibly awaits the United States should the coronavirus continue its seemingly inexorable march across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key To Curing Cancerous Brain Tumors -- Could Be Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-the-key-to-curing-cancerous-brain-tumors-in-humans-could-be-dogs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say studying and treating brain tumors in dogs will lead to effective treatment options for humans, especially children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jordan Cries...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/kobe-bryant-memorial-michael-jordan-jokes-about-crying-jordan-meme-during-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jordan provided some comic relief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce bans photos of her performance during Kobe memorial...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/02/24/photos-of-beyonce-banned-during-performance-at-kobe-bryant-memorial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editors at the AP and Getty Images said that organizers of the live-streamed Staples Center event prohibited them from taking photos of Beyoncé.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaq Drops F-Bomb...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/02/24/shaq-kobe-lakers-memorial-cnn-f-word/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBA legend Shaquille O'Neil dropped an f-bomb on national television Monday while giving a speech at the memorial for Kobe and Gianna Bryant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New England Mired In Snow Drought...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/02/24/new-england-winter-boston-weather-wbz-snow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe, just maybe, we will be golfing and hitting the soccer and baseball fields earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Trump Barricades the Border, Legal Immigration Beginning to Plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-trump-barricades-the-border-legal-immigration-is-beginning-to-plunge/ar-BB10jOQM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Western diet kills sperm count, lowers male testosterone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/21/health/poor-diet-kills-sperm-quality-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast-food, high sugar, fats and carbs diet of Western countries may be contributing to the nosedive of sperm counts in men, a new study says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YIELDS CRASH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/24/treasury-yields-plunge-amid-escalating-global-coronavirus-fears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury yields tumbled on Monday as investors ran for cover amid fears that the coronavirus is spreading globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYSTEMS BUCKLE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/24/fidelity-says-some-clients-experiencing-technical-issues-amid-800-point-dow-plunge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Fidelity and Schwab clients were experiencing difficulties accessing their accounts amid an 800-point drop in the markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crackdown on immigrants who use public benefits takes effect...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e069e5a84057752a8535b1abe5d2ba6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Pastor Antonio Velasquez says that before the Trump administration announced a crackdown on immigrants using government social services, people lined up before sunrise outside a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis use among older adults on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/02/24/cannabis-use-among-older-adults-is-on-the-rise-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proportion of adults 65 years and older who reported using marijuana increased from 2.4% in 2015 to 4.2% in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As startup boom deflates, reckoning coming for Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/As-the-Startup-Boom-Deflates-Tech-Is-Humbled-15078764.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(EMBARGO: No electronic distribution, Web posting or street sales before 3:00 a.m. ET, Monday. No exceptions for any reasons.); (ART ADV: With photos.)  SAN FRANCISCO - Over the past decade, technology startups grew so quickly that they couldn't hire people fast enough.  Now the layoffs have started coming in droves. Last month, robot pizza startup Zume and car-sharing company Getaround slashed more than 500 jobs. Then DNA testing company 23andMe, logistics startup Flexport, Firefox maker Mozilla and question-and-answer website Quora did their own cuts.  "It feels like a reckoning is here," said Josh Wolfe, a venture capitalist at Lux Capital in New York.  It's a humbling shift for an industry that long saw itself as an engine of job creation and innovation, producing ride-hailing giant Uber, hospitality company Airbnb and other now well-known brands that often disrupted entrenched industries.  Their rise was propelled by a wave of investor money - about $763 billion washed into startups in the United States over the past decade - that also fueled the growth of young companies in delivery, cannabis, real estate and direct-to-consumer goods. Unlike low-cost software startups, these private companies frequently took on old-line competitors by spending heavily on physical assets and workers while losing money.  Now a pullback is unfolding in precisely the areas that drew the most hype.  Around the world, more than 30 startups have slashed more than 8,000 jobs over the past four months, according to a tally by The New York Times. Investments in young companies have fallen, with 2,215 startups raising money in the United States in the last three months of 2019, the fewest since late 2016, according to the National Venture Capital Association and PitchBook, which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgian city says anti-Semitic parade 'just fun'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51612541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aalst prompts an outcry over negative Jewish stereotypes, which an official defended as "our humour".</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
