<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Legal clouds gather over Rudy... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/01/rudy-giuliani-trump-ukraine-legal-jeopardy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts say an indictment is likely as prosecutors focus on Giuliani’s work for Trump and himself in Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Santa rally power stocks to best in generation?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/will-a-santa-claus-rally-power-the-sp-500-and-dow-to-their-best-years-in-a-generation-2019-11-30?mod=home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strong showing in December could set the S&amp;P 500 for its best year since 1997.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala imploding...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7743559/Kamala-Harris-aide-writes-stinging-resignation-letter-joins-Mike-Bloombergs-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kelly Mehlenenbacher, the former state operations director on Kamala Harris' presidential campaign who quit to join rival Mike Bloomberg's bid for the White House, left behind a stinging resignation letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trillion-dollar deficits as far as eye can see, and hardly a voice of caution to be heard...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/472480-trillion-dollar-deficits-as-far-as-the-eye-can-see-and-not-a-voice-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the old days, a decade or so ago, Democrats would have assailed Donald Trump's failure on federal deficits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief says humanity's 'war against nature' must stop...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-chief-says-humanitys-war-against-nature-must-134851057.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The devastating impact of global warming that threatens humanity is a pushback from Nature under assault, UN chief Antonio Guterres warned Sunday ahead of a key climate conference. "For many decades the human species has been at war with the planet, and now the planet is fighting back," he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM MESS ON BIGGEST TRAVEL DAY</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191201160957-1t1aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/ (PIX):U.S. snowstorms, rain make Thanksgiving trip home a nightmare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese tech groups writing UN facial recognition standards...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191201154956-tr6nz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDIA-Chinese tech groups writing UN facial recognition standard:MEDIA-Chinese tech groups writing UN facial recognition standards - FT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces two deadlines as Congress ramps up impeachment focus...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191201154626-kvh7r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Trump faces two deadlines as U.S. Congress ramps up impeachment focus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unsavory,' not impeachable: Dem explains why he opposes removing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/12/01/democratic-lawmaker-trump-unsavory-not-impeachable/2567848001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Democrat Jeff Van Drew, who knows Donald Trump, said voters should decide next year whether to remove the president, not lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Divided Left Is Losing Abortion Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/01/us/politics/abortion-planned-parenthood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miscalculations, and an unexpected victory by President Trump, have put abortion access at its most vulnerable point in decades, and the left on the defensive. Now it is trying to recover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV vaccine in 2021? Leading experts 'optimistic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/hiv-vaccine-2021-leading-experts-optimistic-about-ongoing-trials-n1092021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drs. Susan Buchbinder and Anthony Fauci, two of the world’s leading HIV experts, say three ongoing HIV vaccine trials are reason to be hopeful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURSE: NFL Teams With Cat Nicknames 0-12 Since Black Cat Ran Onto Field On MNF...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/nfl-teams-with-cat-nicknames-are-0-12-since-infamous-black-cat-ran-onto-the-field-at-metlife-stadium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perhaps it's a little bit of black cat voodoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian Asks Fans to Sign $1 Million NDA Before Show...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/pete-davidson-nda-sign-snl-saturday-night-live-dave-chappelle-1203420180/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever you do, never tweet at a Pete Davidson comedy show. The “Saturday Night Live” cast member has recently been dolling out non-disclosure agreements before each of his recent come…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74 others out early...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10460240/boris-johnson-london-bridge-usman-khan-terror/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEVENTY-four other people have been released early from similar sentences to that of the London Bridge attacker, Usman Khan, Boris Johnson revealed. The Prime Minister today blamed Labour for the t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PA County's Election Day Nightmare Underscores Voting Machine Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/11/30/a-pennsylvania-countys-election-day-nightmare-underscores-voting-machine-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - EASTON, Pa. — It was a few minutes after the polls closed here on Election Day when panic began to spread through the county election offices. Vote totals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World first' cell phone detection cameras rolled out in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/01/australia/cell-phone-detection-camera-australia-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Australian state of New South Wales rolled out "high definition detection cameras" on Sunday, designed to catch drivers using cell phones behind the wheel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic apple: New variety 'keeps in fridge for year'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/cosmic-crisp-apple-new-variety-keeps-in-the-fridge-for-up-to-a-year-11875167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new variety of the fruit took more than two decades to develop and allegedly lasts for up to a year in the fridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 shot in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/nopd-at-least-11-people-shot-along-canal-street/30064186#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOPD: At least 11 people shot along Canal Street</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEREMY: Terrorists should 'not necessarily' serve full sentences...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-security-corbyn-idUSKBN1Y50VO?taid=5de3b3b8ee0d2300017c7a3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Convicted terrorists should "not necessarily" serve their full prison ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed robbers hold up drivers, steal 60 packages...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/armed-robbers-hold-amazon-drivers-steal-packages-cops-say/IIBhfMGAFkQCEbcyZYlRzL/#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 60 online shoppers will receive their orders later than expected after a group of robbers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocky road ahead for Merkel after ally loses shock vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rocky-road-ahead-merkel-ally-loses-shock-vote-110602823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Merkel faces a rocky political road ahead as she battles to hang on until 2021 as German chancellor, after her junior coalition partner SPD elected a left-leaning leadership duo. Rank and file Social Democrats late Saturday delivered a humiliating blow to Finance Minister Olaf Scholz's run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong pro-democracy rally cut short by police tear gas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/584dfb8a30804634bb422ba715fd4a82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Thousands took to Hong Kong’s streets Sunday in a new wave of pro-democracy protests, but police fired tear gas after some demonstrators hurled bricks and smokes bombs, breaking a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack now political football as Johnson, Corbyn spar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/01194743767948599f8007b4da663255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain’s political leaders sparred Sunday over who is responsible for the early release of a convicted extremist who launched a stabbing attack in central London that left two dead...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONDAY:  Schiff to circulate Ukraine report...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/30/intelligence-committee-draft-ukraine-report-074518</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a crucial step in the House's fast-moving impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 shot in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/10-people-shot-new-orleans-police-say-n1093721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An individual was detained near the scene on the city's Canal Street, police added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China introduces mandatory face scans for phone users...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-introduces-mandatory-face-scans-phone-users-091042257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will require telecom operators to collect face scans when registering new phone users at offline outlets starting Sunday, according to the country's information technology authority, as Beijing continues to tighten cyberspace controls. In September, China's industry and information technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 killed in South Dakota plane crash... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.keloland.com/news/local-news/9-dead-in-brule-county-sd-plane-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.keloland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;12 people were on board the plane. The three survivors were taken to Sioux Falls and are in critical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Unusual Tornadoes Confirmed in Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/weather/news/2019-11-30-tornadoes-confirmed-arizona-phoenix-late-november</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three tornadoes were confirmed in Arizona as a powerful low pressure system moved through the West after Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus on early release of convict in London stabbings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10459154/london-bridge-terrorist-ex-convict/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE London Bridge terrorist was banned from entering London but had a one day exemption to attend an ex-convict event, it has emerged. Usman Khan, 28, from Staffordshire, was released from prison i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS WAS WARNED OVER RISKS OF FREEING TERRORISTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/boris-johnson-warned-london-bridge-attack-usman-khan-stabbing-terrorist-a9227681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate debt nears record $10 trillion; Poses new risks..</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Corporate-debt-nears-a-record-10-trillion-and-14870792.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little more than a decade after consumers binged on inexpensive mortgages that helped bring on a global financial crisis, a new debt surge - this time by major corporations - threatens to unleash fresh turmoil.  A decade of historically low interest rates has allowed companies to sell record amounts of bonds to investors, sending total U.S. corporate debt to nearly $10 trillion, or a record 47% of the overall economy.  In recent weeks, the Federal Reserve, the International Monetary Fund and major institutional investors such as BlackRock and American Funds all have sounded the alarm about the mounting corporate obligations.  The danger isn't immediate. But some regulators and investors say the borrowing has gone on too long and could send financial markets plunging when the next recession hits, dealing the real economy a blow at a time when it already would be wobbling.  Some of America's best-known companies, including AT&amp;T, Ford Motor and CVS Health, have splurged on borrowed cash. This year, the weakest firms have accounted for most of the growth and are increasingly using debt for "financial risk-taking," such as investor payouts and Wall Street dealmaking, rather than new plants and equipment, according to the IMF.  Amid the avalanche of debt, the sharp growth in lower-quality corporate bonds, just one notch above junk, represents a special concern. Investors hold nearly $4 trillion in these bonds, including $2.5 trillion from U.S. companies, according to the credit rating agency Standard &amp; Poor's.  Since Oct. 1, familiar names like Hasbro, Nordstrom, Marriott and Hyundai all have tapped investors for cash by selling near-junk bonds that S&amp;P labels "BBB."  This low-quality corporate debt bulge, by itself, is unlikely to cause a recession, according to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick speaks at Native American 'Un-Thanksgiving Day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7742499/Colin-Kaepernick-speaks-Thanksgiving-Day-criticizes-government.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former 49ers star was at the Indigenous People Sunrise Ceremony Thursday, main. He later tweeted the US government 'has stolen over 1.5 billion acres of land', inset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPY:  I was hired by Weinstein to dig dirt on his accusers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7742171/Spy-admits-befriending-Harvey-Weinsteins-alleged-rape-victim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stella Penn Pechanac befriended Scream actress Rose McGowan after claiming that she worked for a London asset management firm which wanted to invite her to speak at a gala dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER JACK:  I'M LEAVING USA FOR 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/29/tech/jack-dorsey-africa-future/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg 'might be better off skipping debates'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/30/michael-bloomberg-might-be-better-off-skipping-democratic-debates-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He may be the 14th richest person on Earth, but one thing Michael Bloomberg can’t buy is a spot in the 2020 Democratic debates. Current Democratic National Committee rules require candidates …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION JOLTED...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191130174142-fwiqb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-SECURITY/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-UK PM Johnson pressured on jail terms after London Bridge attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU investigating GOOGLE data collection...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191129180550-7qhd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regulators are quizzing companies about the details of any agreements to share data with the tech firm, according to a document seen by Reuters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California famous for earthquakes and wildfires -- but don't forget about its volcanoes...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/california-is-famous-for-earthquakes-and-wildfires-but-don-t/article_ce2dbb40-e8dd-5571-90a2-0e281b0bdc02.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Margaret Mangan didn’t sleep well in the weeks following the Ridgecrest, Calif., earthquakes. The July shaking triggered a swarm of smaller tremors in the nearby Coso Volcanic Field, a cluster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN IOWA BLITZ</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b70788340dee4d82ab6078637ee0e002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COUNCIL BLUFFS, Iowa (AP) — Joe Biden launched an eight-day bus tour of Iowa on Saturday projecting confidence, ignoring his many Democratic presidential competitors and pledging that he will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  WORLD'S MOST POWERFUL NEWS SITES...</title>
      <link>http://www.mentaldaily.com/article/2019/11/worlds-most-powerful-news-outlets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mentaldaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the transition into the digital age, there's been a substantive rise in online-based news outlets and blogs. In this excerpt, we compiled a list of the ten most powerful news outlets on the web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family fury after finding out killer on day release tackled terrorist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10457317/familys-fury-killer-hero-london-bridge-james-ford/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE family of one of the London Bridge have-a-go-heroes are furious that the killer was allowed out of prison without their knowledge – and that he’s being hailed a hero. James Ford, 42…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast braces for foot of snow during first days of December...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/northeastern-us-braces-for-foot-of-snow-during-first-days-of-december/637449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein, Blackmail and Lucrative 'Hot List'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/11/30/jeffrey-epstein-blackmail-and-a-lucrative-hot-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon after the sex criminal Jeffrey Epstein died in August, a mysterious man met with two prominent lawyers. Towering, barrel-chested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane season ending, but Dorian left 'massive, massive crisis' in Bahamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article237664359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico rise in violence starts sticking to 'Teflon president' after year in office...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/mexico-s-rise-in-violence-starts-sticking-to-teflon-president/article_63f21506-6e0f-5ee8-83a2-da65962b4c3a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — At 7 a.m. each weekday morning, as the sun is still rising over this sprawling mountain capital, Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador steps in front of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS STRIKES AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/london-bridge-terror-attack-isis-20998291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Islamic State has claimed responsibility for Usman Khan’s knife-wielding attack on London Bridge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As members of Congress head for exits, loosely regulated gravy train beckons...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-excongress-lobbying-20191129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON The road from Capitol Hill to K Street is designed to have a speed bump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Yesterday's Cocaine: Death Toll Rising From Tainted Drug...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/not-yesterdays-cocaine-death-toll-rising-from-tainted-drug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the U.S. continues to focus mainly on the opioid crisis, cocaine is quietly making a comeback and has become one of the biggest overdose killers of African Americans when tainted with fentany…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein, Blackmail and Lucrative 'Hot List'...</title>
      <link>https://bdnews24.com/world/2019/11/30/jeffrey-epstein-blackmail-and-a-lucrative-hot-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bdnews24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wide receiver stabbed in Pittsburgh...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d8d4c3f93ef43579201ed01ffddb986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — NFL wide receiver Terrelle Pryor was stabbed in Pittsburgh, but an agent said Saturday that the player is expected to make a full recovery. Police officers were called to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem presidential campaign has produced confusion rather than clarity...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-Democratic-presidential-campaign-has-produced-14872449.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential candidates have been on the campaign trail for nearly a year. Confusion rather than clarity continues to be the story of their contest for the 2020 nomination.  Early in the year, the party's liberal wing seemed to be ascendant, defined by the candidacies of Sens. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., and the embrace of a single-payer, Medicare-for-all health-care program. Sanders and Warren were calling for other dramatic changes to the system - economic and political - and their voices stood out. Some other candidates offered echoes of their ideas.  That proved to be a misleading indicator of where the Democratic electorate was on some of the issues, particularly health care, in part because there were fewer moderate voices being heard. Former Vice President Joe Biden didn't join the race until April. South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg wasn't being taken very seriously. Sen. Amy Klobuchar, D-Minn., wasn't breaking through.  The candidate debates provided the setting for the arguments to play out before a larger audience. Warren and Sanders came under attack from moderate Democrats at the first debate in June in Miami, with former Maryland congressman John Delaney the most vocal. But Warren and Sanders more than held their own. It appeared as though the progressive wing was on solid ground.  Subsequent debates, however, have produced a different impression. The progressives have been much more on the defensive and the moderates more assertive. Biden tangled with Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., in the Detroit debate over the issue of health care. Harris subsequently modified her position, moving toward the center. On the issue of Medicare-for-all, the ground has shifted.  During the Atlanta debate in late November, even Sanders seemed to be tempering his overall message....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER BOWL PREVIEW? </title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/sports/nfl/san-francisco-49ers/article237804539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right AfD party elects new leader backed by radical wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-politics-afd/german-far-right-afd-party-elects-new-leader-backed-by-radical-wing-idUSKBN1Y40A2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The far-right Alternative for Germany on Saturday elected a decorator from the e...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Kerry Launches Star-Studded Climate Coalition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/30/climate/john-kerry-climate-change.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Kerry and a group that includes some Republicans, some military members and a lot of Hollywood, are launching a new  coalition to push for public action on climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In bitter British election, influence of wealthy U.S. donors causes stir...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-a-bitter-British-election-influence-of-14872390.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Dec. 12 election is a bitter fight to shape the country's future, with voters not only hoping to chart the next steps of Brexit, but also picking between startlingly different visions of the country from right-wing Prime Minister Boris Johnson and left-wing Labour Party leader Jeremy Corbyn.  However, it isn't just British voters who are influencing Britain's future. A number of wealthy American individuals and organizations appear also to be having a big influence on this fraught British election.  The prominent left-leaning newspaper the Guardian reported Friday that 11 wealthy American donors have given a total of more than $3.7 million to influential right-wing British groups over the past five years.  One conservative American billionaire who was having an outsize influence on right-wing groups across the pond is no longer alive. John Templeton, who died in 2008, was behind a set of foundations that gave $3.3 million to British groups, the newspaper reported.  The news comes as Washington focuses on allegations of foreign influence on U.S. elections and is a reminder that outside the United States, the problem is often seen through the opposite lens: wealthy Americans seeking to influence foreign elections.  The U.S. donations in Britain do not appear to be illegal, and some of the think tanks involved have pushed back against the Guardian's framing. One recipient of Templeton-linked money, the Legatum Institute, told the paper that it had "a strong policy of maintaining intellectual independence" despite foreign financial backing.  In a statement in response to the article, the John Templeton Foundation, one of the organizations linked to the late investor, said that it was "proud to support academic research and civil dialogue in the natural sciences, human sciences, philosophy, classical liberalism, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KID ROCK GOES ON DRUNKEN RANT ABOUT OPRAH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7741989/Kid-Rock-explains-reason-lurid-rant-against-Oprah.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rocker - who was caught on camera making foul-mouthed slurs  last week - took to Twitter on Saturday night after the footage went viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete to Visit Black Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/11/30/pete-buttigieg-visit-black-church-pastor-said-president-country-racist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg will visit a black church in North Carolina Sunday, seeking to improve support with the early primary state’s black community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg health scare raises prospect of election year Supreme Court battle...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/472354-ginsburg-health-scare-raises-prospect-of-election-year-supreme-court-battle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent hospitalization of Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg following a year of health scares has raised the prospect of a Supreme Court vacancy in an election year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Woes Pile Up From Winter Storms as Thanksgiving Ends...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/travel-woes-pile-winter-storms-162409169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Millions of travelers heading back from their Thanksgiving holiday could be caught up in a fast-moving winter storm making its way east from California to the Midwest and beyond.The National Weather Service expects significant travel impacts across wide swaths of the U.S. this weekend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merry Clickmas: Black Friday online sales hit record $7.4B...</title>
      <link>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/ap-news/merry-clickmas-black-friday-online-sales-hit-record-74b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;1010wins.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — This year’s Black Friday was the biggest ever for online sales, and Adobe Analytics says carts filled on phones, computers and tablets rang up $7.4 billion in transactions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
