<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Business owner charged after scamming a scammer...</title>
      <link>http://www.wmur.com/article/police-woman-admits-swapping-items-in-scammers-shipment/22029218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wolfeboro police said a woman who didn't realize she was getting herself in the middle of an international scam allegedly tried to pull one over on another criminal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC CHAIR: OCASIO-CORTEZ IS THE FUTURE!</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/395436-dnc-chair-ocasio-cortez-represents-the-future-of-our-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic National Committee (DNC) Chairman Tom Perez said Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez represents the “future of our party” on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish charity attaches GPS to migrating stork... Bird flies to Sudan, where someone steals SIM card to run up huge phone bill...</title>
      <link>http://www.euronews.com/2018/07/03/roaming-stork-lands-polish-charity-with-huge-phone-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone removed a SIM card from a GPS tracker placed on a stork's back to clock in 20 hours of phone calls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbaric jihadists ban plastic bags -- 'to protect Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6690062/al-shabaab-bans-plastic-bags/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of the world’s most barbaric terrorist organisations has banned plastic bags – because they believe they harm life on Earth. The Somali terror group al-Shabaab, known for butchering thous…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God Male or Gender-Neutral? Episcopal Convention Debates...</title>
      <link>http://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/us/2018/july/is-god-male-or-gender-neutral-episcopal-church-begins-debate-on-book-of-common-prayer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Episcopal Church is debating about overhauling its Book of Common Prayer, which is used in Episcopal congregations worldwide. The debate centers on making sure that prayers in the book are clear that God is not male, but doesn't have a gender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Stand For Flag' Song 'Censored' On Social...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/tech/2018/07/03/facebook-slammed-for-censorship-country-groups-patriotic-song.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has been slammed by The Wes Cook Band for preventing the country group from using the social network’s paid tools to promote its song “I Stand for the Flag.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK a publisher? Publicly says no, but tells court YES...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jul/02/facebook-mark-zuckerberg-platform-publisher-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In its defense against a former app startup, Facebook is contradicting its long-held claim to be simply a neutral platform</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey gives state-funding to local news...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/02/new-jersey-state-funded-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Power Use at Highest Levels in Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-03/the-heat-wave-has-u-s-power-use-at-the-highest-levels-in-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heat wave roasting the U.S. East Coast may be slowing down U.S. stock trading and foiling July 4 road trips. But it’s the best friend of power market bulls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon stops posting troop numbers for Iraq, Syria and Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/07/03/625544265/pentagon-questioned-over-war-zone-numbers-blackout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon has stopped reporting troop levels for Afghanistan, Iraq and Syria following President Trump's declaration that the U.S. would not talk about troop numbers in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girlfriend burns down home because man went to see another woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/cobb-fire-woman-burns-down-home-because-man-went-see-another-woman/D7atxQtN2au9X873OUxbQI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was in Cobb County jail Tuesday morning for allegedly burning down a house because a man went to see another woman. Earnica Lowe, 32, faces a felony arson count after Cobb fire investigators say she lit the home on fire June 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After fish pedicure, woman loses toenails...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/03/health/fish-pedicure-toenail-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a young woman's toenails started to separate from her toes, a doctor finally zeroed in on the reason: a fish pedicure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup ratings in USA down 42%...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/sports/la-sp-world-cup-updates-20180612-world-cup-tv-ratings-in-the-u-s-are-1530639130-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lack of a U.S. team caused a big viewership drop for World Cup telecasts. The 48 group stage telecasts on Fox and FS1 averaged 2,069,000 viewers, according to Nielsen Media Research. That is down 42 percent from the 3.54 million average on ESPN, ESPN2 and ABC four years ago and down 15 percen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel cancels peace prize concert for lack of funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nobel-cancels-peace-prize-concert-lack-funds-165646280.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The traditional concert after the annual awarding of the Nobel Peace Prize on December 10 in Oslo will not be staged this year due to financial difficulties, the organisers said Tuesday. "There will be no Nobel Peace Prize concert" in 2018, said a statement from the Nobel Institute, Warner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 NEW SPACEY SEX ASSAULTS INVESTIGATED...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/03/kevin-spacey-new-london-sexual-assaults-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey is now being investigated for 6 sexual assaults in London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33 neglected shih tzus found in sweltering Manhattan apartment...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-metro-malnourished-dogs-owner-charged-20180703-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty-three malnourished shih tzus were rescued from an overheated Manhattan apartment when police showed up and arrested their owner on animal cruetly charges, police said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethiopia new PM meets humanoid robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8012fe4a0124485c8c57d8d56bcc7521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADDIS ABABA, Ethiopia (AP) — In one of the world's more unusual diplomatic encounters, Ethiopia's new prime minister has met with a humanoid robot.        The chief of staf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife sliced off cheating husband's penis, threw out window...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/03/wife-says-she-sliced-off-cheating-husbands-penis-then-threw-it-out-the-window/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jealous wife has been arrested after allegedly hacking off her husband’s penis Tuesday with a 12-inch-long carving knife. Karuna Sanusan, 24, carried out the bloody attack on 40-year-old Siripan …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRONES REPLACE FIREWORKS IN WEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/news/2018/07/03/drones-replace-july-4th-fireworks-western-towns-worried-wildfires/752966002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Towns in California, Colorado and Arizona – facing another season of drought and wildfire – are turning to drone shows as a less risky alternative to organized fireworks, encouraged by the development of jaw-dropping, choreographed shows such as the one Intel put on at the Winter Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service Officer Assaulted Outside White House After Immigration Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/investigations/Man-Assaulted-Secret-Service-Officer-Outside-White-House-After-Immigration-Rally-Feds-487224761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Secret Service officer was injured in an assault while on patrol outside the White House on Saturday shortly after the major immigration rally in Lafayette Park, according to newly filed federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfer misses key tourney after airline loses clubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2018/07/03/graeme-mcdowell-misses-open-qualifier-airline-loses-golf-clubs/754037002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graeme McDowell, the 2010 U.S. Open winner, said on Twitter that he was forced to withdraw from an Open qualifier after Air France misplaced his golf clubs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas tries spying with fake dating apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/edc3fe2d11064d4aa16936b991d5b3db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — The Israeli military said Tuesday it had uncovered a plot by Hamas militants to spy on soldiers by befriending them on social media and then luring them in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snow Blankets Northern Rockies Before July Fourth...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/weather/news/2018-07-03-snow-in-july-montana-idaho-northern-rockies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The calendar might say "July," but in some spots, it looks more like winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Testosterone pushes men to luxury brands...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/testosterone-pushes-men-luxury-brands-study-163420875.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A single dose of testosterone steers men towards luxury brands of cars, watches, pens, or clothes which, like stag anglers and peacock tails, signal "status" to the female gender, scientists said Tuesday. The sex hormone, it turns out, is a major influencer of male consumer behaviour, according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overtime work for women increases diabetes risk...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2018/07/overtime-work-may-increase-diabetes-risk-in-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working overtime may help your paycheck and give you a leg up in the office, but a new study suggests that women who log too many hours may have an increased the risk of diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Turn Violent In Front Of Philly ICE Building...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/07/03/protests-turn-violent-as-demonstrators-arrested-in-front-of-philadelphia-ice-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protests are taking place in front of the ICE office on 8th and Cherry Streets in Center City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bartiromo Crushes CNBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2018/07/03/crushing-it-maria-bartiromo-beats-squawk-box-as-fox-business-sweeps-cnbc-in-q2-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We have great momentum and will continue crushing it,' Bartiromo says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania secret trip to visit injured service members...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/57e8b8bed73d4255aeb2683de5aef79a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Melania Trump has made another secret trip, though this one was carried out closer to home.        The first lady is visiting wounded service members at W</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS executioner who BURNED soldiers alive SHOT DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/713848/isis-execution-video-turkey-soldiers-burned-alive-killed-bounty-abu-talha-al-turki-syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Reassigns Reporter Who Had Sex Relationship With Senate Aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/new-york-times-reassigns-ali-watkins-reporter-sexual-relationship-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"For a reporter to have an intimate relationship with someone he or she covers is unacceptable," says executive editor Dean Baquet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ABOLISH ICE' Vandals Throw Brick Through Window Of Republican Office...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/03/abolish-ice-vandals-nebraska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Party blames 'increasingly radical rhetoric of national Democrat leaders'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART boycott launched after outcry over 'Impeach 45' clothing...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/2018/07/03/walmart-boycott-campaign-launches-after-outcry-over-impeach-45-clothing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart drew outrage Monday after it was discovered that the superstore was selling “Impeach 45” apparel on its website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminally ill dogs at canine hospice treated to steak dinners, trips to MCDONALD'S and birthday parties in their final days...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/terminally-ill-dogs-canine-hospice-12842554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former nurse Nicola Coyle runs the Grey Muzzle Canine Hospice Project in Mansfield - thought to be the first of its kind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREWORKS COSTING MORE THIS YEAR...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/03/washington-dc-4th-july-fireworks-price/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government is shelling out more dough on the National Mall 4th of July fireworks this year ... $30k more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS PRICES HIT HOUSEHOLDS</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Oil-Prices/This-Is-How-Much-US-Households-Lose-As-Gas-Prices-Rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. households are feeling the pinch and are expected to have around $440 less disposable income as higher gasoline prices are offsetting part of the tax cuts from earlier this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Serial Killer Arrested After Death of Eight Babies at Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/suspected-serial-killer-arrested-in-britain-after-death-of-eight-babies-in-hospital?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health-care worker has been arrested on suspicion of murdering eight infants and trying to kill six more at a hospital in northwest England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man threatens to burn down TV station, calls journalist 'dead man walking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article214251504.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Eric Bewley, 47, is charged with transmitting threats through interstate communications, a federal crime, after authorities say he threatened to burn down Texas TV station KBTX and called the general manager 'a dead man walking.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin court OKs unconscious drunk drivers' blood draws...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wisconsin-court-oks-unconscious-drunk-drivers-blood-draws-140047075.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — The Wisconsin state Supreme Court says police can legally draw blood from unconscious drunken drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenpeace activists 'crash' drone into nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/greenpeace-activists-crash-drone-french-nuclear-plant-134507827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenpeace activists said Tuesday they had flown a drone fitted out as a flying Superman into a nuclear energy plant in southeast France, aiming to show how the country's reactors are vulnerable to terror attacks. A video released by the environmental group shows the drone zipping through restricted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vampire' killer caught after seen drinking blood of victim...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5912437/Vampire-killer-caught-seen-drinking-blood-woman-throat-slit-Zimbabwe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Sibanda struck his elderly victim several times with a log in Sikhewu village before allegedly cutting her throat with a sharp implement. A passerby saw him sucking her wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Surgeons argue, flirt, throw things while patients under the knife...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5912371/Medics-fight-flirt-throw-things-patients-knife-study-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Emory University in Atlanta, Georgia have revealed medical staff dance to music and quarrel with one another to gain status while operating on unconscious patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Arnold's bonkers strategy for nailing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/07/03/tom-arnolds-bonkers-strategy-for-nailing-trump-218944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-energy comedian says he knows exactly how to take down the president. Now, if he could only get his hands on one little tape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water main break floods downtown Philly streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/water-main-break-flooding-downtown-philly-streets-100206398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — A large water main break has flooded a number of streets in downtown Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five-ton tractor 'missing' following tornado...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/07/02/tornadoes-five-ton-tractor-missing-south-dakota-following-tornado/752475002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tornadoes have been known to toss around everything from cars and trucks to cows and people, but usually the objects don't vanish completely. But last Thursday, a tornado near the Montana/South Dakota border lofted and destroyed some farm machinery including a 5-ton tractor that has yet to be found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS adds MORE stores to closings list...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/nation-now/2018/07/02/sears-closings-78-kmart-and-sears-closing-september/750127002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears Holdings list of closing locations is growing. Now, 62 Sears and 16 Kmart stores are expected to close in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pruitt becomes latest Trump official to be harassed at restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/02/scott-pruitt-becomes-latest-trump-official-to-be-harassed-at-a-restaurant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Scott Pruitt became the most recent Trump administration figure to get an earful while trying to get a mouthful at a DC restaurant, according to a Face…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bono warns existence of UN, EU, NATO threatened...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/prime-minister-honors-87-irish-un-peacekeepers-died-175547438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Irish rock star Bono warned Monday that the United Nations and other international institutions including the European Union and NATO are under threat — and nations must work together to ensure their continued existence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tow-an-iceberg plan being floated to ease Cape Town drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tow-iceberg-plan-being-floated-ease-cape-town-030704601.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a plan as crazy as the situation is desperate -- towing an iceberg from Antarctica to Cape Town to supply fresh water to a city in the grip of drought. Earlier this year, Cape Town came within weeks of shutting off all its taps and forcing residents to queue for water rations at public standpipes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
San Fran appalling street life repels residents -- now it's driven away convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/SF-s-appalling-street-life-repels-residents-13038748.php?t=0c15a3045e&amp;f?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move that is alarming San Francisco's biggest industry, a major medical association is pulling its annual convention out of the city - saying its members no longer feel safe.         "It's the first time that we have had an out-and-out cancellation over the issue, and this is a group that has been coming here every three or four years since the 1980s," said Joe D'Alessandro, president and CEO of S.F. Travel, the city's convention bureau.         D'Alessandro declined to name the medical association, saying the bureau still hopes to bring the group back in the future.         As a rule, major conventions book their visits at least five years in advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-apocalypse now: End of the world at the movies...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/post-apocalypse-now-end-world-moviespost-apocalypse-now-045458539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the Bible to Nostradamus, the Mayan calendar and the Millennium Bug, fatalists, fantasists and the fervently religious have long been fascinated by the end of the world. Movie directors love nothing more than feeding our deepest fears concerning overpopulation, pestilence and nuclear armageddon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA DEVELOPS 'LASER GUN'</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-firm-develops-laser-gun-064153947--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese firm has developed a laser gun designed for police use that can set fire to protesters' hair or banners from a range of almost one kilometre. The general manager of the ZKZM fiber laser company, who asked to remain anonymous, said the weapon would "immediately" produce a "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN: FAMILY AND COUNTRY 'FIRST LOYALTY'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/michael-cohen-family-country-president-trump-loyalty/story?id=56304585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen told George Stephanopoulos that his family is his "first loyalty."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malls Vacancies Hit Six-Year High as Online Shopping Takes Toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mall-vacancy-rate-hits-six-year-high-1530588600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malls are the emptiest they’ve been since 2012, when the U.S. economy was still struggling to recover from the last recession, as more consumers shifted their shopping online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian General Accuses Israel of Stealing Clouds to Cause Drought...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/07/03/iran-thinks-israel-stealing-clouds-cause-drought-7679005/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brigadier General Gholam Reza Jalali, head of Iran's Civil Defence Organisation, alleged that his country was facing cloud 'theft' during a press conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters is done with 'nice guy politics'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/395250-maxine-waters-is-done-with-nice-guy-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the perspective of some House Democrats, Rep. Maxine Waters (D-Calif.) has the right message. She’s just not always the best messenger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AMLO earthquake might rattle Mexico...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/782498/how-amlo-earthquake-might-rattle-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What does Mexico's new president want?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA BUILDS 'LASER AK-47' THAT BURNS THROUGH SKIN...</title>
      <link>http://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2153310/china-brings-star-wars-life-laser-ak-47-could-set-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Handheld weapons that could set fire to targets from long distances are no longer confined to science fiction but a fact of life, according to researchers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPKINS nurse files suit, saying doctor squirted patient's bodily fluids on him...</title>
      <link>http://www.baltimoresun.com/health/bs-hs-hopkins-bodily-fluids-20180629-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Johns Hopkins nurse has filed a lawsuit against a doctor who he said sprayed bodily fluid from a patient on him while he was assisting with a surgery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
San Fran appalling street life repels residents -- now it's driven away convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/SF-s-appalling-street-life-repels-residents-13038748.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move that is alarming San Francisco's biggest industry, a major medical association is pulling its annual convention out of the city - saying its members no longer feel safe.         "It's the first time that we have had an out-and-out cancellation over the issue, and this is a group that has been coming here every three or four years since the 1980s," said Joe D'Alessandro, president and CEO of S.F. Travel, the city's convention bureau.         D'Alessandro declined to name the medical association, saying the bureau still hopes to bring the group back in the future.         As a rule, major conventions book their visits at least five years in advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist Dems Say Bernie Too Right-Wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/socialist-dems-say-bernie-too-right-wing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America can move far-left if Trump voters grow too complacent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can zapping brains reduce violence? Controversial study sees potential...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/07/02/brain-electric-stimulation-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers hailed their results as evidence that increasing activity in the prefrontal cortex can reduce "intentions to commit aggression."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New threat for famous wild horses: Tourists offering junk food...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article214180694.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corolla Wild Horse Fund kicks off effort to stop tourists from feeding the herds of wild horses roaming NC's Outer Banks. Foreign food, even apples and carrots, is making the animals sick and can kill them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bid to split California into 3 states gains traction...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/02/bid-to-split-california-into-3-states-gains-traction-could-it-really-happen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a midterm season marked by primary upsets and the prospect of Democrats claiming a congressional check on President Trump’s power, another sensational development has been the momentum behind a ballot measure to split up the unwieldy, high-tax state of California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPRAH: RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT WOULD KILL ME...</title>
      <link>http://www.vogue.co.uk/article/august-cover-vogue-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the issue, the media icon discusses race, feminism, and the loves and losses in her life with writer Decca Aitkenhead in the rarest of one-on-ones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanist strangles boyfriend during sex; Chops up body in devil sacrifice...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/713809/satanist-murder-russia-dismembered-bdsm-sex-anastasia-onegina-dmitry-sinkevich-baphomet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest boots family from funeral after chalice knocked over...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/local-news/archdiocese-of-washington-apologizes-after-maryland-family-kicked-out-of-funeral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Archdiocese of Washington has issued an apology after a family was kicked out of a funeral in Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS PROBE FACEBOOK STATEMENTS</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-facebook-investigation-broadened-20180702-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal investigation into Facebook's sharing of data with political consultancy Cambridge Analytica has broadened to focus on the actions and statements of the tech giant and involves three agencies, according to people familiar with the official inquiries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives Sound Alarm Over Potential Supreme Court Pick's Christianity...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2018/07/amy-coney-barrett-under-progressives-religiou-ignorance-bigotry-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Efforts to block the highly qualified Barrett from the Supreme Court because of her faith betray our nation’s founding ideals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for threatening to chop Rand Paul, family with ax...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/politics/2018/07/02/man-threatens-kill-sen-rand-paul-ax/751211002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rand Paul has faced several threats and attacks in the past year: A shooting, a dispute with a neighbor and now a man threatening to ax him, literally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-lb Bag Of 'Human Poop' Dumped On San Fran Sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/San-Francisco-human-waste-feces-homeless-Reddit-13044317.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A foul odor permeated from a massive bag of human excrement sludge left on a street corner in San Francisco's Tenderloin district Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel chain uses biometric data to find guest vacation spots...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90179273/this-hotel-chain-is-using-biometric-data-to-find-you-the-perfect-vacation-spot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new program from AccorHotels will use your own biometrics to determine the destination of your dreams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA-Bron Move Ups Hollywood Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/lebron-james-move-la-should-up-his-producing-game-1124391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After signing a four-year $154 million deal with the Lakers, the NBA’s biggest star will only need to travel 11 miles from his new basketball home at the Staples Center and his SpringHill offices on the Warner Bros. lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Solitary confinement' retreats free guests from modern life distractions...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/capital/story/20180702-a-south-korean-prison-for-people-seeking-peace-and-quiet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former lawyer came up with a bizarre antidote for stressed-out workers: being locked in a cell for two days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED GETS SHREDDED DOCS...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jasonleopold/here-are-the-documents-recovered-from-michael-cohens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“NEVER MET: Donald Trump, George Lucas, Harrison Ford, Steven Spielberg, Michael Jackson, The Jackson’s family, Sony.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans To Make History Competing in Miss Universe...</title>
      <link>https://www.advocate.com/people/2018/7/02/trans-woman-makes-history-will-compete-spain-miss-universe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.advocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety of lions in captivity no longer guaranteed...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/02/demand-big-cat-parts-fueling-lion-killings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surge in demand for big cat body parts on South Africa&amp;rsquo;s black market is endangering the future of the country&amp;rsquo;s captive lion population, conservationists have warned.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
