<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK plans first smartwatch -- 2 cameras, heart monitor...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/9/22526266/facebook-smartwatch-two-cameras-heart-rate-monitor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A way for Facebook to get around Apple and Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Cold Makes Big Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/06/08/reemergence-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Perry Halkitis with Rutgers says it's going around, and you may catch it no matter how healthy or strong your immunity is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Pandemic Changed Antarctica...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7ev5n/how-the-covid-pandemic-changed-antarctica-v28n2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers returning home from Antarctica ‘left one world and have come back to another.’ But while their lives were in stasis, the continent they live on continued to struggle under the weight of diplomatic pressures and environmental concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns Venezuela, Cuba to turn away Iran ships believed to be carrying arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/09/venezuela-cuba-iran-ships-492602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caracas is trying to leverage the situation to gain relief from U.S. sanctions, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorbitant NFT prices mirror modern art?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/dont-dismiss-digital-art-opinion-1598683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With money machines around the world humming, it is not surprising that pieces of digital art have been selling at record prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials worry adversaries may exploit energy-emitting devices to harm Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/mystery-over-havana-syndrome-lingers-new-concern-emerges-n1270082</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials are concerned that foreign adversaries may exploit energy-emitting devices to harm Americans now that they’re suspected of causing debilitating symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB cheating worries as sticky baseballs become concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/09/mlb-working-to-combat-cheating-after-sticky-baseballs-become-a-concern.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MLB officials plan to empower umpires to enforce rules about players using sticky substances on baseballs, and the league could explore increasing suspensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mormon church unlocked medical pot for deep red states...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/09/mormon-church-medical-marijuana-491924</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They did everything that they could to fight this until the people had spoken," a former state lawmaker said of the church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Mead lowest in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/08/weather/hoover-dam-lake-mead-water-level-drought/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crippling drought in the western US is dropping the water level at Lake Mead and the Hoover Dam to a historically low level, putting pressure on the region's drinking water supply and the dam's electric capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Makes Rapid Tests Key to Everyday Freedoms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/09/germany-makes-rapid-virus-tests-a-key-to-everyday-freedoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — Want to go out for a meal indoors in Germany? Get a test. Want to stay at a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboards supporting Morgan Wallen pop up in Nashville before CMT Awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2021/06/08/morgan-wallen-billboards-pop-up-nashville-days-before-cmt-awards/7600098002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billboards mark the third set of billboards funded by fans of Morgan Wallen, voted ineligible now for multiple CMA Music Awards on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire rages near Jerusalem, villages evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210609-fire-rages-near-jerusalem-villages-evacuated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire rages near Jerusalem, villages evacuated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global internet outage caused by customer change of setting...</title>
      <link>https://timesofmalta.com/articles/view/global-internet-outage-caused-by-customer-change-of-setting.878054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofmalta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worldwide internet outage affecting major websites was caused by a "customer configuration change" which triggered a "bug" in a key delivery network, the technology firm at the centre of the mishap said Wednesday. Nick Rockwell of US-based tech firm Fastly said in a blog post that the outage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics WILL NOT Be Cancelled Declares NBC, With Big Bucks On Line...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/nbcuniversal-says-tokyo-olympic-games-are-on-with-7000-hours-of-programming-across-platforms-1234770686/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBCUniversal said Monday that it will present an unprecedented 7,000 hours of coverage of the Tokyo Olympics this summer on two broadcast networks, six cable networks and multiple digital platforms…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House drops orders trying to ban TIKTOK, WECHAT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tiktok-wechat-technology-biden-trump-d866cf95c7f1b802ffb88b2834117f0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House has dropped Trump-era executive orders that attempted to ban the popular apps TikTok and WeChat and will conduct its own review aimed at identifying national security risks with software applications tied to China, officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All-in' Buddhist practice combines meditation and martial arts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-meditation-sports-martial-arts-religion-cc3c4a0c8a3ab0b89aec4d5d711be07d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — In all Zen traditions, meditation is the backbone of the practice. Students sit with a tall spine, hands loosely interlocked and eyes half-closed. At Chosei Zen in Madison, Wisconsin, though, new students are never quite prepared for the rigor of Rinzai Zen, which asks participants to remain motionless for up to 45 minutes — twice a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega Rich Laughing From Escape Pods...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeff-bezos-hardly-pays-taxes-and-is-going-to-space-and-hell-no-we-are-not-in-this-together</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If America were a group dinner, the uber wealthy would be the ones ordering several of the most expensive items on the menu and then skipping out without paying the tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House 'Perplexed' By Performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/white-house-perplexed-over-kamala-harris-first-foreign-policy-trip-performance-according-to-cnn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unnamed White House “insiders” were left “perplexed” by the performance of Vice President Kamala Harris on her recent trip to Guatemala and Mexico to address the root causes of the immigration problems at the US Southern border. This report comes from CNN’s Jeremy Diamond, who joined the vice president on her trip and shared his […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron slapper ID'd as far right follower, Middle Ages enthusiast...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/french-president-emmanuel-macron-slapper-identified-far-right-royalist-middle-ages-enthusiast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two 28-year old men have been arrested following the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The perfect storm making everything you need more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/business/rising-prices-inventories-post-pandemic/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steel, lumber, plastic and fuel. Corn, soybeans, sugar and sunflower oil. Houses, cars, diapers and toilet paper. Prices are rising almost everywhere you look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' set to blaze sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/solar-eclipse-ring-of-fire-rare-watch-june-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Look up! But don't forget your solar eclipse glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China conducts amphibious landing drill after US senators land on Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-taiwan-media-business-health-9d53b2ed7b38462888e5ec1fc659ad88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese military has conducted an amphibious landing exercise in waters near Taiwan amid renewed tensions between Beijing and Washington .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisoners hold $100 million in govt-run accounts; Shielded from scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/federal-prisoners-hold-dollar100-million-in-government-run-accounts-shielded-from-some-criminal-scrutiny-and-debt-collection/ar-AAKRr04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The program run by the Bureau of Prisons has long frustrated law enforcement officials, who say it poses significant risks for abuse, money laundering and corruption, yet the agency has for years resisted efforts to change it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs Repeatedly Took Nuke Facilities Offline, Whistleblower Says...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/us/202106091083107584-ufos-repeatedly-took-offline-us-nuclear-capabilities-ex-chief-of-pentagon-secret-unit-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Sputnik) - Unidentified flying objects (UFO) have repeatedly meddled with US nuclear technology, forcing some facilities to go offline, ex-head of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery shaking, boom heard across San Diego for third time...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2021-06-08/mystery-shaking-felt-boom-heard-across-san-diego-county-for-third-time-in-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the third time since February, a mysterious "skyquake" rattled San Diego County and Tijuana; authorities say it wasn't an earthquake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA asks office staff for help, offers bonuses and mandates overtime to keep checkpoints moving...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tsa-asks-office-staff-for-help-offers-bonuses-and-mandates-overtime-to-keep-airport-checkpoints-moving/ar-AAKRET9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TSA put out a call over Memorial Day weekend asking agency employees to volunteer to take on shifts helping at 131 airports facing a "staffing challenge."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite vow of poverty, nun stole $830,000 from Catholic school, prosecutors say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/despite-her-vow-of-poverty-nun-stole-more-than-24830000-from-a-catholic-school-prosecutors-said/ar-AAKR6Zo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sister Mary Margaret Kreuper, 79, pleaded guilt to wire fraud and money laundering charges after prosecutors said she embezzled more than $835,000 from St. James Catholic School in Torrance, Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump election fraud claims propelled them to Capitol. His ongoing comments keeping them in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-s-election-fraud-claims-propelled-them-to-16235117.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Many of those charged in the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol have blamed former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newest Meme Stocks Extend Gains With No Sign of Craze Fading...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/newest-meme-stocks-extend-gains-092445847.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The newest additions to the meme-stock frenzy surged in premarket trading as retail traders latched on to their latest favorites.ContextLogic Inc. soared 32% and Clover Health Investments Corp. rose 17% as of 6:30 a.m. in New York, both extending huge gains on Tuesday. Fast-food restaurant chain Wendy’s Inc. edged higher, extending Tuesday’s 26% advance and brushing aside a downgrade from Stifel.There’s no sign of the meme-stock craze slowing as members of Reddit’s WallStreetBets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software bug blamed for global internet outage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/software-technology-business-71e6096a8fae0c44e988d3eefe9bca8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Fastly, the company hit by a major outage that caused many of the world's top websites to go offline briefly this week, blamed the problem on a software bug that was triggered when a customer changed a setting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Kim Jong Un's $12,000 IWC Watch Says About His Weight Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/what-kim-jong-un-e2-80-99s-2412000-iwc-watch-says-about-his-weight-loss/ar-AAKRAdn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong Un certainly looked slimmer last weekend when he emerged from his latest lengthy absence. But it may be the North Korean leader’s Swiss timepiece that provides the clearest evidence he’s been watching his weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's press plane was about to depart. Then cicadas 'invaded' engines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-press-plane-was-about-to-head-to-europe-then-brood-x-cicadas-e2-80-98invaded-e2-80-99-the-engines/ar-AAKQR6N </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Cases Surge Over 10,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/russian-covid-cases-surge-over-10-000-for-first-time-since-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Covid Cases Surge Over 10,000 for First Time Since March</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive World of Diamonds in Grips of Buying Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/buying-frenzy-drives-price-surge-in-the-hidden-world-of-diamonds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spiking prices, and buyers’ willingness to pay them, are the latest sign of roaring demand in the secretive rough-diamond trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Paying 0.00%. Depositors Flocking...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-09/the-fed-is-paying-0-00-such-a-deal-depositors-are-flocking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed’s none-too-generous interest rate attracted $497 billion in funds on June 8</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyprus, Malta Warned Over Passports for Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-09/cyprus-and-malta-warned-by-eu-over-passports-for-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyprus and Malta were warned again by the European Commission to stop so-called ‘golden passport’ programs that grant European Union citizenship to investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden heads to Europe at difficult moment for domestic agenda...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/557461-biden-heads-to-europe-at-difficult-moment-for-his-domestic-agenda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is headed to Europe on Wednesday, an inopportune time for his first foreign trip as president as his domestic priorities hit the rocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Type of Exercise? Blood Test Holds Clues...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/09/the-best-type-of-exercise-a-blood-test-holds-clues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If we all begin the same exercise routine tomorrow, some of us will become much fitter, others will get a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Known as Max Is 55-Year-Old Woman From Russia, U.S. Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/hacker-known-as-max-is-55-year-old-woman-from-russia-us-says/ar-AAKRtxB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alla Witte’s plans for a new career as a computer programmer included helping clients make enough money to see the world, according to YouTube videos and social media posts. She was in her late 40s with a degree in applied mathematics and an itch to do computer programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border surge sends prices soaring; Smugglers can earn $200,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/8/border-surge-sends-prices-soaring-smugglers-can-ea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victoria Perez spent 10 months as a migrant smuggler. When agents finally caught up with her, she told them she had made $200,000 over that time, working two days a week, driving migrants through a Border Patrol highway checkpoint near El Paso, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators request Supreme Court travel records...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/06/08/whitehouse-and-kennedy-request-supreme-court-travel-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key senators asked the Justice Department and the U.S. Marshals Service for information about the last 10 years of trips for justices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plexiglass Is Everywhere, With No Proof It Keeps Covid at Bay...</title>
      <link>https://www.crainsnewyork.com/small-business/plexiglass-everywhere-no-proof-its-keeping-covid-bay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.crainsnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian UPS Driver Brutally Beaten, Robbed Of Package In Broad Daylight In Middle Of San Fran Street...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/08/ups-driver-attacked-viral-video-vicious-robbery-attempt-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UPS driver was just doing his job when a thief swiped a package from his car, and then beat him in the middle of a San Francisco street. The victim opened up exclusively for the first time to KPIX 5's Betty Yu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Declares 'new era' for US, Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vice-president-harris-meets-mexicos-144319172.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris met with Mexican President López Obrador after visiting Guatemala and drawing criticism for telling Central Americans to "not come" to U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought-hit California scales up plan to truck salmon to ocean...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/drought-hit-california-scales-plan-013704446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With chronic drought drying up rivers earlier than usual this year, California is scaling up a drastic operation to help its famous Chinook salmon reach the Pacific -- transporting the fry by road in dozens of large tanker trucks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW RICH AVOID TAX</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/the-secret-irs-files-trove-of-never-before-seen-records-reveal-how-the-wealthiest-avoid-income-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ProPublica has obtained a vast cache of IRS information showing how billionaires like Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk and Warren Buffett pay little in income tax compared to their massive wealth — sometimes, even nothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ransomware attack: 60 members of Congress left unable to access data...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9664229/60-members-Congress-parties-victims-latest-ransomware-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 60 members of Congress from both parties have been unable to access data for weeks in the latest ransomware attack to strike the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris hears criticism from all sides amid difficult first trip...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/557433-harris-hears-criticism-from-all-sides-amid-difficult-first-trip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris is enduring a difficult first foreign trip as vice president, highlighting the difficulty she faces in her role as the Biden administration’s chief official handling the flow of migrants from Central America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microscopic Animal Brought Back To Life After Being Buried For 24,000 Years!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/animal-brought-back-to-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say the tiny creature, dug out of the subsurface soil in a state of "suspended animation," has even reproduced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Israeli airstrike targets Syria from Lebanese airspace...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/alleged-israeli-airstrike-targets-syria-from-lebanese-airspace-670476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OXFORD votes to remove portrait of Queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9664583/Oxford-University-college-votes-remove-portrait-Queen-common-room.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Common room members at Magdalen College passed the measure by a substantial majority, with one student commenting that 'patriotism and colonialism are not really separable'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global treaty to regulate plastic pollution gains momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/article/global-treaty-to-regulate-plastic-pollution-gains-momentum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even producers have an interest in global rules on plastic waste that would resolve the inconsistencies among countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ERS rookies freak about Bay Area housing cost...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/blog/san-francisco-49ers/post/_/id/39107/sticker-shock-49ers-rookies-warned-about-bay-area-housing-cost</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average house in Santa Clara County sells for $1.96 million -- a lot more than in markets like Green Bay or Trey Lance's Marshall, Minnesota.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Alyssa Milano mulls run for Congress...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/politics/actress-alyssa-milano-considers-congressional-run-for-cas-4th-district-report/10762622/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Alyssa Milano is reportedly considering a run for Congress for California's 4th District, which includes Sierra communities from Truckee, down to Kings Canyon National Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Publishes, Deletes Article Claiming Watermelons Found on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/new-york-times-watermelons-mars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This afternoon, the New York Times published an article making a surprising claim about exobiology: that watermelons had been discovered on Mars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid mega-drought, rightwing militia stokes water rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jun/08/klamath-falls-oregon-protests-ammon-bundy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrations have sparked fears of a confrontation between law enforcement and rightwing anti-government activists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Pharmacist Who Destroyed 500 Doses Of Vax Sentenced To 3 Years In Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/steven-brandenburg-sentenced-three-years-prison-tampering-covid-19-vaccine-doses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Brandenburg pleaded guilty in February to two felony counts of attempting to tamper with a consumer product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES writer 'disturbed' by sight of American flags...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/new-york-times-editorial-board-member-disturbed-by-sight-of-american-flags/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gay said the message of the American flag is ‘this is my country, this is not your country, I own this.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC eases travel recommendations on 110 countries...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210608175629-kry0s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-AIRLINES (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. CDC eases travel recommendations on 110 countries, territories including Japan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France launches 'health pass'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210608-covid-19-france-resumes-indoor-dining-launches-health-pass-as-next-phase-of-easing-lockdown-begins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France enters its third and penultimate phase of easing Covid-19 restrictions on Wednesday as indicators continue to show the country's rate of infections subsiding. FRANCE 24 looks at the changes in…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
