<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Jamie Dimon warns: 'Recession ahead'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/15/jpmorgan-chase-ceo-jamie-dimon-warns-theres-a-recession-ahead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JPMorgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon warned on Tuesday that a recession is on the horizon thanks to the continuing trade tensions with China. “Of course there’s a recession ahead,” Dimo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Pro-Iran Hackers Took Down Top WSJ Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iranian-american-businessman-coordinated-with-uae-monarch-to-target-iran-critics-lawsuit-alleges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iranian-American businessman tied to a network of pro-Tehran advocates coordinated with a Middle Eastern monarch to target prominent Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OR MAYBE NOT...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/viacom-fox-news-shari-redstone-donald-trump-1202760698/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesman for Viacom said that no plans are in the works to launch a news channel, “conservative or otherwise,” after a report that Shari Redstone was quietly exploring such a plan to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani won't comply with congressional subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/giukiani-comply-congressional-subpoena/story?id=66293635</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani, the president's personal lawyer, told ABC News on Tuesday that he will not comply with a congressional subpoena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Cuomo drops n-word during live radio interview...</title>
      <link>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/gov-cuomo-uses-n-word-radio-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;1010wins.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (1010 WINS) – Gov. Andrew Cuomo used the n-word in a live radio interview Tuesday while talking about discrimination against Italian-Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 aftershocks follow...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/earthquakes/article/earthquake-4-5-Pleasant-Hill-Concord-14535347.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 4.5 earthquake rocked the Bay Area Monday night, the largest temblor to strike the region in five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHISTLEBLOWER: CNN Picks Winners, Losers...</title>
      <link>https://www.projectveritas.com/2019/10/15/part-2-cnn-leadership-and-staffers-reveal-true-sentiments-network-picks-favorites-among-democratic-candidates-on-eve-of-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.projectveritas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shari Redstone Explores Plan to Launch FOXNEWS Competitor...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/shari-redstone-explores-plan-launch-fox-news-competitor-1247475</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mogul, who has spoken with former Fox News star Megyn Kelly, may look to rebrand an existing Viacom linear channel to create a conservative-leaning news network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Cuomo drops n-word during live radio interview...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/15/gov-cuomo-drops-the-n-word-during-live-radio-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo used the n-word during a live radio interview Tuesday while discussing racism against Italian Americans. Cuomo called into WAMC radio, where he was asked about the controversy sur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputies ask man to quit calling about his stolen marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24f62c5d8b374717bb8c7a1cf97835e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DADE CITY, Fla. (AP) — Authorities say a Florida man repeatedly called 911 to report that his roommate had stolen his marijuana. A deputy for the Pasco County Sheriff's Office posted a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Book Sellers Begin Banning...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/australian-book-sellers-begin-banning-ronan-farrow-book-under-pressure-from-amis-dylan-howard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Some Australian outlets—Booktopia,  Amazon Aus—caved and banned it due to frivolous legal threats,” Farrow revealed on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surreal steal: Man walks out of San Francisco gallery with Dali painting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/man-walks-out-san-francisco-art-gallery-salvador-dali-painting-n1066391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect can be seen on security footage grabbing the painting, titled "Surrealistic Bullfight: Burning Giraffe," off the wall and walking out the door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA CASHES IN ON IMPEACHMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-impeachment-pop-up-news-media-products-14b2633d-7a1e-4e53-a79e-046a08751dec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They include newsletters, podcasts and devoted verticals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family found in cellar 'waiting for end of time'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dutch-family-found-cellar-waiting-end-time-160444464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch police found a father and six adult children hidden in the basement of a remote farmhouse where they had reportedly spent years "waiting for the end of time", officials said Tuesday. Local media said the family were found after one of the sons went to a nearby pub in a confused state,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside APPLE's Long, Bumpy Road to Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/apples-bumpy-tv-launch-inside-tech-giants-impending-arrival-hollywood-1247577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a few false starts and a little offscreen drama, AppleTV+ finally makes its big debut with a slate of shows, Jennifer Aniston and Reese Witherspoon and a billion potential customers ready to see what original programming looks like from the world's largest company, led by CEO Tim Cook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Choosing Democratic Socialism Over Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/15/why-some-young-voters-are-choosing-democratic-socialism-over-the-democratic-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - COLUMBUS, Ohio — As Tuesday night’s Democratic debate approached, members of the Young Democratic Socialists of America chapter at Ohio State University</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing defends Pro-China players...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2019/10/15/china-defends-pro-communist-nba-players-stars-have-done-nothing-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's English-language state media extended support to pro-China NBA "stars" after LeBron James criticized Hong Kong protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts At Risk? Mind-Reading Tech Security Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/is-mind-reading-tech-your-next-big-security-nightmare-yes-but-not-in-the-way-you-might-expect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mind-reading technology is about to go mainstream. Are your thoughts at risk?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren enters as frontrunner...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/live/2019/oct/15/trump-news-today-live-elizabeth-warren-turkey-syria-democrats-impeachment-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunter Biden chose the day of the fourth Democratic presidential debate to express his regret that he got involved in the Ukraine ‘swamp’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Stolen Pope Charity Cash Fund Priest Party Pads?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/did-pope-francis-stolen-charity-cash-fund-priest-party-pads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pope fired the head of his security detail and called in a mafia prosecutor to get to the bottom of secret London apartments, and what happened to money in his charity fund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roy Cohn, architect of Trump strategy on impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Roy-Cohn-the-architect-of-Trump-s-strategy-on-14534364.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's road to fame has been propelled by willfully distorting reality to cloak the truth. "The Apprentice," for example, was perhaps TV's greatest "extreme makeover" of all time, portraying Trump as a fabulously wealthy businessman even as he was declaring fifth and sixth bankruptcies.  Given this history, Trump's repeated lies in the White House and his approach to combating the impeachment investigation undertaken by the House shouldn't surprise us. Trump is executive producing his own defense, including a letter produced by the White House counsel declaring the impeachment inquiry illegitimate - even though that is quite evidently not true - and refusing to cooperate.  While deception is a longtime Trump tactic, so too is it a longtime Republican tactic, one that dates to the beginning of the Cold War. And there is a tie between Trump's usage of the practice, and Republicans' usage: Trump's mentor, Roy Cohn.  In 1945, Republicans were desperate to stop the dynastic Democratic dominance of President Franklin Roosevelt. This led the GOP to inflame and exploit the nascent U.S. conflict with the Soviets to damage liberalism, and by extension, the Democratic Party. It built upon long-standing suspicions of the Soviet Union to create a villainous, fearsome cartoon enemy that threatened the possible apocalypse.  It didn't matter that the U.S.S.R. was a wreck after World War II, an impoverished, dysfunctional state, weaker than the United States by every metric. What mattered were the potential domestic political benefits of hysterical rhetoric about the risk posed by the Soviets, not actual national security issues. By dramatically overestimating the might of the Soviet Union, Republicans justified political attacks on anyone who minimized the communist threat. In that propaganda campaign, Cohn emerged as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No longer King James for Hong Kong protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/749af77ef6b64376ac11da5358092307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — When the ball smashed into a photo of LeBron James' face stuck above the hoop and dropped into the basket, the Hong Kong protesters cheered. His standing took a hit from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screams...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/10/15/monkeys-scream-pain-secret-footage-recorded-german-lab-10919669/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An animal rights activist went to work undercover at a lab in Germany where the footage was allegedly shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Returning to FOXNEWS for Interview...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/megyn-kelly-fox-news-tucker-carlson0internview-1202760066/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly, who abruptly left Fox News Channel for NBC in January 2017, is heading back to that network for the first time since. FNC host Tucker Carlson said today that she will appear on his pro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Greek migrant camp in flames as arrivals continue to rise...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191015130929-bw0n5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Samos camp, initially built for about 650 people, is unravelling under the weight of more than 5,700 asylum-seekers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani was paid $500,000 to consult on indicted associate's firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-whistleblower-giuliani-excl/exclusive-trump-lawyer-giuliani-was-paid-500000-to-consult-on-indicted-associates-firm-idUSKBN1WU07Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's personal attorney, Rudy Giuliani, was paid $500,00...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton called Ukrainian investigation effort  'drug deal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/bolton-wanted-white-house-lawyers-alerted-ukrainian-efforts-called-it-n1066141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Russian analyst Fiona Hill testified to members of Congress on Monday behind closed doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden hits back at Trump in interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/news/story/exclusive-hiding-plain-sight-hunter-biden-defends-foreign-66275416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goodmorningamerica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No topic was off-limits when Hunter Biden sat down with ABC News' Amy Robach over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 questions that loom over field...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a200774753c40438e45270008ea849f </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WESTERVILLE, Ohio (AP) — Just a month has passed since the last presidential debate, but the state of the Democrats' 2020 race has shifted. The political world is suddenly consumed by an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Suspects Spiteful John Bolton Behind Ukraine Leaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-suspects-a-spiteful-john-bolton-is-behind-ukraine-leaks </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump fears the leaks are now coming from the people he chose to serve—and that only increases the paranoia currently infecting the West Wing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYRIA UNRAVELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-syria-security-turkey-usa/trump-sanctions-fail-to-slow-turkey-assault-moscows-allies-advance-idUSKBN1WU1D8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey ignored new sanctions from the United States to press on with its assault...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owl killings spur moral questions about human intervention...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/69730cac7ade4f73b36f4c59a0e7dea7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORVALLIS, Ore. (AP) — As he stood amid the thick old-growth forests in the coastal range of Oregon, Dave Wiens was nervous. Before he trained to shoot his first barred owl, he had never fired a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob Of 200 Juveniles Cause Havoc In Philly; Traffic Disrupted, Businesses Shut...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/10/14/group-of-approximately-200-juveniles-disrupt-traffic-businesses-in-northeast-philadelphia-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In total, police say four arrests were made -- one for vandalism and three for disorderly conduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain braces for fresh unrest over Catalan sentence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spain-braces-fresh-unrest-over-catalan-sentence-112732555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catalonia geared up for more upheaval on Tuesday a day after thousands of pro-independence activists stormed Barcelona airport in an angry response to Spain's jailing of nine of its leaders following a failed secession bid. Activists engaged in running battles with riot police as they sought to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR CANADA to stop announcing 'ladies and gentlemen'... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/air-canada-to-stop-announcing-ladies-and-gentlemen-in-recognition-of-gender-fluidity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees aboard Air Canada flights will no longer greet guests by referring to them as "ladies and gentlemen" or "mesdames et messieurs," which has been typical protocol for years, in an effort to be conscious of gender fluidity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Most disgraceful moment of career...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/columnist/dan-wolken/2019/10/14/lebron-james-daryl-morey-china-hong-kong-tweet/3982436002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James' Monday news conference played right into the hands of Chinese government propaganda and undermined the values he has publicly espoused.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Coming for Your Face...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/immigrant-dna-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal data is routinely harvested from the most vulnerable populations, without transparency, regulation, or principles—and this should concern us all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN HOLDING US NUKES 'HOSTAGE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-followed-his-gut-on-syria-calamity-came-fast/ar-AAILbg6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.5 MAG QUAKE RATTLES SAN FRAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-14/earthquake-4-7-quake-reported-near-walnut-creek-calif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 4.5 earthquake was felt widely in the San Francisco Bay Area on Monday evening at 10:33 p.m., with an epicenter in the Walnut Creek and Pleasant Hill area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scotty Bowers, 'Male Madame' to Stars, Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/scotty-bowers-dead-male-madame-stars-was-96-1247422 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The industry's genial sex fixer — who claimed to arrange liaisons for everyone from Rock Hudson to Bette Davis — challenged Golden Age Hollywood's baseline-heterosexual conception of itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Protestors: He Supports Totalitarianism?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hong-kong-protestors-lebron-james-he-supports-totalitarianism-1247621 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The L.A. Lakers star tried to clarify his comments — "My team and this league just went through a difficult week" — but many in Hong Kong argued that any such unpleasantness was little compared to police brutality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Haunted' doll filmed 'swearing' at ghost hunters...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/most-foul-mouthed-haunted-doll-20578051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The doll is thought to be 100 years old and may hold a sinister side</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigar-shaped object hovering over Baltimore...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/huge-cigar-shaped-object-with-20576445</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The witness claimed to see several of the cylinder-shaped objects in the skies over several hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'First baby born in space within 12 years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7574453/First-baby-born-space-12-years.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Egbert Edelbroek, founder and chief executive of SpaceBorn United, said the company is designing missions where pregnant women can give birth in orbit on a 24- to 36-hour mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden stumbles have Bloomberg reconsidering run...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/14/bloomberg-signals-he-would-run-for-president-if-biden-struggles-against-warren.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg could be in for a showdown with Elizabeth Warren, whether he runs or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Guinea Pigs Prepare for 20-Hour Marathon Flights!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/human-guinea-pigs-prepare-for-20-hour-marathon-flights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While researchers in this field understand how light enters the brain and adjusts the master clock, theyâ€™re still learning more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment threatens conflicts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/465777-impeachment-threatens-to-create-conflicts-for-democratic-candidates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are concerned the House impeachment inquiry could bleed into the primary season and take presidential candidates such as Sens. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) and Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) off the campaign trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON BOWS TO COMMUNISTS</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/lebron-under-fire-blaming-china-row-misinformed-rockets-083902730--nba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basketball superstar LeBron James was accused of turning a blind eye to Chinese repression on Tuesday after he criticized a Houston Rockets executive for angering China with a &amp;quot;misinformed&amp;quot; tweet supporting protesters in Hong Kong. James told reporters that Rockets general manager Daryl Morey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Swarm Film Crew Using 'Guns' For AMAZON TV Show...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/10/13/police-converge-local-filmmakers-using-fake-guns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stockton filmmaker Keith Lea said a group of police officers swarming an area market parking lot isn’t a scene from his upcoming Amazon Prime TV series. It was in response to a report of people with guns in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NASA scientist says they found life on Mars in '70s...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/10/15/us/nasa-life-on-mars-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We may have already discovered the essence of life on Mars 40 years ago, according to a former NASA scientist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors turn enemies over Trump in swing-vote Michigan suburbs...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191015093324-2li98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/WHISTLEBLOWER-BATTLEGROUND (PIX):Americans divided: Neighbors turn enemies over Trump in swing-vote Michigan suburbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN: NATIONAL ENQUIRER shredded secret Trump documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/14/ronan-farrow-national-enquirer-shredded-trump-documents-046711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Key-copying kiosks pose new security threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/keyme-kiosks-cbs-news-radio-investigation-key-copying-kiosks-security-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KeyMe is making it easier to copy electronic access cards and key fobs – and some security experts are worried</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Kurds are Assad's responsibility...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7572645/Donald-Trump-says-Kurds-Assads-problem-threatens-sanctions-against-Turkey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump issued a statement threatening sanctions against Turkey after saying that 'Anyone who wants to assist Syria in protecting the Kurds is good with me.' The U.S.-armed and trained Kurds to fight ISIS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent clashes erupt as Spain jails Catalonia leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49974289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jailing of politicians and activists over the illegal 2017 referendum sparks protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren flaunts fitness as candidates' health becomes issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/elizabeth-warren-flaunts-her-fitness-as-democratic-candidates-health-becomes/article_fe634e1c-fda3-538a-ae23-57845ea7f63b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As hundreds of people gathered for a recent Elizabeth Warren rally in Rock Hill, S.C., the heat built so much that one woman in the crowd passed out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vet gets groundbreaking penis transplant after losing his in Afghan blast...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/14/veteran-gets-groundbreaking-penis-transplant-after-losing-his-in-afghanistan-blast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran who lost the lower half of his body in an explosion has received one of the world’s first penis transplants — and he’s calling it “one of the best decisions I ever made.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 1,000 US troops to stay in Middle East to contain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8852b7419e94d7fadcbe0858db4709d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the United States and the military withdrawal from northern Syria (all times local): 5:00 p.m. Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell says the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos at Barcelona airport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d687e56bf3f47d7954b9aa898fae066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — The Latest on the conviction of Catalan politicians and activists (all times local): 9:00 p.m. Health authorities in northeastern Spain say 37 protesters have been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Fort Worth officer resigns after killing black woman...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df8aab0962b44f65a5cd52139d6f0143</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas (AP) — A white Fort Worth police officer who shot and killed a black woman in her home while responding to a call about an open front door acted inappropriately and resigned...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another utility-sparked wildfire? SOCAL EDISON had malfunction at start of Saddleridge Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/Another-utility-sparked-wildfire-SoCal-Edison-14520672.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Southern California Edison reported to the California Public Utilities Commission that it suffered an electrical malfunction that may be linked to the massive Saddleridge Fire in Los Angeles County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope's bodyguard resigns over new financial leaks scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/pope-s-bodyguard-resigns-over-new-financial-leaks-scandal-n1065871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican said its police chief, 57-year-old Domenico Giani, bore no responsibility for a leaked police flyer but resigned to avoid disrupting the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save me from selfies, says drag star RuPaul...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/save-selfies-says-drag-star-rupaul-183115482.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television superstar RuPaul Charles gave his millions of fans a little piece of friendly advice Monday: don't stop him in the street for a selfie. RuPaul joked that his show has been such a hit that he was thinking of making spin-offs like "'Drag Race Prison Break' or 'Drag Race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Controversy, Liberals Use Gun Control As Shield...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/nbas-kerr-latest-to-pivot-to-gun-control-amid-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Golden State Warriors coach Steve Kerr last Thursday became the latest liberal figure to attempt a rebound from scandal by pivoting to gun control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US troops scramble for the exits in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/594ac1ca4c294c29b7a213ccf5d4dfad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. troops are scrambling for Syria's exits while the Trump administration threatens economic penalties on Turkey for an invasion that opened the door to a resurgence of the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
