<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NFL IN LONDON:  4 JAGUARS arrested after brawl over $64,000 bar tab...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/7599437/nfl-team-bar-brawl-arrests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN football stars were involved in a nightclub brawl over a £50,000 bar bill. The four Jacksonville Jaguars players were arrested by cops at 4am. Trouble flared after they were accused of try…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire tycoon feared dead after helicopter crashes outside soccer stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/football/7599458/leicester-city-fc-owners-helicopter-crashes-stadium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEICESTER City owner Vichai Srivaddhanaprabha’s helicopter crashed in a ball of flames in the club’s stadium car park last night. The eight-seater helicopter belonging to 60-year-old ch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Riling Up the Crazies... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/27/opinion/sunday/donald-trump-fear.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only thing we have to fear is Trump himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seinfeld on Cosby, Roseanne and Tense Times in Comedy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/26/arts/television/jerry-seinfeld-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analytical as ever, the comic has strong opinions about disgraced peers like Cosby. He says the audience is always right (even about his #MeToo joke).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland Votes to Overturn Constitutional Ban on Blasphemy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ireland-set-to-overturn-constitutional-ban-on-blasphemy-1540626649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ireland has voted to remove a reference to blasphemy as a punishable offense from the country’s constitution, paving the way for repeal of a law that criminalizes public utterances judged offensive to religious sensibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silicon Valley is trying to help Dems capture Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Staying-on-the-sidelines-is-no-longer-an-13342348.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Baer faces a tough task on Election Day: She's a first-time Democratic candidate for Congress vying against a veteran Republican in "one of the swingiest swing districts" in southeastern Florida, as she puts it. Like many in her party, Baer says she benefits from a secret weapon - one that is 2,500 miles away from her slice of the Sunshine State. In Silicon Valley, Baer is among a flood of candidates capitalizing on new apps, activist groups and other organizations that spawned after President Donald Trump's 2016 victory with the explicit goal of triggering a Democratic wave this November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba's private sector grows, but restrictions generate millions for other countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article220690245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access to wholesale markets where they can buy raw materials has been one of the principal demands of Cuban entrepreneurs. Without it, Cubans travel overseas to buy products for their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Neither of this week's attacks will affect midterms...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/27/neither-of-this-weeks-attacks-will-affect-the-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whom can we blame? How will it play in November? For the second time in a week, those were the crass calculations running through the minds of the political class. First it was the pipe bombs and n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol stretched thin...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-border-patrol-commissioner-20181026-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a visit to California crossings Friday, Border Patrol Commissioner Kevin McAleenan warned staff are already spread thin, processing and detention space limited</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail bomb suspect's personality changed radically...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mail-bomb-suspect-personality-changed-radically-225705110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Thirteen years ago, mail bomb suspect Cesar Sayoc traveled the country leading a mixed-race troupe of male exotic dancers — he ran scams and had a temper, but a fellow dancer who is African-American said he never expressed racism or homophobia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida mulls letting felons vote again...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-mulls-letting-felons-vote-again-012629413.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yraida Guanipa did time for drug-related offenses and was released more than 10 years ago, but she still is not eligible to vote in the US midterm elections on November 6. Like we are another class of people, an inferior group that cannot speak," said Guanipa, who is 56. Thwarted by the US Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the machines: Automation reshapes job market...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/business/rise-of-the-machines-automation-reshapes-job-market/comment-page-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Melanie Mason, Los Angeles Times FONTANA — Looking at a map of California on a projector screen, Johannes Moenius, an economics professor at the University of Redlands, hovered his mouse over the Inland Empire, which glowed with a splotch of red pixels. The colored dots signified how susceptible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St sours on Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-sours-silicon-valley-140138671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors for years have seemingly adored technology stocks as much as most people love their smartphones. Some of the hardest hit stocks belong to five companies — Facebook, Apple, Amazon, Netflix and Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCTOBER WITCH:  Long-Anticipated Crash Upon Us?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-10-27/long-anticipated-crash-now-upon-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air pollution the 'new tobacco,' warns WHO head...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/oct/27/air-pollution-is-the-new-tobacco-warns-who-head</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Simple act of breathing is killing 7 million people a year and harming billions more, but ‘a smog of complacency pervades the planet’, says Dr Tedros Adhanom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid Granted Visa...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paularmstrongtech/2018/10/27/ai-humanoid-sophia-is-granted-first-ever-robot-visa-speaks-with-president/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's first ever visa was just issued to a robot in the Caucasus but there's more going on that will shape the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy Flashes Signs It's Downhill From Here...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-economy-flashes-signs-its-downhill-from-here-1540656002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private analysts and the Federal Reserve say a slowdown is looming. Though few believe a recession is near, a slowdown in growth would have far-reaching implications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New spotlight on embattled Andy Lack...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/megyn-kelly-debacle-puts-new-spotlight-on-embattled-nbc-news-honcho-andy-lack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly’s disastrous tenure at NBC News is coming to an end as her low-rated “Megyn Kelly Today” was canceled Friday on the heels of backlash after she questioned if “blackface” is racist. Now the pressure is one NBC News chairman Andy Lack, who handed Kelly a bank-breaking, three-year contract worth $69 million in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warning: 'We are preparing for war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1037059/Russia-INF-treaty-world-war-3-Donald-Trump-Vladimir-Putin-Mikhail-Gorbachev-US-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LEADING Russian official has warned that Russia is preparing for war in the wake of the US’s unilateral withdrawal from the Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty (INF), in a sign of growing tensions between the two foes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida wipeout?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/26/trump-florida-senate-2018-senate-governor-941802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is mounting an 11th-hour effort to head off high-profile losses for governor and Senate in his adopted home state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuPaul brings drag queens out of the closet...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-icon-rupaul-brings-drag-queens-closet-011058843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long kept within the confines of gay bars, drag queen culture is spreading like wildfire in the United States, propelled by the most famous of them all, RuPaul and his cult television show. "I wouldn't have predicted this even five years ago," says Raymond Alvarez, one of those attending</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Gunman opens fire at Pittsburgh synagogue... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/breaking-pittsburgh-synagogue-shooting-gunman-13489212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tree of Life Congregation Synagogue in Wilkins Avenue has been sealed off by police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai rappers cause stir with anti-junta lyrics...</title>
      <link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/world/2018/10/27/thai-rappers-cause-stir-with-anti-junta-lyrics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freemalaysiatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creative criticism through music and arts has been harder to control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control of Senate may hinge on Mississippi runoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/control-u-senate-may-hinge-possible-mississippi-runoff-102220038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Republicans and two Democrats are contesting a special election to serve out the remainder of retired Republican Senator Thad Cochran's term. Under state law, if no one gets 50 percent of the vote, the top two candidates regardless of party affiliation will go to a Nov. 27 runoff. "Mississippi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romans protest at eternal decline of Italian capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-rome-protests/romans-protest-at-eternal-decline-of-italian-capital-idUSKCN1N10GO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several thousand people protested in front of Rome City Hall on Saturday to deno...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots -- to make robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-abb-robots/robots-to-make-robots-at-abbs-new-150-million-factory-in-china-idUSKCN1N109X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots will make robots at a new ABB factory in China, which the Swiss engineeri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus kills 8th child at facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/eighth-child-s-death-reported-new-jersey-rehabilitation-facility-n925131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I am calling on the Wanaque Center to take immediate appropriate measures to address this tragic situation," said legislative leader Craig J. Coughlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's 'Tropical Trump' poised to win presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/bolsonaro-brazils-tropical-trump-poised-win-presidency-051840854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes called a "Tropical Trump" for his politically incorrect vitriol, Brazilian far-right presidential candidate and heavy favorite Jair Bolsonaro has successfully played to an electorate disgusted with politics as usual. Bolsonaro, 63, has built an image as a political outsider ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Best Shot in 30 Years to Turn Arizona Blue...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/democrats-get-best-shot-in-30-years-to-put-blue-stamp-on-arizona#gs.fLGvjT0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Get Best Shot in 30 Years to Put Blue Stamp on Arizona</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Faces Next Test of Authority in German Regional Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/merkel-faces-next-test-of-her-authority-in-german-regional-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel Faces Next Test of Her Authority in German Regional Vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your DNA Is Out There. Want Law Enforcement Using It?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/your-dna-is-out-there-do-you-want-law-enforcement-using-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your DNA Is Out There. Do You Want Law Enforcement Using It?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surreal World: TV Delves Into Paranoia, Anxiety, Misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-surreal-world-tv-delves-into-paranoia-anxiety-and-misinformation-1540645108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New TV dramas like “Homecoming,” “Maniac” and “Legion” are exploring the issues unsettling society with characters who struggle to maintain a grip on reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Workers Fume Over Payouts After Misconduct Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/google-workers-fume-over-executives-payouts-after-sexual-misconduct-claims/17949270/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — At Google’s weekly staff meeting Thursday, the top question employees voted to ask Larry Page, a co-founder, and Sundar Pichai, the chief executive, was one about sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Faces Deepening Criminal Probe Over Production Figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tesla-faces-deepening-criminal-probe-over-whether-it-misstated-production-figures-1540576636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla, with a fresh civil fraud settlement now behind it, faces a new legal problem: a deepening criminal investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail Bombs, Other Threats Have Wealthy Cranking Up Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/27/us/terror-private-security-bodyguard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrities and the rich are creating a boom in demand for bodyguards, drivers and similar amenities. Not everyone has that luxury, of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan Could Pose Public Health Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/10/26/medical-expert-migrant-caravan-could-pose-public-health-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Jane Orient, executive director of the Association of American Physicians and Surgeons, said migrants could bring diseases to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'could tone up' rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/413418-trump-rejects-calls-to-temper-rhetoric-i-think-ive-been-toned-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday rejected calls to temper his political rhetoric in the aftermath of a nationwide bomb scare involving many prominent Democrats with whom he has traded barbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly Crash at NBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/-megyn-kelly-today-is-canceled-as-the-nbc-host-negotiates-an-exit/17948668/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four days that sank Megyn Kelly and sparked a vicious standoff inside NBC News began with a simple, cheery welcome to her “Today” show audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he 'could tone up' rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-says-he-could-tone-rhetoric-after-mail-bomb-arrest-n925106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: With a mail bomb suspect in custody, Trump finds himself in a political box of his own making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama rips Trump, GOP in fiery speeches for Midwest Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/06ec76cf0cf14a4fa0cc5aeefdf7ba82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Former President Barack Obama criticized President Donald Trump's tenure in office Friday in fiery speeches in Milwaukee and Detroit that took aim at him and other Republicans for "making stuff up." The speeches were among Obama's sharpest and most direct takedowns of Trump's presidency, although the former president was careful to not mention Trump by name. He said the "character of our country is on the ballot" in the first midterm election since Trump took office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOT HIM</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/26/suspected-mail-bomber-found-a-father-in-trump-former-lawyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspected Florida mail bomber is a lost and “sick individual’ who estranged himself from his family but eventually “found a father” in President Trump, his family’…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
