<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FIREBALL LIGHTS UP MISSOURI SKY...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/article217439200.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 people reported seeing a fireball over Missouri Monday evening. The bright meteor was primarily seen in Missouri, but the American Meteor Society received sighting reports from people in Kansas, Oklahoma, Arkansas, Illinois, Iowa, Indiana and Nebraska.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: CNN 'Deliberately Lied' In Blockbuster Story?</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/28/cnn-credibly-accused-of-lying-to-its-audience-about-a-key-claim-in-its-blockbuster-cohen-story-refuses-to-comment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen lawyer Lanny Davis says he was an anonymous source for CNN's blockbuster story. CNN told viewers he refused to comment. Who is lying?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER CONFIDENCE RISES TO 18-YEAR HIGH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a9444498173d4f42a52c83adb947fa74/US-consumer-confidence-rises-to-18-year-high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Americans' consumer confidence rose in August to the highest level in nearly 18 years as their assessment of current conditions improved further and their expect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Despite strong economy, many Americans struggling to get by...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1d31cf4b56e449769ab4cb456237ea1f/Despite-strong-economy,-many-Americans-struggling-to-get-by</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a strong economy, about 40 percent of American families struggled to meet at least one of their basic needs last year, including paying for food, health care, housing or utiliti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agent says bureau leaked stories, then used them to get FISA warrants...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/28/fbi-agent-says-bureau-leaked-stories-then-used-them-to-get-fisa-warrants.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top FBI special agent admitted to House committees last week that bureau officials were known to leak information to the press and then use the resulting articles to help obtain surveillance warrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller 'gearing up' to subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/alan-dershowitz-robert-mueller-gearing-up-to-subpoena-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Alan Dershowitz suspects special counsel Robert Mueller's team of federal prosecutors is preparing to subpoena President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Majority can't name a single Supreme Court justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/poll-majority-cant-name-a-single-supreme-court-justice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every voter in the nation believes that the U.S. Supreme Court impacts their everyday life, but a majority can’t name a single justice on the all-important bench, according to a new survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  How Online Media Companies Are Suppressing Conservative Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/ashley-rae-goldenberg/2018/04/16/censored-how-online-media-companies-are-suppressing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Summary Like it or not, social media is the communication form of the future — not just in the U.S., but worldwide. Just Facebook and Twitter combined reach 1.8 billion people. More than two-thirds of all Americans (68 percent) use Facebook. YouTube is pushing out TV as the most popular place to watch video. Google is the No. 1 search engine in both the U.S. and the world. War is being declared on the conservative movement in this space and conservatives are losing — badly. If the right is silenced, billions of people will be cut off from conservative ideas and conservative media. It’s the new battleground of media bias. But it’s worse. That bias is not a war of ideas. It’s a war against ideas. It’s a clear effort to censor the conservative worldview from the public conversation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS OUT GOOGLE FOR BIAS SEARCH, CENSORSHIP; VOWS ACTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/28/trump-accuses-google-of-rigging-search-results-in-favor-of-bad-coverage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump accuses Google of altering search results to prioritize negative coverage and left-leaning outlets and warns that the issue "will be addressed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH GIANT RESPONDS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/303cecf1f4fc43c0a466955622c3ecb0/Trump-takes-on-Google-in-complaints-about-social-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump promised Tuesday to address what he says is the "very serious situation" of social media companies "suppressing" conservative voices and "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas dethrones Seattle as nation's hottest housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/real-estate/seattle-dethroned-as-nations-hottest-housing-market-for-first-time-in-nearly-two-years/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Vegas is now the nation's hottest housing market, overtaking Seattle, which had held the top spot every month since August 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH GIANT RESPONDS...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/president-trump-accuses-google-of-rigging-search-result-1828647850</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s first tweet of the day, sent at 5:24am local time, has accused Google of rigging search results against conservatives. Right-wing media personalities often claim, without evidence, that companies like Twitter and Facebook are conspiring against them, but Google search results aren’t often part of that conversation. They certainly are now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica land expropriation bill withdrawn for further reconsideration...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/business/437051-south-africas-ruling-anc-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa's African National Congress (ANC) said that a bill allowing the government to seize private land without compensation has been withdrawn by the Portfolio Committee on Public Works pending further study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover genetic link between marijuana and SCHIZOPHRENIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/scientists-discover-genetic-link-between-13151184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large-scale genetic study is the biggest of its kind ever to look at the potential side effects of cannabis use</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SMASH RECORD ON NEW NAFTA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/28/us-markets-us-mexico-trade-deal-and-economic-data-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Tuesday, boosted by an improved outlook on global trade after the U.S. and Mexico struck a deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast Set to Sweat With Temps Near 100 Degrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/28/u-s-northeast-set-to-sweat-with-temperatures-near-100-degrees#gs.CKk9__0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Northeast Set to Sweat With Temperatures Near 100 Degrees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Atlantic About to Wake Up?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2018-08-27-tropical-atlantic-about-to-wake-up-september-peak-hurricane-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could the Atlantic finally show signs of life as we approach the peak of the hurricane season?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to be human: The man who was raised by wolves...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/aug/28/how-to-be-human-the-man-who-was-raised-by-wolves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long read: Abandoned as a child, Marcos Rodríguez Pantoja survived alone in the wild for 15 years. But living with people proved to be even more difficult</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enraged Student Arrested After Snatching MAGA Hat Off Classmate's Head, Slapping Teacher...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/08/27/maga-trump-hat-taken/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jo-Ann Butler is facing battery charges after an altercation in her classroom over a Donald Trump “Make America Great Again” campaign hat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provocative Erdogan statue erected for German art festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/provocative-erdogan-statue-erected-german-art-festival-112926287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A golden effigy of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan evoking the famous statue of Saddam Hussein has been erected in a central German city as part of an art festival whose motto is "bad news."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans can't pay for basic needs?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/almost-half-of-americans-cant-pay-for-basic-needs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a growing economy, even the middle class is struggling to pay for rent, groceries, utilities or health care</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dull Skin? Restless Sleep? There's Drink for That...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/dull-skin-restless-sleep-theres-a-drink-for-that-1535457600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money is pouring into developing beverages that claim to do much more than quench thirst. Conglomerates and startups alike are placing bets on “enhanced” drinks that promise everything from better sleep to a more youthful complexion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley Takes Another Step Toward Autonomous Flying...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/28/technology/autonomous-flying-emergency-silicon-valley.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new flying ambulance service will use small helicopters outfitted with tech that could eventually let them fly without pilots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of 22 grizzly bears up to judge's decision. Should trophy hunters be allowed to kill?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/08/28/grizzly-hunt-pits-tourists-against-sportsmen-wyoming/1065854002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge is deciding whether to let trophy hunters kill grizzly bears near Yellowstone National Park or put them back on the Endangered Species list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri first state to regulate use of word 'meat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/08/28/animal-meat-missouri-law/1114285002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meat must come from animals, not plants or labs, according to the new law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Saudi Arabia's barbaric plan to behead human-rights activist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/27/saudi-arabias-barbaric-plan-to-behead-a-human-rights-activist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israa al-Ghomgham has spent nearly three years in prison for her nonviolent advocacy of greater rights for Saudi Arabia’s Shiite minority — and now her government wants to execute her. It’s barbari…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Droid butlers coming to Miami hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article217154420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three robots will roam the halls of YotelPad Miami delivering towels, soap and mail to guest and residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS OUT GOOGLE FOR BIAS SEARCH, CENSORSHIP; VOWS ACTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-takes-aim-at-google-claims-search-results-rigged-against-him-illegal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE DRUDGE LINK THAT STARTED IT ALL...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/google-search-results-show-pervasive-anti-trump-anti-conservative-bias/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does Google have its thumb on the scale?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECESSION: Redstone Civil War Heats Up Again As Daughter Prepares To Take Control...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/sumner-redstone-mental-capacity-hearing-cbs-viacom-shari-redstone-1202453307/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood and Wall Street has long wondered how much Sumner Redstone really knows about what is being done and said in his name. Now, thanks to an irate filing today by lawyers for the rarely seen …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquee Republican Races Set to Test Loyalty to President...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/florida-arizona-and-oklahoma-hold-primaries-for-midterms-1535448600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona and Florida have contested primaries for both parties, while Oklahoma Republicans will choose a candidate for governor. The marquee Republican contests are tests of loyalty to President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After driving ban ends, Saudi women taste thrill of speed...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/207/after-driving-ban-ends-saudi-women-taste-thrill-speed-doc-18j0bd1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope silent on claim he ignored abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pope-hold-giant-mass-dublin-abuse-victims-rally-030337491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has declined to comment on a claim that he ignored sexual abuse allegations against a senior clergyman amid speculation conservative elements in the Catholic hierarchy are using the issue to mount a "putsch" to remove the liberal pontiff. Archbishop Carlo Maria Vigano, a former</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCain Death, Florida Shooting Cast Shadows On Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/08/28/642402809/mccain-death-florida-shooting-cast-shadows-on-tuesdays-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Senate candidate in Arizona raised eyebrows with comments about McCain a day before he died. A Trump ally is vying to be governor of Florida, where a gun debate was reignited by a weekend tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals defend selves over cover-up storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180828-us-cardinals-defend-themselves-over-cover-storm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crippling costs of war reporting and investigative journalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180828-crippling-costs-war-reporting-investigative-journalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading journalists join call for EU copyright reform...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-08-journalists-eu-copyright-reform.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading journalists from more than 20 countries joined a call Tuesday for European MPs to approve a controversial media reform aimed at forcing internet giants to pay for news content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immunity Deal Shows Value of CFO in Prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/immunity-deal-shows-value-of-cfo-in-prosecution-1535448600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors granting Allen Weisselberg immunity after he testified before a grand jury in the investigation on President Trump’s former lawyer, underscores the critical role accountants and CFOs play in criminal prosecutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Car Sales Hit Speed Bump After Decade of Growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-car-sales-hit-speed-bump-as-demand-slows-and-trade-tensions-loom-1535448601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After nearly a decade of growth, new-vehicle sales in the world’s largest auto markets are entering their first sustained slowdown since the global financial crisis as uncertainty around the U.S.’s trade policies looms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths from drugs, alcohol, suicide now outpace diabetes...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/deaths-drugs-alcohol-suicide-now-outpace-diabetes-study/story?id=57438591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More people now die from drugs, alcohol and suicide than from diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Org CFO provided info on at least one probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/immunity-deal-shows-value-of-cfo-in-prosecution-1535448600 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors granting Allen Weisselberg immunity after he testified before a grand jury in the investigation on President Trump’s former lawyer, underscores the critical role accountants and CFOs play in criminal prosecutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Global-Warming' Advocates Pressure Media to Silence Skeptics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/global-warming-alarmists-pressure-media-to-end-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “experts” don’t get to decide when “the debate is over.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAmerica's 1st sex doll brothel to open...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/436986-sex-doll-brothel-toronto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toronto will soon be welcoming a brothel to the city, but the prostitutes won't have a woman’s or even a human touch; instead, they'll be hi-tech sex dolls made of silicone. It's said to be the first of its kind in North America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia biggest war games in four decades; 300,000 troops...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180828074024-rbrak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-WARGAMES/ (URGENT):Russia to hold biggest war games in nearly four decades - agencies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/picture-gallery/life/music/2018/08/27/burning-man-photos-fabulous-far-out/1111326002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Janet Ha of Austin, Texas, shows off her outfit at Burning Man during a pause between dust storms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whiteouts, high winds, dust storms cause festival to stop entry...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/burning-man-2018-whiteout-entrance-dust-storm-wind-conditions-updates-a8510256.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dust storms are a common phenomenon at Burning Man</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man: 10 hours to get in!</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/burning-man-black-rock-city-wait-times-hit-10-hours-after-dust-storms-2018-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burning Man officially began on Sunday, with thousands of participants arriving in Black Rock City, Nevada. Dust storms caused dangerous driving conditions, prompting a three-hour closure of city gates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot strawberry pickers could end need for human workers...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6103873/Experts-steps-create-ROBOT-strawberry-pickers-end-need-human-workers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 20 per cent of soft fruits are going to waste due to a shortage of workers,  University of Essex researchers say, and this will worsen when Britain leaves the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Anchor 'Angry' Tiger Woods Refused to Attack Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/video/2018/08/27/espns-kellerman-tiger-woods-defending-trump-really-bothers-me-im-angry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday, ESPN "First Take" co-host Max Kellerman responded to golfer Tiger Woods saying people need to "respect the presidency" when it comes to President | Breitbart TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fish die-off creates smelly mess in Malibu...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/pets-animals/massive-fish-die-off-creates-smelly-mess-in-malibu/4071053/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget about enjoying fresh air at Malibu Lagoon State Beach - a massive die-off has claimed hundreds of fish, which are now rotting along the shoreline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER VICTORY FOR JARED KUSHNER...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/kushner-and-lighthizer-pressed-for-deal-before-mexican-president-leaves-office-1535413789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months of tensions between the U.S. and Mexico ended with a presidential phone call on Monday after officials raced to complete a Nafta deal before the transition to a new Mexican administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica Civil War? White Farmers, 'Black Hitler' Willing To Die Over Land... </title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-27/south-africa-civil-war-looms-white-farmers-black-hitler-willing-die-over-property </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dog that went vegan...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/would-sir-like-some-pawsecco-with-his-lentils-the-rise-of-vegetarian-dog-food-fmq0h6bzx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept of the vege-terrier had never occurred to me until six weeks ago, during the dog days of the heatwave, when our mutt, Dublin, 18 months and generally a good girl, stopped eating. Not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 7 adults on pot... </title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-marijuna-us-adults/one-in-seven-u-s-adults-used-marijuana-in-2017-idUSKCN1LC2B7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters Health) - With more and more states legalizing marijuana, whether for medical use, recreational use, or both, increasing numbers of Americans are using cannabis. A new survey finds that one in seven had used marijuana in 2017, with smoking being the most common manner of consumption, according to a report published in the Annals of Internal Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover mysterious new type of human brain cell...</title>
      <link>https://www.geekwire.com/2018/rosehip-neuron-discovered/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geekwire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gene-by-gene, neuron-by-neuron search has turned up a new breed of brain cell that may serve as a fine-scale “volume control” for neural activity in humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Trump's Missing Signature Force Him to Be Deposed?</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/could-trump-s-missing-signature-force-him-to-be-deposed-/17799862/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the history of presidential scandals, it is often the hidden things that end up proving decisive. Think, for example, of Monica Lewinsky’s stained blue dress or of Richard M. Nixon’s secret Oval Office tapes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diocese buys $2.3M home for retiring bishop...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/08/26/san-jose-diocese-buys-bishop-2-3-million-retirement-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diocese says it must provide a home for retired bishop and bought Willow Glen house with proceeds from selling his predecessor’s condo and funds exclusively for housing retired bishops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redford rides into sunset...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ad1d531fd11493794306e96b0dd51e4 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — In "The Old Man and the Gun," the elderly bank robber Forrest Tucker, played by Robert Redford, walks up to a bank teller, smiles, says a few words in a kindly man</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANNY BLOWS IT!</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Michael-Cohen-s-lawyer-has-done-real-damage-to-13185791.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most bizarre aspects of the investigations engulfing the Trump administration is the lawyers involved. Here we have a presidency on the line, and this is Trump's team? The top legal spokesmen for each side are . . . Rudy Giuliani and Lanny Davis!? Up until this point, though, Giuliani was the Great Contradictor and Davis was merely a colorful character. Now that has changed in a big way. In a new interview with The Washington Post's Tom Hamburger and Rosalind S. Helderman, Davis is backing off two massive claims he made in recent weeks, including that former Trump lawyer Michael Cohen has told people he witnessed President Donald Trump being informed of Donald Trump Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Withholding Samples of Dangerous Flu Virus From USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-nz/news/world/china-has-withheld-samples-of-a-dangerous-flu-virus/ar-BBMwyrr </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside world of 'DARK TOURISM' with trips to nuke zones...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/7113989/netflixs-dark-tourism-reveals-why-people-are-visiting-japans-suicide-forest-and-nuclear-disaster-zones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOST of us prefer to spend our holidays sunbathing on the beach with a drink. But for others only visiting places associated with natural disasters or tragedies count as a proper getaway. In Netfli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ Gov Aims To Please With Replacement Pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/27/doug-ducey-john-mccain-seat-voters-798875</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arizona governor has grown closer to the White House since cautiously embracing the president in 2016, but can't risk moderate voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Warren Buffett TWITTER account giving life advice, and people are listening...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/fake-warren-buffett-twitter-account-giving-life-advice/story?id=57424237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fake Warren Buffett Twitter account has racked up tens of thousands of retweets with life advice that is not actually from the billionaire philanthropist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago ride-share passengers targeted by armed robbers...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/08/27/chicago-ride-share-passengers-being-targeted-by-armed-robbers-cops-warn.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women in Chicago's Near North Side district are allegedly targeting ride-share passengers and robbing them at gunpoint, police revealed Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Indicted Republican Congressman Holds 8-Pt Lead...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/politics/sd-me-hunter-poll-20180827-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a federal indictment for misuse of campaign funds, Rep. Duncan Hunter (R-Alpine) appears to be maintaining his lead over Democratic challenger Ammar Campa-Najjar in the race for the 50th Congressional District — although with an advantage that seems to be shrinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Couple locked elderly relative in dog kennel, starved, forced to walk on broken glass...</title>
      <link>http://www.kltv.com/story/38970405/affidavit-east-texas-couple-locked-victim-in-dog-kennel-woman-physically-abused-her</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers with the Malakoff Police Department arrested a couple in connection allegations that they locked an elderly relative of the woman in a dog kennel and starved her. The woman also allegedly ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange online persona...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/27/jacksonville-shooting-fbi-atf-searches-baltimore-home/1108711002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement searched a home in Baltimore in connection with a deadly shooting in Jacksonville. The suspect, David Katz, came to Florida to participate in the Madden NFL 19 competition at the Jacksonville Landing entertainment complex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wine country paper turns readers into shareholders...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/27/in-liberal-wine-country-turning-newspaper-readers-into-shareholders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with a business model that was "failing rapidly," a newspaper publisher in Northern California decided to get creative and do a community IPO -- selling stock in the paper to readers, the New York Times reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Housing Authority employees accused of using projects for wild orgies...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/27/nycha-employees-accused-of-using-projects-for-wild-orgies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYCHA workers transformed a Bronx housing project into their own personal sex club — engaging in wild, boozy orgies inside offices, the groundskeepers shop and even empty apartments, sources …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIAN: Online insults nothing compared to public slander in ancient Rome...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6101807/Todays-online-insults-compared-public-slander-Rome.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancient historian Professor Dr Martin Jehne from the Technische Universität Dresden has suggested people should toughen up, claiming Romans could be even more cruel than the trolls of today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Goodman: Roseanne's Character Will Be Killed Off...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/the-conners-john-goodman-says-roseanne-barr-character-will-be-killed-off-report-1202452990/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Goodman did not go into detail but confirmed to The Sunday Times that Roseanne Barr’s character will be killed off this fall in the upcoming The Conners spinoff on ABC. When talking abou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jumping shark, taggings close Cape Cod beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.necn.com/news/new-england/Nauset-Beach-Cape-Cod-Great-White-Shark-Tagging-Sighting-491804331.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.necn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two shark taggings and a shark breaching the water near the shore have prompted beach closures along Cape Cod on Monday. The tagged sharks, which became the 10th and 11th tagged of the season, were tagged about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOSE CALL: Diver surprise 'eye contact' with 16-ft Great White!</title>
      <link>http://www.capecodtimes.com/news/20180825/diver-captures-encounter-with-great-white-shark</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capecodtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wildlife photographer comes face to face with a great white, approximately 16 feet long, in waters of Stellwagen Bank National Marine Sanctuary - and it's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Air pollution causes 'huge' intelligence reduction...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/aug/27/air-pollution-causes-huge-reduction-in-intelligence-study-reveals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impact of high levels of toxic air ‘is equivalent to having lost a year of education’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to Pay Farmers $4.7B to Offset Trade-Conflict Losses...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-to-pay-farmers-up-to-4-7-billion-to-offset-trade-conflict-losses-1535396442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration said it would make $4.7 billion in payments to U.S. farmers to offset losses from trade battles rippling across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC POLITICAL MAP ORDERED REDRAWN -- BEFORE NOV?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/article217419880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A court ruled Monday that North Carolina’s legislative districts are the result of an unconstitutional gerrymander and proposed drawing new districts before November’s election as a possible remedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Beatty, Gary Hart, Michael Bloomberg pallbearers...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6104195/McCains-pallbearers-include-Warren-Beatty-Joe-Biden-Gary-Hart-FedEx-CEO.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain's casked will be born by pallbearers who speak to his decades-long career in public service and his enduring friendships formed in the Senate, as well as his business ties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists urge killer robot ban 'before too late'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/activists-urge-killer-robot-ban-too-180139072.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Countries should quickly agree a treaty banning the use of so-called killer robots "before it is too late", activists said Monday as talks on the issue resumed at the UN. "Killer robots are no longer the stuff of science fiction," Rasha Abdul Rahim, Amnesty International's advisor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin to Play BATMAN's Father as 'Trump-Like Figure'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/alec-baldwin-joins-joker-movie-as-bruce-waynes-father-1137843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert De Niro, Zazie Beetz and Marc Maron are already on the call sheet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIEL: President Only Republican Who Isn't 'Zombie'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/2018/08/27/peter-thiel-says-trump-is-the-republican-who-isn-t-a-zombie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Thiel Says Trump Is the Republican Who Isn't a ‘Zombie’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE: I'LL BE INDICTED...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/403838-roger-stone-predicts-hell-be-indicted-next-in-mueller-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone is predicting that special counsel Robert Mueller will soon indict him as part of the investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czech PM calls for no illegals in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.it/20180827/czech-pm-calls-for-no-illegal-migrants-in-europe-ahead-of-visit-to-italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.it&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Czech Prime Minister Andrej Babis said on Monday August 27th that a comprehensive action plan is necessary to stop illegal migration, which he will address on a visit to Italy and Malta this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcaster defends not covering grim murder by refugee...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20180827/when-should-the-media-report-on-murders-by-refugees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibly reporting on violent crime committed by refugees is one of the hardest things for a news organization to get right. A national broadcaster’s decision not to cover one such murder caused Jörg Luyken to take a closer look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walked Past Patrons, Targeted Competitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/gunman-with-2-guns-extra-ammo-targeted-gamers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 24-year-old man accused of opening fire Sunday afternoon at a Madden NFL 19 regional tournament at the Jacksonville Landing, killing two and shooting 10 others, clearly targeted fellow gamers, Sheriff Jacksonville Sheriff Mike Williams announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran, Damascus Showcase Military Cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Iran-showcases-new-defense-cooperation-in-blow-to-US-Israel-565878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Syria and Iran want to show off the military cooperation and the official connections between Tehran and Damascus in light of US pressure for Iran to leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE WATERS: KEEP FOCUS ON IMPEACHMENT...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/waters-trump-will-be-impeached-democrats-make-impeachment-central-issue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Rep. Maxine Waters (Calif.) on Sunday said that President Donald Trump "will be impeached" and criticized her party for not making his removal from office a "central issue" while taking their electoral case to the American people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA Suspends Vet-Owned Biz for Criticizing Kneelers...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/08/27/instagram-permanently-suspends-veteran-owned-business-for-criticizing-nfl-kneelers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project War Path, a clothing company owned by Navy SEAL and Army Special Forces combat veterans, has been permanently suspended from Instagram for criticizing NFL players who kneel during the national anthem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Suits Up As Varsity Football Team's First Female Player...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/08/25/high-school-teen-first-female-football-player-southlake-carroll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madi Martin is the first girl to play on the Southlake Carroll varsity team as its kicker. On Friday, she suited up for a scrimmage against Arlington High.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort Sought Deal in Next Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/manafort-sought-deal-in-next-trial-but-talks-broke-down-1535404819</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort’s legal team held talks with federal prosecutors to resolve a second set of charges against the former Trump campaign chairman before he was convicted last week. But no deal was made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Why Saudi King shelved Aramco IPO plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-aramco-ipo-king-exclusive/exclusive-saudi-king-tipped-the-scale-against-aramco-ipo-plans-idUSKCN1LC1MX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The king spoke, and a $2 trillion dream went up in smoke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA TROUBLES: BUZZFEED asks readers for donations...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90227629/can-you-spare-a-dime-for-buzzfeed-news-site-plans-to-start-asking-for-reader-donations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news website is looking for new ways to grow revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Official: Ambassador Telling 'Truth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/former-nunciature-official-vigano-said-the-truth-38319</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholicnewsagency.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monsignor Jean-François Lantheaume, the former first counsellor at the apostolic nunciature in Washington D.C., has said that the former nuncio, Archbishop Carlo Maria Viganò, told “the truth” in his explosive statement released to the press on Aug. 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuns Killed Children, Say Former Residents Of Orphanage...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/christinekenneally/orphanage-death-catholic-abuse-nuns-st-josephs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of American children were placed in orphanages. Some didn’t make it out alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House returns flag to half staff...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/27/white-house-returns-flag-to-half-staff-after-backlash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a national outpouring of scorn, the White House relented Monday afternoon and once again lowered flags on the grounds to half staff in honor of the late Sen. John McCain. The flags had been …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking trend: Pet owners abuse own animals to get drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2018/08/27/pet-owners-abusing-animals-drugs-opioid-crisis/1066712002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogs, cats and other pets have become victims in the nation's worst drug crisis. Vets have been warned to watch out for pet owners seeking narcotics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Pulled From Sewer After Stuck Underground For Day...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/08/27/officials-man-pulled-from-sewer-system-after-being-stuck-underground-for-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two rescuers were lowered into the sewer, found the man and pulled him out about 22 minutes after the department arrived on scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants Push Upscale Shots:  'Classy Way of Beer Bong'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-classy-way-of-doing-a-beer-bong-restaurants-push-upscale-shots-1535397268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shot, long a mainstay of spring break, is being reinvented with a twist for more grown-up diners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany condemns far-right demonstration after killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-chemnitz/german-government-condemns-far-right-demonstration-after-killing-idUSKCN1LC1DD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany will not tolerate "vigilante justice", Chancellor Angela Merkel's spokesman said on Monday, after hundreds of far right protesters staged a violent demonstration following a fatal stabbing that authorities blamed on a Syrian and an Iraqi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster squid washes up on popular beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/environment/natural-wonders/divers-stumble-upon-42-metre-long-squid-carcass/news-story/6309245ff3542ec6b8ae2ee00f34379e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MONSTER 4.2 metre-long squid has washed up on the shores of New Zealand’s capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Pursuing 'Con Queen' Impersonating Top Hollywood Execs...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hollywood-con-queen-fbi-opens-investigation-1137720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI and NYPD have opened investigations into the prolific scam artist impersonating Amy Pascal, Kathleen Kennedy and other top female execs — including one male suspect with a talent for female voice work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Drug For Dogs Holds Promise For People...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/08/27/experimental-cancer-drug-dogs-could-hold-promise-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An experimental cancer drug being tested on dogs could hold promise for people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCAIN SLAMS TRUMP FROM BEYOND THE GRAVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/mccain-s-farewell-message-n904171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arizona Republican's final words were read to the public by his close friend Rick Davis in Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROPANE TANKS BURST INTO FLAMES...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/27/liberty-island-evacuated-over-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberty Island was evacuated Monday morning after a fire erupted there, according to the FDNY. Fire officials got the call around 11:50 a.m. that three propane tanks had burst into flames. There we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRE ON LIBERTY ISLAND...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/08/27/fire-on-liberty-island-prompts-evacuation-of-park-statue-of-liberty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An propane fire on Liberty Island prompted a partial evacuation of the park and Statue of Liberty monument.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVACUATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/liberty-island-evacuated-after-propane-tank-fire/4067846/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A construction mishap sparked a propane fire on Liberty Island on Monday afternoon forcing thousands of tourists to evacuate the Statue or Liberty and the island itself, National Parks Service said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Best Islands In USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/best-islands-america/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's coasts are dotted with many magnificent islands. It's hard to list just a dozen, but CNN Travel has. Martha's Vineyard made the cut. What 11 others join it on the list?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child punished for calling teacher 'ma'am'...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/education/tarboro-child-punished-for-calling-teacher-maam-/4041588/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents of a Tarboro fifth grader are concerned after their child was punished for referring to his teacher as "ma'am."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER VICTORY FOR JARED: Mexico Praises For New Trade Agreement...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/nafta-another-win-for-jared-kushner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s secret weapon and son-in-law has struck again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force tests 'base in box' for future wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/air/2018/08/27/us-air-force-tests-base-in-a-box-in-poland-to-prep-for-future-wars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force is getting more expeditionary thanks to a new kit that will enable the service to rapidly move to a partner nation’s airfield, set up a squadron and begin flying combat missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER VICTORY FOR JARED: Mexico Praises For New Trade Agreement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/08/jared-kushner-scores-another-victory-mexico-praises-trump-son-in-law-for-exceptional-work-on-new-us-mexico-trade-agreement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacrilegious spies:  Tried hacking Orthodox clergy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26815e0d06d348f4b85350e96b78f6a8/Sacrilegious-spies:-Russians-tried-hacking-Orthodox-clergy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The Russian hackers indicted by the U.S. special prosecutor last month have spent years trying to steal the private correspondence of some of the world's most senior</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
