<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Why does internet keep breaking?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-58873472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outages of Facebook and its family of apps now lead to significant disruption for firms worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO argues show too popular to cancel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/netflix-ceo-argues-that-chappelle-e2-80-99s-new-special-criticized-as-transphobic-is-too-popular-to-cancel/ar-AAPpSgO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing criticism that Chappelle's new comedy special is transphobic, Netflix's CEO said argued that "some people find stand-up to be mean-spirited but our members enjoy it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghostface Returns in Slasher Reboot...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2021/10/scream-trailer-neve-campbell-1234670073/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The writers of “Zodiac” and “Ready or Not” penned the first new installment since the passing of the franchise’s creator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian warships fire missiles in massive show of strength...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3838631/russian-warships-missiles-japan-disputed-islands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has staged a military show of strength by firing missiles off its warships near Japan after Tokyo claimed sovereignty over the disputed Kuril Islands. The Kuril archipelago was grabbed by St…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New male contraceptive device zaps sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/3840339/new-male-contraceptive-testicle-bath-zaps-sperm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOULD you try a new male contraceptive that zaps sperm in order to prevent a pregnancy? That’s the concept of a new bath-like device that warms the testicles, reducing sperm mobility. This should p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Prehistoric Girl In Cave; New Type Of Ancient Human...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/new-type-of-ancient-human/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remains belonged to a young female buried in a cave on the Indonesian island of Sulawesi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden Complicates White House Anti-Corruption Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/10/12/hunter-biden-corruption-515583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Questions about the First Son could detract from the president’s efforts to position himself as a global good-government crusader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF cuts global growth forecast, citing supply disruptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/12/imf-cuts-growth-forecast-as-supply-disruptions-covid-pandemic-weighs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revised outlook for this year comes amid supply chain issues in advanced economies and a worsening health situation in emerging countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Testing Armed Drone Ships...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/10/11/chinese-testing-experimental-armed-drone-ships-at-secret-naval-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In front of scenic cliffs and an ornamental European-style windmill is a secret People’s Liberation Army Navy pier. Here, at a former tourist resort on China’s northern coast, is where the PLAN is developing some of its most secretive, and previously unreported, naval programs, USNI News has learned. The pier near Dalian is where China …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Desperate for tires.' Components shortage roils harvest...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/the-great-reboot/desperate-tires-components-shortage-roils-us-harvest-2021-10-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dale Hadden cannot find any spare tires for his combine harvester. So the Illinois farmer told his harvest crew to avoid driving on the sides of roads this autumn to avoid metal scraps that could shred tires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$80 oil here. $100 next?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/12/investing/premarket-stocks-trading/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since late 2014, US oil prices are back above $80 per barrel — a boon for the energy industry, which was battered during the pandemic, but bad news for the economic recovery as winter approaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic chemical in consumer products linked to early death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/12/health/plastic-chemical-early-death-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some synthetic chemicals called phthalates in consumer products may linked to early death, especially from heart disease, a new study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Out of stock' items plague grocery delivery services...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/12/shipt-is-an-underappreciated-growth-engine-for-targets-sales-analyst-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a crowded delivery landscape, Shipt uses customer relationships to retain consumers and the gig workers who shop for them, and ultimately, to increase sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers say fossil shows humans, dogs lived in C. America in 10,000 BC...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-10-fossil-humans-dogs-america-bc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fossil of a jaw bone could prove that domesticated dogs lived in Central America as far back as 12,000 years ago, according to a study by Latin American scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio signals coming from hidden planets?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3835608/radio-signals-in-outer-space-could-prove-alien-existence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEAK radio signals in the depths of space could indicate the existence of aliens. The sounds, detected by the world’s most powerful telescope, appear to be from hidden planets. Astronomers picked u…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents sue schools after children catch covid: 'Recklessly exposing public'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/parents-sue-wisconsin-schools-after-their-children-catch-covid-19-e2-80-98recklessly-exposing-the-public-e2-80-99/ar-AAPpSDd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawsuits filed in Wisconsin federal courts blame the schools’ lax policies on masks, quarantining and contract tracing. “It’s unfortunate that it came to this.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital diagnosed woman with homosexuality. It was all mistake, they say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-spanish-hospital-diagnosed-a-woman-with-homosexuality-it-was-all-a-mistake-they-say/ar-AAPpRir</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The doctor told local media that the incident was a “mistake” that happened when completing the patient’s record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Tax Deal Faces Emerging Hurdle in USA Debate Over Treaty...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/global-tax-deal-faces-emerging-hurdle-in-u-s-debate-over-treaty/ar-AAPpcac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Biden administration and governments around the world celebrate another advance toward an historic global tax accord, an obscure legal question in the U.S. threatens to tear it apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Brazilians flock to USA; Smuggler cashes in...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211012105915-pla45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/BRAZIL (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-As Brazilians flock to the U.S. border, an alleged smuggler cashes in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Shatner heads toward stars, visions of space collide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-william-shatner-technology-science-entertainment-2f300ec9fc37e5625d56bbc6de3f42b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code red for humanity -- more like false alarm?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/energy-environment/576197-code-red-for-humanity-more-like-a-false-alarm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reaction from many people was one of genuine alarm— but does the report really provide anything new or alarming?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grassley embrace of Trump shakes Republican landscape...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/576273-grassleys-embrace-of-trump-shakes-gop-landscape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Chuck Grassley’s (R-Iowa) enthusiastic appearance at a Trump event in Iowa over the weekend shows that the former president has further strengthened his grip on the GOP following the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Big Tech Grows in Pandemic, Seattle Grows With It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/12/as-big-tech-grows-in-the-pandemic-seattle-grows-with-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic was a disaster for commercial real estate markets. In the Seattle area, it was a boon. In 2020,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea displays hypersonic weapon?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/at-exhibition-showing-off-nuclear-arms-n-korea-displays-apparent-new-weapon/ar-AAPp2im</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as Pyongyang showcased what it calls a “hypersonic” weapon on Monday, Kim Jong Un insisted he was not interested in war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China has won AI battle with USA, Pentagon's ex-software chief says...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211011063736-r28k4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CHINA/AI (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-China has won AI battle with U.S., Pentagon's ex-software chief says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 4 OF TRAVEL HELL</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/airline-news/2021/10/11/southwest-flights-canceled-airlines-holiday-flight-cuts/6091631001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines canceled 1 in 4 flights over the holiday weekend, but it wasn’t clear why. Here’s what President and COO Mike Van de Ven said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Charles reveals his car runs on cheese and wine byproducts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/oct/11/prince-charles-car-runs-on-cheese-wine-byproducts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charles’s ‘quaint’ solution to decarbonise his Aston Martin using high blend of bioethanol is not scalable, experts say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANGER GROWS</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Southwest-Airlines-flight-woes-extend-to-Monday-16524657.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines faced a fourth day of disruptions Monday - after canceling hundreds of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid  'Detectives' Deployed To San Fran Airport To Test Travelers For New Variants...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/10/11/covid-variant-detectives-deploying-to-san-francisco-international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Monday announced the launch of a pilot testing program to identify new COVID variants at the San Francisco International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  TX Gov. bans covid mandates in state, rips Biden for 'bullying'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211012001717-jysyx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TEXAS (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Texas governor bars all COVID-19 vaccine mandates in state, rips Biden for 'bullying'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro says he is 'bored' by questions on deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211011202736-kdvw8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/:Brazil's Bolsonaro says he is 'bored' by questions on COVID-19 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gruden resigning as Raiders coach after more leaked emails reveal homophobic language...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/jon-gruden-resigning-as-raiders-coach-after-more-leaked-emails-reveal-homophobic-language-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Raiders coach is stepping down</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLAAD PUSHES HARDER...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/dave-chappelle-trans-remarks-glaad-response-netflix-ryan-murphy-ted-sarandos-suspended-staffer-1234854223/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after a memo by Netflix’s co-CEO declaring that trans remarks in Dave Chappelle’s latest special didn’t “cross the line” was made public, one of the nation’s leading LGBTQ+ advocacy organizat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS AT SOUTHWEST</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-travel-airlines-2a099f47993c0833c8a7104e1e46af0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Southwest Airlines canceled more than 350 flights Monday following a weekend of major disruptions that it blamed on bad weather and air traffic control issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor with 8 DUIs tries to 'murder' officers with car...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/pastor-with-8-duis-tries-to-murder-officers-with-his-car-report/ar-AAPojfr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The holy man's most recent drunk driving incident was in September</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star says she 'has threesomes with GOD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3833485/threesomes-god-sex-onlyfans-nita-marie-this-morning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;​ONLYFANS star Nita Marie has told This Morning that she’s having “the best sex of her life” thanks to her “threesomes with God”. ​It comes after the Christian model d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Opens Fire On Suspects In $4 Million Jewelry Heist...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/10/11/nypd-shots-fired-midtown-traffic-stop-fleeing-vehicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shows the moment police officers tried to stop the men suspected in at least a dozen robberies, including stealing $4 million worth of jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART, COSTCO limit toilet paper sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10079935/The-shortage-Shelves-bare-delays-deliveries-pharmacies-without-medication.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goods exist, but backlogs at shipping yards and rail yards across the country combined with a lack of workers means the items aren't being offloaded quickly enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA won't share recipe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-technology-business-united-nations-europe-d4aff7ddb273194b312354a57c244ce6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Moderna has no plans to share the recipe for its COVID-19 vaccine because executives have concluded that scaling up the company's own production is the best way to increase the global supply, the company’s chairman said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homes destroyed in San Diego small plane crash...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/news/local-news/plane-crashes-near-high-school-in-santee-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plane crashed in a Santee neighborhood Monday afternoon, destroying two homes and damaging a third while the extent of injuries remained unclear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How whistleblower learned to use data as weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-education-of-frances-haugen-how-the-facebook-whistleblower-learned-to-use-data-as-a-weapon-from-years-in-tech/ar-AAPnMEu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook whistleblower Frances Haugen’s calls to change the company have broken through, winning bipartisan support on Capitol Hill, calls for more regulation and triggering soul searching among the American public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones deliver sushi, ice cream above Tel Aviv...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/drones-deliver-sushi-and-ice-cream-above-tel-aviv-skyline-681628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the National Drone Initiative test operation, drones will bring sushi deliveries ordered by customers via a dedicated app and will deliver them to Tzuk beach in Herzliya.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life on Mars: Simulating Red Planet base in desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211011-life-on-mars-simulating-red-planet-base-in-israeli-desert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life on Mars: simulating Red Planet base in Israeli desert</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Investigate Ashes Spread At STEELERS Stadium...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/10/11/fan-spreads-ashes-at-heinz-field/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Heinz Field crew was made aware of a fan that spread a relative's ashes in the stands and on the edge of the field on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condo Board Fought 9/11 Vet Over Shoes. Now It Has Bigger Problem: DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-condo-board-fought-a-9-11-vet-over-his-shoes-now-it-has-a-bigger-problem-the-doj/ar-AAPnRks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An apparently intractable conflict between a Florida condo board and a disabled 9/11 responder over him leaving his shoes outside his front door has become so toxic that the federal government has stepped in to try and resolve it. Charlie Burge worked for the New York City Department of Sanitation for 35 years, first hitting the pavement in 1981 and eventually overseeing nighttime operations in North Brooklyn. On September 11, 2001, Burge ran...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas prices skyrocket as global energy crisis worsens...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/11/business/gas-prices-oil-opec/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of energy was dirt cheap in the spring of 2020 as roads and airports sat nearly empty during the height of the Covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mag 6.9 quake off Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/alaska-earthquakes-c223e11a1445d1e6f6d5c8ddfd429828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHIGNIK, Alaska (AP) — An earthquake with a preliminary magnitude of 6.5 struck early Monday off the coast of Alaska. The epicenter was about 114 kilometers (71 miles) east of the village of Chignik, the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Including Trans Who Criticized Chappelle...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/dave-chappelle-netflix-suspends-trans-employee-1235086394/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has suspended three employees for crashing a meeting of its top executives, including an out trans person who criticized a new comedy special from Dave Chappelle, sources tell Variety. Terr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci green lights rick-or-treating...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Amid-drop-in-covid-rates-Fauci-encourages-16523574.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While traditional Halloween celebrations last year were discouraged by federal health...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIMON:  Bitcoin 'worthless'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/11/jpmorgan-chase-ceo-jamie-dimon-says-bitcoin-is-worthless.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamie Dimon, JPMorgan Chase chairman and CEO, isn't a fan of bitcoin, the largest cryptocurrency by market value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As drought worsens, farmers being paid NOT to grow crops...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/drought-worsens-california-farmers-being-130059812.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Colorado River levels continue to drop, water agencies are working with local growers to leave some fields fallow in exchange for cash payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake tech's potential to change media, disrupt society...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/deepfake-technologys-potential-to-change-media-and-disrupt-society/ar-AAPlTBU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Synthetic media, better known as deepfakes, could be a goldmine for filmmakers. But the technology has already terrorized women who have had their faces inserted into pornography. And it could potentially disrupt society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN MURDERED OVER ALABAMA FOOTBALL ARGUMENT...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/11/texas-am-alabama-argument-shot-killed-bessemer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is dead because of an argument over the Alabama/Texas A&amp;amp;amp;M game. He was shot and killed in Bessemer, AL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ship That Became a Bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/10/11/the-ship-that-became-a-bomb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stranded in Yemen’s war zone, a decaying supertanker has more than a million barrels of oil aboard. If—or when—it explodes or sinks, thousands may die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST GAME OF CAREER?</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/10/11/tom-brady-needed-five-weeks-throw-more-touchdowns-than-every-44-year-old-nfl-history-combined/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady officially confirmed that he's better than every single person who ever tried to play quarterback at the age of 44.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN employees say toxic 'bro culture' led to mistrust, low morale...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/inside-blue-origin-employees-say-toxic-dysfunctional-e2-80-98bro-culture-e2-80-99-led-to-mistrust-low-morale-and-delays-at-jeff-bezos-e2-80-99s-space-venture/ar-AAPniVe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s condescending. It’s demoralizing,” said one former top executive of conditions prompting many to leave the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>37% Think Economy In Good Shape...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/democrats-build-back-better-americans-dont-know-opinion-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Policy ideas are popular, but more know about the cost of the bill than about its plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Melbourne's eternal lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/10/inside-melbournes-eternal-lockdown/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will the city ever recover from its pursuit of Zero Covid?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At age 44, Brady leads NFL in passing yards...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/10/11/at-age-44-tom-brady-leads-nfl-in-passing-yards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is not slowing down at the age of 44. In fact, after Brady’s 411-yard game in Sunday’s 45-17 win over the Dolphins, he now leads the NFL with 1,767 yards in the 2021 season. That’s just not supposed to happen, a 44-year-old leading the NFL in passing yards. Or for that matter leading [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Putrid Odor Plagues Southern CA City...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/10/10/city-and-county-leaders-call-for-nuisance-declaration-over-pungent-odor-in-carson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some residents, though, the nuisance declaration comes as little comfort and feels like living under a new kind of lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Sick?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-says-he-has-a-cold-assures-officials-it-is-not-covid-19/ar-AAPnEWU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin said he has a cold and he isn’t suffering from Covid-19, after he was heard repeatedly coughing at a televised meeting with officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superman Comes Out, as DC COMICS Ushers In New Man of Steel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/11/superman-comes-out-as-dc-comics-ushers-in-a-new-man-of-steel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up, up and out of the closet! The new Superman, Jonathan Kent — who is the son of Clark Kent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress off rails? Lawmakers barrel toward fall fights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-congress-filibusters-27ee5558714da1347b68d58952cc137b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Year-end pileups of crucial legislation and the brinkmanship that goes with them are normal behavior for Congress. This autumn, lawmakers are barreling toward battles that are striking for the risks they pose to both parties.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
