<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DOJ SPIED AND GAGGED NYT</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/06/04/us/politics/times-reporter-emails-gag-order-trump-google.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The push began in the Trump administration and continued under President Biden, and the Justice Department obtained a gag order to keep it from public view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATTEMPTED HIJACKING ON DELTA FLIGHT FROM LAX...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/04/fbi-investigating-attempted-hijacking-on-flight-from-lax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Bureau of Investigation Friday was investigating after a man reportedly attempted to break into the cockpit on a flight from Los Angeles International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Star Reporters Push Back Against Union...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-york-times-star-reporters-push-back-against-union</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A contingent of Times journos, including many Pulitzer winners, has stood in opposition to the NewsGuild’s proposed dues hike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China military uses AI to track rapidly increasing UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3136078/china-military-uses-ai-track-rapidly-increasing-ufos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To the People’s Liberation Army they are ‘unidentified air conditions’ and artificial intelligence is the best way to keep up with them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk of 2024 run builds as legal pressure intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/michael-pence-donald-trump-campaign-2016-election-2020-government-and-politics-7306533132e2fa9aa0e9b5da60db9420</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump was calling into yet another friendly radio show when he was asked, as he often is, whether he's planning a comeback bid for the White House. “We need you," conservative commentator Dan Bongino told the former president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI subpoenas USATODAY for information on readers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/03/usa-today-subpeona-florida-shooting-491847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gannett, the publisher, contends that demand for details on who accessed article violates the First Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Pipeline breached using compromised password...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/hackers-breached-colonial-pipeline-using-compromised-password-1.1612851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hack that took down the largest fuel pipeline in the U.S. and led to shortages across the East Coast was the result of a single compromised password, according to a cybersecurity consultant who responded to the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden quietly deploys app for asylum seekers: Facial recognition, geolocation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-biden-quietly-deployed-app-190234787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials have quietly deployed a mobile app relying on facial recognition technology to collect data on asylum seekers before they cross the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food fears rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/food-costs-world-labor-384b0a07-977d-466d-884a-f70a7f4eea51.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-related labor disruptions likely aren't helping, but climate change may lead to more volatile production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court upholds conviction for threatening tweet...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/senate-elections-religion-courts-88cd4b4dbf19752044217a73e4140e68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court on Friday upheld the conviction of a North Carolina man who posted an anonymous threat on social media to lynch a Muslim-American political candidate from Virginia. A three-judge panel from the 4th U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalization rates in teens double...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/coronavirus/article251900783.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consistent with demographics of adults, about two thirds of the hospitalized teens were Hispanic or Black.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BING Censors Image Search for 'Tank Man' -- Even in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qj8v9m/bing-censors-tank-man</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are no results for tank man," the Bing website reads after searching for the term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaxx protesters, dressed as MARVEL superheroes, camp out in front of DISNEYLAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/disneyland/article/Disneyland-Anti-vaccine-protesters-Marvel-avengers-16225024.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney has yet to shut the protest down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new journalism -- and the PR firms behind it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-new-journalism-and-the-pr-firms-behind-it/ar-AAKIjgD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These sites say they report the news. But it’s not always clear who is paying the bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dept stops responding to certain 911 calls amid 'staffing crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/north-carolina-police-911-staffing-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Carolina’s Asheville Police Department (APD) has ordered its officers not to respond to certain types of crimes so that the agency can adequately answer more serious calls for help amid a "staffing crisis."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves obesity drug...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-obesity-lifestyle-business-health-c6f992d717c6461ef20f40e6d4ee9d25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regulators on Friday said a new version of a popular diabetes medicine could be sold as a weight-loss drug in the U.S. The Food and Drug Administration approved Wegovy, a higher-dose version of Novo Nordisk’s diabetes drug semaglutide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA brought Trump Org controller to testify before special grand jury...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/manhattan-da-brought-trump-organization-controller-testify-special/story?id=78088595</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Organization controller Jeff McConney has testified before a special grand jury in the investigation into Donald Trump and his company, sources told ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  What would Orwell say about our debased discourse?</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/our-politics-and-the-english-language-8be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What would Orwell say about our debased discourse?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV positive patient had 216 days -- virus mutated 32 times inside her...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/africa/article/3136136/woman-hiv-had-covid-19-seven-months-virus-mutated-32-times-inside</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If more such cases are found, it raises the prospect that HIV infection could be a source of new variants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah gov asks residents to join him in 'weekend of prayer' for rain...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/556888-utah-gov-asks-residents-to-join-him-in-weekend-of-prayer-for-rain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah Gov. Spencer Cox (R) is asking residents to join him in a "weekend of prayer" for rain amid a statewide drought emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What caused downfall of Israel's legendary prime minister?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/netanyahu-what-caused-the-downfall-of-israels-legendary-prime-minister-670070</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDDLE ISRAEL: Historians will agree that Netanyahu's downfall was caused not by any event, idea or trend, but by his character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oldest woman in world' found at age of 124 while getting jab...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/06/04/indian-woman-124-found-by-covid-doctors-could-be-oldest-ever-14718038/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 100+ Cats Removed From Home After Neighbor Complained Of Stench...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/06/03/south-bound-brook-nj-cats-rescued/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Hubert's Animal Welfare Center was called in to assist police officers after a neighbor complained about a foul smell coming from the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  $7 Gas In CA?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Northern-Calfornia-Mendocino-most-expensive-gas-16220638.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of gas is up everywhere, but this California station has desert island...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale's head impaled on spike as brutal slaughter returns to islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/whales-head-impaled-spike-brutal-24177666</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: WARNING - DISTRESSING IMAGES Ten pilot whales were slaughtered in the first hunt of the year in the Faroe Islands, with campaigners worried that 2021 could be a particularly bloody year with whales and dolphins slaughtered with knives on the green list country's beaches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon 'covering up hypersonic drone tech'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/pentagon-ufo-report-may-cover-24251095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A university academic suggests the final report will guide the public into looking for aliens to hide the details of hypersonic drone technology developed by the US and its rival powers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOKYO: Olympic teams forbidden from going outside...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/olympics/1001189/olympic-teams-arriving-in-japan-arent-even-allowed-to-go-outside-for-a-walk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Falwell: LIBERTY lawsuit excuse to shame him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lawsuits-government-and-politics-religion-d702cc5a0f49b5ff4a92fd3dc3fcf919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LYNCHBURG, Va. (AP) — Jerry Falwell Jr. is asking a court in Virginia to dismiss a lawsuit Liberty University filed over his headline-grabbing departure last year as leader of the evangelical school his father founded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis star arrested for 'deliberately losing match'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-tennis-arrests-french-open-sports-2b5b2403531f6190fa4d699c70ad408d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A Russian tennis player suspected of match-fixing last year has been arrested during this year's French Open, her lawyer told The Associated Press on Friday. The player, 765th-ranked Yana Sizikova of Russia, denied the allegations, according to her lawyer, Frederic Belot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NC county bans Coke machines over 'left wing' politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/3/surry-county-north-carolina-bans-coke-machines-ove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Carolina county commission has kicked Coca-Cola vending machines from government office buildings, accusing the soda giant of engaging in left-wing politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET RUSSIAN TECH?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3014192/uk-us-investigate-ufo-pentagon-report-hypersonic-aircraft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world must ramp up its investigations into UFOs as the Pentagon’s “disturbing” report appears unable to rule out that foreign hypersonic technology could be behind the sightings, an expert clai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK harvest of face scans...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3015362/tiktok-privacy-policy-face-voice-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIKTOK has updated its privacy policy in the US so it can collect things like “faceprints and voiceprints” from its users. The app said it “may collect biometric identifiers and biometric informati…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Puppies Born With Human-Like Social Skills, Wired To Communicate With People...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/puppies-human-like-social-skills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We found that there's definitely a strong genetic component, and they're definitely doing it from the get-go," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis star arrested for 'deliberately losing match'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/sport/other-sports/french-open-match-fixing-arrested-24248080?%3F%3F=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian tennis star Yana Sizikova was arrested on Thursday evening on suspicion of deliberately losing a match at the ongoing Roland Garros tournament in France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>151,620,000 Americans Employed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/national/susan-jones/bls-151620000-americans-employed-may-444000-more-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a disappointing employment report in April, the Labor Department's Bureau of Labor Statistics on Friday produced an improving picture as the nation continued to emerge from its COVID slump in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  $7 Gas In CA?</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/03/most-expensive-gas-in-the-us-mendocino/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is currently charging $6.73 a gallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK marketing user thoughts, prayers?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/facebook-wants-your-thoughts-and-prayers-1847028464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s found a new way to capitalize on the thoughts, prayers (and data) from the religious side of its user base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum protesters denounce Picasso's treatment of women...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210604131756-1fl24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPAIN-MUSEUM/PROTEST (PIX, TV):Museum protesters denounce Picasso's treatment of women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake patient reviews make it increasingly hard to find medical help on GOOGLE, YELP...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fake-patient-reviews-are-making-it-increasingly-hard-to-seek-medical-help-on-google-yelp-and-other-directory-sites/ar-AAKHtpN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia scrambles fighter jet to accompany U.S. military plane...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210604123153-5pygs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/MILITARY (URGENT):Russia scrambles fighter jet to accompany U.S. military plane</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrest erupts after man dies in Minneapolis arrest attempt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/death-of-george-floyd-minneapolis-business-death-of-daunte-wright-shootings-0c3907f72981ad591187d07a393e698d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Crowds vandalized buildings and stole from businesses in Minneapolis’ Uptown neighborhood after officials said a man wanted for illegally possessing a gun was fatally shot by authorities who were part of a task force trying to arrest him that included U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent cardinal offers to resign, citing 'catastrophe' of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/prominent-german-cardinal-offers-to-resign-citing-e2-80-98catastrophe-e2-80-99-of-sexual-abuse/ar-AAKHTds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reinhard Marx, the archbishop of Munich and Freising, is a close adviser to Pope Francis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear videos show Chinese weapons tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1445491/UFO-investigation-Pentagon-aliens-China-Russia-military-threat-hypersonic-weapons-news-vn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON'S highly-anticipated report into UFOs has been briefed by US intelligence officials ahead of its release, with suggestions that the mysterious objects and inexplicable technology captured on video could in fact be experiments from Chinese and Russian military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VT decriminalizes possession of opioid addiction drug...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vermont-opioids-health-0b9efd46f0eed0d765fc576a9d29139e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTPELIER, Vt. (AP) — Gov. Phil Scott has signed a bill into law decriminalizing possession of the opioid use disorder treatment drug buprenorphine. The measure decriminalizes possession of up to 224 milligrams of the drug by people without a prescription, WPTZ-TV reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIRING STRUGGLES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-bb295afe6ec8d8b88b1b944f3eba7931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. employers added a modest 559,000 jobs in May, an improvement from April’s sluggish gain but still evidence that many companies are struggling to find enough workers as the economy rapidly recovers from the pandemic recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She could hold keys to dismantling world's most dangerous cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/04/emma-coronel-el-chapo-wife-sinaloa-cartel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Chapo's wife, Emma Coronel Aispuro, could be the key to smashing the notorious Sinaloa drug cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY JOBS: +559K...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/04/jobs-report-may-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls in May were expected to increase by 671,000, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci calls on China to release medical records of Wuhan researchers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/556815-fauci-calls-on-china-to-release-medical-records-of-wuhan-researchers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci is calling on China to release medical records of researchers at a laboratory in Wuhan, China, that reportedly became sick with COVID-like symptoms prior to the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
