<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Politicians face violence, threats from voters -- and each other. Nearing civil war?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/politicians-face-violence-threats-voters-each-other-are-we-nearing-ncna1283824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The signs give cause for concern. America suffers from societal and political conditions that predispose it to violence, and the list seems to be growing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's Medical Leave Continues After 'Sprained Back'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211114-uk-s-queen-suffers-sprained-back-palace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II has a "sprained back" and will miss Sunday's Remembrance service -- her first planned public appearance since resting on medical advice, Buckingham Palace said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More turn to abortion pills by mail, with legality uncertain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-abortion-texas-covid-19-pandemic-health-13c2fbe3f1de416d88a5ef6d1ca3406e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPEKA, Kan. (AP) — Before her daughter’s birth, she spent weeks in bed. Another difficult pregnancy would be worse as she tried to care for her toddler. Faced with that possibility, the 28-year-old Texas woman did what a growing number of people have considered: She had a friend in another state mail her the pills she needed to end her pregnancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 snow leopards with covid die at zoo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-lincoln-tigers-animals-c55c7c432e0a80caa5fea3c8a4f5d1c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINCOLN, Neb. (AP) — Three snow leopards have died at the Lincoln Children's Zoo in Nebraska of complications from COVID-19. The zoo made the announcement in a Facebook post  Friday, describing the deaths of the three leopards — named Ranney, Everest, and Makalu— as “truly heartbreaking."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAME GAME INTENSIFIES</title>
      <link>https://www.spiegel.de/international/coronavirus-in-deutschland-wenn-impfverweigerer-auf-ein-land-ohne-politische-fuehrung-treffen-1636729575-a-1495255a-25af-4b8e-9727-4ea7f26db55f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many in Germany thought the worst of the pandemic was behind them. But the country is now being slammed by the fourth wave – fueled by millions of people who refuse to be vaccinated and political leaders who have abdicated leadership. The situation, say virologists, is grave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL URGENT PLEA</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/merkel-calls-shots-avoid-bad-112649534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Angela Merkel on Saturday called on all unvaccinated Germans to get their shots as quickly as possible as the country’s coronavirus infection rate hit the latest in a string of new highs and death numbers were growing. Germany’s disease control center said that the country's infection rate climbed to 277.4 new cases per 100,000 residents over seven days, up from 263.7 the previous day. The Robert Koch Institute reported 45,081 new infections, two days after the daily total topped 50,000 for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. remains quiet on Cuba as government quashes dissidents...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuban-government-dissidents-head-toward-monday-confrontation/ar-AAQFGM5?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Christie paints himself as future of Republicans in new book...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10198683/Chris-Christies-book-guaranteed-anger-Trump-hits-2020-election-fraud-conspiracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his book, Christie argues that the GOP faces dangerous from conspiracy theorists trying to overtake the party and move on from the politics of former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers compromise FBI email system, send thousands of messages...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211113230358-t8bvm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-FBI/CYBER (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Hackers compromise FBI email system, send thousands of messages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine says Russia has nearly 100,000 troops near its border...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211113211122-i585d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE-CRISIS/RUSSIA (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Ukraine says Russia has nearly 100,000 troops near its border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY COVID NIGHTMARE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211113191714-8n353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-German state health ministers call to extend state of emergency as COVID cases soar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Western boom cities see spike in harmful ozone...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-11-western-boom-cities-spike-ozone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reduction of harmful ground-level ozone across most of the U.S. over the past several decades has been an air pollution success story. But in some parts of the country, especially in the heavily populated mountain valleys of the West, the odorless, colorless gas has remained stubbornly difficult to reduce to safe levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING FOR MAGA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-big-warning-signal-steve-bannon-e2-80-99s-indictment-sends/ar-AAQE4EO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris, Buttigieg under spotlight amid uncertainty over Biden future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/harris-and-buttigieg-under-the-spotlight-amid-uncertainty-over-biden-e2-80-99s-future/ar-AAQFkt8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERITAS Tells Judge It Was Assured Biden Diary Legally Obtained...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/12/project-veritas-tells-judge-it-was-assured-biden-diary-was-legally-obtained/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project Veritas, the conservative group under scrutiny in a Justice Department investigation of how a diary kept by President Biden’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 probe threatens fragile Trump-Pence peace...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/581363-jan-6-probe-threatens-fragile-trump-pence-peace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation into the Jan. 6 insurrection at the Capitol poses a serious threat to the tenuous relationship between former President Trump and former Vice President Pence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma National Guard rejects Pentagon order...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-army/2021/11/12/oklahoma-guard-goes-rogue-rejects-covid-vaccine-mandate-after-sudden-change-of-command/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than 24 hours after an unexpected change of command, the Oklahoma National Guard rejected the Pentagon's vaccine mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Jan. 6 threats of violence escalate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/581415-gop-silence-deafening-as-post-jan-6-threats-of-violence-escalate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Practically the entire party is missing in action in resisting the nation’s descent into violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Rendered in UK-US Split Screen...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/13/for-meghan-an-image-rendered-in-a-u-k-u-s-split-screen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — When Prince Harry and his wife, Meghan, stepped out last week at a gala for veterans in New</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police: Ecuadorian prison clash leaves at least 52 dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/guillermo-lasso-ecuador-guayaquil-violence-crime-5ae3283e86d3f5326e9b598dc80c9d21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — Clashes inside Ecuador’s largest prison early Saturday left at least 52 inmates dead in the latest violence to hit the Litoral Penitentiary, which recently saw what authorities said was the country’s worst ever prison bloodbath.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Prison Riot In Ecuador Leaves 58 Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/new-prison-riot-in-ecuador-leaves-58-dead-police-01636820707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ferocious clashes have left 58 inmates dead in an Ecuador prison, police said Saturday, in the latest unrest at a Guayaquil jail that was the scene of a September riot which killed 119 prisoners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German army prepares to step in...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/merkel-urges-unvaccinated-reconsider-7-day-covid-incidence-rate-hits-record-2021-11-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel urged unvaccinated people to reconsider their decision in a video message on Saturday, as the country's seven-day coronavirus incidence rate rose to the highest level since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher burnout leaves schools scrambling...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/teacher-burnout-fatigue-pandemic-covid-schools-75df52ab-720c-470f-ac9b-426514e0452a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I just feel like we're trying to go back to normal but normal wasn't great to begin with."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Disappearance of Husband...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mysterious-disappearance-ghislaine-maxwell-maybe-050249525.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyWeeks before Jeffrey Epstein’s arrest in summer of 2019, his alleged accomplice and former girlfriend, British heiress Ghislaine Maxwell, breezed into a social gathering on the North Shore of Massachusetts on the arm of her secret husband.Maxwell, once a fixture in elite Manhattan circles, was now leading a quieter life, assuming the role of environmental activist, suburban stepmom, and spouse to one Scott Borgerson, an entrepreneur a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High school roiled by allegation of racist, sexual hazing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-massachusetts-hockey-hazing-rituals-race-and-ethnicity-f52bcfa76092517c3a2cb37034974133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANVERS, Mass. (AP) — Teachers in Danvers are praising a student-athlete who came forward to detail violent, sexual, homophobic and racist hazing rituals in a high school hockey team locker room. Danvers High School has been roiled by the description of rituals where players disrobed and were fondled, something dubbed “Gay Tuesday,” and where players were roughed up if they didn’t shout a racial slur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FBI raid on O'Keefe home sparks questions about press freedom...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/13/raid-veritas-okeefe-biden-press-521307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The action against James O’Keefe has prompted concern about the Biden administration’s commitment to the First Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raves blamed?</title>
      <link>https://edm.com/news/violent-crime-spikes-in-tulum-hotel-association-blames-raves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reported rise in drug demand aligns with an increase of local electronic dance music parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI emails hacked in huge breach...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4059641/fbi-hacked-spam-email-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) had its email system hacked this morning, sending out fake messages about cyberattacks. The rogue emails, sent from the FBI’s email infrastructure are said…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Caribbean jewel of Tulum deals with rapid rise in violence...</title>
      <link>https://mexiconewsdaily.com/news/analysis/caribbean-jewel-of-tulum-deals-with-rapid-rise-in-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mexiconewsdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between January and September 2021, the Quintana Roo resort town recorded 65 murders, an 80.5% increase over the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Hell: 3 In 5 Banning Unjabbed Relatives From Gatherings...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/unvaccinated-relatives-banned-holiday-family-gatherings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two-thirds of vaccinated Americans are banning unvaccinated family members from their holiday gatherings this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC chair's challenging bid to avert midterm defeat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-jaime-harrison-south-carolina-congress-elections-197d1c896908cebc6f4d8945c0b97fb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's not particularly close to the White House. He's never won statewide office or a seat in Congress. And just last year, he lost a high-profile Senate race by double digits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan thanks NBA star for support as Oz pledges help in island's defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/taiwan-thanks-nba-star-kanter-for-support-as-australia-pledges-to-help-us-in-island-e2-80-99s-defense/ar-AAQEUAS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ships Keep Coming, Pushing Port Logjam and Waits to Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/ships-keep-coming-pushing-us-port-logjam-and-waits-to-records/ar-AAQEMaZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW VARIANT IN FRANCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/new-covid-variant-found-in-france-reason-for-panic-or-not-quite-yet-684878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spike protein of the variant known as B.1.640 has some unprecedented mutations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Asghari: More Than Mr. Spears...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/13/more-than-mr-britney-spears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Sam Asghari is a nascent actor and erstwhile personal trainer. But this highly polite, handsome and friendly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants Say Belarusians Took Them to EU Border and Supplied Wire Cutters...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/13/migrants-say-belarusians-took-them-to-e-u-border-and-supplied-wire-cutters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SULAIMANIYA, Iraq — The sudden surge of migrants to Belarus from the Middle East that is now the focus of</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
