<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Elder says 'racial epithets' were yelled during egg attack, calls out silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/larry-elder-racial-epithets-yelled-egg-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican candidate told Fox News in a phone interview that the racist phrases were screamed at him while a White woman wearing a gorilla mask with neon magenta hair threw an egg at him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Oahu median home sale price tops $1 million for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2021/09/08/hawaii-news/oahus-median-home-sale-price-tops-1m-for-the-first-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $1 million house on Oahu has officially become run-of-the mill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Want Justice Stephen Breyer To Retire. His Response? Not Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/09/1035092720/progressives-want-justice-stephen-breyer-to-retire-his-response-not-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with NPR, the 83-year-old said: "When exactly I should retire, or will retire, has many complex parts to it. I think I'm aware of most of them, and I ... will consider them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT delays return to work indefinitely...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/microsoft-return-to-u-s-offices-delayed-indefinitely</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft told employees Thursday that it has indefinitely delayed their return to U.S. offices until it’s safer to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA BANS ALL NEW VIDEO GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/china-announces-blanket-ban-new-24943641</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have banned all new video games from being released indefinitely, as the government attempts to tackle what it calls gaming addiction in the under-18s. The suspension was revealed at a meeting with game company Tencent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran adds mindfulness, meditation to public school curriculum...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/san-francisco-school-district-adds-mindfulness-to-curriculum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco public schools add mindfulness meditation to curriculum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 80% Oppose Tax Hikes Coming Out of Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/poll-80-oppose-tax-hikes-coming-out-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#13;By an 80-20 margin voters oppose tax increases as the U.S. comes out of the pandemic, according to a new poll conducted by HarrisX.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;The poll was conducted by HarrisX between Sept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of baby at center of Roe v. Wade revealed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/09/roe-v-wade-baby-revealed-to-be-shelley-lynn-thornton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her biological mother had been 22, unmarried, unemployed, and pregnant with her third daughter in 1969 when she sought to have an abortion in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden in December '20: 'I Don't Think' COVID Vaccinations 'Should Be Mandatory'...</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/washington/michael-w-chapman/biden-december-2020-i-dont-think-covid-vaccinations-should-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(CNS News) -- Democratic President Joe Biden is expected to sign an executive order today requiring all federal workers to receive the COVID vaccine, without the option of regular COVID testing to opt out of the mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Man gets 10 years in prison for stabbing woman with semen-filled syringe...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/syringe-stabber-sentenced-982150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 8--The 53-year-old fiend who jabbed a woman in the rear end with a semen-filled syringe has been sentenced to a decade in state prison following his guilty plea to assault charges. A Maryl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY TAKES THE SEX OUT OF LEWINSKY...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/09/no-cigar-ryan-murphys-monica-lewinsky-series-impeachment-opens-low-fails-to-score-a-million-viewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Impeachment” is impaired. The Ryan Murphy FX series about Monica Lewinsky and Bill Clinton failed to score 1 million viewers on Tuesday night. The total came in at 916,000. Since FX is…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ sues Texas over abortion law...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/justice-department-sue-over-texas-restrictive-abortion-law-n1278783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The law bans abortions after six weeks of pregnancy, before many women know they are pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Can Liberals Be Convinced Genetics Matters?</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/09/13/can-progressives-be-convinced-that-genetics-matters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The behavior geneticist Kathryn Paige Harden is waging a two-front campaign: on her left are those who assume that genes are irrelevant, on her right those who insist that they’re everything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Office air quality affects workers' cognitive function...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210909-office-air-quality-affects-workers-cognitive-function-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Office air quality affects workers' cognitive function, study shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN CRUSHED IN FREAK ACCIDENT AT MCDONALD'S DRIVE THRU...</title>
      <link>https://www.bellinghamherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article254107763.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bellinghamherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He leaned out to pick up something and the vehicle rolled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA  poised to mandate student vaccinations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/los-angeles-poised-to-mandate-student-vaccinations-in-nation-s-second-largest-school-district/ar-AAOgzY2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It would be by far the largest school district in the country to take this step.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France to offer free birth control to all women...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-france-birth-control-f5a1df14f886dfeff4c3d43dc530129d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France will offer free birth control to all women up to age 25 starting next year, the health minister announced Thursday. The measure will also include free medical visits about contraception, and will start Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxer Suggests Feinstein Should Retire from Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/column-barbara-boxer-on-abortion-being-mugged-and-dianne-feinstein/ar-AAOgEf5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's life beyond the Beltway, says the Democrat, who gets by with a little help from Siri.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban accused of torturing journalists for covering protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/9/9/talibans-violence-against-women-reporters-intensifies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports show the armed group being violent and intimidating journalists, despite their free-press pledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Judy returning to TV, with granddaughter...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-arts-and-entertainment-14f68c5734275ec126dc27d8098c149b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Judge Judy Sheindlin is returning to television on Nov. 1 with a new red robe, a granddaughter in tow and the challenge of competing with herself. She announced on Thursday the start date and name of her new show, “Judy Justice,” which will be available weekdays on the little-known IMDb TV, a free streaming service offered by Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Belarus launch massive war games -- worrying NATO...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210909-russia-belarus-launch-massive-war-games-%E2%80%93-worrying-nato</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and Belarus formally opened vast joint military drills on Thursday, a week-long exercise across the territory of both countries and in the Baltic Sea that has alarmed some NATO countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Buckingham:  Steve Nicks Is 'Like Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-features/lindsey-buckingham-fleetwood-mac-stevie-nicks-new-album-1221755/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buckingham on his new solo album and why his dismissal from Fleetwood Mac was the result of the other band members cowering before Stevie Nicks: “It became a little bit like Trump and the Rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art, terror, erections show VR potential at Venice...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210909-art-terror-and-erections-show-vr-potential-at-venice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Art, terror and erections show VR potential at Venice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICK-FIL-A Dealing With Closures As Worker Shortage Continues...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/chick-fil-a-dealing-closures-worker-shortage-continues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Chick-fil-A locations are currently dealing with a current worker shortage. CBS News reported [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Was the First U.S. Covid Death? CDC Investigates 4 Early Cases...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/09/when-was-the-first-u-s-covid-death-c-d-c-investigates-4-early-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late last year, the federal government’s chief statistician on death received word about a tantalizing discovery: Someone had died from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASES 10X TOO HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fauci-no-control-covid-a2572210-dbdb-48b0-aa2e-92e8e9fcd69a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. needs to drop from 160,000 to &lt;10,000 new cases a day to get out of the pandemic phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As 'buy now, pay later' surges, third fall behind on payments...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210909135950-qy1xg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINTECH-CONSUMERS/PAY-LATER (PIX):As 'buy now, pay later' surges, a third of U.S. users fall behind on payments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study links too much free time to lower sense of wellbeing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/sep/09/study-links-too-much-free-time-to-lower-sense-of-wellbeing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research shows there is a ‘sweet spot’ and subjective wellbeing drops off after about five hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America struggling to keep up with other countries in exercise, overall health...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/america-struggling-exercise-health-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight in 10 Americans believe their health is a “work in progress,” and many are now taking steps to improve their lifestyles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos Of NKorea Military Parade Show People Marching In Hazmat Suits...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/siladityaray/2021/09/09/photos-of-north-koreas-national-day-military-parade-show-people-marching-in-hazmat-suits-but-no-ballistic-missiles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The photos of North Korean personnel parading in hazmat suits emerge a week after the country’s leader Kim Jong Un turned down Covid-19 vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MATRIX RESURRECTIONS' Stuns With First Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/matrix-4-trailer-released-1235010322/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Warner Bros. franchise installment will be released theatrically and on HBO Max on Dec. 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX MANDATE FOR ALL FEDERAL WORKERS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/09/politics/joe-biden-covid-speech/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Thursday will impose more stringent vaccine rules on federal workers, and take steps to encourage private businesses to do the same, during a major speech meant to lay out a new approach to combating the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane could hit Los Cabos resorts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-caribbean-floods-storms-hurricanes-38c94cbeccf41ffb49aab906e8737154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Olaf was building toward hurricane force Thursday while on a track toward the Los Cabos resorts at the tip of Mexico's Baja California Peninsula. The U.S, National Hurricane Center said the storm was likely to bring hurricane conditions to the area overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania closest adviser to release book...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/09/politics/stephanie-grisham-book/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Grisham, whose career with the Trump administration included stints as East Wing communications director, White House press secretary and chief of staff to Melania Trump, has written a book that will be released next month, two people familiar with the project tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why everyone wants to punch Jake Paul in face...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/08/jake-paul-knows-you-want-to-see-him-knocked-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high school dropout, who went from social media influencer to Disney star to professional boxing, has courted controversy and negativity wherever he goes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KICKOFF: Brady, BUCS begin defense of title against COWBOYS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-nfl-tom-brady-bruce-arians-tampa-2ebf6cd8abf1261bf8c94ff870d53536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — Lofty, maybe even gargantuan, expectations don’t faze Tom Brady and the Tampa Bay Buccaneers. The reigning Super Bowl champions open the 2021 NFL season against the Dallas Cowboys on Thursday night, confident they have everything it takes — at least on paper — to become the first team to win back-to-back titles since Brady led the 2003 and 2004 New England Patriots to consecutive crowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi crackdown remaking Chinese society...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Xi-s-crackdown-is-remaking-Chinese-society-16445407.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The orders have been sudden, dramatic and often baffling. Last week,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman was late for flight. So she told airline workers there was bomb on plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-woman-was-late-for-her-flight-so-she-told-airline-workers-there-was-a-bomb-on-the-plane-police-say/ar-AAOfu8k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago mother's alleged bomb threat forced an airline to evacuate the plane, delaying the flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device tests for corona in armpit sweat...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210909-thai-device-tests-for-coronavirus-in-armpit-sweat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thai device tests for coronavirus in armpit sweat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffing shortage on Rikers spawning violent beatdowns, wild parties, fatal ODs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/09/staffing-shortage-on-rikers-breeding-beatdowns-and-fatal-ods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffing crisis on Rikers Island has created a dangerous and chaotic situation for inmates that’s allowed inmates to assault each other, fatally overdose and post TikTok videos of themselves part…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Holmes drawn as villain, underdog as trial begins...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elizabeth-holmes-trial-begins-70c62afae356279ef8706b3ac9f5bcae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif. (AP) — Prosecutors and defense attorneys sketched dueling portraits of fallen Silicon Valley star Elizabeth Holmes as her trial got underway Wednesday, alternatively describing her as a greedy villain who faked her way to the top and as a passionate underdog whose spent years trying to shake up the health care industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Could Eventually Collapse, Swedish Central Banker Warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/cryptocurrency-news/bitcoin-could-eventually-collapse-swedish-central-banker-warns-2611490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin Could Eventually Collapse, Swedish Central Banker Warns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau struggles, two weeks before election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20210909-canada-s-trudeau-struggles-two-weeks-before-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triumphant Taliban start putting policies into practice...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210909-triumphant-taliban-start-putting-policies-into-practice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Triumphant Taliban start putting policies into practice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED warns of unpaid leave for staff given religious jab exemptions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/571409-united-airlines-warns-of-unpaid-leave-for-staff-given</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Airlines told its staff on Wednesday that those who are granted religious exemptions from getting vaccinated against the coronavirus will be placed on a temporary unpaid leave,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red states eye Texas abortion law as new model...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/571392-red-states-eye-texas-abortion-law-as-new-model</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican state legislators who oppose abortion rights are eyeing a just-implemented measure in Texas as a model for opening a new front in the war over reproductive choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to deliver six-step plan on pandemic... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210909085925-9os8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BIDEN:Biden to deliver six-step plan on COVID-19 pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proponents of Post-Trump Curbs on Executive Power Prepare New Push...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/09/proponents-of-post-trump-curbs-on-executive-power-prepare-new-push/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As Donald J. Trump’s norm-busting presidency careened through two impeachments, his departure set the stage for lawmakers to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Missouri '2nd Amendment Sanctuary' Fight...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/09/inside-missouris-2nd-amendment-sanctuary-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OZARK, Mo. — Brad Cole is a fiery defender of the Second Amendment, a set-jawed lawman with a lacquered alligator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Jew leaves...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-israel-afghanistan-evacuations-c616b5b847da79f0cfc1de6f0f37b0b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The last member of Afghanistan's Jewish community has left the country. Zebulon Simentov, who lived in a dilapidated synagogue in Kabul, kept kosher and prayed in Hebrew, endured decades of war as the country's centuries-old Jewish community rapidly dwindled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala rallies at critical time...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/2021/09/08/Harris-and-Newsom-align-at-critical-time-as-recall-vote-nears/stories/202109080146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president echoed Mr. Newsom’s campaign message that the outcome will ripple beyond the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen triggers alarm bells over debt ceiling cliff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/571413-yellen-triggers-alarm-bells-over-debt-ceiling-cliff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen is setting off alarm bells over a looming brawl about the nation's borrowing limit that could spark a global economic crisis if Congress fails to take action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CIGAR!</title>
      <link>https://heavy.com/entertainment/monica-lewinsky-cigar-bill-clinton-brand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;heavy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment: American Crime Story" aims to paint a more nuanced portrait of the Bill Clinton and Monica Lewinsky sex scandal and the resulting impeachment process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL 'cyber grave robbers' charged with condo collapse ID theft...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/three-charged-with-stealing-identities-florida-condo-collapse-victims-2021-09-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man and two women were arrested and charged with stealing the identities of seven victims of the Surfside condominium collapse near Miami Beach this summer and attempting to obtain credit cards in their names, a Florida prosecutor said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA on mission -- to get more social media followers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/08/the-cias-on-a-mission-to-get-more-social-media-followers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CIA wants to crack the code to Instagram popularity to soften up its shadowy image as part of a quirky new public relations campaign.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
