<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Journalists struggle to keep online threats from escalating...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/journalists-struggle-keep-online-threats-escalating-030708079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — After a Florida radio station's general manager told hosts they didn't have to put an obnoxious repeat caller on the air a couple of months ago, the man stood on the sidewalk outside and vented his irritation with the station through a bullhorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding wildfires in West...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/07/04/exploding-wildfires-in-us-west-derail-holiday-plans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing swath of wildfires in western United States threatens to damper holiday plans as park rangers and fire officials across the region have greatly curtailed accessibility to National Parks and campgrounds to increase public safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will tell NATO nations USA cannot be world piggy bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-nato/trump-will-tell-nato-nations-us-cannot-be-the-worlds-piggy-bank-idUSKBN1JT2XD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will tell fellow NATO countries at next week's summit that the United States cannot be "the world's piggy bank," White House spokesman Hogan Gidley said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islamic State says leader's son killed in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59698eff72214974bc8f91ac17addbd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — The Islamic State group says the son of its leader has been killed fighting Syrian government forces.        The announcement of the death of the young son of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's president-elect shuns guards, asks 'people' for protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics-security/mexicos-president-elect-shuns-guards-asks-people-for-protection-idUSKBN1JU04E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President-elect Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador left the country's national palace on Tuesday in the front passenger seat of a white Volkswagen Jetta, swarmed by hundreds of jubilant supporters including one waving a live rooster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman, 92, killed 72-year-old son...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/region-northeast-valley/fountain-hills/mcso-92-year-old-refuses-assisted-living-shoots-and-kills-son-in-fountain-hills</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 92-year-old woman is facing multiple charges after she allegedly shot and killed her son in Fountain Hills Monday because she refused to be admitted into an assisted living facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life, liberty and the pursuit of hot dogs...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/u-birthday-life-liberty-pursuit-hot-dogs-080605135--mlb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fireworks, music and the pursuit of hot dogs will mark the 242nd year of independence for the United States on what is expected to be a steamy Wednesday in much of the country. The Independence Day holiday, which brings out crowds from small towns to big cities, is also a time when law enforcement agencies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART takes heat as it removes 'Impeach 45' shirts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/walmart-takes-heat-removes-impeach-trump-shirts-202917261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart on Tuesday removed shirts and other gear from its online marketplace bearing the phrase "Impeach 45" after supporters of US President Donald Trump lambasted the retail giant on social media. Walmart nixed the items after images of jerseys and baby gear with the anti-Trump slogan went</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans celebrating Fourth of July face scorcher...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/americans-celebrating-fourth-of-july-face-scorcher/ar-AAzz5rn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortage of vets spells misery for zoo animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/shortage-vets-spells-misery-karachi-zoo-animals-034916299.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Management have been pushing the city council to approve a third veterinary position for the zoo's population, including lions, tigers, elephants, chimpanzees, birds and reptiles. "This is unfortunate, that the zoo is heavily understaffed and thus not able to take good care of the animals,&amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  From cash-strapped roommates to AIRBNB billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cash-strapped-roommates-airbnb-billionaires-033859101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade ago a pair of San Francisco roommates decided to make rent money by using air mattresses to turn their place into a bed-and-breakfast when a conference in the city made hotel rooms scarce. The brainwave led to the creation of Airbnb, a startup now valued at more than $30 billion which boasts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare US independence declaration found...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rare-us-independence-declaration-found-uk-archive-111216150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare parchment copy of the American Declaration of Independence has been found at a British archive among the papers of an aristocrat who supported the rebels, officials have said. The manuscript was discovered at the West Sussex Record Office in the southern English city of Chichester by a team of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns Trump against trade war...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/merkel-warns-trump-against-trade-war-101839767.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel on Wednesday warned US President Donald Trump against unleashing an all-out trade war after he threatened to impose steep tariffs on cars from the European Union. In a speech to the Bundestag federal parliament, Merkel said both sides were effectively locked in a "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHATSAPP 'horrified' over India lynchings, promises action...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/india-slams-whatsapp-over-deadly-rumours-050022052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WhatsApp said Wednesday it was "horrified" by a spate of lynchings in India sparked by false rumours shared on its platform as the government accused the messaging service of irresponsibility. More than 20 people have been killed in India in the last two months, according to media reports,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan to be sworn in with new powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-sworn-monday-powers-105106231.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Recep Tayyip Erdogan will on Monday be sworn in for a second mandate as Turkey's head of state after his election triumph last month, assuming sweeping powers granted under a new constitution, a presidential source said. Erdogan, who has dominated Turkey first as premier from 2003 then</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuts may boost male fertility...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nuts-may-boost-male-fertility-study-111927092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eating nuts "significantly" boosted the number and health of sperm in young men in a scientific trial, researchers said Wednesday. The findings "support a beneficial role for chronic nut consumption in sperm quality," they said, but stressed the study participants were all healthy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Becoming Kingmaker In Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-endorsements-boost-other-left-democratic-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Democratic insurgent candidate has raised the profile of a number of other challengers around the country—leading to significant fundraising boons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK police probing 6 assault claims against Kevin Spacey...</title>
      <link>https://in.news.yahoo.com/uk-police-probing-6-assault-claims-against-kevin-103306486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British police are investigating six claims of sexual assault or assault by Academy Award-winning actor Kevin Spacey, three more than previously disclosed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK anti-terror police join 'unknown substance' probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/british-police-2-people-critical-near-poisoned-spy-050512731.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMESBURY, England (AP) — British counterterrorism police were investigating Wednesday after two people were left in critical condition, exposed to an unknown substance a few miles from where a former Russian spy and his daughter were poisoned with a nerve agent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US World Cup ratings down 42% without American team...</title>
      <link>https://in.news.yahoo.com/us-world-cup-ratings-down-42-percent-without-143824342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The lack of a U.S. team caused a big viewership drop for World Cup telecasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refugee who fled violence mourns daughter slain in Idaho...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/family-friend-says-slain-birthday-girl-mothers-shadow-012909096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little Ruya Kadir had sparkling eyes, a few basic belongings and not much else when she arrived in Boise, Idaho more than two years ago. Bifituu's home was "always a monument to Ruya," full of things the child loved, Schwab said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viral vid of woman's arrest sparks anger, but LAPD says involved in violent kidnapping plot...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-kidnapping-suspect-viral-video-20180702-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many have criticized a viral video that shows several Los Angeles police officers pointing guns at an unarmed woman. Authorities said the woman was involved in a kidnapping and believed to be armed and dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81-year-old runs for life, survives 1000-sting bee attack!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/neighborhood/cleveland/news/article/Tarkington-man-survives-aggressive-bee-attack-13047416.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tarkington man is recovering from an aggressive bee attack that resulted in more than 1,000 bee stings. Tom Mizell, 81, known for his roadside vegetable stand on CR 2224 in Tarkington, says he was mowing a field on CR 2184 just off of FM 2518 on June 26 when he was attacked by bees. "I was running a dozer in the woods, helping my cousin clear a right-of-way for a fence. All of a sudden, I saw a black cloud of bees surrounding me," he said. "I jumped off the dozer, which happened to be in neutral. I left it running and took off through the woods, trying to make my way to a little lake I had dug on the property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphones WATCHING everything you do?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/7/3/17531698/conspiracy-theory-facebook-android-phone-listening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a new conspiracy theory in town</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business owner charged after scamming a scammer...</title>
      <link>http://www.wmur.com/article/police-woman-admits-swapping-items-in-scammers-shipment/22029218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wolfeboro police said a woman who didn't realize she was getting herself in the middle of an international scam allegedly tried to pull one over on another criminal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC CHAIR: OCASIO-CORTEZ IS THE FUTURE!</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/395436-dnc-chair-ocasio-cortez-represents-the-future-of-our-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic National Committee (DNC) Chairman Tom Perez said Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez represents the “future of our party” on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish charity attaches GPS to migrating stork... Bird flies to Sudan, where someone steals SIM card to run up huge phone bill...</title>
      <link>http://www.euronews.com/2018/07/03/roaming-stork-lands-polish-charity-with-huge-phone-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone removed a SIM card from a GPS tracker placed on a stork's back to clock in 20 hours of phone calls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbaric jihadists ban plastic bags -- 'to protect Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6690062/al-shabaab-bans-plastic-bags/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of the world’s most barbaric terrorist organisations has banned plastic bags – because they believe they harm life on Earth. The Somali terror group al-Shabaab, known for butchering thous…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God Male or Gender-Neutral? Episcopal Convention Debates...</title>
      <link>http://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/us/2018/july/is-god-male-or-gender-neutral-episcopal-church-begins-debate-on-book-of-common-prayer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Episcopal Church is debating about overhauling its Book of Common Prayer, which is used in Episcopal congregations worldwide. The debate centers on making sure that prayers in the book are clear that God is not male, but doesn't have a gender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Stand For Flag' Song 'Censored' On Social...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/tech/2018/07/03/facebook-slammed-for-censorship-country-groups-patriotic-song.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has been slammed by The Wes Cook Band for preventing the country group from using the social network’s paid tools to promote its song “I Stand for the Flag.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK a publisher? Publicly says no, but tells court YES...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jul/02/facebook-mark-zuckerberg-platform-publisher-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In its defense against a former app startup, Facebook is contradicting its long-held claim to be simply a neutral platform</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey gives state-funding to local news...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/02/new-jersey-state-funded-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Power Use at Highest Levels in Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-03/the-heat-wave-has-u-s-power-use-at-the-highest-levels-in-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heat wave roasting the U.S. East Coast may be slowing down U.S. stock trading and foiling July 4 road trips. But it’s the best friend of power market bulls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon stops posting troop numbers for Iraq, Syria and Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/07/03/625544265/pentagon-questioned-over-war-zone-numbers-blackout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon has stopped reporting troop levels for Afghanistan, Iraq and Syria following President Trump's declaration that the U.S. would not talk about troop numbers in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girlfriend burns down home because man went to see another woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/cobb-fire-woman-burns-down-home-because-man-went-see-another-woman/D7atxQtN2au9X873OUxbQI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was in Cobb County jail Tuesday morning for allegedly burning down a house because a man went to see another woman. Earnica Lowe, 32, faces a felony arson count after Cobb fire investigators say she lit the home on fire June 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After fish pedicure, woman loses toenails...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/03/health/fish-pedicure-toenail-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a young woman's toenails started to separate from her toes, a doctor finally zeroed in on the reason: a fish pedicure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup ratings in USA down 42%...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/sports/la-sp-world-cup-updates-20180612-world-cup-tv-ratings-in-the-u-s-are-1530639130-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lack of a U.S. team caused a big viewership drop for World Cup telecasts. The 48 group stage telecasts on Fox and FS1 averaged 2,069,000 viewers, according to Nielsen Media Research. That is down 42 percent from the 3.54 million average on ESPN, ESPN2 and ABC four years ago and down 15 percen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel cancels peace prize concert for lack of funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nobel-cancels-peace-prize-concert-lack-funds-165646280.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The traditional concert after the annual awarding of the Nobel Peace Prize on December 10 in Oslo will not be staged this year due to financial difficulties, the organisers said Tuesday. "There will be no Nobel Peace Prize concert" in 2018, said a statement from the Nobel Institute, Warner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 NEW SPACEY SEX ASSAULTS INVESTIGATED...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/03/kevin-spacey-new-london-sexual-assaults-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey is now being investigated for 6 sexual assaults in London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33 neglected shih tzus found in sweltering Manhattan apartment...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-metro-malnourished-dogs-owner-charged-20180703-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty-three malnourished shih tzus were rescued from an overheated Manhattan apartment when police showed up and arrested their owner on animal cruetly charges, police said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethiopia new PM meets humanoid robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8012fe4a0124485c8c57d8d56bcc7521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADDIS ABABA, Ethiopia (AP) — In one of the world's more unusual diplomatic encounters, Ethiopia's new prime minister has met with a humanoid robot.        The chief of staf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife sliced off cheating husband's penis, threw out window...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/03/wife-says-she-sliced-off-cheating-husbands-penis-then-threw-it-out-the-window/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jealous wife has been arrested after allegedly hacking off her husband’s penis Tuesday with a 12-inch-long carving knife. Karuna Sanusan, 24, carried out the bloody attack on 40-year-old Siripan …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRONES REPLACE FIREWORKS IN WEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/news/2018/07/03/drones-replace-july-4th-fireworks-western-towns-worried-wildfires/752966002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Towns in California, Colorado and Arizona – facing another season of drought and wildfire – are turning to drone shows as a less risky alternative to organized fireworks, encouraged by the development of jaw-dropping, choreographed shows such as the one Intel put on at the Winter Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service Officer Assaulted Outside White House After Immigration Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/investigations/Man-Assaulted-Secret-Service-Officer-Outside-White-House-After-Immigration-Rally-Feds-487224761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Secret Service officer was injured in an assault while on patrol outside the White House on Saturday shortly after the major immigration rally in Lafayette Park, according to newly filed federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfer misses key tourney after airline loses clubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2018/07/03/graeme-mcdowell-misses-open-qualifier-airline-loses-golf-clubs/754037002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graeme McDowell, the 2010 U.S. Open winner, said on Twitter that he was forced to withdraw from an Open qualifier after Air France misplaced his golf clubs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas tries spying with fake dating apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/edc3fe2d11064d4aa16936b991d5b3db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — The Israeli military said Tuesday it had uncovered a plot by Hamas militants to spy on soldiers by befriending them on social media and then luring them in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snow Blankets Northern Rockies Before July Fourth...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/weather/news/2018-07-03-snow-in-july-montana-idaho-northern-rockies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The calendar might say "July," but in some spots, it looks more like winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Testosterone pushes men to luxury brands...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/testosterone-pushes-men-luxury-brands-study-163420875.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A single dose of testosterone steers men towards luxury brands of cars, watches, pens, or clothes which, like stag anglers and peacock tails, signal "status" to the female gender, scientists said Tuesday. The sex hormone, it turns out, is a major influencer of male consumer behaviour, according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overtime work for women increases diabetes risk...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2018/07/overtime-work-may-increase-diabetes-risk-in-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working overtime may help your paycheck and give you a leg up in the office, but a new study suggests that women who log too many hours may have an increased the risk of diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Turn Violent In Front Of Philly ICE Building...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/07/03/protests-turn-violent-as-demonstrators-arrested-in-front-of-philadelphia-ice-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protests are taking place in front of the ICE office on 8th and Cherry Streets in Center City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bartiromo Crushes CNBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2018/07/03/crushing-it-maria-bartiromo-beats-squawk-box-as-fox-business-sweeps-cnbc-in-q2-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We have great momentum and will continue crushing it,' Bartiromo says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania secret trip to visit injured service members...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/57e8b8bed73d4255aeb2683de5aef79a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Melania Trump has made another secret trip, though this one was carried out closer to home.        The first lady is visiting wounded service members at W</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS executioner who BURNED soldiers alive SHOT DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/713848/isis-execution-video-turkey-soldiers-burned-alive-killed-bounty-abu-talha-al-turki-syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Reassigns Reporter Who Had Sex Relationship With Senate Aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/new-york-times-reassigns-ali-watkins-reporter-sexual-relationship-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"For a reporter to have an intimate relationship with someone he or she covers is unacceptable," says executive editor Dean Baquet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ABOLISH ICE' Vandals Throw Brick Through Window Of Republican Office...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/03/abolish-ice-vandals-nebraska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Party blames 'increasingly radical rhetoric of national Democrat leaders'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART boycott launched after outcry over 'Impeach 45' clothing...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/2018/07/03/walmart-boycott-campaign-launches-after-outcry-over-impeach-45-clothing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart drew outrage Monday after it was discovered that the superstore was selling “Impeach 45” apparel on its website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminally ill dogs at canine hospice treated to steak dinners, trips to MCDONALD'S and birthday parties in their final days...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/terminally-ill-dogs-canine-hospice-12842554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former nurse Nicola Coyle runs the Grey Muzzle Canine Hospice Project in Mansfield - thought to be the first of its kind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREWORKS COSTING MORE THIS YEAR...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/03/washington-dc-4th-july-fireworks-price/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government is shelling out more dough on the National Mall 4th of July fireworks this year ... $30k more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS PRICES HIT HOUSEHOLDS</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Oil-Prices/This-Is-How-Much-US-Households-Lose-As-Gas-Prices-Rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. households are feeling the pinch and are expected to have around $440 less disposable income as higher gasoline prices are offsetting part of the tax cuts from earlier this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Serial Killer Arrested After Death of Eight Babies at Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/suspected-serial-killer-arrested-in-britain-after-death-of-eight-babies-in-hospital?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health-care worker has been arrested on suspicion of murdering eight infants and trying to kill six more at a hospital in northwest England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man threatens to burn down TV station, calls journalist 'dead man walking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article214251504.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Eric Bewley, 47, is charged with transmitting threats through interstate communications, a federal crime, after authorities say he threatened to burn down Texas TV station KBTX and called the general manager 'a dead man walking.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin court OKs unconscious drunk drivers' blood draws...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wisconsin-court-oks-unconscious-drunk-drivers-blood-draws-140047075.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — The Wisconsin state Supreme Court says police can legally draw blood from unconscious drunken drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenpeace activists 'crash' drone into nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/greenpeace-activists-crash-drone-french-nuclear-plant-134507827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenpeace activists said Tuesday they had flown a drone fitted out as a flying Superman into a nuclear energy plant in southeast France, aiming to show how the country's reactors are vulnerable to terror attacks. A video released by the environmental group shows the drone zipping through restricted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vampire' killer caught after seen drinking blood of victim...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5912437/Vampire-killer-caught-seen-drinking-blood-woman-throat-slit-Zimbabwe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Sibanda struck his elderly victim several times with a log in Sikhewu village before allegedly cutting her throat with a sharp implement. A passerby saw him sucking her wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Surgeons argue, flirt, throw things while patients under the knife...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5912371/Medics-fight-flirt-throw-things-patients-knife-study-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Emory University in Atlanta, Georgia have revealed medical staff dance to music and quarrel with one another to gain status while operating on unconscious patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Arnold's bonkers strategy for nailing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/07/03/tom-arnolds-bonkers-strategy-for-nailing-trump-218944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-energy comedian says he knows exactly how to take down the president. Now, if he could only get his hands on one little tape.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
