<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HARD TIME:  California's jails are so bad some inmates beg to go to prison instead...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/california-s-jails-are-so-bad-some-inmates-beg-to/article_f7903d65-f147-5593-b8a9-8519370d5a31.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Ever since he stole his first car at age 10, Cody Garland has spent much of his life behind bars. Now 35, he has served time at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craddock was violent with co-workers before Virginia Beach rampage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/02/dewayne-craddock-had-been-getting-violent-with-co-workers-before-virginia-beach-shooting-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman who shot dead 12 people at a Virginia Beach municipal building had been facing disciplinary action for a violent fight at work, according to a report. DeWayne Craddock, 40, was still emp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On eve of UK visit, Trump denies 'nasty' Meghan Markle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eve-uk-visit-trump-denies-taped-remark-nasty-162350215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump denied on Sunday that he had called Meghan Markle "nasty" just days before heading to Britain to be hosted, and lavishly feted, by other members of the royal family. Trump's tweet Sunday came a day before his three-day state visit is to begin with a pomp-filled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass shootings transform how America talks, prays, prepares...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/73d3cdd6ee5643449bab86c3fe301ce8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Pardeep Singh Kaleka has surveyed the landscape of an America scarred by mass shootings. Seven years ago, a white supremacist invaded a Sikh temple in Wisconsin and killed six...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More turning to 'La Bestia'...</title>
      <link>http://www.hastingstribune.com/despite-perils-more-u-s--bound-migrants-are-turning/article_fa8bbb08-4321-5f01-add7-1579ea41bab1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARRIAGA, Mexico — They gathered at dawn in this railyard in southern Mexico, contemplating their next move: catching a ride on the roof of La Bestia (the Beast) — the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE:  'ROCKETMAN'   does less biz than 'BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/06/godzilla-king-of-the-monsters-rocketman-ma-opening-weekend-box-office-1202624876/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;5TH WRITETHRU SATURDAY AM after FRIDAY 11:06PM post: Godzilla: King of the Monsters has slowed down significantly, from the $24M opening day that many were seeing midday Friday to an estimated $19.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Cruise ship slams into Venice wharf as tourists flee... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cruise-ship-loses-control-slams-venice-wharf-tourist-102753489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive cruise ship lost control as it docked in Venice on Sunday, crashing into the wharf and hitting a tourist boat after suffering an engine failure. Tourists on land could be seen running away as the 13-deck MSC Opera scraped along the dockside, its engine blaring, before knocking into a tourist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-in-10 Aliens Released Not Showing Up to Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/30/nearly-nine-in-ten-illegal-aliens-recently-released-into-u-s-not-showing-up-to-court-hearings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 9-in-10 illegal aliens recently released into the U.S. while they await their asylum hearings are not showing up to their court dates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Syria after rockets fired at Golan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-attacks-syria-over-rockets-fired-mount-hermon-045107419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel carried out air strikes in Syria on Sunday in response to rare rocket fire from the neighbouring country, its military said, with a war monitor reporting 10 killed including Syrian soldiers and foreign fighters. In response, the army attacked "two Syrian artillery batteries, a number of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Large group from AFRICA wades across Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-first-large-group-from-africa-wades-across-rio-grande-into-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of illegals from Angola, Cameroon and Congo waded across the Rio Grande River and into the United States, video from Customs and Border Protection shows. The video shows male and female adults walking through the water and into Texas, several with children on their shoulders. U.S. Border Patrol agents assigned to Del Rio …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid USS McCain controversy, Pentagon says military will not be politicized...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190602095909-3cd5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MILITARY/TRUMP-POLITICS (CORRECTED):REFILE-Amid USS McCain controversy, Pentagon says military will not be politicized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians say U.S. 'deal of century' will finish off their state...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190602064302-zdxhp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MIDEAST/PLAN (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-Palestinians say U.S. 'deal of the century' will finish off their state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARABS RIOT AS JEWS ARE ALLOWED TO ENTER TEMPLE MOUNT ON JERUSALEM DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Jews-allowed-to-enter-Temple-Mount-on-Jerusalem-Day-riots-break-out-591341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the police attempted to enter the place, Arab worshipers began throwing stones, chairs and other objects at the forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contagion Puts Markets on Alert for Fresh Risk Selloff...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/trade-war-contagion-puts-markets-on-alert-for-fresh-risk-selloff-1.1267370</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXED OUT:  BOEING Faces Doubtful Airline Chiefs in Mission to Restore Faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/boeing-faces-doubtful-airline-chiefs-in-mission-to-restore-faith-1.1267366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi met with cries of 'impeach'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/446505-pelosi-met-with-cries-of-impeach-at-california-democratic-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) was met with chants of "impeach" during her remarks at the California Democratic Party's convention on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAYOR OF LONDONISTAN CALLS TRUMP 'FASCIST'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/01/donald-trump-like-20th-century-fascist-says-sadiq-khan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London mayor hits out at US president before his state visit to Britain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president hints at migration 'concessions' to avoid tariffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/01/mexican-president-hints-at-migration-concessions-to-defuse-trade-spat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's president on Saturday hinted his country could tighten migration controls to defuse U.S. President Donald Trump's threat to impose tariffs on Mexican goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to announce re-election bid at Orlando rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/politics/president-trumps-2020-campaign-rents-out-amway-center-for-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump re-election campaign has rented the Amway Center for a June 18 event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India heatwave temperatures pass 123&amp;#176;! </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-heatwave-temperatures-pass-50-celsius-204506312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures passed 50 degrees Celsius (122 Fahrenheit) in northern India as an unrelenting heatwave triggered warnings of water shortages and heatstroke. The thermometer hit 50.6 degrees Celsius (123 Fahrenheit) in the Rajasthan desert city of Churu on Saturday, the weather department said. All of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store in crosshairs as APPLE courts developers... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/app-store-crosshairs-apple-courts-developers-034045451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is set to court software savants at its annual developers conference beginning Monday while contending with criticism that the iPhone maker has made its App Store a walled garden. The App Store is the lone shop for content for Apple devices, with the technology giant deciding which software creations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wide range of emotions underscores challenge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be19ecb4078b4f62919a53eab912059c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YORKTOWN, Va. (AP) — In suburban Philadelphia, it took a little more than eight minutes into the question-and-answer session at freshman Rep. Madeleine Dean's town hall before someone asked about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Syria after rockets fired at Golan...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190602050300-olupk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-CRISIS/ISRAEL-SYRIA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Israel strikes Syria after rockets fired at Golan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration oversees five-year high in approved citizenship applications...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/31/dhs-says-citizenship-approvals-rose-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security reached a five-year high in approvals of citizenship applications last year, and swore in more people as naturalized citizens as well, according to the new statistical report released Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON FACES ANTITRUST</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Amazon-could-face-heightened-antitrust-scrutiny-13916551.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon could face heightened antitrust scrutiny under a new agreement between U.S. regulators that puts it under closer watch by the Federal Trade Commission, three people familiar with the matter said.  The move is the result of the FTC and the Department of Justice, the U.S. government's leading antitrust enforcement agencies, quietly divvying up competition oversight of two of the country's top tech companies, according to those people, who spoke on the condition of anonymity because the government's work is confidential. The Justice Department is set to have more jurisdiction over Google, The Washington Post reported on Friday, paving the way for a potential investigation of the search-and-advertising giant.  The FTC's plans for Amazon and the Justice Department's interest in Google are not immediately clear. But the kind of arrangement brokered between the Justice Department and the FTC typically presages more serious antitrust scrutiny, the likes of which many Democrats and Republicans on Capitol Hill have sought out of fear that tech companies have become too big and powerful.  The Justice Department this week declined to comment, citing a policy against confirming or denying investigations. The FTC also declined to comment. Amazon did not immediately have comment. (Jeff Bezos, the founder and chief executive of Amazon, owns The Washington Post.)  "If there is an active discussion of where the boundaries are, that would indicate there's a reason for that discussion, whether it's a new interest, study or investigation," said Maureen Ohlhausen, a partner at the law firm Baker Botts who previously served as chair of the FTC.  The early moves from the government's twin antitrust agencies mark the latest attempts by U.S. regulators to better supervise tech giants. Earlier this year, the FTC established a special task...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES PAGE ONE SUNDAY:  For U.S. and China, it's not trade war anymore  -- it's something worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-us-china-trade-stalemate-20190531-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the U.S. and China, trade tensions are just part of a rapidly deteriorating relationship. Harsh talk of a "clash of civilizations" is becoming a new norm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Takes Down Accounts Ahead of Tiananmen Anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2019/06/01/twitter-china-takedown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has suspended a large number of Chinese-language user accounts, including those belonging to critics of China’s government. It seems like a particularly ill-timed move, occurring just days before thirtieth anniversary of the Tiananmen Square massacre on June 4. “A large number o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite warnings, Guatemalans say they won't stop coming...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/01/government-warnings-cant-turn-back-migrants-from-guatemala/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN CRISTOBAL DE TOTONICAPAN, Guatemala — Dressed in a bright orange shirt, Francisco Gomez yells and uses his arms to vigorously direct the myriad souped-up buses at the crossroads known as Cuatro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Biden absent, his rivals pounce at California gathering...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bc131de0d434bbca127d04761520823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Democratic presidential hopefuls took rival Joe Biden's absence at a California state party gathering Saturday as a chance to take subtle digs at the former vice president and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUFF?  Threatening Mexico With Tariffs...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-move-forward-mexico-tariffs-objections-top-advisors/story?id=63426946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's top advisors have opposed the tariffs against Mexico, which will begin at 5% and move up each month.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
