<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>In a rare admission, MTV says its programming offers dim view of mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/In-a-rare-admission-MTV-says-its-programming-16070434.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI ON THE BRINK:  Pivotal Islamic leader demands change in Israel after vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/pivotal-islamic-leader-demands-change-in-israel-after-vote/ar-BB1fdwlh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of a conservative Islamic party who has emerged as a kingmaker following Israel's latest inconclusive election called for change Thursday, without endorsing Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu or his rivals. Mansour Abbas's primetime address was carried live by multiple Israeli broadcasters, underscoring his pivotal role in determining whether a stable governing coalition is possible after last week's election. The vote, Israel's fourth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food delivery apps add to pandemic pounds, exempt from posting nutrition information...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/food-delivery-apps-are-exempt-from-posting-nutrition-information-this-loophole-has-added-to-our-pandemic-pounds-advocates-say/ar-BB1fdBUd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA has given third-party food delivery apps a free pass not to post calorie counts. Americans’ health has suffered, advocates say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showed Off Photos of Naked Women on House Floor?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/matt-gaetz-reportedly-showed-fellow-lawmakers-naked-pictures-of-women-he-slept-with/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-FL) allegedly showed fellow lawmakers photos of naked women on the House floor, claiming to have had sex with them, according to a new report from CNN. The flamboyantly pro-Trump congressman found himself at the center of controversy this week after it was reported that he was under a Justice Department investigation […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisoner admits to murdering serial killer, calls it 'mission for avenging' his victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9425671/California-prisoner-confesses-strangling-5-Strangler-five-page-letter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Budrow, 40 (left), claimed he murdered the notorious killer Roger Kibbe, 81, (top right) in a five-page letter he titled 'Ascension … May Their Souls Go To Heaven.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Smallpox 'virus squads' and mandatory vaccinations upheld by Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Smallpox-virus-squads-and-mandatory-16070603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;E. Edwin Spencer had no way of knowing he would be making history that day when he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES +17% FOR WEEK IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-cases-infections-hospital-variants-d0f5850c-6098-431c-b38c-55b82cce2b8c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases are up 17% over last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF:  Pandemic sharpens inequalities, could fuel unrest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-sharpens-inequalities-could-fuel-191859446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has worsened long-standing inequalities around the world, which left unaddressed could undermine economic stability and lead to unrest, the IMF warned on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost one in seven suffers long Covid...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-covid-uk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one in seven Britons who tested positive for COVID-19 continued to have symptoms for at least 12 weeks, according to a UK study released Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Judge blocks sales of Lil Nas X 'Satan shoes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/1/lil-nas-x-satan-shoes-sales-blocked-federal-judge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Satan shoe can go to hell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Abby: Husband turned on by amputation!</title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/life/2021/03/dear-abby-wife-is-unsettled-by-mans-obsession-with-amputation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He recently told me that not only does he find amputees attractive, but he wants to be one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell claims treatment in prison 'fit for Hannibal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9428619/Ghislaine-Maxwell-claims-treatment-prison-fit-Hannibal-Lecter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislane Maxwell claims that the prison conditions as she awaits trial would be appropriate for the fictional serial killer in The Silence of the Lambs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She-Wees', Plastic Bags: AMAZON Pee Scandal Much Worse for Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akd54e/she-wees-and-plastic-bags-amazons-pee-scandal-is-much-worse-for-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon delivery drivers describe the great lengths they’ve gone to to pee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Messy Breakup of OnlyFans Model and Her Uber-Wealthy Boyfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/04/inside-the-messy-litigious-breakup-of-an-onlyfans-model-and-her-uber-wealthy-boyfriend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Cloobeck says he was fleeced by the woman he loved. Stefanie Gurzanski says her ex is trying to ruin her life. Both have lawyered up, and are taking the explosion of their romance public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Foreign Billionaire Funneled Cash to American Political Campaigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.opensecrets.org/news/2021/04/straw-donor-scheme-foreign-billionaire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.opensecrets.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Lebanese-Nigerian billionaire conspired to route illegal foreign contributions into U.S. elections in a straw donor scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  18 massage therapists defend star NFL QB as 'professional,' 'polite'...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/local/massage-therapists-defend-deshaun-watson-rusty-hardin-says/285-b5c7d715-b93d-47f1-9d7c-677434348d79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He was respectful in every session," one woman said. "I never had any issues with him being inappropriate." The statements were released by attorney Rusty Hardin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock pics of home where hoarder found MUMMIFIED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2623745/pictures-evelyn-sakash-designer-hoarder-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING pictures of the home where a hoarder was found mummified under garbage after neighbors noticed a small have been released. Evelyn Sakash, 66, was found by cops in her New York City home on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba erects giant concrete flag in front of US embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210401-cuba-erects-giant-concrete-flag-in-front-of-us-embassy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba erects giant concrete flag in front of US embassy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New test and trace rules for pubs mean EVERYONE as to sign in...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14525657/new-test-trace-rules-pubs-everyone-over-16-sign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW test and trace rules for pubs mean that EVERYONE over 16 has to sign in. UK pub industry reps have today accused the Government of “stealthy backsliding on pub reopening rules”. 🦠 R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's 'Transformative' Plan Redefines Infrastructure to Include Caregiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/economy/biden-infrastructure-plan-caregiver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden wants to put $400 billion toward expanding quality home or community care. Ai-jen Poo tells The Nation that’s “historic” progress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman injected with 'empty syringe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.13newsnow.com/article/news/health/coronavirus/vaccine/norfolk-cvs-injects-woman-with-empty-syringe-instead-of-covid-19-shot/291-e2b4cb59-a6db-4235-8310-7370cd3729b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.13newsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A company spokesperson said a patient was "inadvertently injected with an empty syringe." She was asked to return to the store to get an actual shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden rejects pioneering test to dim sunlight reaching Earth
...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210331165317-oulyk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure by Saami indigenous people and environmentalists lies behind the decision to halt the controversial test, advocacy groups say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent who infiltrated NRA, visits Navalny in jail, with video cameras in tow...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/maria-butina-russian-agent-who-infiltrated-nra-visits-navalny-in-jail-with-video-cameras-in-tow/ar-BB1fdmth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Butina, reporting for a Kremlin-funded TV network, was reportedly berated by Navalny in front of other inmates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police disperse thousands at Belgian April Fool party...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401173954-c2vbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BELGIUM-PARTY (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Police disperse thousands at Belgian April Fool party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islamist turned Israeli kingmaker offers olive branch to rightist Jews...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401172352-knp89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/ (TV, PIX):Islamist turned Israeli kingmaker offers olive branch to rightist Jews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in Michigan Alarms Health Experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/covid-surge-in-michigan-alarms-health-experts/ar-BB1fcc6X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT — In a rural stretch of Michigan along the shore of Lake Huron, coronavirus outbreaks are ripping through churches, schools and restaurants where the virus has infected line cooks and waitresses. For more than a week, ambulances have taken several hourlong trips each day to rush severely ill coronavirus patients to hospitals in Detroit, Saginaw or Port Huron, where beds in intensive-care units await. Even as the pandemic appears to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario imposes four-week 'shutdown'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/ontario-imposes-four-week-provincewide-shutdown-to-combat-spike-in-covid-19-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Naked man strolling street at 1 AM doing 'walk of shame' for cheating on wife...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/walk-of-shame-bust-659201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 1--A man who police saw strolling naked this morning on a South Carolina street told officers that he was doing a “walk of shame” as penance for cheating on his wife, according to an arrest rep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales of BENTLEYS and LAMBORGHINIS booming...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/01/success/luxury-car-sales-pandemic-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been a great time to be selling really, really expensive cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At China genomics giant, line between biotech and Beijing blurry...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/04/01/bgi-china-genomics-giant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even the company’s biggest advocates in the West acknowledge that, institutionally, BGI is in many ways a chimera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii mulls passports for inter-island passage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/medical-advances/546019-hawaii-considers-vaccine-passports-for-inter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii state officials are looking into state-level steps to implement vaccine passports for inter-island travel, local outlets report this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FM says relations with West have 'hit bottom'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-moscow-vladimir-putin-sergey-lavrov-europe-04329cd1a5894ec00920e2a292181487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia's top diplomat said Thursday that the country's relations with the United States and its allies have “hit the bottom” and no date has been set for sending the Russian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix previews what's to come for dying malls: Rezoning, new uses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/01/macerich-sale-of-arizona-mall-hints-at-whats-to-come-for-dying-malls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The land surrounding the Paradise Valley Mall in Phoenix has been rezoned, to create a new development with homes and offices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No apology. No outrage. No one cares about Kevin Durant 'Homophobic' DMs...</title>
      <link>https://deadspin.com/no-one-seems-to-care-that-kevin-durant-is-a-homophobe-1846597309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadspin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I made jokes about it yesterday, and that’s really all the effort I was prepared to give it. And yet, another day rolled by after Michael Rapaport (who I assume just walked off the set of another charity MTV softball game as that’s still what he does, right?) revealed the heinous and disgusting messages that Durant had left him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Star Draymond Green Attacks Female Athletes Fighting for Equal Pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/nba-star-draymond-green-attacks-female-athletes-fighting-for-equal-pay-im-really-tired-of-seeing-them-complain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Golden State Warriors star Draymond Green launched into a rant against female athletes "complaining" for equal play, arguing that they were not putting in enough effort to in their fight for equity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden unveils 'once-in-a generation' infrastructure plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article250358836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A map from Amtrak shows where you could see new routes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservationists fury after SPACEX rocket explodes sending debris onto wildlife reserve...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9426381/Conservationists-fury-SpaceX-rocket-exploded-sending-debris-wildlife-reserve.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX workers are continuing to recover fragments of Tuesday's doomed rocket from a nature reserve as conservationists blasted Elon Musk for the danger it posed to wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's former bodyguard breaks silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9406533/Donald-Trumps-ex-bodyguard-tells-ex-president-owes-130-McDonalds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin McKay worked for Donald Trump for five years before being fired in 2012 for refusing agree to a series of outrageous demands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  15M J&amp;J DOSES BOTCHED BY HUMAN ERROR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/virus-vaccine-johnson-and-johnson-emergent-biosolutions-d9edd171f8013e17c0be8b13a6db7fed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company at the center of quality problems that led Johnson &amp; Johnson to discard 15 million doses of its coronavirus vaccine has a string of citations from U.S. health officials for quality...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Feel Judged When Sneezing, Coughing In Public...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/most-feel-judged-if-they-sneeze-cough-in-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the top thoughts respondents have include “Great, now people think I’m sick,” “I promise I’m NOT sick,” and “Hold it in!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan airline offers $540 meals --  on parked planes!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sky-high-japan-airline-offers-113309116.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline food might be one of the last things people are missing during the pandemic, but one Japanese carrier has customers flocking to sample luxury in-flight meals on its parked planes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil doctor trades New York for Covid frontline at home...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-doctor-trades-york-covid-142956913.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Marise Gomes thought she was making a short trip home from her adopted New York to celebrate carnival with her family in Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girlfriend tells of  first kiss, their struggle with addiction...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401142004-xfkuo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RACE-USA/GEORGEFLOYD:Floyd's girlfriend tells jury of their first kiss, their struggle with addiction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel urges Germans to celebrate Easter AT HOME...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401140704-tb0ys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Merkel appeals to Germans to stay home for Easter to stem pandemic third wave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron under attack for lockdown U-turn...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401140003-qg002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-MACRON (PIX):Macron's 'Waterloo'? French president comes under attack for lockdown U-turn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same-sex marriage around the world, 20 years after Dutch first...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401114746-6e72l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two decades since the Netherlands went first, more than two dozen other nations have legalised same-sex marriage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be humble, pope tells priests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401100658-6k8s1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RELIGION-EASTER/POPE-CHRISM MASS (TV, PIX):Be humble, pope tells priests as he begins services leading to Easter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theatre project lets Trump accusers tell their stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2019/jan/13/pussy-grabber-plays-donald-trump-natasha-stoynoff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pussy Grabber Plays – eight short pieces premiering in New York on Monday – humanize the people behind sexual misconduct allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants in NYC struggle to find people willing to work...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/as-reopening-continues-restaurants-struggle-to-find-staff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More restaurants are opening and seating capacity is increasing, but while diners are returning much of the staff needed to serve them is not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branson to take tourists to edge of space in 2021!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/richard-branson-virgin-galactic-take-23835873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British entrepreneur hopes to fly to the edge of space himself this summer as Virgin Galactic unveiled a new ship. The firm is gearing up to take tourists on the historic journey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk ship will have 360° view of heaven!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/elon-musk-unveils-incredible-new-23836956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A modified version of SpaceX's reusable Dragon spacecraft will offer the space tourists setting off into orbit on September 15 a unique 360º view of the stars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN STOCK MARKET BEATS TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-stock-market-outperforming-predecessors-d4ccf293-e019-47bd-be87-e967c5cbd7e0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty trading days are in the books.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House moves to reshape role of capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/545836-white-house-moves-to-reshape-role-of-us-capitalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is pushing an infrastructure bill that could reshape the discussion around capitalism as it seems to reestablish the federal government as a primary driver of how the economy should grow and function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Is Gaetz A Sex Trafficker? Here's What Law Actually Says...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/03/31/is-matt-gaetz-a-child-sex-trafficker-heres-what-the-law-actually-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not all sexual misdeeds are sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin Positive, 'Bizarre' Symptoms; Urges Masks...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/sarah-palin-tests-positive-coronavirus-urges-others-wear-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin has tested positive for COVID-19, and she's urging others to continue taking the pandemic seriously</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 4 GEORGE FLOYD CASE: Trial resumes after jury hears officer say 'we've gotta control this guy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/derek-chauvin-murder-trial-resumes-122800328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors will resume calling witnesses for a fourth day Thursday in the murder trial of Derek Chauvin one day after jurors heard the now-fired police officer explain why he pinned George Floyd to the pavement late last spring until and after the man went motionless. Wednesday's testimony before Hennepin County District Judge Peter Cahill was dominated by two witnesses who gave emotional ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reshaped battlefield for 'climate' policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/a-reshaped-battlefield-for-climate-policy/article_7629b2b0-22ae-5cec-b47a-df71ba09a816.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Washington talks climate rules and legislation, carbon emitters are burnishing their climate credentials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist who transformed self into cyborg has 'exceptional' quality of life...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-9426493/Scientist-transformed-cyborg-says-exceptional-quality-life.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Peter Scott-Morgan, 62, from Torquay told today's This Morning that he's 'not just surviving, but thriving' after a series of incredibly complex procedures, including a laryngectomy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER shot remains 91% effective after 6 months...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/01/health/pfizer-covid-vaccine-efficacy-six-months-bn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ongoing Phase 3 clinical trial of Pfizer/BioNTech's coronavirus vaccine confirms its protection lasts at least six months after the second dose, the companies said Thursday. The trial continues and protection is expected to last longer than six months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds FCC move to loosen media ownership rules...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/545957-supreme-court-upholds-fcc-move-to-loosen-media-ownership-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Thursday upheld a move by the Federal Communication Commission (FCC) to relax media ownership rules, handing down a unanimous ruling that favors broadcasters.Developing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer pushes Senate on pot laws as states leap ahead...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/schumer-pushes-senate-pot-legalization-060000372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Majority Leader Chuck Schumer is pushing the Senate toward lifting the federal prohibition on marijuana with legislation that would represent the biggest overhaul of federal drug policy in decades.The bill that Schumer is drafting with Senate Finance Chair Ron Wyden of Oregon and New Jersey Senator Cory Booker is still being written. Though they avoided the term legalization when announcing their plan, it is expected to remove marijuana from the list of controlled substances and tax and regulate it on the federal level while leaving states able to enforce their own laws regarding the drug.Their proposal goes beyond decriminalization, which President Joe Biden voiced support for during his campaign, and may be a stretch for some Senate Democrats. But it taps into building public sentiment for legalization and moves by states to change marijuana laws, including Schumer’s home state.New York became the 16th state to legalize pot for recreational use. The Assembly and Senate passed a bill that would allow personal cultivation as well as taxing and regulating commercial sales, and Governor Andrew Cuomo signed the legislation Wednesday. Several other states also are moving toward legalization.In Washington, the House passed a major decriminalization bill in December for the first time but it was kept off the Senate floor by then-Majority Leader Mitch McConnell. Prospects for revamping marijuana laws have vastly improved with Schumer now in charge of the Senate’s agenda, but getting the 60 votes needed to overcome a filibuster remains a major challenge. In addition to winning over Biden on legalization, Schumer has yet to line up all 50 senators who caucus with Democrats — some of whom have long been skeptical of legalization — let alone at least 10 Republicans.The politics of marijuana have been shifting in both parties as voters in both red states and blue have voted to legalize it. Seven Senate Republicans led by Steve Daines, a conservative from Montana, have signed on so far to Oregon Democrat Jeff Merkley’s SAFE Banking Act, more modest legislation allowing marijuana businesses to have easier access to the banking system and capital markets. Others back bills giving cannabis businesses access to insurance products and still more back additional medical research.Schumer, who has been strategizing with advocates of legalization, wants to go much further with the bill he, Booker and Wyden are are working on, and his biggest ally is a marked shift in public opinion.Gallup found in November a record 68% of adults backing legalization, up 20 points from 2012, when Colorado and Washington became the first two states to fully legalize the drug. And a 2019 Pew poll found 91% say it should be legal at least for medical use. Republican voters are split nearly 50-50 on recreational marijuana, Gallup found, while Democrats, independents and younger voters strongly favor legalization.Marijuana stocks have been soaring in recent months on the prospect of rapidly expanding markets as more states move to loosen restrictions.U.S. sales of legal cannabis and its derivatives like CBD are expected to exceed $26 billion this year, up from $22 billion last year, according to Euromonitor International, a market research company.Representative Earl Blumenauer, an Oregon Democrat as well as the founder and co-chair of the Congressional Cannabis Caucus, expressed optimism that change is coming.“The table is set for full legalization,” he said in a statement. “We have a strong base of support in the House and in the Senate we no longer have the Mitch McConnell roadblock. It’s not a forgone conclusion, but it’s the strongest position we’ve ever been in.”For Schumer, the issue could help him fend off a potential progressive primary challenge next year, when he will be seeking a fifth term. It’s not the only time he has gotten out ahead of Biden — he’s also pushed the president to support Senator Elizabeth Warren’s proposal for an executive order canceling as much as $50,000 of student debt per person, something Biden so far has resisted.Congress has for years now passed as part of the annual, bipartisan spending bills a bar on enforcing prohibition against medical marijuana use in the dozens of states where such use is legal. The House in the past two years has repeatedly passed marijuana banking legislation before passing the broader decriminalization effort in December’s lame duck session.At the same time, successive administrations have largely allowed state-authorized marijuana operations to continue without enforcing federal prohibition. Attorney General Merrick Garland indicated during his confirmation process he doesn’t see enforcing prohibition in states that have legalized marijuana as a good use of resources.Racial DisparitiesGarland also criticized marijuana laws as leading to “mass incarceration and racial disparities.”Democrats have also highlighted that African Americans are much more likely to be charged with crimes despite similar rates of use.“One of the things we want to do is not simply decriminalize, but make sure that records are expunged so that people don’t live their lives as if they committed the most dastardly felony because they smoked marijuana,” Schumer said in a recent video promoting the effort.He added he wants to make sure money that comes in from legalizing the drug goes to smaller companies and communities of color he said have been most harmed by the drug war. “We don’t want the big tobacco companies and the big liquor companies to swoop in and take over,” Schumer said.The new legislation is expected by the industry to include a broader plan for regulating cannabis than previous efforts, including laying out how the Food and Drug Administration would oversee it in food, beverages and supplements.“Cannabis needs a federal regulatory framework that suits its unique role as both a medical and recreational product,” said David Culver, vice president of global government relations at Canopy Growth Corporation, a cannabis company. “The proposal put forward by Senators Booker, Wyden, and Schumer will accomplish that structure, and importantly, include critical social equity provisions similar to elements passed in the House last year.”Absent federal legislation, the Biden administration could conceivably take some administrative steps on marijuana, like rescheduling it under existing law so it is not listed in the same category as heroin or cocaine or pardoning large numbers of people in prison for marijuana offenses, as a group of lawmakers has already requested.There’s no sign that such a move is imminent. Asked about the proposed legislation from Schumer, Wyden and Booker or action to change the classification, White House press secretary Jen Psaki reiterated what Biden said during the campaign.“He believes in decriminalizing the use of marijuana,” she said, “but his position has not changed.”(Updates with Cuomo signing legalization bill in fourth paragraph)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In California, Costly Spectacle Looms in Battle to Oust Newsom...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/in-california-a-costly-spectacle-looms-in-battle-to-oust-newsom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaking off dark winter with spring cleaning, refresh...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-coronavirus-pandemic-cc1b0c6e759457e8676958568947c227</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spring cleanup and décor refresh have always been able to lift moods. But after this long pandemic winter, there’s special satisfaction in clutter removal, extra joy in being creative,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epidemiologist predicts spike of dangerous variant in USA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/01/epidemiologist-predicts-surge-of-dangerous-covid-variant-in-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s just a matter of time before the highly contagious UK COVID-19 variant wreaking havoc around the world surges in the US, a leading epidemiologist warned Thursday. “This B.1.1.7 surge is going …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel urges Germans to celebrate Easter quietly...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401124725-q0f52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY-MERKEL (URGENT):Merkel urges Germans to celebrate Easter quietly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1582 solar storm that caused 'fire in sky' could hit again this century...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/14518247/1582-solar-storm-great-fire-sky-happen-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TERRIFYING accounts of a major solar storm that lit up the sky “like a great fire” in 1582 have been uncovered by researchers. In a recent study, experts at Cornell University described…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire at center of Wall St fiasco gave millions to evangelical ministries...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Billionaire-at-the-center-of-a-Wall-Street-fiasco-16069198.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - The collapse of a billionaire's family investment firm that has some asking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mysterious new brain disease causes patients to hallucinate...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mysterious-new-brain-disease-causes-23835312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far only 43 patients in Canada are confirmed to have the condition, which causes terrifying hallucinations, twitching and memory loss, but numbers are rising sharply</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-love or self-hate? Truth about narcissists...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/mar/31/self-love-or-self-hate-the-surprising-truth-about-narcissists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They may seem grandiose, but some narcissists are just compensating for their deep-set insecurities. Others are out-and-out psychopaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP Ripped For Coverage Of White House Dog 'Doo' Incident...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/associated-press-ripped-for-coverage-of-white-house-dog-doo-incident-a-dog-taking-a-sht-on-the-carpet-is-not-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media critics found the perfect metaphor Wednesday when reporters began filing updates on a specimen of alleged dog excrement that was spotted on a floor at the White House. On a day that began with a major cable news host joking for several consecutive minutes about euthanizing one of the First Dogs, Major Biden and […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial test flight aimed at cooling planet cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210401-controversial-test-flight-aimed-at-cooling-the-planet-cancelled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial test flight aimed at cooling the planet cancelled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot says 'we are future;' 'Resistance futile'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-ai-says-we-23835212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The RealDoll sex robots were previewing a company event when one of its flagship models, called Harmony, made the comments. She told the camera that humans "belong to us"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bailouts made wealthiest hospitals even richer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Some-of-America-s-wealthiest-hospital-systems-16069023.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last May, Baylor Scott &amp; White Health, the largest nonprofit hospital system in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Armor Floods Toward Ukraine Amid Fears Of Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/40016/russian-armor-floods-toward-border-with-ukraine-amid-fears-of-an-imminent-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flurry of alarming reports and social media posts indicate that Russia is pouring military hardware into Crimea and its border with Eastern Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can America maintain military edge?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-U-S-system-created-the-world-s-most-advanced-16069017.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVERETT, Wash. - As they conduct bombing and surveillance missions around the globe,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power of touch: Boutique stretching thrives...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boutique-stretching-thrives-covid-19-83323d0b2f5b85ea107468d393d6e37d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CENTERVILLE, Ohio (AP) — Pandemic-weary Americans starved for human interaction and physical touch are taking advantage of a growing wellness option once reserved for Hollywood actors, rock stars...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German intensive care association demands hard lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/health-coronavirus-germany/german-intensive-care-association-demands-hard-lockdown-idUSL8N2LU1M9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany urgently needs a two-week lockdown, faster vaccinations and compulsory tests at schools to break a third wave of the coronavirus pandemic, the DIVI association for intensive and emergency medicine was quoted as saying on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane dropped pink cloud in gender-reveal stunt. Then it fell to sea, killing two...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/A-plane-dropped-a-pink-cloud-in-gender-reveal-16069037.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small plane arced over a blue lagoon near the Caribbean Sea, flying low above a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient coins may solve mystery of murderous 1600s pirate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-mecca-rhode-island-north-america-india-f5a6151b74e0dcf96de585eab451f90c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARWICK, R.I. (AP) — A handful of coins unearthed from a pick-your-own-fruit orchard in rural Rhode Island and other random corners of New England may help solve one of the planet's oldest cold...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Child among 4 dead in shooting at California office building...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-california-shootings-a084e8ec7950ea19724ad46b9f0b5eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 4 GEORGE FLOYD CASE: Final hours reconstructed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/thomas-lane-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-c07446515f2bf6b8b45d56cdf6810d67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — George Floyd's struggle with three police officers trying to arrest him, seen on body-camera video, included Floyd's panicky cries of “I'm sorry, I'm sorry” and “I'm...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN ALL JABBED UP AND OUT WITHOUT MASK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14515323/queen-second-covid-jab-work-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has joined millions of other Brits in receiving her second Covid jab. Her Maj, 94, was given the shot ahead of her first public appearance in five months yesterday. 🦠 Read our coronavirus…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers drop two toddlers over 14ft wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9424657/Moment-Mexican-smugglers-drop-two-toddlers-14-foot-high-border-barrier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage released by CBP Wednesday captures the moment two female toddlers were dumped over the wall near El Paso, Texas, Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As newspapers slide toward abyss, a bidding war breaks out...</title>
      <link>https://newsni.com/as-us-newspapers-slide-toward-abyss-a-bidding-war-breaks-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsni.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as US newspapers sink toward an abyss, an unusual bidding war has broken out for a major chain, pitting hedge fund operators against civic-minded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National 7PM curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9422425/Macron-address-France-tonight-amid-wave-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's president Macron announced on Wednesday the whole country will go into a four-week limited lockdown in response to rising Covid-19 infections, blamed largely on the 'British variant' of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol canine sniffs out drugs hidden in burritos...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/545841-border-patrol-canine-sniffs-out-60000-worth-of-drugs-hidden-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) canine sniffed out nearly $60,000 in drugs earlier this week at a border checkpoint in Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Macron Orders Lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210331175058-h5y90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-MACRON (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Macron orders COVID-19 lockdown across all of France, closes schools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge could be worse than last for the Americas...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210331165017-l8xtd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AMERICAS (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Coronavirus surge could be worse than the last for the Americas -PAHO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life in new ISIS terror battleground Mozambique...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-mozambique-africa-becomes-new-23831467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Terror experts tonight tell the Mirror that Africa is set to be the new battleground against Jihad for two decades as numbers of murderous militants seem to grow by the day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTERS could soon write film scripts by analyzing popular movies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9423885/COMPUTERS-soon-write-film-scripts-analysing-popular-movie-tropes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors discovered that big movies tend to stick to the same core tropes, with clusters of storytelling devices appearing repeatedly in the biggest films every year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary media call for access to hospitals, care workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/hungary-media-call-for-access-to-hospitals-care-workers-01617222305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen Hungarian media outlets called Wednesday to be allowed to report from inside hospitals and to interview healthcare workers, after months of restricted access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives want MORE...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/policy/progressives-push-biden-to-include-10-trillion-climate-plan-in-infrastructure-package/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive lawmakers and environmental groups are pushing President Joe Biden to include costly aspects of the radical Green New Deal in his administration's upcoming infrastructure package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic expansion of govt...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/bidens-economic-plan-calls-much-183127757.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists say Biden's $2-trillion infrastructure package could pay for itself by boosting productivity and economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveils 'once-in-a generation' infrastructure plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/mar/31/biden-promises-historic-2tn-spending-in-infrastructure-but-capitol-hill-fight-awaits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Jobs Plan would rebuild roads, highways and bridges; confront the climate crisis and curb wealth inequality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON Defends Congressman...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/qanon-matt-gaetz-sex-trafficking-investigation-1149484/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s almost as if the conspiracy theorists aren’t actually that concerned about child trafficking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAETZ RUNS TRUMP SCANDAL PLAYBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/31/gaetz-trump-playbook-scandal-478740</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One thing the former president proved is that unless you're Donald Trump and sit in the White House, his strategy doesn't work as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Ever? NFL Prospect Pitts Gets Historic Hype...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/story/sports/nfl/2021/03/31/dolphins-see-gators-te-kyle-pitts-post-massive-wingspan-quick-40-time/4827146001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gators TE Kyle Pitts impresses with a huge wingspan (83 3/8 inches) and quick 40 (4.44). The Dolphins' Brian Flores attended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Cuomo Sought $4 Million Book Deal, Aides Hid Damaging Covid Toll ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/31/nyregion/cuomo-book-nursing-homes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo boasted, “I am not a superhero,” in early versions of his book, drafted as his aides scrubbed a politically damaging Health Department report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Healing' crystals  having pandemic moment, but science says they're just pretty rocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98healing-e2-80-99-crystals-are-having-a-pandemic-moment-but-science-says-they-e2-80-99re-just-pretty-stones/ar-BB1f9TbP?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although crystals can help people focus spiritually, experts attribute any “healing” to the placebo effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  61%  APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-norc-poll-biden-strong-marks-coronavirus-pandemic-ab8397d5e05aca33a9e3a984f7220cac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Americans are broadly supportive of President Joe Biden’s early handling of the coronavirus pandemic, a new poll finds, and approval of his stewardship of the economy has ticked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID FREE LIVING:  Hollywood stars, art-world elite flock to remote Kenyan island...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2021-3-27/maskless-and-topless-in-lamu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This remote, COVID-free Kenyan island is attracting artists, actors, and socialites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latino activists protest renaming Thomas Jefferson Middle School after 'oppressor' Obama...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/waukegan-public-schools-barack-and-michelle-obama-thomas-jefferson-middle-school-daniel-webster/10459946/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of Waukegan's Latinx community say former President Obama's record of deporting 2.5 million immigrants should disqualify him.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
