<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sex, travel, peace of mind. How life changing for fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/sex-travel-peace-of-mind-how-life-is-changing-for-some-of-the-fully-vaccinated/article_51a1566d-ba27-5a02-9724-14c9155908a5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dating during the pandemic is becoming less complicated and risky for attorney Shelley O'Connor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images reveal extent of damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/27/middleeast/us-syria-iran-airstrikes-analysis-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A resident of al-Bukamal, a city near the Syrian-Iraqi border, told CNN the explosions from US airstrikes targeting a compound the Pentagon said was used by Iranian-backed militia groups were unlike anything he had heard before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Rock' v. The Don: A serious comparison...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/540290-dwayne-the-rock-johnson-v-donald-trump-a-serious-comparison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson has that 'it' factor that Trump had in 2016, and his growing platform makes Trump’s look unsophisticated and outdated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Dog Used by Police Stirs Privacy Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/27/digidog-a-robotic-dog-used-by-the-police-stirs-privacy-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were being held hostage in a Bronx apartment. They had been threatened at gunpoint, tied up and tortured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes may show early warnings for Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.iol.co.za/news/world/the-eyes-could-show-early-warnings-for-alzheimers-researchers-say-c0271978-4424-595c-992e-a79adf9bd84a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iol.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say a picture of your eye could assess your future risk of neurodegenerative disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Russia's mass arrests: Claims of beatings, threats and 'war' against rights monitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Inside-Russia-s-mass-arrests-Claims-of-beatings-15984774.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - Authorities call it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skiers defy death in descent of Yosemite's Half Dome...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-top-news-eb713b3d3b2de28dd9a82b5ab72798b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK, Calif. (AP) — Two skiers navigated a thin layer of snow with no margin for error down the precipitous shoulder of Half Dome in Yosemite National Park and alternately skied...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon wolf makes history on lengthy journey to California...</title>
      <link>https://defenders.org/newsroom/oregon-wolf-or-93-makes-history-traveling-californias-central-sierra-nevada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;defenders.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, a gray wolf from western Oregon dubbed OR-93 became the first collared wolf to explore the central Sierra region of California. According to the California Department of Fish and Wildlife (CDFW), OR-93, a former member of the White River Pack near Mt. Hood, has traveled farther south into the state than any known wild wolf in a century, a historic journey that highlights the importance of habitat connectivity and the dispersal ability of this iconic species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will AI get along with us?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/540821-will-artificial-intel-get-along-with-us-only-if-we-design-it-that-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People would be much more guarded with social media if they realized those platforms are actively profiling them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo wife to rat out cartel?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/27/el-chapos-wife-emma-coronel-aispuro-poised-to-snitch-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emma Coronel Aispuro went back to being a brunette for her mug shot last week. The glamorous beauty-queen wife of Mexico’s most notorious drug trafficker had last appeared in public as a blonde, he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing tension in Minneapolis as trial looms in Floyd death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-health-trials-coronavirus-pandemic-minneapolis-075d9b5f4a2a1f80d26cb33b77ca59b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Barbed wire and concrete barriers surround the courthouse where the former Minneapolis police officer charged with killing George Floyd will soon go on trial, a sign of the deep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plunging demand for tests may leave USA exposed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-b1c1f6fc83977830231c065625510e4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Just five weeks ago, Los Angeles County was conducting more than 350,000 weekly coronavirus tests, including at a massive drive-thru site at Dodger Stadium, as health workers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists uncover ancient ceremonial carriage near Pompeii...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-pompeii-idUKKBN2AR0E1?taid=603a67e6186e2a0001d275a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists have unearthed a unique ancient-Roman ceremonial carriage from a villa just outside Pompeii, the city buried in a volcanic eruption in 79 AD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>800-year-old prophecy predicts war?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/800-year-old-prophecy-predicts-23576016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ancient texts says the United States will be drawn into a conflict involving Iran and Saudi Arabia, with the fighting bringing "great strife and darkness into the world"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A road like no other, in peril like never before...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-road-like-no-other-in-peril-like-never-before-15984513.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GORDA, Calif. - Life here in this tiny town built on the continent-ending cliffs of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Beats Virus -- 150 Days After Being Admitted Hospital!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/02/26/isabel-pupo-coronavirus-south-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isabel Pupo was all smiles, just days after opening her eyes from a medically induced coma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue dog that nobody wanted saves life of new owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/steve-hartman-on-the-road-rescue-dog-2021-02-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Myers gave Sadie a chance. She saved his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COINBASE Mafia Shows How Tight Circle Holds Sway Over Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/coinbase-mafia-shows-how-tight-a-circle-holds-sway-over-bitcoin/ar-BB1e4lQe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Coinbase Global Inc.’s filing to become a publicly-traded company provides a glimpse into the remarkably small circle of mostly men who command the incredibly lucrative digital landscape. This U.S.-based power list starts with Brian Armstrong, the now billionaire chief executive officer of Coinbase, and his co-founder, Fred Ehrsam, who went on to create Paradigm Operations. Fellow billionaire Fred Wilson of Union Square Ventures,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Why Bill Gates is now biggest farmland owner...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/27/why-bill-gates-is-now-the-us-biggest-farmland-owner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real reason billionaire Gates just became the biggest owner of farmland in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinzinger -- The Man Who Refused to Bow...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/02/man-who-refused-bow/618156/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Kinzinger says he’ll fight to take his party back from Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sasse marches to own tune as GOP implodes around him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/27/ben-sasse-gop-471764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there's a model for how to successfully build a conservative GOP out of Trump's shadow, it might as well be the Nebraska Republican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper's Arrest Awakens Rage in Spanish Youth Chafing in Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/27/rappers-arrest-awakens-rage-in-spanish-youth-chafing-in-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA — It had all the markings of a free speech showdown: Pablo Hasél, a controversial Spanish rapper, had barricaded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Baron and Bezos Remade WASH POST...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/27/how-marty-baron-and-jeff-bezos-remade-the-washington-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On July 30, 2013, Martin Baron left The Washington Post building and crossed 15th Street for an extremely rare happy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakout 'BORAT' star Maria Bakalova conquers Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/maria-bakalova-sacha-baron-cohen-shootings-golden-globe-awards-bulgaria-f74d35197d8f38752698b4725d2063cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So what did YOU do at 5 a.m. after staying up all night for your prom? Maria Bakalova became a movie star. The 24-year-old actress has been telling the story of how she had a few free hours...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA fines passenger $27,500 for hitting flight attendant over mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/faa-seeks-27500-fine-from-passenger-for-hitting-flight-attendant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials are seeking a $27,500 civil penalty against an airline passenger who allegedly struck a flight attendant who asked the passenger and a companion to leave the plane after a dispute over wearing a face mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF GLOBAL DIGITAL TAX</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-drops-key-obstacle-global-173148199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen told her G20 colleagues Friday that Washington is dropping a push for a controversial provision in a global digital tax, opening the door to a likely agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For crematorium worker, mounting toll is measured in ashes and anguish...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crematorium-worker-covid-19s-mounting-153234671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never experiencing the relief of seeing COVID patients recover takes it toll on crematorium workers. One worries he'll develop a 'hard heart, a cold heart.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of social media: Warning for dog owners as thefts rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/feb/26/beware-social-media-warning-uk-dog-owners-thefts-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say people should be wary of posting pictures of pets online that could reveal their location</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overshadowed by ethics controversy, lack of diversity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/feb/26/golden-globes-ethics-controversy-criticism-lack-diversity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carey Mulligan and Chadwick Boseman are predicted to win big, but ceremony to air following damning investigation into voting membership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE investigators used private utility database covering millions to pursue violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/ICE-investigators-used-a-private-utility-database-15982865.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers have tapped a private database...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As USPS delays persist, bills, paychecks and medications are getting stuck in mail...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/As-USPS-delays-persist-bills-paychecks-and-15983524.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Mark Currie of Virginia had three checks snagged in postal delays in three...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE NATION Boss Predicts Music Festivals Could Be Back by Summer!</title>
      <link>https://www.spin.com/2021/02/live-nation-ceo-michael-rapino-says-largescale-u-s-concerts-could-start-in-midsummer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At almost full capacity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechs confined to their districts as infections soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/czech-republic-coronavirus-new-state-of-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vote will mean tougher restrictions as country battles sharp rise in coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid restrictions ease in Mexico's most popular tourist cities ahead of spring break season...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Coronavirus-restrictions-ease-in-some-of-Mexico-s-15982876.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican state of Quintana Roo is softening its coronavirus restrictions following a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says gave only few mins warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/26/russia-ally-syria-fumes-us-airstrike-against-milit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia, a key military ally of the government of Syrian President Bashar Assad, on Friday sharply condemned the U.S. airstrike targeting an Iran-allied Iraqi militia group operating in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Branson's Space Tourism Dream Crashing?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/02/virgin-galactic-crashing-uk-launch-partner-reject-space-tourism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic’s flight schedule is pushed back to 2022 due to a recent test failure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE PREPARES ORDER FOR AIRPORT EBOLA SCREENINGS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-white-house-preparing-order-for-enhanced-airport-screenings-for-ebola-203354978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is moving forward with plans to screen airline passengers from two African countries arriving in the U.S. for Ebola, which will involve sending them to one of about a half dozen designated airports, Yahoo News has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  GOLDEN GLOBES Aim To Go More Intimate Than Ever For Sunday's Star-Studded Show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globes-behind-the-scenes-tina-fey-amy-poehler-hfpa-dcp-sarah-paulson-sandra-oh-tracy-morgan-barry-adelman-1234702044/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: In this time of a global pandemic, the 78th annual Golden Globes intend to spotlight the foreign in Hollywood Foreign Press Association for Sunday’s Tina Fey and Amy Poehler bicoastal ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  Strikes in Syria sent warning to Iran...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-syria-airstrike-kills-1-34b4d7ac56fa8d0d2db8dc2ec8e921d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said Friday that Iran should view his decision to authorize U.S. airstrikes in Syria as a warning that it can expect consequences for its support of militia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Girl, 12, busted for selling stun guns to middle school classmates...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/k-12/stun-gun-salesgirl-389670</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 26--A 12-year-old Florida girl is facing criminal charges after she admitted to selling stun guns to classmates, police report. According to investigators, a staff member at Coleman Middle S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. diplomat rails against Jews...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/26/diplomat-online-activity-blood-and-faith-471755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fritz Berggren’s hundreds of blog posts, videos and podcasts date back several years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Suspends Advanced Learning Classes Citing Racial Inequities...</title>
      <link>https://www.wgbh.org/news/education/2021/02/26/citing-racial-inequities-boston-public-schools-suspend-advanced-learning-classes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wgbh.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An analysis of the program found that more than 70 percent of students enrolled in the program were white and Asian, even though nearly 80 percent of all Boston public school students are Hispanic and Black.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA panel endorses J&amp;J shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/26/fda-johnson-johnson-vaccine-advantages-471766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vaccine, which is given as a single dose and is easy to ship, appeals to officials struggling to vaccinate hard-to-reach or skeptical populations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police chief warns of threat during Biden speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/capitol-law-enforcement-heads-detail-intelligence-failures-leading-jan-6-n1258829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acting chief said members of militia groups want to "kill as many members as possible" in an attack during Biden's coming address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Yang rushes to aid of photographer during assault...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/26/andrew-yang-rushes-to-help-photographer-during-assault-on-si-ferry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayoral candidate Andrew Yang rushed to the aid of a news photographer who was attacked Friday on the Staten Island Ferry. Getty photojournalist Spencer Platt told The Post he was part of a small m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House and press at odds over plan to charge reporters for testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/White-House-and-press-are-at-odds-over-plan-to-15983010.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters who cover the White House may soon be paying what amounts to an admission fee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden doesn't penalize crown prince despite promise to punish...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/26/politics/biden-mohammed-bin-salman-jamal-khashoggi/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite promising to punish senior Saudi leaders while on the campaign trail, President Joe Biden declined to apply sanctions to the one the US intelligence community determined is responsible for the death of journalist Jamal Khashoggi: Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions About Legality, Precedent...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-02-26/pentagon-stands-by-syria-strikes-despite-questions-about-legality-precedent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘It was very much a defensive operation,’ Pentagon spokesman John Kirby said of the unilateral strike in Syria against pro-Iran targets in retaliation for deadly rocket attacks in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ man admits neo-Nazi group's 'Operation Kristallnacht' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/operation-kristallnacht-richard-tobin-synagogue-vandalism-rinaldo-nazarro-the-base-20210226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Tobin, of Brooklawn, also told FBI agents he recently sat in the parking lot of the Menlo Park Mall in Middlesex County with a machete willing himself to 'let loose' on Black shoppers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Stands By USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210226182856-v7d61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SYRIA/STRIKE-FRANCE (CORRECTED, URGENT):CORRECTED-France says stands by U.S. air strikes against Iran-backed militias in syria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bust of Queen beheaded in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/have-you-seen-her-majestys-head-bust-of-the-queen-desecrated-in-victoria-b-c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PET DETECTIVES STUMPED...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/why-lady-gaga-s-dognapping-has-stumped-pet-detectives/ar-BB1e3nca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamie Katz has seen a lot in her seven years as a pet detective. She had one case of a man who was walking his dog at 5 a.m. when “a car pulled up and just, like, four to five people got out and started beating the hell out of him.” The assailants kicked the dog during the attack, prompting it to run away. In another case, a client had their French Bulldog stolen from its crate in their home, along with $10,000 in cash. But even she was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia reserves 'right to retaliate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/02/26/us-airstrike-first-under-biden-kills-iran-backed-militiaman-militia-reserves-right-to-retaliate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Air Force F-15E aircraft launched seven precision guided munitions at facilities used by Iran-backed militias near Boukamal, on the Syrian side of the Iraq border, along the Euphrates River.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinyl sales beat CDs -- for first time since '86...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/vinyl-record-sales-increased-almost-30-in-2020-riaa-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Streaming expectedly continued to grow throughout the pandemic while downloads and CD sales continued to decline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Keeping Huge, Secretive DNA Database in Orange County...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4ade3g/why-are-prosecutors-keeping-a-huge-secretive-dna-database-in-orange-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The fact that you are giving up your DNA for a relatively smaller misdemeanor crime—forever—is pretty scary, when you think about it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 convicted in '93 World Trade Center bombing have had sentences cut...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bombings-619788d2b7b5806c34463e4dd6854774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Decades after going to prison, some of the men responsible for the World Trade Center bombing that killed six people 28 years ago Friday are still trying to whittle down their...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
