<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens Turkey after greenlighting Syria invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-forces-start-syria-border-pullback-alarming-kurds-082650162.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump warned Turkey on Monday against going too far in Syria, one day after giving Ankara a green light to invade its southern neighbor and sparking panic among Washington&amp;#39;s Kurdish allies. The US pulled back 50 to 100 &amp;quot;special operators&amp;quot; from Syria&amp;#39;s northern frontier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Deepfakes Are Porn, and They're Multiplying Fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/most-deepfakes-porn-multiplying-fast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers worry that doctored videos may disrupt the 2020 election, but a new report finds that 96 percent of deepfakes are pornographic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR:  15,000 ISIS fighters will break out of prison camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10087333/fears-isis-will-use-turkish-invasion-to-break-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KURDISH fighters have warned that Turkey’s Syrian invasion may allow ISIS to attempt mass prison breaks as the US backs out of its occupied territories. More than 15,000 ISIS fanatics are cur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: League Choosing Money over Human Rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/daryl-morey-nba-hong-kong-houston-rockets-895706/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daryl Morey is now being forced to apologize because he… supports Democracy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETS owner, ALIBABA co-founder pens open letter defending China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-basketball-nba-tsai/brooklyn-nets-owner-alibaba-co-founder-tsai-decries-houston-rockets-gms-hong-kong-tweet-idUSKBN1WM0C8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph Tsai, owner of the Brooklyn Nets and co-founder of Chinese e-commerce gia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Struggles to Piece Together Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/08/caught-between-trump-turkey-and-kurds-pentagon-struggles-to-piece-together-syria-strategy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — For nine months, the Pentagon played down the presence of its 1,000 troops in Syria, hoping that President Trump would not focus on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former George W. Bush chief of staff endorses Trump impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/464763-former-george-w-bush-chief-of-staff-endorses-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Card, who served as White House chief of staff during the George W. Bush administration, on Monday expressed support for House Democrats’ impeachment inquiry of President Trump, saying that "clearly lines have been crossed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Using Trade Deals to Shield Tech Giants From Foreign Regulators... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/07/business/tech-shield-trade-deals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The push is the latest salvo in a global fight over who gets to set the rules for the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS fighters will break out of prison camps?</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/08/trumps-green-light-to-turkey-raises-fears-about-isis-detainees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — President Trump’s sudden blessing of a Turkish military operation in northern Syria and his announcement of an American troop withdrawal from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls begin to signal rising impeachment threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/07/polls-begin-to-signal-rising-impeachment-threat-to-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite last week's hailstorm of bad news, President Trump's job approval rating stood virtually unchanged. Yet surveys in recent days show public sentiment evolving more than Trump's steady topline would suggest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City Grinds to Halt as Cabs Block Airport to Protest UBER...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/mexico-city-taxi-drivers-block-191555656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of medallion taxi drivers parked their pink-and-white cabs to block major Mexico City thoroughfares for hours Monday in protest of ride-hailing apps such as Uber, causing long delays for motorists. Taxi drivers say they have to comply with requirements for licensing, tax, inspection and tests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  New York-based WBAI radio abruptly shuts down...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/07/new-york-based-wbai-radio-abruptly-shuts-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WBAI FM 99.5, a listener-supported radio station in New York City that has been on the air since 1955, abruptly announced on Monday it is shutting down. The station’s California-based nonprofit par…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, son could be forced to testify in impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/7/joe-biden-hunter-biden-could-be-forced-testify-don/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joseph R. Biden and his son Hunter could be forced to testify if the Senate ends up holding an impeachment trial of President Trump, say congressional aides who questioned whether Democrats have thought through the full implications of their impeachment drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE WALKS IT BACK?</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-10-07/trump-administration-appears-to-reverse-syria-decision-following-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  'I in my great and unmatched wisdom'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/10/07/donald-trump-unmatched-wisdom-syria-tweet/3898498002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics said Donald Trump showed anything but wisdom in suddenly announcing a U.S. troop withdrawal from northern Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA scrambles after ROCKETS pro-democracy tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/oct/07/nba-scrambles-after-china-angered-by-houston-rockets-regrettable-pro-democracy-tweet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houston’s general manager has tried to defuse the rapidly growing fallout over his deleted tweet that showed support for anti-government protesters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of robbing bank to pay for wedding... </title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article235869077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems consider masking identity of whistleblowers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/House-Democrats-consider-masking-identity-of-14498966.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats eager to protect a whistleblower who raised alarms over President Donald Trump pressuring a foreign leader to investigate a political rival are considering testimony at a remote location and possibly obscuring the individual's appearance and voice - extraordinary moves to prevent Trump's congressional allies from revealing the identity, according to three officials familiar with the discussions.  Democratic investigators are concerned that without such rare precautions, Republicans on the House Intelligence Committee could learn and then leak the identity of the whistleblower, who has agreed to answer questions before the intelligence committees in both the House and Senate.  Democrats overseeing the logistics of the testimony for the House impeachment inquiry are discussing a location away from the Capitol as well as a staff-only session that would prevent lawmakers from attending and asking questions.  Aides have considered having the whistleblower testify from a separate location via a video hookup in which the camera would obscure the whistleblower's image and alter his voice, possibly with modification technology. They also are talking about having the whistleblower sit behind a screen or partition. A third option being floated includes audio-only testimony.  "Schiff does not want to burn his identity," a senior congressional official said.  "There are lots of different protocols and procedures we're looking into to find out what works and doesn't work to protect the identity of the whistleblower," said a different official familiar with the talks. "That is paramount."  The officials spoke on the condition of anonymity to freely describe private deliberations.  The discussion underscores the toxicity between Republicans and Democrats on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court session begins without ill Clarence Thomas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court/u-s-supreme-court-kicks-off-new-term-with-justice-thomas-absent-idUSKBN1WM1JW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday debated the insanity defense in criminal prosec...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAT ROBERTSON WARNS TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/pat-robertson-destroys-trump-allowed-khashoggi-to-be-cut-in-pieces-may-lose-the-mandate-of-heaven-over-syria-pullout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Televangelist Pat Robertson has joined the chorus of conservative critics lambasting President Donald Trump's decision to pull U.S. forces out of Syria and endangering America's Kurdish alli</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBD/TIPP POLL:  Warren Overtakes Biden In Dem Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/politics/elizabeth-warren-overtakes-joe-biden-democratic-presidential-nomination-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West Slams Social Media Mind Control, Defends Trump Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/kanye-west-slams-social-media-mind-control-defends-trump-support-in-saturday-sermon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Says Republicans freed slaves, bashes Democrat identity politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget office estimates US deficit just under $1 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e107e95d7fd422bbcf1bbdf0cd12454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The government ran a budget deficit of just under $1 trillion in the just-closed fiscal year, the Congressional Budget Office said Monday. The $984 billion deficit tally...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shut down huge parts of London...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10079914/extinction-rebellion-london-protest-arrests-boris-johnson-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson slammed the “uncooperative crusties and protesters” after they caused travel misery for thousands of commuters in London. Hundreds of Extinction Rebellion protesters pitched tents and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Efforts To Eat 'Clean' Become Unhealthy Obsession...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2019/10/07/766847274/when-efforts-to-eat-clean-become-an-unhealthy-obsession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether it's gluten or dairy, many people avoid certain types of foods these days. Sometimes food avoidance can take over people's lives and veer into an eating disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems consider hiding identity, holding testimony at remote location...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/464738-democrats-mull-masking-whistleblower-holding-testimony-at-remote-locale-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are looking to prevent the whistleblower from being identified by holding the person's testimony at a remote location and potentially changing their appearance and voice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>84% of Women Failing Army Combat Fitness Test...</title>
      <link>https://news.clearancejobs.com/2019/10/05/army-combat-fitness-test-fiasco-slides-reveal-84-of-women-failing-acft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.clearancejobs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs fear 'especially bad' flu season...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article235871907.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Contradict Claim She Was Fired Over Pregnancy...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/county-records-contradict-warrens-claim-she-was-fired-over-pregnancy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Riverdale Board of Education approved a contract for a second-year teaching stint for a young Elizabeth Warren, documents show, contradicting the Democratic presidential candidate’s repeated claims that she was fired after a year because she was "visibly pregnant."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAHAM: GIVING 'SECOND LEASE ON LIFE'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/07/lindsey-graham-isis-syria-withdrawal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graham reacted to Trump's withdrawal angrily, saying that this decision will benefit ISIS and Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA diplomatic standoff with England...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/harry-dunn-crash-us-diplomat-wife-anne-sacoolas-pm-boris-johnson-diplomatic-immunity-today-2019-10-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family of teen killed in road accident and the British prime minister say American's diplomatic immunity should be waived</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARDEN: 'We love China'...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/james-harden-apologizes-daryl-morey-china-hong-kong-nba-backlash-hong-kong-protests-142140112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;We love everything there about them.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS to make Trump show based on fired FBI chief's book...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cbs-trump-show-based-fired-fbi-chiefs-book-195235532.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US production company CBS Studios said on Monday it is to make a miniseries based on the memoir of former FBI director James Comey, who was fired by President Donald Trump as the Russia election interference scandal erupted in 2017. Jeff Daniels ("Dumb and Dumber," "The Newsroom"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Emergency': Climate protesters block streets around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-protests/sorry-this-is-an-emergency-climate-protesters-block-streets-around-the-world-idUSKBN1WM1JP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of climate-change protesters took to the streets in cities around the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORTMAN: Wrong to seek help from Ukraine, China...</title>
      <link>https://www.dispatch.com/news/20191007/ohio-gop-sen-rob-portman-trump-wrong-to-seek-help-from-ukraine-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While he still says impeachment is too extreme, Sen. Rob Portman readily acknowledged today that President Donald Trump should not have asked the Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters force acting DHS chief to abandon speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kevin-mcaleenan-migration-policy-institute-speech-interrupted-by-protesters-chanting-names-of-migrant-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists chanted the names of migrant children who've died in U.S. custody</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL BLASTS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191007174057-tiklx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-USA-CONGRESS (URGENT):Top two lawmakers blast Trump's move to withdraw U.S. troops from northeast Syria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police stage show of force on streets, jeered by residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests/hong-kong-police-stage-show-of-force-on-streets-jeered-by-residents-idUSKBN1WM02G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong police staged a show of force on Monday night in a district hit by som...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani to Sue Schiff...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/giulianis-answer-to-impeach-inquiry-sue-schiff-164553599.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudolph Giuliani says he is working with outside lawyers to prepare lawsuits against prominent Democrats such as House Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff of California and Rep. Rashid Tlaib of Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS fighters will break out of prison camps?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-administration-to-pull-troops-from-northern-syria-as-turkey-readies-offensive/ar-AAIoeoJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two earthquakes rattle Charlotte area...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article235874402.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulls genetically engineered without horns to stop farmers being gored...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/bulls-genetically-engineered-without-horns-165310684.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grasping the bull by the horns could soon be a distant memory for British dairy farmers after scientists genetically engineered male animals to rid them of their dangerous prongs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KURDS ALARMED...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-forces-start-syria-border-pullback-alarming-kurds-082650162.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US forces in Syria started pulling back Monday from Turkish border areas, opening the way for Ankara's threatened military invasion and heightening fears of a jihadist resurgence. The withdrawal from key positions along Syria's northern border came after the White House said it would step aside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How exercise keeps CBS anchor Norah O'Donnell sane... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/Exercise-keeps-CBS-Evening-News-anchor-Norah-14498119.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television correspondents and news anchors have stressful, demanding jobs, especially in today's never-ending news cycle. We asked Norah O'Donnell, anchor and managing editor of "CBS Evening News," how she takes care of herself. After many years as a TV correspondent and a recent stint as co-anchor of "CBS This Morning," O'Donnell, 45, became the third solo female anchor of a network evening newscast when she took over this summer. She will also anchor the network's election specials and continue to contribute to "60 Minutes." She lives in New York, but she and the evening show will relocate to Washington later in the fall. The interview has been edited and condensed.  - - -  Q: What do wellness and self-care mean to you?  A: I really appreciate that you used the word self-care because I do think that health, exercise and wellness should be put in the category of self-care. Several years ago, I was sitting next to a friend of my husband's at an event, and he said: "How are you doing?" And I said, "Well, I'm doing fine. I'm doing this at work, and work is really busy, and you know the kids are really busy." And he said, "OK, but I'm asking about you and how you are doing." It really became this lightbulb moment that probably a lot of people can relate to: Our lives are defined by our work, and they're defined by our families, but we also need to be selfish when it comes to self-care.  I try to approach a lot of this stuff, whether it's what I eat or when I exercise, by asking: What am I doing to my body so that I can do the job that I do every day? I'm putting fuel in my body so that I can do all of the things that I really want to do and not worry about it. I approach nutrition that way, too. For breakfast I try to eat eggs, or blueberries with yogurt. Lunch can be hard when I'm running around, but I like to eat a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World on brink of unavoidable 'black swan' apocalypse, security panel warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/world-brink-unavoidable-black-swan-20531142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This type of disaster event is unforeseen and could have catastrophic consequences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY: 'Betrayal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/10/07/mitt-romney-trumps-syria-withdrawal-a-betrayal-of-kurds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitt Romney condemned President Trump's decision to withdraw U.S. troops in northern Syria, stating the move is a "betrayal" of the Kurds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:  'JOKER' Borders on Genius...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/10/joker-review-joaquin-phoenix-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regardless of my mixed feelings, I think it’s the best film about the psychological effect of violence as pop art since Stanley Kubrick’s ‘A Clockwork Orange.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Ilhan Omar Files For Divorce From Husband...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/07/ilhan-omar-files-for-divorce-from-husband-amid-affair-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Ilhan Omar has filed for divorce from the father of her three kids, claiming the marriage is “irretrievable” – amid allegations that she had an affair with DC-based political…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Miracle' Dog Found Still Alive Under Rubble --- One Month After Hurricane Dorian!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/10/07/miracle-dog-saved-hurricane-dorian-debris-bahamas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone helped rescue a miracle dog trapped under buildings in the Bahamas one month after Hurricane Dorian devastated the Bahamas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Syria withdrawal announcement draws GOP condemnation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ac3115b4eb564288a03a5b8be868d2e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's sudden decision to pull back U.S. troops from northern Syria drew quick criticism Monday from some of his closest allies in Congress as well as Kurdish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY MOVES IN...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191007152713-1kbux</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-STATE (URGENT):U.S. official says planned Turkish incursion into Syria 'very bad idea'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces crucial decision on trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/trump-faces-crucial-decision-on-china-as-both-economies-strain/ar-AAIozia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Nasdaq CEO warns recent IPOs like tech bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/07/ex-nasdaq-ceo-bob-greifeld-recent-ipos-remind-him-of-dot-com-bubble.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"At the end of the day, you've got to take away the hype," Bob Greifeld says about companies going public in today's climate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems foothold in swing district tested...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b54d3c867d854c8f8e4455b70adf78af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. (AP) — In front of New Hope Baptist Church in Virginia Beach, supporters of President Donald Trump hollered for his reelection. Behind it, taped-up signs on the doors warned,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Ilhan Omar Files For Divorce From Husband...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/10/07/rep-ilhan-omar-files-for-divorce-from-husband-ahmed-hirsi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Congresswoman Ilhan Omar has filed for divorce, according to court records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican considers ordaining married men, giving women official church ministries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7dcb69eae7a4938a70757bc47ca4c33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis urged South American bishops on Monday to speak "courageously" at a high-profile meeting on the Amazon, where the shortage of priests is so acute that the Vatican...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd whistleblower may give House Dems fresh info...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6ad09244d0a4e159a7c9c416507e70e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats leading an impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump's dealings with Ukraine may have fresh information to work with after a new whistleblower stepped forward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Deepfake 'Arms Race'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-deepfake-arms-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can countermeasures neutralize the coming wave of high-tech disinformation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial 'SLAVE PLAY' Opens on Broadway; Begins with Graphic Sex, Ends with Rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/10/06/review-controversial-slave-play-opens-on-broadway-begins-with-graphic-sex-play-ends-with-a-rape-critics-love-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I did not care for “Slave Play.” The only other writer who agrees with me it seems is Variety’s Marilyn Stasio. The rest of the Broadway crowd can’t get enough of it. If you…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN: Harvey Spies Hacked My Phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/annals-of-espionage/the-black-cube-chronicles-the-private-investigators</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How two operatives tasked with surveilling reporters became embroiled in an international plot to suppress sexual-assault allegations against Harvey Weinstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOUTH PARK' Scrubbed From Chinese Internet After Critical Episode...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/south-park-banned-chinese-internet-critical-episode-1245783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the "Band in China" episode mocked Hollywood for shaping its content to please the Chinese government, Beijing has responded by deleting all clips, episodes and discussions of the Comedy Central show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concentration Camp Survivors: China Using Forced Sterilization, Abortion for Genocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2019/10/07/concentration-camp-survivors-china-using-forced-sterilization-abortion-for-genocide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women who have survived China's concentration camps reported rape, forced abortions, and other extreme sexual human rights atrocities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND WHISTLEBLOWER COMES FORWARD...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a6ad09244d0a4e159a7c9c416507e70e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats leading an impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump's dealings with Ukraine may have fresh information to work with after a new whistleblower stepped forward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Drinking 3 Cups Of Coffee, Tea Daily Can Trigger Migraines...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-drinking-3-cups-coffee-tea-daily-can-trigger-migraines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three or more servings of a caffeinated beverage in one day is associated with the development of a headache on the same or following day among patients who suffer from episodic migraines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restoring felon voting rights 'mess' in battleground Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-florida-felons-insight/restoring-felon-voting-rights-a-mess-in-battleground-florida-idUSKBN1WM0YV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clifford Tyson wants to help choose America’s next president. But the Florida re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump Exec Predicts President Will Resign 'To Save Face'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/former-trump-exec-predicts-trump-will-resign-over-impeachment-threat-to-save-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former executive of the Trump Organization believes that Donald Trump will resign the presidency out of fear of where the threat of impeachment will take him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVT CONSIDERING KILLING INTERNET...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/hong-kong-government-considering-internet-ban-to-stop-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mimicking how Chinese authorities routinely block web to stifle unrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy pilot says mystery 'dark mass' emerged from ocean and swallowed torpedo...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/navy-pilot-says-mystery-dark-20529086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commander David Fravor shot to fame for his account of the USS Nimitz UFO encounter – but he has now claimed something even spookier was spotted some 10 years earlier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials bringing back the mustache...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/05/millennials-are-binging-back-the-mustache/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goodbye, lumberjack beard: A substantial ’stache is the facial-hair trend du jour among style-conscious millennials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average commute time hits record...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Average-commute-time-reached-a-new-record-last-14497488.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average American commute grew to just over 27 minutes one way in 2018, a record high, according to data released in September by the U.S. Census Bureau.  The average American has added about two minutes to their one-way commute since 2009, the data shows. That may not sound like a lot, but those numbers add up: The typical commuter now spends 20 more minutes a week commuting than they did a decade ago. Over the course of a year, it works out to about 17 additional hours commuting.  Relative to 1980, the picture is even more grim: Since then, American workers have lost nearly an hour a week to their commutes, the equivalent of one full-time workweek over the course of a year. All told, the average American worker spent 225 hours, or well over nine full calendar days, commuting in 2018.  The shift is being driven in large part by an increase in the share of workers with long commutes. In 2010, about 8 percent of workers had a one-way commute of 60 minutes or more. By 2018, that share had edged up to nearly 10 percent. As of 2018, there were 4.3 million workers with commutes of 90 minutes or more, up from 3.3 million in 2010.  Rising commute times reflect the challenges of life in many metropolitan areas where new housing isn't being built fast enough. As a result, many workers are forced out to far-flung suburbs and exurban areas in search of affordable homes.  Transit and infrastructure woes are another factor. Many metropolitan areas put off necessary spending on roads, bridges and public transit as their populations soared, creating congestion as people try to get to and from work. In Washington, D.C., daily Metro ridership has fallen by 17 percent since 2008 while the population of the greater metro region has grown by several hundred thousand, resulting in one of the worst commutes in the nation.  Research has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was There Really an Exorcism at Fort Bragg?</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/off-duty/2019/10/02/was-there-really-exorcism-fort-bragg.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did famed Catholic priest Malachi Martin really travel to the Army base for an exorcism?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Warren Presidency Might Not Be So Bad for Stocks, RBC Says...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-presidency-might-not-bad-091019608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Concern on Wall Street has been rising along with 2020 Democratic presidential contender Elizabeth Warren’s poll numbers. But worries about her potential success may be overdone, according to RBC Capital Markets.“Any pain from a Warren win is likely to be temporary,” Lori Calvasina, RBC</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
