<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bull run finale not far off?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-stocks-global-poll/bull-run-finale-for-global-stocks-not-far-off-now-reuters-poll-idUSKCN1NY00L</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An end to the bull run in global stocks is not far away, according to a Reuters ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola epicenter hit with malaria outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/745154/ebola-malaria-double-epidemic-democratic-republic-of-kivu-world-health-organisation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2-FOOT-TALL squirrels in NCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article222294420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Carolina coast has a seldom seen breed of squirrel that is 2 feet tall and weighs as much as a chihuahua. A state camera trap program is capturing images of these fox squirrels in remote areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVERDOSES RECORD HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-life-expectancy-drops-again-overdoses-climb-055720445.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life expectancy in the United States dropped yet again as drug overdose deaths continued to climb -- taking more than 70,000 lives in 2017 -- and suicides rose, a US government report said Thursday. The drug overdose rate rose 9.6 percent compared to 2016, while suicides climbed 3.7 percent, said the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK, Computer: How Much Is House Worth?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ok-computer-how-much-is-my-house-worth-1543492800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal regulators have proposed loosening real-estate appraisal requirements to enable a majority of U.S. homes to be bought and sold without being evaluated by a licensed human appraiser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Abs, Hottest Workout for Fingers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/forget-your-washboard-abs-the-hottest-workout-is-for-your-fingers-1543422250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serious rock climbers train their digits by clinging to tiny ledges inches off the ground, lifting heavy grocery bags, and something called the ‘Transgression.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Watch adds years to life?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/apple-watch-could-add-two-years-life-research-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple watches could add two years to your life, a major study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUICIDES 50-YEAR PEAK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/de57909c5bcc4162b122948539ed9c6a </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Suicides and drug overdoses pushed up U.S. deaths last year, and drove a continuing decline in how long Americans are expected to live. Overall, there were more than 2.8 million U.S. deaths in 2017, or nearly 70,000 more than the previous year, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Thursday. It was the most deaths in a single year since the government began counting more than a century ago. The increase partly reflects the nation's growing and aging population. But it's deaths in younger age groups — particularly middle-aged people — that have had the largest impact on calculations of life expectancy, experts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If your TESLA knows where you are, Beijing may too...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4a749a4211904784826b45e812cff4ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHANGHAI (AP) — When Shan Junhua bought his white Tesla Model X, he knew it was a fast, beautiful car. What he didn't know is that Tesla constantly sends information about the precise location of his car to the Chinese government. Tesla is not alone. China has called upon all electric vehicle manufacturers in China to make the same kind of reports — potentially adding to the rich kit of surveillance tools available to the Chinese government as President Xi Jinping steps up the use of technology to track Chinese citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German antitrust agency opens AMAZON investigation...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-german-antitrust-agency-amazon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's antitrust agency says it has begun an investigation of online retailer Amazon to over complaints it's abusing its position to the detriment of sellers who use its "marketplace" platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE EXPECTANCY FALLS FURTHER</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-life-expectancy-falls-further-1543467660</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Life expectancy for Americans fell again last year, despite growing recognition of the problems driving the decline and federal and local funds invested in stemming them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK Offices Searched in Money-Laundering Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/german-prosecutors-search-deutsche-bank-premises-over-money-laundering-probe-1543484932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank offices were searched by police and prosecutors seeking evidence in connection with alleged money laundering, the Frankfurt prosecutor’s office said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi, Backing Away From Plea Deal, Wants to Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/corsi-backing-away-from-plea-deal-wants-to-take-on-mueller</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corsi, Backing Away From Plea Deal, Wants to Take On Mueller</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jay-Z says panel 'too white' to be fair in trademark case...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/28/jay-z-says-panel-is-too-white-to-be-fair-in-trademark-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best-selling rapper and entrepreneur is suing to stop the American Arbitration Association from judging a trademark case, saying the panel is too lily-white to be fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Ma using AI to create dystopian cities?</title>
      <link>Jack Ma using AI to create dystopian cities?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Economy, Storm Clouds on Horizon...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/for-the-u-s-economy-storm-clouds-on-the-horizon/18025978/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Emerging signs of weakness in major economic sectors, including auto manufacturing, agriculture and home building, are prompting some forecasters to warn that one of the longest periods of economic growth in U.S. history may be approaching the end of its run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Bobbie Talks, I'm Finished': How Moonves Tried to Silence Accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraphindia.com/world/if-bobbie-talks-i-m-finished-how-cbs-boss-les-moonves-tried-to-silence-an-accuser/cid/1676977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraphindia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress recollected Moonves saying: “Be my girlfriend and I’ll put you on any show.” Then he grabbed her by the neck, pushed her to her knees and forced his penis into her mouth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORMY: Avenatti Filed Trump Defamation Case Against My Wishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/stormy-daniels-michael-avenatti-filed-defamation-case-against-trump-against-my-wishes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The porn star also says her lawyer refused to give her information about how her crowdfunding money was being spent, and launched a second crowdfund without her knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel investigating candidate Trump's late-night calls to Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Mueller-s-team-investigating-candidate-Trump-s-13429790.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The calls almost always came deep into the night. Caller ID labeled them "unknown," but Roger Stone said he knew to pick up fast during those harried months of the 2016 presidential campaign. There would be a good chance that the voice on the other end of the line would belong to his decadeslong friend - the restless, insomniac candidate Donald Trump - dialing from a blocked phone number. Those nocturnal chats and other contacts between the man who now occupies the Oval Office and an infamous political trickster have come under intensifying scrutiny as special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation bores into whether Stone served as a bridge between Trump and WikiLeaks as the group was publishing hacked Democratic emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani bragging may prove problematic...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2018/11/28/giulianis-bizarre-bragging-about-manafort-trump-alliance-raises-new-obstruction-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could Giuliani and Paul Manafort's lawyer get in any trouble?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glowing green fireball seen over Putin secret weapons lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7854332/mystery-glowing-green-fireball-top-secret-research-lab-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GLOWING green fireball buzzing over Russia’s hi-tech “scientific city” in Siberia has sparked claims Vladimir Putin could be developing space weapons. The bright flash and streaking tail was seen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Time to set record straight'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/stormy-daniels-says-michael-avenatti-sued-trump-defamation-against-her-n941446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a phone interview with NBC News, Avenatti said he was surprised by her allegations, and said "a number of things" were "not accurate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: PRESIDENT'S KEY ANSWERS MADE UNDER OATH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/trump-mueller-answers-wikileaks-trump-tower/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump told special counsel Robert Mueller in writing that Roger Stone did not tell him about WikiLeaks, nor was he told about the 2016 Trump Tower meeting between his son, campaign officials and a Russian lawyer promising dirt on Hillary Clinton, according to two sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff says written responses not adequate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/418807-schiff-says-trumps-written-responses-to-mueller-are-not-adequate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind man with seeing eye dog attacked on DC Metro...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/local/dc/18-year-old-juvenile-arrested-for-assault-of-blind-man-on-metro-red-line-train/65-618510816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The assault happened at the Rhode Island Avenue Metro Stop on the Red Line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half As Many Employees Protest China Censored Search As Protested Pentagon Project...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/28/google-employees-chinese-surveillance-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Don't be evil'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities raid TX Archdiocese, search for 'secret archives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Authorities-raid-Archdiocese-of-Galveston-Houston-13427999.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are raiding the offices of the Archdiocese of Galveston-Houston for additional evidence in the case of a Conroe priest accused of sexual misconduct, according to the Montgomery County District Attorney’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm terrorized by rhyme and riddle extortion; Barn burned, animals harmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/fbi-investigates-violence-threats-targeting-hollis-farm/25325208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials are investigating an extortion case involving a Hollis farm that they said has been the target of violence, threats and animal abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alien artifacts' may be lurking in solar system, Harvard astronomers claim...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/28/mysterious-alien-artefacts-could-be-lurking-in-our-solar-system-astronomer-claims-8185768/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stargazer says studying 'interstellar objects' which arrived here from deep space could allow us to discover proof of extraterrestrial life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online sex ads rebound after shutdown of BACKPAGE...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-online-sex-ads-rebound-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smaller escort websites are vying for the lucrative online sex-for-hire market Backpage.com dominated before U.S. authorities shut it down earlier this year, a move that fractured the industry and forced law enforcement to adapt their efforts combating sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger says DELTA pilot used GRINDR to hit on him DURING flight...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/28/passenger-says-delta-pilot-used-grindr-to-hit-on-him-during-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger onboard a Delta plane was creeped out after a pilot messaged him on Grindr during their flight. JP Thorn, a 27-year-old college student, told The Post that the strange interaction happe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian hackers charged with attacks on US cities...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2018/11/28/news/nation/justice-department-charges-iranian-hackers-with-attacks-on-us-cities-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defendants, Faramarz Shah Savandi and Mohammad Mehd Shah Mansouri, were charged with conspiring to hack victims between December 2015 and this month. The suspects are believed to be in Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alberto Gonzales: Problem With Perjury Traps...</title>
      <link>http://insider.foxnews.com/2018/11/28/alberto-gonzales-robert-mueller-setting-perjury-traps-would-be-unfair-and-unprofessional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;insider.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Attorney General Alberto Gonzales said that it'd be "unfair" and "unprofessional" for the special counsel's team to set perjury traps in its Russia probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-year-old dies after duo crash into her...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/90-year-old-woman-dies-collision-electric-scooter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 90-year-old Spanish woman has died after a collision with an electric scooter in what is believed to be the first accident of its kind in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If Bobbie Talks, I'm Finished': How Moonves Tried to Silence Accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/28/business/les-moonves-bobbie-phillips-marv-dauer-cbs-severance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trove of text messages details a plan by Mr. Moonves and a faded Hollywood manager to bury a sexual assault allegation. Instead, the scheme helped sink the CBS chief, and may cost him $120 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mnuchin Says His TWITTER Was Compromised, Deletes GM Retweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-28/mnuchin-suggests-his-twitter-was-compromised-deletes-retweet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein returns -- at least on screen...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/sundance-film-festival-premieres-lineup-harvey-weinstein-movie-toni-morrison-miles-davis-dr-ruth-full-list-1202510342/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein is returning to the Sundance Film Festival, at least on screen. A looming and powerful presence at the Robert Redford founded huddle for decades, an Ursula MacFarlane directed docu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asked about RNC platform change regarding Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/mueller-asked-trump-2016-rnc-platform-change-ukraine/story?id=59476035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller asked Trump about 2016 RNC platform change regarding Ukraine: Sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems overwhelmingly nominate Pelosi as Speaker amid rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/418653-democrats-overwhelmingly-nominate-pelosi-as-speaker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats voted overwhelmingly Wednesday to nominate Rep. Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) to the Speakership in a 203-32 vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Helium Shortage Making Party Balloons Scarce...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/11/27/deflated-excitement-national-helium-shortage-making-party-balloons-hard-to-find/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nationally, helium is in demand for things more important than balloons right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data scientist cracks NYTIMES Best Seller list code...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/a-data-scientist-cracks-the-code-to-landing-on-the-new-york-times-best-seller-list-2018-11-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Write a mystery, romance or memoir. And publish in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB Slammed as 'Anti-Semitic'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/trump-admin-congress-slam-airbnb-boycott-israel-anti-semitic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent decision by Airbnb to stop its services for Jews living in the West Bank of Israel is being met with criticism by the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBERXXX: MAN WHO 'LIKED TO MASTURBATE IN FRONT OF DRIVERS' ARRESTED...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/indecent-exposure/the-sharing-economy-375902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iowa man was arrested today for allegedly exposing himself in an Uber car and telling the driver that he “liked to masturbate in front of Uber drivers,” according to a court complaint. Christopher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisoners sextort $500k from troops in dating app scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2018/11/28/prisoners-steal-more-than-500k-from-troops-through-dating-app-sextortion-ring/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NCIS agents executed arrest warrants Wednesday in connection to a sextortion ring that has victimized hundreds of service members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta postal workers busted delivering cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/postal-workers-took-bribes-deliver-cocaine-metro-atlanta/uHYRAe7ASqytzDBRReJFqO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixteen U.S. Postal Servies workers in metro Atlanta were sentenced for delivering cocaine in exchange for bribes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes poised to limit police power to seize property...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f60d5690704648edbf7a967cb6d6e8df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court left little doubt Wednesday that it would rule that the Constitution's ban on excessive fines applies to the states, an outcome that could help an Indiana man recover the $40,000 Land Rover police seized when they arrested him for selling about $400 worth of heroin. A decision in favor of 37-year-old Tyson Timbs, of Marion, Indiana, also could buttress efforts to limit the confiscation by local law enforcement of property belonging to someone suspected of a crime. Police and prosecutors often keep the proceeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Suspect Scrap Metal Thieves In Theft Of 300-Pound Menorah From Synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/28/menorah-stolen-brookline-temple-emeth-found-west-roxbury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Menorah stolen from a temple in Brookline was found in Boston Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATTIS:  'No smoking gun' linking to Khashoggi killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa-mattis-statement/u-s-defense-chief-no-smoking-gun-linking-saudi-crown-prince-to-khashoggi-killing-idUSKCN1NX2JE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary James Mattis said on Wednesday the United States has &amp;quo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Crashes On Highway -- While Watching NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/27/netflix-while-driving-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Patrol is reminding people not to Netflix and drive after a woman crashed her vehicle while watching the streaming service on her iPad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French film star Depardieu questioned in rape probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-film-star-depardieu-questioned-rape-probe-173951109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police have questioned film star Gerard Depardieu over allegations that he raped a young actress, which he strongly denies, a police source said Wednesday. The source said the 69-year-old actor attended a police interview on Tuesday and is not being kept in custody. "Gerard Depardieu absolutely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 78-year-old man may be most prolific serial killer in US history...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/78-old-man-may-most-prolific-serial-killer-180730498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 78-year-old drifter in prison in Texas has confessed to 90 murders and is being investigated as possibly the most prolific serial killer in US history. Samuel Little preyed mainly on drug addicts and prostitutes during a decades-long murder spree that stretched from coast to coast, the Federal Bureau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  White liberals dumb down vocabulary when speaking to minorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/nov/28/white-liberals-patronize-minorities-downplaying-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White liberals present themselves as less competent when addressing minorities, while conservatives use the same vocabulary no matter what the race of their audience, according to a newly released study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO to allow use of X as sex identifier on driver's licenses...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2018/11/08/colorado-drivers-license-x-gender/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado residents who do not identify as male or female will be allowed to choose “X” as the symbol to represent their gender on their driver’s licenses when an emergency rule go…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed chair hints at higher rates following President's attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-fed-chairman-hints-higher-rates-following-trump-172525241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after President Donald Trump's latest attack on the US central bank, Federal Reserve chief Jerome Powell hinted that the key lending rate would move higher but said there was no preset course. Powell said in a speech in New York that interest rates remained "low by historical standards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR fires film critic after 'LAST TANGO' rape joke...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ba3b94c975a4ba1a5861c4d50730cdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — NPR's "Fresh Air" has parted ways with contributor David Edelstein after the film critic made a joke about the rape scene in "Last Tango in Paris" on his Facebook page following Monday's death of director Bernardo Bertolucci. In a statement Tuesday, "Fresh Air" said the post was "offensive and unacceptable" because of what actress Maria Schneider experienced filming the scene. Schneider said in a 2007 interview that the simulated sex scene was unscripted and that she felt bullied by Bertolucci and unsupported by her co-star Marlon Brando. "I was crying real tears," said Schneider, who died in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Chair Powell signals interest rates near neutral...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/28/stock-market-wall-street-looks-to-fed-chair-speech-and-trade-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Wednesday as investors awaited a key speech from the top Federal Reserve official, while hope that a U.S.-China trade truce could come lifted sentiment on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang Members Charged In L.A. Celebrity Burglary Spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/10-accused-gang-members-charged-celeb-home-burglaries-1164445</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities accused the men of going after their high-profile targets when they knew the house's resident would be out of town on business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MURPHY BROWN' Reboot Canceled Amid Historically Low Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/murphy-brown-happy-together-end-initial-orders-cbs-1164428</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As CBS continues to solidify its midseason lineup, both rookie series will make way on the schedule for freshman 'Fam' and the third season of 'Man With a Plan,' while 'Criminal Minds' hits the bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Committee Examines Whether TWITTER Dorsey Lied in Testimony...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/house-committee-examines-whether-twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-lied-in-his-testimony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEO swore his company's rules aren't political...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi IPO advisor spends $62 million on NYC penthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wall-street-rainmaker-shells-out-62-million-for-manhattan-penthouse-1543420249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investment banker Ken Moelis purchased a six-bedroom unit at 520 Park Avenue in one of New York’s biggest transactions of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming spike in dolphin deaths off Florida coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/sarasota-county/researchers-suddenly-see-alarming-spike-in-dolphin-deaths-across-southwest-florida/1622771062</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past few days, an alarming number of dead dolphins have washed ashore along southwest Florida beaches, including in the Tampa Bay area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  New Home Sales Collapse 8.9%, Far Worse Than Expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy-housing/u-s-new-home-sales-drop-to-more-than-2-1-2-year-low-idUSKCN1NX1WU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of new U.S. single-family homes tumbled to a more than 2-1/2-year low in O...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injured electric scooter riders flooding emergency rooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/electric-scooters-by-bird-and-lime-are-causing-injuries-and-accidents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Injured scooter riders are flooding US emergency rooms. Accident rates could be as high as 1,000 per month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA:  America Has a 'Great Smugness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/video/2018/11/28/obama-america-has-a-great-smugness-about-wealth-status/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While speaking Tuesday at Rice University’s Baker Center with author Jon Meacham and former White House chief of staff, James Baker, former President | Video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight-time deported 'drug mule' headed back to prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/11/27/eight-time-deportee-gets-5-years-for-illegally-re-entering-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge sentenced a Honduran national to five years in federal prison for illegally re-entering the U.S. after being deported eight times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China defends Jack Ma after outed as Communist...</title>
      <link>http://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1129282.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.globaltimes.cn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our Joe McCarthy era'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-lashes-mueller-probe-joe-mccarthy-era-152144569.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump lashed out once more at the head of the Russia probe Robert Mueller Wednesday, accusing him of pressuring witnesses to lie, while retweeting an image that shows the US president's perceived adversaries behind bars. Among the dozen figures it showed behind bars were former president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China scientist defends gene-editing babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/gene-edited-baby-trial-paused-china-scientist-070016806.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese scientist who claims to have created the world's first genetically-edited babies defended the highly controversial procedure Wednesday, but announced a halt to the trial following an international outcry. "The clinical trial was paused due to the current situation," said He</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims break silence to MIAMI HEARLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article220097825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach multimillionaire Jeffrey Epstein was accused of sexually abusing dozens of underage girls. Prosecutors, including future Trump labor secretary Alexander Acosta, cut Epstein an extraordinary plea deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops worked to put  Epstein in prison. Prosecutors worked to cut him a break...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article214210674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexander Acosta and Jeffrey Epstein’s attorneys — including Alan Dershowitz and Ken Starr — stitched together an extraordinary deal, allowing Epstein to escape federal sex charges and never serve time in a federal or state prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince arrives in Buenos Aires for G20...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/saudi-crown-prince-arrives-buenos-aires-g20-115742296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman arrived in Buenos Aires on Wednesday to join a Group of 20 summit, media reported, as he aims to shrug off the lingering stigma of journalist Jamal Khashoggi's murder. The prince was received at the airport by Argentina's foreign minister Jorge Faurie,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to Capture Space Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/11/amazons-plan-capture-space-data/153088/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon launched a new service that can port data from commercial satellites directly into its cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TWEETS WARNING TO OPPONENTS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/418630-trump-shares-image-calling-for-his-opponents-to-face-trials-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday morning shared an image calling for his opponents to face trial for "treason," with many of them behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Robosexuality' on rise as thousands now sharing sex-bot porn online...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7849874/robosexuality-sex-robots-sexbot-porn-forum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROBOSEXUALITY is on the rise as hi-tech horn-dogs take to the internet to share creepy sex-bot pornography. Forums dedicated to sex-bot smut have sprung up across the web, drawing in thousands of o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants Regret Caravan: 'I'm Done With the United States'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/migrants-in-tijuana-regret-the-caravan-im-done-with-the-united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After being gassed by the U.S. and held in a camp by Mexico, hope is running out for some who left Honduras with dreams of a better life in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV epidemic as Europe sees its highest ever rate of infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7847597/hiv-epidemic-eastern-europe-infection-highest-rate-infection-spread/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE than 130,000 people were newly diagnosed with HIV last year in Eastern Europe, the highest rate ever for the region. As the number of infected sky rocketed in one half of the continent the num…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missionary killed by tribe 'may still be ALIVE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7835035/john-chau-missionary-killed-tribe-may-still-be-alive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHRISTIAN missionary who was shot dead with bows and arrows on a remote Indian island may have survived the attack, his friends and family believe. American John Allen Chau, 26, was reportedly ki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii man who suffered heart attack during missile false alarm sues state...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/hawaii-man-who-suffered-heart-attack-during-missile-false-alarm-n941081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Both plaintiffs believed this message to be true and were extremely frightened and thought they were going to die," the lawsuit says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland high school football players accused of raping teammates...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/four-maryland-high-school-football-players-accused-raping-teammates-n941126</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors said that the football players targeted smaller teammates, threw them to the ground and stomped on them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared to be honored with Mexico's highest honor!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/27/jared-kushner-to-be-honored-with-mexicos-order-of-the-aztec/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His father-in-law may be squabbling with the country over trade and immigration, but White House adviser Jared Kushner will receive the highest honor Mexico can bestow on foreigners, according to a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist claiming gene-edited babies reports 2nd pregnancy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3dcd5d7c599e4694b2f13c6ab03ef399</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — A Chinese researcher who claims to have helped make the world's first genetically edited babies says a second pregnancy may be underway. The researcher, He Jiankui of Shenzhen, revealed the pregnancy Wednesday while making his first public comments about his controversial work at an international conference in Hong Kong. He claims to have altered the DNA of twin girls born earlier this month to try to make them resistant to infection with the AIDS virus. Mainstream scientists have condemned the experiment, and universities and government groups are investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brushes aside Mueller probe...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/exclusive-ivanka-trump-defends-private-email-brushes-mueller/story?id=59455437</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump maintained that all of the emails on her private account were properly archived and contained no classified information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's behavior toward military 'disturbing': Retired Gen. McChrystal...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trumps-behavior-military-disturbing-retired-gen-stanley-mcchrystal/story?id=59442288</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On ABC News' Powerhouse Politics Podcast, retired Army Gen. Stanley McChrystal said Trump's behavior toward the military is upsetting. He also discussed his new book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida FREEZING...</title>
      <link>https://www.wftv.com/weather/chilly-week-ahead-as-major-cold-front-moves-into-central-florida/878705255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wftv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bundle up! The coldest weather in more than eight months has arrived in Central Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel unveils rare and ancient mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181128-israel-unveils-rare-ancient-mask</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American missionary shot by isolated tribe 'may still be ALIVE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/745091/us-missionary-shot-north-sentinal-tribe-still-alive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team fakes death of player to try to avoid game...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/soccer/2018/11/28/soccer-irish-team-ballybrack-fc-apologizes-faking-players-death/2135669002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ballybrack FC, a lower-level Irish soccer team, apologized for faking the death of one of its players in an apparent attempt to avoid upcoming game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College gives professors hockey pucks to fight off shooters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/michigan-university-gives-professors-hockey-pucks-to-fight-off-shooters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of, you know, guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS: Massive Levies in Carbon Tax Bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/details-horrible-carbon-tax-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How FACEBOOK and 'frat-boy billionaire' Zuckerberg were torn to shreds...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/facebook-and-mark-zuckerberg-shredded-by-lawmakers-at-fake-news-hearing-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers from nine countries tore into Facebook on Tuesday during an international committee hearing in Westminster, London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch rail company to pay reparations for WWII deportations...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d32f62be86e0476b801a3a5b382ec593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The Dutch national railway company is setting up a commission to investigate how it can pay individual reparations for its role in mass deportations of Jews by Nazi occupiers during World War II. In a written statement, the rail company, NS, said that its involvement in the deportations "is a black page in the history of our country and our company." Company spokesman Erik Kroeze said Wednesday that the commission will look at making payments to Dutch Holocaust survivors and direct family members of Jews who died at the hands of the Nazis. He said it is not yet clear how many people could be eligible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poo found on every MCDONALD'S touchscreen tested...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/28/poo-found-on-every-mcdonalds-touchscreen-tested-8178486/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samples were taken from the new machines that have been rolled out at restaurants across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unruly' young boy upstages Pope...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-boy/unruly-young-boy-upstages-pope-francis-idUSKCN1NX18J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young boy upstaged Pope Francis on Wednesday, escaping from his mother and run...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furhat, a robot with the human touch, wants to hear your woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-robot-mask/furhat-a-robot-with-the-human-touch-wants-to-hear-your-woes-idUSKCN1NX0U4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furhat tilts his or her head, smiles, exudes empathy and warmth, and encourages ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First pictures of World Cup stadium ridiculed for looking like 'vagina'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/first-pictures-qatar-world-cup-13657047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 40,000-seater venue in Al-Wakrah has drawn some rather rude comparisons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China warns USA trade war could escalate into 'Great Depression, World War'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/asia/201811281070198623-china-us-trade-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is considering sanctions against companies and officials linked to China's alleged crackdown on the country’s minority Muslims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Churches Dying Each Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/between-6000-and-10000-churches-in-the-u-s-are-dying-each-year-and-that-means-that-over-100-will-die-this-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any institution needs resources in order to survive, and churches are not any different</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major storm to bring snow, rain to West Coast...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/major-storm-bring-snow-rain-west-coast/story?id=59464811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new storm system is about to slam California with heavy rain and heavy snow. Numerous flash flood watches have been posted for burn scar areas in the northern part of the state all the way to just outside of Los Angeles and San Diego. A winter storm warning has been issued for the Sierra...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies before voting, wife returns to cast her ballot...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyjournal.net/2018/11/28/us-election-2018-dying-voter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyjournal.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election officials say a Mississippi man died on the way to vote with his wife who went back later to cast her ballot</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
