<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Sophisticated' new Chinese hacking tool found...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/united-states-canada/article/3168740/sophisticated-new-chinese-hacking-tool-found</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cybersecurity firm Symantec says the malware, which it calls Daxin, has been used to target high level, non-Western government agencies in Asia and Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oligarchs move yachts as USA looks to 'hunt down', freeze assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/28/russian-oligarchs-move-yachts-as-us-moves-to-hunt-down-and-freeze-assets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian oligarchs are moving their yachts as the United States and its allies look to target personal property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US NETFLIX to be forced to broadcast Putin propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/us-streaming-giant-netflix-set-to-broadcast-putin-propaganda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix comes under new rules in Russia on March 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Ambassador Calls for Putin to Kill Himself Like Hitler 'Did in Bunker'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ukrainian-ambassador-to-un-calls-for-putin-to-kill-himself-like-hitler-did-in-a-bunker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine’s ambassador to the United Nations called on Russian President Vladimir Putin to kill himself like Adolf Hitler “did in a bunker.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Fighters Rushing to Join War...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akvyq4/russian-ukraine-invasion-foreign-fighters-battalion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of a volunteer unit told VICE World News hundreds of foreign fighters had signed up following a direct appeal by Ukraine's President Volodymyr Zelenskyy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA faces new lawsuit over lucrative shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/moderna-faces-new-lawsuit-over-lucrative-coronavirus-vaccine/ar-AAUpsmL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN 'PROPAGANDA CHIEF' THREATENS WEST WITH '500 NUKES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4789026/putins-propaganda-chief-threatens-west-with-nuclear-destruction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s “propaganda chief” has threatened the West with nuclear annihilation during a rambling broadcast on Russian TV. News anchor Dmitry Kiselyov told viewers across Ru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew could face more sex abuse lawsuits...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4749540/prince-andrew-sexual-abuse-lawsuits-grope-royal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew could face more sex abuse lawsuits in the US due to a potential change in the law – including from a woman who claims she was groped by the disgraced royal.  The Duke of Yo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/02/28/review-the-batman-brings-david-fincher-like-darkness-to-a-young-goth-bruce-wayne-and-a-woke-catwoman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia thrown out of soccer World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/breaking-russia-banned-fifa-uefa-26350537</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FIFA and UEFA have moved to ban Russian clubs and its national teams from footballing competition following Russia's attacks on Ukraine ordered by president Vladimir Putin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-reviews/batman-robert-pattinson-1235100390/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Caped Crusader is back on Gotham City’s crime-infested streets, exposing corruption at the highest levels in Matt Reeves’ reboot, also featuring Zoë Kravitz, Paul Dano and Colin Farrell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Woman attacked with human feces in NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/woman-attacked-with-feces-to-the-face/3574539/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are looking for a man who smeared human feces on the face and back of the head of a 43-year-old woman who was sitting on a subway station bench on a Bronx platform during the evening rush last week, authorities say. The woman was sitting on the bench on the southbound platform at the East 241st Street station around…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking scenes at Ukraine border sees thousands of kids separated from dads...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-heartbreaking-evacuation-ukraine-many-26343744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mirror reporter Andy Lines is on the frontline of the evacuation efforts across Ukraine as thousands are faced with the devastating decision to run in a bid to save their lives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm staying for those jews who cannot flee, pledges Kyiv Chief Rabbi...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/news/im-staying-for-those-who-cannot-flee-pledges-kyiv-chief-rabbi-2rTJXEnrM2aCK4B0uZJJ79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Trading Platform Founder Indicted in $2 Billion 'Global Ponzi Scheme'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2022/02/founder-crypto-trading-platform-bitconnect-indicted-global-ponzi-scheme/362512/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice charged Satish Kumbhani with conspiracy to commit fraud and misleading investors in the latest crypto crackdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Woman attacked with human feces in NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-subway-feces-attack-investigated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in New York were investigating a very disturbing subway attack in which a woman was struck in the face and the back of her head with human feces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invisible drones, robot tanks and attack dogs?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-unleash-nightmare-war-toys-26346047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin has a vast array of terrifying weapons at his disposal that he could use on Ukraine, including "invisible" T-14 robot super tanks and parachuting attack dog regiments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS bans models...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/onlyfans-bans-russian-models-selling-26345036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adult stars in Russia claim to have been banned from selling their X-rated content online as a result of sanctions imposed on Russia following Vladimir Putin's Ukraine invasion last week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>African Students Fleeing Ukraine Report Being Told 'No Blacks' Allowed on Buses...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2022/02/27/african-students-fleeing-ukraine-report-being-told-no-blacks-on-buses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boring to 'historic': The awakening of  Olaf Scholz...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220228-boring-to-historic-the-awakening-of-germany-s-olaf-scholz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often described as predictable and "robotic", Chancellor Olaf Scholz has become emboldened since Russia's invasion of Ukraine, smashing policy taboos to steer Germany into "a new era" that could resh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fears fade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-pandemics-public-health-only-on-ap-eaaf9967f97089f6e869b08573c292b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron is fading away, and so are Americans' worries about COVID-19. As coronavirus pandemic case numbers, hospitalizations and deaths continue to plummet, fewer people now than in January say they are concerned that they will be infected after the rise and fall of the wildly contagious virus variant, according to a new poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neutral Swiss adopt sanctions in break with past...</title>
      <link>https://www.deccanherald.com/international/world-news-politics/neutral-swiss-adopt-eu-sanctions-against-russia-in-break-with-past-1086204.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deccanherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neutral Switzerland will adopt European Union sanctions against Russians involved in Moscow's invasion of Ukraine and freeze their assets, the government said on Monday in a sharp deviation from the Alpine country's traditions. "In view of Russia’s continuing military intervention in Ukraine, the Federal Council took the decision on February 28 to adopt the packages of sanctions imposed by the EU on February 23 and 25," the government said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: What Courage Says About the West...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2022/02/volodymyr-zelensky-courage-ukraine-russia/622948/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ukrainian leader’s refusal to back down is as inspiring as it is illuminating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Most Americans More Sensitive To Noise Since Pandemic Began...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/noise-sensitivity-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be time to get your ears checked. More than half of Americans say they’ve become more sensitive to noise since the pandemic started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous takes down state run news services in major cyber attack...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/02/28/anonymous-hacks-russias-tass-news-service-with-latest-cyber-attack-16188295/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Websites belonging to TASS, Izvestia, Fontaka, RBC and Kommersant have been replaced with anti-Putin messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key interest rate doubles...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rouble-us-dollar-russia-interest-rates-101044165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's central bank has raised its key interest rate from 9.5% to 20% in an attempt to shore up the rouble after it plunged 30% to a record low against the dollar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON voice assistant Alexa to start seeking doctor help...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-health-lifestyle-dcc673a14cc14e1604a314f7df5fe46c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there is no doctor in the house, Amazon’s Alexa will soon be able to summon one. Amazon and telemedicine provider Teladoc Health are starting a voice-activated virtual care program that lets customers get medical help without picking up their phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians line up at banks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-japan-9fbeb1c66c523f4018abb8ebc6580839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Ordinary Russians faced the prospect of higher prices and crimped foreign travel as Western sanctions over the invasion of Ukraine sent the ruble plummeting, leading uneasy people to line up at banks and ATMs on Monday in a country that has seen more than one currency disaster in the post-Soviet era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How man's death in Beverly Hills exposed sprawling Hollywood drug delivery business...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/how-a-mans-death-in-beverly-hills-exposed-a-sprawling-hollywood-drug-delivery-business/ar-AAUpSfR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guns, radicalization and father's alleged threat: First Jan. 6 trial set to begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/guns-radicalization-and-a-father-e2-80-99s-alleged-threat-first-jan-6-trial-set-to-begin/ar-AAUpvod</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil unrest?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4786894/russian-ruble-trouble-western-sanctions-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUN on Russian banks has begun as Western sanctions send the ruble into freefall, sparking hopes of civil unrest against Vladimir Putin. Pictures show long queues outside cash machines in St Pete…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, European allies freeze 'Vlad's war chest' as Russia careens toward economic crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-european-allies-freeze-putin-s-war-chest-as-russia-careens-toward-economic-crisis/ar-AAUpyWR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New UN report warns of deadly climate consequences...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/596056-new-un-report-warns-of-deadly-climate-change-consequences</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from a United Nations climate panel is warning of deadly impacts of climate change both now and in the future — finding that those impacts are currently worse than scientists had believed they woul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Foreign Policy U-turn, Germany Ups Military Spending, Arms Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/27/in-foreign-policy-u-turn-germany-ups-military-spending-arms-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — It took an invasion of a sovereign country nearby, threats of nuclear attack, images of civilians facing off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On cusp of Biden speech, state of disunity, funk and peril...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-state-of-the-union-address-joe-biden-coronavirus-pandemic-39fc55c088ac4b5101dbb217e838fafb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In good times or bad, American presidents come to Congress with a diagnosis that hardly differs over the decades. In their State of the Union speeches, they declare “the state of our union is strong" or words very much like it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas primary is George P. Bush's biggest test yet in GOP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elections-austin-texas-donald-trump-george-p-bush-175e56cb746a986417ec43bc757557b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKEWAY, Texas (AP) — Fighting to stay in office, George P. Bush — the last of the Bush family still on the ballot — greeted a small outdoor crowd at an Austin brewery sounding like most Republicans running in Texas' primary Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Capitol riot cases could hinge on 1st trial's outcome...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-texas-riots-donald-trump-f7c650caa88498c510d7275662ae650f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department launched one of the largest and most complex criminal investigations in its history after a mob of Donald Trump supporters stormed the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BISHOP: Vlad is 'anti-Christ of our time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/ukrainian-bishop-putin-is-the-anti-christ-of-our-current-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Ukrainian archbishop and spokesman for the Orthodox Church of Ukraine condemned Russian President Vladimir Putin as the “anti-Christ of our current time" as Russia invades Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Life on moon by 2040' with plan for humans to survive off rocks in 'lunar village'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/life-moon-2040-plan-humans-26345847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Space Agency has made an £840,000 deal to make a blueprint for a new machine which extracts oxygen from moon rocks meaning the resources would be in place to create 'lunar villages'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market shuttered as ruble crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/28/business/russia-ruble-banks-sanctions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's currency crashed to a record low against the US dollar Monday as the country's financial system reeled from crushing sanctions imposed by Western countries in response to the invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland and Sweden to join NATO?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-united-states-moscow-sweden-finland-38bc14feac1d35c4c86dcb710b44f60c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Finland and Sweden have brushed off warnings from neighboring Russia that their possible joining of NATO would trigger “serious military-political consequences” from Moscow for the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin sends militia into Kyiv to assassinate Zelensky...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10558749/Kremlin-sends-400-mercenaries-Kyiv-assassinate-President-Zelensky.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A private militia known as the Wagner Group 'has orders from Vladimir Putin to decapitate Zelensky's government to pave the way for Moscow to take over.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified, stronger Europe emerging...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putins-fears-unified-stronger-europe-210531046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin's assault on Ukraine is turning his fears of a more resolute Europe and NATO alliance into a self-fulfilling prophecy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe sends fighter jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/europe-stares-down-putins-nuclear-threat-everything-is-on-the-table-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin’s open threat to use nuclear weapons against NATO allies supporting Ukraine appears to European officials to be a watershed in high-stakes brinkmanship that could foreshadow a new level of carnage in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking scenes at Ukraine border sees thousands of kids separated from dads...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4785056/ukraine-border-heartbreaking-scenes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UKRAINIAN rail hub was swamped by desperate families fleeing to Poland yesterday — as brave fighters piled on to trains heading the other way to join the war against Russia. Refugees from all ove…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC plans to lift vax mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/new-york-city-lifts-vaccine-mandate-businesses-events-rcna17415</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mask rules for city schools were likely to end the same day, March 7, Mayor Eric Adams said. Masks are optional at Tuesday’s State of the Union address in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump praises Zelensky as 'brave man' two years after extorting him for political dirt on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/world/trump-praises-zelensky-as-a-brave-man-two-years-after-he-tried-to-extort-him-for-political-dirt-on-biden/ar-AAUlZPm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump praises Zelensky as a 'brave man' two years after he tried to extort him for political dirt on Biden -</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 'paranoid' Vlad has lost his mind!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/fears-paranoid-putin-lost-mind-26340870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears have been shared over the mental health of Russian President Vladimir Putin, with rumours the pandemic scrambled his mind, leading to the brutal invasion of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ominous signs BEFORE invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/7-ominous-warning-signs-world-26340795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin, 69, rose to power in Russia in 2000 and is the longest-serving Kremlin leader since Soviet dictator Joseph Stalin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney Excoriates 'Disgusting' Pro-Putin Republicans: 'Almost Treasonous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/mitt-romney-excoriates-disgusting-pro-putin-republicans-almost-treasonous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Mitt Romney tore into his fellow Republicans who've spoken positively about Vladimir Putin while Ukraine remains under attack from Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Licht to be next CNN president...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-chris-licht-to-replace-jeff-zucker-as-cnn-president-per-dylan-byers-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Licht is reportedly set to become the next president of CNN, replacing Jeff Zucker who resigned earlier this month shocking the cable news world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. embassy advises Americans in Russia to leave 'immediately'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-embassy-americans-russia-73cb348a-4598-4749-b974-b0fc76c25766.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came hours after the EU announced that it would ban all Russian aircraft from its airspace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite pics: Huge Russian convoy converges on Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/satellite-image-russian-troops-approach-kyiv-15cd8239-89a1-4c81-96fc-e433102643ba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convoy is 3.25 miles long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky emerges as global hero...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/596036-zelenskyy-emerges-as-global-hero-in-ukraine-battle-against-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has emerged as a hero to his nation's citizens and far beyond as the former actor and comedian first elected in 2019 remains in his country at great personal risk during its bombardment by Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lost his grip'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/596063-barr-says-trump-lost-his-grip-in-forthcoming-memoir</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Attorney General William Barr writes in his forthcoming memoir that former President Trump “lost his grip” after the 2020 Presidential election, also urging the Republican party to find a different candidate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUKE CRAZY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-business-europe-moscow-2e4e1cf784f22b6afbe5a2f936725550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — President Vladimir Putin dramatically escalated East-West tensions by ordering Russian nuclear forces put on high alert Sunday, while Ukraine's embattled leader agreed to talks with Moscow as Putin's troops and tanks drove deeper into the country, closing in around the capital.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
