<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Reviews roundup: LIL NAS X new album impresses critics...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/montero-reviews-roundup-lil-nas-103503073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 15-track album has prompted many positive reactions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New disclosures show how General tried to check Trump. They could also further politicize military...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-disclosures-show-how-gen-mark-a-milley-tried-to-check-trump-they-could-also-further-politicize-the-military/ar-AAOy6s1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters say the country’s top officer sought to protect the Constitution, but some fear his actions could compound existing problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oath Keepers founder draws scrutiny from federal officials, followers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/oath-keepers-founder-draws-scrutiny-from-federal-officials-and-followers/ar-AAOxRIN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The private army that leader Stewart Rhodes boasts of is largely a myth. The real danger, extremism analysts say, is his ability to spread violent far-right propaganda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 10% of Kentucky deaths since June were under age 50, a fivefold increase...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/coronavirus/article254284698.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andy Beshear says the deadly virus is taking a toll on hospital staff and intensive care beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida county celebrated Hispanic Heritage Month with dancing Taco GIF. Outrage ensued...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Florida-county-celebrated-Hispanic-Heritage-Month-16466004.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The taco was supposed to be harmless, entertaining even.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St Influencers Making $500,000, Topping Bankers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-17/social-media-influencers-income-advertising-wall-street-products</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finance firms have long struggled to reach young and new customers — until now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 10,000 migrants await processing under bridge in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/572712-more-than-10000-haitian-migrants-await-processing-under-bridge-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 10,000 mostly Haitian migrants were crowded under a border bridge in South Texas awaiting processing Thursday, prompting U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ reviewing policies on trans inmates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-crime-prisons-minnesota-illinois-007d87693249a9831867a5289c09e612</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department is reviewing its policies on housing transgender inmates in the federal prison system after protections for transgender prisoners were rolled back in the Trump administration, The Associated Press has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILLEY DEFENDS CHINA CALLS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-china-joint-chiefs-of-staff-1b23ba339e50a7c17c43c1281a0b4e04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — The top U.S. military officer said Friday that calls he made to his Chinese counterpart in the final stormy months of Donald Trump's presidency were “perfectly within the duties and responsibilities” of his job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED AIRLINES experiencing system-wide outage... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3679975/united-airlines-down-outage-website-boarding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED Airlines is experiencing a huge outage causing issues for passengers boarding planes and using the website. Reports that the website was down started to arise at 7am EST on Friday morning. U…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Security forces under pressure to prevent repeat of Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/572687-security-forces-under-pressure-to-prevent-repeat-of-jan-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is bracing for Saturday's “Justice for J6” rally where demonstrators will be backing people who invaded the Capitol on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resorts Make Staying Put More Appealing...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/17/resorts-make-staying-put-more-appealing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Amanda Stephens, a doctor in North Florida, had two cruises canceled last year, she turned to the next-best thing:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clarence Thomas criticizes judges for veering into politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-courts-religion-judiciary-south-bend-746c700c52a7216b582dbd64b68d409f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas on Thursday criticized some in the judiciary for veering into the role of legislators and politicians, saying it is not the role of judges to make policy or to base decisions on their personal feelings or religious beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>660,000 white flags and climbing: Artist shows what America's death toll looks like...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/09/16/660000-white-flags-artist-covid-19-death-toll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around the Washington Monument 20 acres are being filled with flags representing the COVID-19 death toll in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marathon runners required to wear face masks in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/why-san-francisco-marathon-runners-will-need-to-wear-masks?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants in four races must wear masks on some portions of the course, race officials announced in updates to the race’s health protocols over the last two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger says voters were right to retain Newsom, calls Republican field 'disastrous'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/arnold-schwarzenegger-says-voters-were-212529529.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Arnold Schwarzenegger, who won office through a recall, says he's glad Newsom wasn't ousted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  1 in 3 patients suffer from long covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/1-3-covid-19-patients-170012968.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These long COVID patients reported at least one symptom of COVID-19 two months after first testing positive for the coronavirus, the CDC study says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Employees in China held hostage by angry investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/business/companies-markets/evergrandes-employees-held-hostage-as-worried-investors-demand-payments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail investors in China are taking drastic measures to get money back from embattled property developer.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find evidence of humans making clothes 120,000 years ago!</title>
      <link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/evidence-of-fur-and-leather-clothing-among-worlds-oldest-found-in-moroccan-cave-180978689/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smithsonianmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans likely sported clothes made of jackal, fox and wildcat skins some 120,000 years ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii told tourists to stay away. Did they listen?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/hawaii-told-tourists-to-stay-away-did-they-listen/ar-AAOwD8O?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ige told travelers to postpone trips last month as delta surged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As world leaders gather at UN, vaccine mandate creates confusion and dissent...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-york-wants-world-leaders-to-show-proof-of-vaccination-at-the-un-russia-says-that-is-e2-80-98discriminatory-e2-80-99/ar-AAOwlHm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate unfolding around the world over coronavirus vaccine mandates is playing out on a small scale at the United Nations headquarters ahead of a meeting of dozens of world leaders in New York next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New humanitarian emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-faces-new-border-emergency-in-texas-where-thousands-of-haitian-migrants-are-stuck-under-bridge-in-squalid-conditions/ar-AAOwoym?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Del Rio say more than 8,000 people have crossed in recent days, overwhelming Customs and Border Protection capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden leans into expansive, populist agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/at-an-economic-e2-80-98inflection-point-e2-80-99-biden-leans-into-expansive-populist-agenda/ar-AAOwr4y?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s pitch was part of a pivot away from the first chapter of his presidency, in which Washington and his administration were consumed by emergency funding measures to combat the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rikers Island spirals into chaos during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/rikers-island-jail-spirals-into-chaos-amid-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City’s Rikers Island jail complex has been troubled by years of neglect and now has spiraled into turmoil during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Removes Accounts Tied to German Anti-Lockdown Group...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/facebook-deletes-accounts-of-german-anti-lockdown-group/a-59206831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech giant says the Querdenken (Lateral Thinking) movement was causing "social harm" by promoting conspiracy theories against coronavirus restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New FTC bureau to police Big Tech?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Why-Democrats-are-rallying-around-creating-a-new-16465110.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Who in the federal government should police data abuses by tech companies -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 states threaten legal action over Biden's vaccine mandate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/572649-24-states-threaten-legal-action-over-bidens-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-four states threatened to sue the Biden administration on Thursday over the president's new rule to require employers with more than 100 employees to mandate vaccinations and frequent testing for their worker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police mine GOOGLE for your location, search history...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/sep/16/geofence-warrants-reverse-search-warrants-police-google</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geofence location and keyword warrants are new law enforcement tools that have privacy experts concerned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest cruise ship in world set to launch..</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/uncategorized/3673655/largest-cruise-ship-royal-caribbean-wonders-seas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE largest cruise ship in the world is launching next year – with new routes from Europe next summer. Royal Caribbean’s Wonder of the Seas, their fifth Oasis Class ship, will be able t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack of domain provider popular among conservatives leaks personal data...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/epik-hack-far-right-sites-anonymous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A breach of Epik exposed a massive trove of data, including the names of individuals behind some of the far-right's most notorious websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS TURN SOUR:   Slow motion deterioration with pockets of shares down 20% or more...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/the-stock-market-is-undergoing-a-slow-motion-deterioration-with-pockets-of-shares-down-20percent-or-more.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks are up against a range of obstacles, including seasonal weakness, uncertainty around the Covid delta variant and rising costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicki Minaj compares cancel culture in US to China...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cancel-culture-china-vaccine-blowback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rap artist Nicki Minaj slammed America’s cancel culture after she spoke out about her vaccine hesitancy and compared it to China's restrictions on residents and visitors from criticizing the country's leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS shutting last store in home state of Illinois...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/sears-is-shutting-its-last-store-in-illinois-its-home-state.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last Sears department store located in the retailer's home state of Illinois is getting ready to close its doors for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Cause Of Alzheimer's?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/likely-cause-of-alzheimers-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toxic protein deposits that form in people with Alzheimer’s likely leak into the brain from fat carrying particles called lipoproteins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Dempsey accused of 'terrorizing set' of 'GREY'S ANATOMY'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/patrick-dempsey-accused-terrorizing-set-192356028.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new book about the landmark series, one 'Grey's Anatomy' producer recalled 'HR issues' swirling around actor Patrick Dempsey before his departure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As workers age, robots take on more jobs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210916205718-xg26w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/ROBOTS (PIX):As workers age, robots take on more jobs -study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special prosecutor charges ex-attorney for Clinton campaign with lying to FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/16/special-prosecutor-john-durham-charges-ex-attorney-for-clinton-campaign-with-lying-to-fbi-512316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Sussmann, who worked as an attorney for the Hillary Clinton campaign, is accused in a grand jury indictment returned Thursday of a single felony coun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris diplomats CANCEL D.C. gala dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9999163/French-officials-CANCEL-gala-dinner-celebrating-ties-protest-losing-90bn-sub-contract.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French officials on Thursday canceled a gala to mark ties with the U.S. amid fury at Washington's role in wrecking a $90billion submarine deal with Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSMUTUAL fined for failing to monitor GAMESTOP saga star...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-media-massachusetts-56f97138b497fa27e8420bec6288d548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Massachusetts regulators are fining MassMutual $4 million and ordering it to overhaul its social-media policies after accusing the company of failing to supervise an employee whose online cheerleading of GameStop's stock helped launch the frenzy that shook Wall Street earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of migrating songbirds crash into NYC skyscrapers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-environment-and-nature-new-york-manhattan-new-york-city-baf07c81dc9fa8da53d4eac627129f7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hundreds of birds migrating through New York City this week died after crashing into the city's glass towers, a mass casualty event spotlighted by a New York City Audubon volunteer's tweets showing the World Trade Center littered with bird carcasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Believes He Can Play Until He's 50:</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/tom-brady-believes-he-can-keep-launching-nfl-touchdowns-until-hes-50-i-dont-find-it-so-difficult/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s never happened before in the history of the sport, but according to Tom Brady the concept of playing in the NFL at age 50 doesn’t seem difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world's most expensive animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210915-the-worlds-most-expensive-animals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which living creatures are the most financially valuable? The answers can be surprising, and also reveal striking insights about the quirks and priorities of human nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convicted hedge fund founder to release tell-all book...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/16/convicted-hedge-fund-founder-raj-rajaratnam-releases-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raj Rajaratnam, the former hedge fund founder who was slapped with a record 11-year prison sentence in 2011 for insider trading, is releasing a tell-all book about his epic fall from grace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cards required for some indoor businesses on Maui...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-business-hawaii-restaurants-612a06ea733c91a2917ea0b5ccffbd62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAILUKU, Hawaii (AP) — Proof of vaccination is now required to patrons who want to sit inside Maui bars and restaurants. Vaccination cards must be shown for indoor dining and drinking as well as for communal areas in businesses like gyms under Maui's “Safer Outside" program, which launched Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital staff must swear off TYLENOL, TUMS to get religious exemption...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/09/hospital-staff-must-swear-off-tylenol-tums-to-get-religious-vaccine-exemption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospital CEO aims to educate staff on the full scope of what they're claiming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama endorses Trudeau in Canadian election...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/obama-endorses-trudeau-in-the-canadian-election/600097815/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama endorsed Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau on Thursday in the Canadian election, calling him an effective leader in a rare endorsement of a candidate in a Canadian election by a former American president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Outraged by U.S. Nuclear Sub Deal With Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/france-is-outraged-by-u-s-nuclear-submarine-deal-with-australia/ar-AAOvXGS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — France reacted with fury on Thursday to President Biden’s announcement of a deal to help Australia deploy nuclear-powered submarines, calling it a “unilateral, brutal, unpredictable decision” that resembled the rash and sudden policy shifts common during the Trump administration. The angry words from Jean-Yves Le Drian, the foreign minister, in an interview with Franceinfo radio, followed an official statement from him and Florence...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese state-run newspaper claims warships could 'soon' be near Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2021/09/15/chinese-state-run-newspaper-claims-warships-could-soon-near-hawaii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newspaper said warships could be on their way following claims that the US Navy challenged international waters near Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body composting 'green' alternative to burial, cremation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-lifestyle-religion-environment-and-nature-health-014a5d0bc4f4039181d9863527334ebe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAFAYETTE, Colo. (AP) — In a suburban Denver warehouse tucked between an auto repair shop and a computer recycling business, Seth Viddal is dealing with life and death. He and one of his employees have built a “vessel” they hope will usher in a more environmentally friendly era of mortuary science that includes the natural organic reduction of human remains, also known as body composting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCID Beats TESLA, Going 520 Miles on Charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Lucid-Beats-Tesla-in-Range-Going-520-Miles-on-a-16464007.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lucid Motors, a startup automaker, has unseated Tesla, the dominant maker of electric...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key senators eye exits ahead of '22 midterms:...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/16/politics/senators-eye-exits-midterms/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Thune, the No. 2 Senate Republican, is struggling with a crucial decision: Whether to ask South Dakota voters for six more years in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FOX Exec Set to Clean Up ABC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/former-fox-exec-peter-rice-is-supposed-to-clean-up-abc-news-but-angry-staffers-say-hes-failing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney exec Peter Rice had promised to address the network’s cultural issues, but angered staffers said they now feel abandoned by him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin says 'several dozen' in inner circle test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/16/europe/russia-putin-coronavirus-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday morning that "not just one or two but several dozen people" from his inner circle had contracted coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia ramps up pressure on foreign tech firms on election eve...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210916154528-e5w1s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-ELECTION/IT (PIX):Russia ramps up pressure on foreign tech firms on eve of election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell raises ethics questions after Fed presidents' multimillion-dollar investments...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/fed-chief-powell-orders-ethics-review-after-multimillion-dollar-trades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed Chair Powell directed staff to review the central bank's rules after filings showed officials made multimillion-dollar trades in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small agency, big job: Biden tasks OSHA with vaccine mandate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-henry-mcmaster-f33acd986ad5045e48088a832c6f9903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Occupational Safety and Health Administration doesn’t make many headlines. Charged with keeping America’s workplaces safe, it usually busies itself with tasks such as setting and enforcing standards for goggles, hardhats and ladders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objects at Solar System Edge Influenced by Something Mysterious?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qj8qeb/objects-at-the-solar-systems-edge-are-being-influenced-by-something-mysterious</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery of hundreds of new objects in the outer solar system confirms weird gravitational effects that could be caused by “Planet Nine.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought Haves, Have-Nots Test How to Share Water in West...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2021-09-16/drought-haves-have-nots-test-how-to-share-water-in-the-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oregon farmers who grow 60% of the world’s carrot seed have been without irrigation water for weeks as drought ravages the American West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone served Capitol riot suit during live interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/roger-stone-capitol-riot-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone, a longtime friend of former president Donald Trump, was served a lawsuit related to the Jan. 6 Capitol Riot Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK keeps researching own harms -- and burying findings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/facebook-keeps-researching-its-own-harms-e2-80-94-and-burying-the-findings/ar-AAOvQpK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of leaked internal reports shows Facebook knows far more than it lets on. That’s by design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like a sunset' -- Developers propose Hollywood office tower with bold design...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/home-and-garden/like-a-sunset-e2-80-94-developers-propose-a-hollywood-office-tower-with-a-bold-sculptural-design/ar-AAOvWyb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developers are proposing a visually stunning $500-million office tower on Sunset Boulevard in the heart of Hollywood called the Star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS TURN SOUR</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow slipped Thursday despite better-than-expected August retail sales, as the latest weekly jobless claims report pointed to a mixed economic picture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes changing porn...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/deepfakes-have-disturbing-implications-for-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artifical Intelligence has been heralded as ‘the future’ for as long as I can remember. The excitement is understandable: scientists may one-day be able to create an AI that is so efficient it can substitute the manual work of humans, replacing doctors, engineers and even journalists. But professional occupations are not the only area AI [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring utility bills alarm Europe, raise fears for winter...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-prices-d783b16fe0a5a2c87e909b15822253ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Wholesale prices for gas and electricity are surging across Europe, raising the prospect of increases in already-high utility bills and further pain for people who have taken a financial hit from the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Benefits of Walking...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/09/happiness-walking-pilgrimage/620075/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What I learned about transcendence from a very boring 100-mile trek</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gray wolf may be re-listed as endangered after Trump removed protections...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/572555-fish-and-wildlife-service-to-review-trump-era-removal-of-gray-wolf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Interior Department will review the Endangered Species Act status of the American gray wolf after the Trump administration delisted it as endangered, the department announced Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 56% Americans Can Name All 3 Branches Of Govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/knowledge-the-first-amendment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual poll of more than 1,000 people finds 56 percent of Americans are now capable of naming all three branches of government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Furious; 'Stabbed in Back'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/french-furious-at-biden-for-cutting-them-out-of-submarine-deal/ar-AAOvpka</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s top diplomat unleashed a stream of invective against President Joe Biden after the U.S. and the U.K. announced a new security alliance for the Pacific region which will cost the French defense industry some A$90 billion (56 billion euros).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piers Morgan Joins NEWS CORP...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3674043/piers-morgan-the-sun-news-corp-tv-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIERS Morgan is joining The Sun and News Corp in a global deal that’s a “bigger comeback than Cristiano Ronaldo.” Britain’s powerhouse journalist is returning to his roots and com…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 1 In 6 Will Quit Job If Not Allowed To Work From Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/remote-work-in-person-policies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;44 percent know at least one person who has quit their job or is planning to quit because their boss is requiring them to restart in-person work.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
