<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY in Trouble? Media Giant Seeks $6 Billion With New Debt Offering...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-looks-to-raise-6-billion-with-new-debt-offering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company plans to use funds for "general corporate purposes"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. intelligence reports from January and February warned about likely pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Intelligence-officials-early-alarms-about-15147137.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - U.S. intelligence agencies were issuing ominous, classified warnings in January and February about the global danger posed by the coronavirus while President Donald Trump and lawmakers played down the threat and failed to take action that might have slowed the spread of the pathogen, according to U.S. officials familiar with spy agency reporting.  The intelligence reports didn't predict when the virus might land on U.S. shores or recommend particular steps that public health officials should take, issues outside the purview of the intelligence agencies. But they did track the spread of the virus in China, and later in other countries, and warned that Chinese officials appeared to be minimizing the severity of the outbreak.  Taken together, the reports and warnings painted an early picture of a virus that showed the characteristics of a globe-encircling pandemic that could require governments to take swift actions to contain it. But despite that constant flow of reporting, Trump continued publicly and privately to play down the threat the virus posed to Americans. Lawmakers, too, did not grapple with the virus in earnest until this month, as officials scrambled to keep citizens in their homes and hospitals braced for a surge in patients suffering from covid-19, the disease caused by the coronavirus.  Intelligence agencies "have been warning on this since January," said a U.S. official who had access to intelligence reporting that was disseminated to members of Congress and their staffs as well as to officials in the Trump administration, and who, along with others, spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe sensitive information.  "Donald Trump may not have been expecting this, but a lot of other people in the government were - they just couldn't get him to do anything about it," this official said....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump could take bailout cash to save his hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/572160/trump-coronavirus-hurting-hotels-hundreds-fired-mar-a-lago-closed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has admitted the coronavirus pandemic is “hurting” his hotels after “hundreds of workers were fired and Mar-a-Lago closed,” reports say. And the President refus…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Drops Deficit Dogma...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/germany-drops-deficit-dogma-as-deaths-surge-in-italy-spain/ar-BB11vRQG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Americans stranded abroad as money, patience run out...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/thousands-of-americans-stranded-abroad-as-money-patience-run-out/ar-BB11vJu2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu implores Gantz to join gov't, vows to rotate as PM without tricks...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Netanyahu-says-unity-deal-with-Blue-and-White-reached-621811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I will leave office on the agreed date, there will be no shticks and tricks. Millions of Israelis are waiting for us."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I don't know what government assistance would be for what I have'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/21/trump-i-dont-know-if-my-businesses-will-receive-coronavirus-aid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I just don't know what the government assistance would be for what I have," President Donald Trump said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia now looks safer than USA?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mess-america-why-asia-now-231402220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a clear sign that the U.S. botched its coronavirus response, some Americans are relieved they stayed in countries closest to the outbreak's origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain tells shoppers to stop panic-buying...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britain-tells-shoppers-stop-panic-buying-195358294.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With supermarket shelves still being stripped of essential items, including toilet paper, officials said there was no need for panic. "There's no risk of food running out," Environment Secretary George Eustice told reporters at the government's daily Downing Street briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Sao Paulo braces for two-week shutdown, Bolsonaro blasts 'hysteria'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200321185230-0kvnz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Brazil's Sao Paulo braces for two-week coronavirus shutdown, Bolsonaro blasts 'hysteria'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symptoms often linger before worsening...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/slow-burn-coronavirus-symptoms-often-linger-worsening-n1164756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some patients may feel better before winding up in the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia testing vaccine on animals in top secret bio weapons lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-testing-coronavirus-vaccine-primates-21731700</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soviet-era complex Vector is one of the world’s leading anti-virus centres and has channelled resources into finding a Covid-19 cure by conducting tests on lower primates and “ferrets”, says a leading scientist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines warn of 'draconian' steps if Congress fails to help...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-airlines-warn-draconian-steps-congress-fails-help-211224987.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief executives of the largest US airline companies asked Congress Saturday for urgent help avoiding widespread layoffs among the industry's 750,000 employees. "Unless worker payroll protection grants are passed immediately, many of us will be forced to take draconian measures such as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK HOSPITALS UNDER PRESSURE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48740e4bdefbb0e2459359a5eda2fdd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo said the state is scouring the globe for medical supplies and scouting temporary hospital locations in and around New York City. Flights were briefly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY CASES SOAR AGAIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3dcb3392a3c566a1caad7444e93fc7e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The coronavirus pandemic took an increasingly bleak toll Saturday in the U.S. and in Europe, producing staggering caseloads in New York and Italy and setting off a desperate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE MILILTARY TOP SECRET PLANS IF OUTBREAK CRIPPLES GOVT...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/exclusive-inside-militarys-top-secret-plans-if-coronavirus-cripples-government-1492878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence To Be Tested After Staffer Positive...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/488808-pence-says-he-will-be-tested-for-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Pence said Saturday that he and second lady Karen Pence will be tested for the coronavirus after a member of the vice president’s staff tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Orders Residents To Stay At Home, Bans All Gatherings...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/03/21/coronavirus-in-new-jersey-gov-phil-murphy-to-make-major-announcement-regarding-efforts-to-curb-spread-of-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, the governor signed an executive order for New Jerseyans to stay indoors in an effort to curb the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO: Half State's Cases Are People Under 50 Years Old...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/half-of-all-coronavirus-cases-in-new-york-are-people-under-50-years-old-gov-cuomo-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You’re not superman and you're not superwoman. You can get this virus and you can transfer the virus,” the New York Governor said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People turning to dogs, cats, chickens to cope with self-isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Alone-no-more-People-are-turning-to-dogs-cats-15146418.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a normal Sunday at the PetSmart in Gaithersburg, Maryland, Lucky Dog Animal Rescue would hold an adoption event and find homes for about 15 dogs.  But as coronavirus news started to spread this past week, the waiting list skyrocketed from 10 to 40 would-be adopters. "And we had 30 adoptions in three hours at that event alone," said Mirah Horowitz, the rescue's executive director.  Forget, toilet paper, milk and hand sanitizer: There's now a rush to stock up on real necessities, such as cats and dogs. And rabbits and fish, even a couple of chickens.  As millions of people across the U.S. work from home and schools close, the promise of companionship even in a time of isolation is prompting some to take in animals. Many say they finally have the time to properly train and care for a new pet. Animal rescuers across the country say they are seeing spiking interest in adoption and fostering, as well as offers to help everywhere from open-admission shelters to smaller nonprofit groups.  In California, where 40 million residents were ordered on Thursday night to stay home except for essential jobs or trips, like getting groceries, Gov. Gavin Newsom noted an important exemption.  "You can still walk your dog," he said.  That was part of the appeal for Kathy Shield, a University of Berkeley graduate student. After years of wanting a dog, Shield on Thursday adopted a 2-year-old brown and white dog from the Milo Foundation shelter in Point Richmond, California and named him Atom.  "I'm a nuclear scientist so it's very on brand," said Shield.  The timing was ideal, because Shield is working from home and can help the Atom adjust to his new environment. She's also excited to have someone to talk to, even if he doesn't have much to say back.  Plus, it will help keep her on schedule....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking stock of strange days: The week that America changed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a82294fc0723630d850603dd7b016ad5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Change came to the United States of America during the third week of March in 2020. It did not come all at once, though it came quite rapidly. As had happened in other lands, there was no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election limbo as outbreak upends primaries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ca82f2fd0b4df4ee7633c6deb20d997</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — U.S. elections have been upended by the coronavirus pandemic. At least 13 states have postponed voting and more delays are possible as health officials warn that social distancing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA gives up on containing; Tells doctors to skip testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-20/coronavirus-county-doctors-containment-testing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decision by L.A. County's public health system not to test patients with coronavirus symptoms could make it difficult to know how many are infected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javits Center To Become Massive Field Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/03/21/coronavirus-update-nycs-javits-center-to-become-massive-field-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Cuomo announced the Javits Center, previously used for big conventions, tops his list as one of several field hospitals treating the COVID-19 outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Terrified' Package Delivery Employees Going to Work Sick...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/21/terrified-package-delivery-employees-are-going-to-work-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hour after hour, day after day, the packages keep arriving: food, medicine, clothes, toys and a million other items brought</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Sees Spike In Severe Child Abuse Cases...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/03/20/texas-hospital-spike-severe-child-abuse-cases-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors at Cook Children’s believe the stresses from the COVID-19 pandemic are linked to six cases of severe child abuse seen this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People moved here to escape big city drama. With coronavirus, that's impossible...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/People-moved-here-to-escape-big-city-drama-With-15147904.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILLCOX, Ariz. - Several employees wore medical masks and almost all wore plastic gloves, a jarring sight for some customers who appeared visibly taken aback as they entered their local Safeway store.  Even in this small town of roughly 3,500 people, the scene wasn't much different than stores in the big city: aisle after aisle of empty shelves where the toilet paper, hand soap and sanitizer used to be. All the Tylenol was sold out, along with cans of beans, cartons of eggs and all the milk - the nondairy kind, too.  And good luck finding a thermometer. Amid the growing concern over the coronavirus, the stock had been cleaned well over a week ago. At first, the pharmacist sent folks over to the Dollar General, but then she'd heard they were out, too.  "I tried to order them, but they're just gone," she said, apologetically.  Up and down the aisles, people shook their heads at the strange scene in a community distant enough to be spared the drama of places like Tucson or Phoenix. This was the place where people came to escape, a small town surrounded by even smaller ones where social distancing was kind of the point.  But all through town, things felt eerie. Restaurants and businesses that were never closed were dark and empty. The dining room at the McDonald's was closed. As shoppers drove into the Safeway parking lot, they passed a panhandler who waved a sign that simply read, "WTF?"  When a Safeway cashier in a medical mask held up the check-out line to wipe down the register area with disinfectant, tensions boiled over. "I mean, this is crazy!" a man said loudly. He ignored fliers posted at the lanes that urged customers to stay at least two shopping carts away from others in the store, inching uncomfortably close to two women ahead of him in line. "This is just too...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will govt nationalize BOEING?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-government-nationalize-boeing-013447260.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 12 years after the US government bailed out General Motors and Chrysler, Washington policymakers are debating how to throw Boeing a lifeline as it reels from dual crises over the coronavirus and 737 MAX. The aerospace giant, which manufactures the US presidential jet Air Force One in addition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLION people confined to homes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nearly-one-billion-people-confined-homes-globally-curb-134625492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Close to one billion people worldwide were confined to their homes on Saturday as the global coronavirus death toll shot past 11,000 and US states rolled out lockdown measures already imposed across swathes of Europe. The pandemic has completely upended lives across the planet, restricting movement,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How It All Came Apart for Bernie Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/21/how-it-all-came-apart-for-bernie-sanders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In mid-January, a few weeks before the Iowa caucuses, Senator Bernie Sanders’s pollster offered a stark prognosis for the campaign:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House members, Senate aides also traded shares...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/21/coronavirus-trading-house-senate-140260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Susan Davis, a California Democrat, sold shares in Alaska Air and Royal Caribbean cruise lines on Feb. 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcists storming heavens with prayers to end pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.philstar.com/headlines/2020/03/21/2002427/priests-seek-exorcise-pandemic-through-prayer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic exorcists are storming the heavens with prayers to end the global scourge of the coronavirus disease 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NJ health official says EVERYONE will get infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/coronavirus/2020/03/im-going-to-get-it-we-all-are-njs-top-health-official-says-as-she-leads-the-states-coronavirus-war.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judith Persichilli, a former ICU nurse with working-class New Jersey roots, says her whole life has prepared her for this moment as she leads the fight against COVID-19 disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Exit strategy' could be months -- or years -- away...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/21/coronavirus-exit-strategy-could-be-months-or-years-away/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learn to love your lockdown, experts say — because it may not end anytime soon. The coronavirus threat will continue to loom for months or even years before mass vaccinations or natural immunities …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Drop Kale and Quinoa to Lock Down With Chips and Oreos...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-drop-kale-quinoa-lock-130000446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Out with the Tuscan kale and acai berries, in with the Spam and popcorn.In a stark reversal, American shoppers who were taking up healthier eating are gravitating back to old ways as they hunker down to weather the coronavirus pandemic. They are loading up on shelf-stable items from canned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift and Kanye West 'unedited' 2016 phone call leaks online...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/11223155/taylor-swift-and-kanye-wests-unedited-2016-infamous-phone-call-leaks-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE infamous 2016 phone call between Taylor Swift and Kanye West has leaked online unedited, revealing the truth behind their lyric dispute. Taylor, 30, called out rapper Kayne for using her name i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A chunk of Yellowstone the size of Chicago has been pulsing. Why?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8135093/Huge-chunk-Yellowstone-National-Park-size-Chicago-breathing-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge chunk of Yellowstone National Park, the size of Chicago, has been found to inflate and deflate by several inches over the past decade due to an intrusion of magma underneath its surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenny Rogers dead at 81...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8137345/Country-music-icon-Kenny-Rogers-dies-aged-81.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, the family is planning to have a small private service at this time with a public memorial at a later date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus killing more than person an hour in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/20/coronavirus-killing-more-than-a-person-an-hour-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus killed city residents at a rate of more than one per hour on Friday. Between just 10 a.m. and 6 p.m., 14 people in New York City died from the virus, pushing the Big Apple’s t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand prime minister:  Please be strong, be kind and unite...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8136895/Jacinda-Ardern-address-nation-amid-coronavirus-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jacinda Ardern has introduced a four-level alert system to allow for improved communication of public health measures as coronavirus spreads in New Zealand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECONOMY DETERIORATING FAST</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/U-S-economy-deteriorating-faster-than-15147050.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy is deteriorating more quickly than was expected just days ago, as extraordinary measures designed to curb the coronavirus keep 84 million Americans penned in their homes and cause the near-total shutdown of most businesses.  In a single 24-hour period, the governors of three of the largest states - California, New York and Illinois - ordered residents to stay home, except to buy food and medicine, while the governor of Pennsylvania ordered the closure of nonessential businesses. Across the globe, health officials are struggling to cope with the growing number of patients, with the World Health Organization noting that while it required three months to reach 100,000 cases, it took only 12 days to hit another 100,000.  The resulting economic meltdown, which is sending several million workers streaming into the unemployment line, is outpacing the federal government's efforts to respond. As the Senate on Friday raced to complete work on a financial rescue package, the White House and key lawmakers were dramatically expanding its scope, pushing the legislation far beyond the original $1 trillion price tag.  With each day, an unprecedented stoppage gathers force, as restaurants, movie theaters, sports arenas, and offices close to shield themselves from the disease. Already, it's clear that the initial economic decline will be sharper and more painful than during the 2008 financial crisis.  Next week, roughly 3 million Americans will file first-time claims for unemployment assistance, more than four times the record high set in the depths of the 1982 recession, according to Bank of America Merrill Lynch. That's just the start of a surge that could send the jobless rate spiking to 20 percent from today's 3.5 percent, a JPMorgan Chase economist told clients on a conference call Friday.  Estimates of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Much of life comes to standstill as countries shut themselves off from rest of world... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Much-of-life-comes-to-a-standstill-as-countries-15147058.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European truck drivers stuck in miles-long backups. Asylum seekers stranded in Mexico. Cities and states within countries - from Rio de Janeiro to Tasmania - sealing themselves off from the rest of their nations.  In a world where the once-steady march of globalization hit strong head winds in recent years from nationalist governments, the novel coronavirus pandemic has done more to suddenly halt and reverse the notion of open - and easily crossed - borders than perhaps any other event in modern history.  The impact to the global economy will be severe. Yet the larger question arising from empty international airports and backed-up land borders may be the long-haul effect of the pandemic on everything from freedom of movement to asylum claims to trade.  "The question is, when the health crisis recedes, be that six months, one year, or two years from now, are we going to see the protectionist measures related to the health crisis recede too?" said Stephanie Segal, a former senior economist at the International Monetary Fund and a senior fellow at the Washington-based Center for Strategic and International Studies. "Certainly they will, but will they ever go back to precrisis levels?"  In the meantime, the pandemic is stranding travelers and upending everything from refugee flows to wedding rites.  In South America, still less impacted than other regions, many nations are striving to keep it that way by imposing some of the strictest border controls in the world. Peru and Bolivia have suspended international flights, restricted crossings at land borders, and deployed police and the military on the streets.  As concerns mount about the ability of crisis-plagued Venezuela to control the pandemic, its neighbors have sealed its borders. The closures have raised fears of a bottleneck that could force migrants - as well as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress may move to remote work...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-lawmakers-begin-falling-ill-from-coronavirus-congress-may-move-to-remote-work/ar-BB11siWH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lou Dobbs in self-quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/488758-fox-business-host-lou-dobbs-in-self-quarantine-after-staffer-tests-positive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television host Lou Dobbs is in self-quarantine after a staffer on his Fox Business show tested positive for the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To release or not to release? Music's dilemma over virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/release-not-release-musics-dilemma-over-virus-183603746.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian hit-machine Weeknd held his nerve and dropped the 14-track "After Hours" Friday, with the cult British artist Baxter Dury also going ahead even though he admitted that "it's terrible timing". The Weeknd's new album for Universal had been heavily trailed on his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acts of kindness abound...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-acts-kindness-abound-us-182309839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From grocery shopping for the elderly to delivering meals or offering free classes online, acts of kindness during the coronavirus pandemic are providing uplifting moments of joy in a United States beset by anxiety. In California, the most populous state in the nation and one of the hardest hit by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON, WALMART Workers Push for Paid Leave, Better Protections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-walmart-workers-push-paid-233035655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A group of workers from Walmart Inc., Amazon.com Inc. and other big retailers demanded paid leave for those affected by the coronavirus outbreak and better protective measures from their employers.The group, United for Respect, held a media call Friday with U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominican govt orders curfew...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200320233808-y5m7x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DOMINICAN REPUBLIC:Dominican government orders curfew to slow spread of coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President considers national quarantine; Only drug, grocery stores open...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/breaking-trump-eyes-2-week-quarantine-only-drug-grocery-stores-open</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump, moving with haste to slow the spread of the coronavirus, is preparing a plan to mobilize the National Guard to help enforce a two-week quarantine of the public if his tough-love efforts so far fail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock moment wheezing man collapses on New York subway... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/568784/coronavirus-new-york-city-subway-shocking-moment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARROWING video shows a man who collapsed on the subway in New York City, where residents remain gripped by the coronavirus outbreak. A witness said the man had been sleeping on the R train in Broo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20% OF POPULATION NOW ON LOCKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/568703/illinois-pritzker-stay-home-order-coronavirus-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ILLINOIS joined New York and California in lockdowns to curb coronavirus spread, as the Governor announced a “shelter in place” order on Friday. The order, limiting all residents to sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffer in Pence office tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/staffer-us-vice-presidents-office-tests-positive-virus-233451710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer in the office of US Vice President Mike Pence, the pointman for Washington's response to the coronavirus outbreak, has tested positive for the illness, a spokeswoman said Friday. Pence has appeared at Trump's side at the daily White House press conferences to announce developments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch destroy millions of flowers as sales wilt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dutch-destroy-millions-flowers-coronavirus-wilts-sales-172310836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's tulip season in The Netherlands but this year growers are destroying millions of flowers a day, in unprecedented scenes as the coronavirus pandemic has cut demand. Brightly coloured blooms that might normally have been destined for a romantic gesture or Mothers Day are scooped up by diggers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires suspected short-range missiles...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200320230104-0ahbq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (UPDATE 3, TV):UPDATE 3-North Korea fires suspected short-range missiles, S.Korea says, amid coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVO'S ANDY COHEN SICK...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/andy-cohen-tests-positive-coronavirus-1202889098/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andy Cohen has revealed he’s tested positive for coronavirus, and his Watch What Happens Live @ Home edition is on hold for now. “After a few days of self-quarantine, and not feeling gr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demands for resignations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d0279fc73d040a1a287f47ed20b4fd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing public outrage, senators in both political parties denied Friday that they exploited advance knowledge when they dumped stocks and other financial holdings before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing faces new headwind: Lab supply shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4aac3a10664097f38633149367ac3928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — First, some of the coronavirus tests didn't work. Then there weren't enough to go around. Now, just as the federal government tries to ramp up nationwide screening, laboratory...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California awakes to new reality: Homebound amid outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/30e5ec0a1967d46c4afbf1b11ff33f17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — While California awoke Friday to the reality of a near lockdown to prevent the spread of coronavirus, it was business as usual for Rick Curnutt and his family, who were hunkered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIH:  UP TO 70,000 CASES NEXT WEEK</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/nih-director-70k-coronavirus-cases-confirmed-us-end/story?id=69717284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NIH directo told employees Friday up to 70,000 coronavirus cases could be confirmed in the U.S. by the end of next week.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
