<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'El Chapo' trial begins amid heavy security...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/u-trial-mexicos-el-chapo-begins-amid-heavy-111315233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial of accused Mexican drug lord Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman will begin with lawyers' opening statements in a federal court in Brooklyn on Tuesday, amid intense public attention and extraordinary security measures. Federal prosecutors say that as leader of Mexico's Sinaloa Cartel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RABBI WARNS START OF BIBLICAL WAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/rabbi-warns-new-israel-palestine-conflict-could-be-start-of-biblical-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE races go to Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4316dc20404a45d68e4d2f36f1a4b7cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — No, it wasn't a blue wave. But a week after the voting, Democrats are riding higher than they thought on election night. As vote counting presses on in several states, the Democrats have steadily chalked up victories across the country, firming up their grip on the U.S. House and statehouses. The slow roll of wins has given the party plenty to celebrate. President Donald Trump was quick to claim victory for his party on election night. But the Democrats, who hit political rock bottom just two years ago, have now picked up at least 32 seats in the House — and lead in four more — in addition to flipping seven governorships and eight state legislative chambers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preacher survives gunman's attack after leaping behind 'Jesus' altar...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6383695/Preacher-survives-gunmans-attack-service-Brazil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weslei Souza, 30, opened fire inside the Temple of Angels church in Mogi das Cruzes, in the state of Sao Paulo, on Sunday evening, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Mocks France for War Losses as Macron Bromance Sours...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-renews-attack-on-macron-as-bromance-turns-sours#gs.cAn4OdQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Mocks France for World War Losses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Magazine defends 'Tarantino cretin' interview with Ennio Morricone...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/nov/13/quentin-tarantino-cretin-ennio-morricone-german-playboy-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Playboy says it is ‘surprised’ by the film composer’s claim that he did not give the interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of all food wasted before reaches plate...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/13/third-food-worldwide-wasted-reaches-plate-says-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third of the world's food is lost before it ever reaches anyone's plate, a panel of global experts has warned as it called for a war on waste to improve worldwide diets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Virtual wargame 'experiment' hits GOOGLE with 'worst ever' internet hijack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6383133/Internet-traffic-hijack-disrupts-Google-services.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet traffic was intercepted by servers in Nigeria, China and Russia - including those run by major state-owned telecoms providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual first responders hit streets amid drug crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dd218e854a53489db344403f1f2d7ea2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sidewalk prayers near shoot-up spots. Sunday sermons in the back of a bar. Pleas to struggling souls to surrender to God. Funerals for members of their flock who didn't make it. Clergy members have become spiritual first responders in the opioid crisis, often leaving the pulpit to minister on the streets. They can be reverends, rabbis, priests or pastors. Though their faiths differ, they invariably approach people with addiction as equals. No Bible-thumping, no blaming. Quite a few are in recovery themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London's homicide rate hits grim milestone after spate of bloodshed...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/13/londons-homicide-rate-hits-grim-milestone-spate-bloodshed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number ofmurders in London so far this year has now matched the total in the whole of 2017, a grim milestone that will fuel the debate of how to tackle rising crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2020 doomsday scenario...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-2020-presidential-election-chances-86143c8b-9045-414d-b61a-80d67be9107a.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the big trends are working against Trump and the GOP for 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrinking Sea of Galilee has some hoping for miracle...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/shrinking-sea-galilee-hoping-miracle-041243511.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was not so long ago when swimmers at Ein Gev would lay out their towels in the grass at the edge of the Sea of Galilee. "Every time we come we feel an ache in our hearts," said Yael Lichi, 47, who has been visiting the famous lake with her family for 15 years. "The lake is a symbol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The scorched cat that survived...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6383809/Heartbreaking-images-animals-injured-California-wildfires-killed-44.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Camp Fire in Northern California, and the Woolsey Fire, raging near Malibu in the south, have forced residents to flee their homes, many unable to also save their beloved pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida recount chugs along as more irregularities surface...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/71472c46f771431aa5c038db78a6c78f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Florida's election recount is chugging along as more irregularities are uncovered and a judge asked the warring sides to "ramp down the rhetoric," saying it erodes public confidence in the election for Senate and governor. One county revealed Monday that it had allowed some hurricane-displaced voters to cast their ballots by email — a violation of state law. Another had to restart its recount after getting about a quarter finished because someone forgot to push a button. And in oft-criticized Broward County, additional sheriff's deputies were sent to guard ballots and voting machines, even though a judge said no Republican who has publicly alleged fraud in the county's process — a list that includes President Donald Trump and Gov. Rick Scott — has filed a criminal complaint or presented evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obesity pill to kill hunger by expanding in stomach...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/11/13/obesity-pill-aims-kill-hunger-expanding-stomach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An obesity pill that expands into a gel almost 100 times its original size after being swallowed has moved one step closer to approval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China scours social media, erases thousands of accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/technology/china-deletes-social-media-accounts-cyber-authority-10925324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's top cyber authority has scrubbed 9,800 social media accounts of independent news providers deemed to have posted sensational, vulgar or ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRINK OF WAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/rocket-barrages-israeli-strikes-threaten-new-gaza-war-doc-1ar8ka15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Longest Losing Streak on Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-under-pressure-with-record-skid-set-to-continue-2018-11-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil trades lower Tuesday, unable to recover from a start-of-the-week pullback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling in love good for blood pressure, pain relief, allergic reactions...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6381807/Why-falling-love-good-blood-pressure-pain-relief-allergic-reactions.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Falling in love is the result of activity in 12 areas of the brain working together, according to researchers at the University of Western Virginia in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman warned about 'sparks' from power lines day before started...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/13/woman-warned-about-sparks-from-power-lines-day-before-deadly-wildfire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman in Northern California said Monday that the Pacific Gas &amp; Electric Co. contacted her about “sparks” in power lines on her property one day before the deadly wildfire in Para…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security Sec Next Chop?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-is-preparing-to-remove-kirstjen-nielsen-as-homeland-security-secretary-aides-say/2018/11/12/77111496-e6b0-11e8-bbdb-72fdbf9d4fed_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She is trying to complete a full year in the job, but the president wants her out sooner, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After conquering the world, smartphone faces uncertain future...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/conquering-world-smartphone-faces-uncertain-future-032038224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is next for the smartphone, which has become the hottest-selling consumer device around the world in just over a decade? The next catalyst for smartphones could be the possibilities offered by the forthcoming 5G, or fifth generation wireless networks, new form factors or advances in virtual and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA INFERNO DEADLIEST IN AMERICAN HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apos-please-don-apos-t-185532688.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Survivors told how they fled California's apocalyptic wildfires as the soles of their shoes melted, celebrities returned to find their multi-million dollars homes in ashes, and the state's governor warned "our whole way of life" was under threat. As the fires continued to rage at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German states want social media law tightened; No 'Hate'...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/german-states-want-social-media-law-tightened-media-220730328--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German states have drafted a list of demands aimed at tightening a law that requires social media companies like Facebook and Twitter to remove hate speech from their sites, the Handelblatt newspaper reported on Monday. Justice ministers from the states will submit their proposed revisions to the German</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuees trickle back to deal with the ashes...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/california-fire-evacuees-trickle-back-deal-ashes-225835866.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We were surrounded by rapidly approaching fire." Instead of smoldering wreckage, however, they found that their neighborhood Tiffany Oaks, which consists of 13 homes spanning two cul-de-sacs, had been saved by firefighters, an oasis in an otherwise scorched landscape. The Camp Fire in northern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM WINS AZ SENATE RACE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democrat-kyrsten-sinema-wins-arizona-us-senate-seat-004232833--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Democrat Kyrsten Sinema won Arizona's open U.S. Senate seat Monday in a race that was among the most closely watched in the nation, beating Republican Rep. Martha McSally in the battle to replace GOP Sen. Jeff Flake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems gain veto-proof supermajority in California legislature...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/california/articles/2018-11-12/democrats-gain-veto-proof-majority-in-california-legislature</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire and police fought fire as blaze hit home: More than 90 first responders lost houses...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article221509110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among residents who lost homes in the Camp Fire in Butte County, California: Cal Fire firefighters, Paradise town police officers, the mayor and others, as they worked to save lives and battle the wildfires, which burned over 6,700 structures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everybody is at risk' from bad air...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/11/11/wildfires-everybody-is-at-risk-from-smoky-conditions-experts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Californians need to prepare for wildfires – including particulate-filled air – just as they do for earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latinos could turn Texas blue in 2020 if enthusiasm holds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2018-elections/2018/11/11/latinos-could-turn-texas-blue-2020-enthusiasm-holds-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blue wave lapped at the shores of Texas this year -- and it was powered by Latino voters.Though Republicans held on against the current in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS:  Trumpism takes a thumping...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/416335-press-trumpism-takes-a-thumping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like beauty, defeat, it seems, is in the eyes of the beholder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhol in New York: Fresh experience for audiences old and new...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/warhol-york-fresh-experience-audiences-old-011405621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His Marilyn Monroe paintings and oversize soup cans are cultural icons, but in an exhibition opening Monday, New York's Whitney Museum hopes to paint a new, more complex picture of Andy Warhol. Now the Whitney, located on the banks of the Hudson River in the city's Meatpacking District, hopes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA locates secret NKorea missile sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-analysts-id-13-secret-north-korean-missile-151833745.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. analysts said Monday they have located 13 secret North Korean missile development sites, underscoring the challenge that the Trump administration faces in trying to reach its promised broad arms control agreement with Pyongyang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 200 still missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/more-200-still-missing-californias-deadliest-wildfire-record-092228965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadly Camp Fire also ranked as California's most destructive ever in terms of property losses, having incinerated more than 6,700 homes and other buildings in the Sierra foothills of Butte County, about 175 miles (280 km) north of San Francisco. Most of the devastation and loss of life was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos, deal or new vote: What is Brexit finale?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chaos-deal-vote-grand-brexit-finale-150958780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Theresa May is trying to clinch a Brexit divorce deal with the European Union but the bigger challenge may be to get any agreement approved by the British parliament. Any deal must be approved by British lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Longest Losing Streak on Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/oil-jumps-as-opec-moves-closer-to-cutting-output-1542019255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices notched their longest losing streak on record Monday, as comments from President Trump negated expectations that the global oil cartel and its allies will cut production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom, Please Stop Talking to My Boss! Parents Invade the Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mom-please-stop-talking-to-my-boss-parents-invade-the-office-1542042333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eager to see what their adult offspring do all day, moms and dads embrace office visits; ‘It’s almost like we’re in a zoo, and we’re the animals’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: Hillary Will Run Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/hillary-will-run-again-1541963599</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reinventing herself as a liberal firebrand, Mrs. Clinton will easily capture the 2020 nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dems consider impeaching Trump, GOP leaders regret pursuing Clinton...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-as-dems-consider-impeaching-trump-gop-leaders-regret-pursuing-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Democrats are trying to reassure anyone that they won't impeach President Trump, they're aren't doing a very good job of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less than 1 in 3 meet new fitness guidelines...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/11/12/physical-fitness-aerobic-activity-sports-social-media-health-human-services-department/1943318002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Baugh, who founded the fitness advocacy, nonprofit group PHITAmerica, says even the dire picture painted in the federal reports may be too optimistic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First TVs controlled only by your mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7725968/samsung-tvs-controlled-by-your-mind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAMSUNG is to start work on the first ever smart TV that can be controlled by the user’s mind, according to reports. The software will allow people to change channels and the volume using onl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland's first sex doll brothel...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7724904/finland-sex-doll-brothel-helsinki-unique-dolls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINLAND will be opening its first sex doll BROTHEL later this week as demand for silicone companions blows up all over the world. Russian-owned Unique Dolls will open its doors in Helsinki on Thurs…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France calls for Europe to become  powerful new 'empire' to rival USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7721886/europe-should-become-empire-to-compete-with-china-and-us-says-french-minister-after-trump-rubbishes-calls-for-eu-army/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE’S finance minister has called for the EU to become a powerful new “empire” to rival the US and China in an interview which will infuriate Donald Trump. Bruno Le Maire’s comments come a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUNDLED AND BAGGED</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/must-see-video-broward-county-elections-officials-block-view-as-ballots-are-bundled-and-bagged-in-davie-florida-voting-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein's Secret Weapon:  'Bloodhound' NYPD Detective Turned Private Eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/weinsteins-secret-weapon-is-a-bloodhound-nypd-detective-turned-private-eye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herman Weisberg worked in the same D.A.’s office prosecuting the movie mogul. Now he’s working against it. ‘He’s the knock at the door you don’t want.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm Emanuel Shops Around for Cable News Gig...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/chicago-mayor-rahm-emanuel-is-shopping-around-for-a-cable-news-gig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The famously pugnacious Democrat is taking meetings at CNN and MSNBC, looking for his next act after running the Windy City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman blows up wedding dress at divorce party. Blast felt miles away...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article221527670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Santleben-Stiteler blew her wedding dress up at her divorce party Saturday in Lacoste, Texas. It was rigged with 20 pounds of explosives and she shot it from 200 yards away, video shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 million Americans live in RVs. Meet 'modern nomads'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/1-million-Americans-live-in-RVs-Meet-the-modern-13383991.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Robert and Jessica Meinhofer told friends they were moving into an RV in 2015, most thought they were crazy. The questions poured in: How could they go from living in a 2,000-square-foot home to living in a 250-square-foot trailer? What would they do with their stuff? What would their children, ages 6 and 9, do for school? Was this a midlife crisis? The hardest people to convince were Jessica's parents, who grew up in an impoverished Latino neighborhood in the Bronx and worked hard so their daughter could have a better life. They couldn't understand why the couple wanted to live like migrant laborers. The Meinhofers are doing this by choice, not financial desperation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: May stares into abyss...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu/may-stares-into-brexit-abyss-as-domestic-opposition-mounts-idUSKCN1NH140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May's Brexit strategy came under attack from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM WINS AZ SENATE RACE</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/arizona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Arizona election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Much Caffeine May Stress Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/12/well/live/too-much-caffeine-may-stress-the-heart.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In moderate doses caffeine has mainly positive effects for most people. But it increases production of cortisol, which can lead to health problems including anxiety, weight gain and heart disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECOUNT 2018!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/step-right-recount-circus-has-come-back-florida-n935011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pro-Trump protesters to swarming lawyers to paper jams, the latest ballot counting isn't making the state look any better than the last one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Personality Chased Out Of Brooklyn Bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/kat-timpf-chased-out-of-brooklyn-bar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fox News and National Review contributor was publicly harassed over the weekend in the third such politically motivated incident she’s faced in the last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys with herpes rapidly breeding in FL park a recipe for trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2018/11/florida-rhesus-monkeys-herpes-running-wild-invasive-species/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Descendants of theme-park escapees, a population of rhesus macaques in a Florida state park may soon double in size—a recipe for trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned to death because of rumor on WHATSAPP...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/whatsapp-rumours-incite-angry-mob-13576897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING CONTENT: The men were dragged out of a jail cell and killed as hundreds cheered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flintstones' couple live like cave dwellers at own 'Stone Age' village ...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/flintstones-couple-build-stone-age-13577912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naomi Walmsley and husband Dan Westall wear Paleolithic designs made from rabbit fur and hunt with a bow and arrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voted by email?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/election/article221536055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Hurricane Michael devastated the Panhandle in October, Bay County Supervisor of Elections Mark Andersen allowed some displaced voters to cast ballots by email or fax, even though there is no provision that allows for it in state law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrons feast on record 5,039-lb nacho serving...</title>
      <link>https://www.lcsun-news.com/story/news/local/community/2018/11/11/world-record-largest-nachos-las-cruces-new-mexico/1964413002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lcsun-news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Cruces has set the world record of the largest serving of nachos. The monstrous creationÂ came in weighing at 5,039 pounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRINK OF WAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/From-the-city-of-peace-to-a-country-on-the-brink-of-war-571772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The premier and his staff headed home in the dead of night, under a shower of rain that dimmed the lights of his convoy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of sunspots to bring record cold, warns NASA scientist...</title>
      <link>https://www.iceagenow.info/lack-of-sunspots-to-bring-record-cold-warns-nasa-scientist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iceagenow.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It could happen in a matter of months,” says Martin Mlynczak of NASA’s Langley Research Center. ________________ “The sun is entering one of the deepest Solar Minima of the Space Age,” wrote Dr Tony Phillips just six weeks ago, on 27 Sep 2018. Sunspots have been absent for most of 2018 and Earth’s upper atmosphere is ... Read moreLack of sunspots to bring record cold, warns NASA scientist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO maps dangerous misuse of antibiotics...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181112-who-maps-dangerous-misuse-antibiotics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 VISION: 36 Dems Running?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/swalwell-joins-crowded-field-of-possible-2020-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three dozen Democrats are believed to be preparing for a possible bid to take on President Trump in 2020 — more than double the crowded field of 17 Republican candidates who fought in 2016 for the chance to face then-President Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congo Ebola outbreak worst in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1044207/ebola-outbreak-congo-2018-ebola-symptoms-vaccine-who-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE current Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is the most severe in the country's history with 319 confirmed and probable cases and at least 198 dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFERNO DEADLIEST IN STATE HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/11/11/crews-continue-to-battle-strong-winds-in-deadly-camp-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters worked to contain the deadly Camp Fire, which had burned some 109,000 acres Sunday and was 25 percent contained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RABID CAT KILLS TOURIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/741947/rabies-morocco-dead-british-death-disease-holiday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm to decide if D unseats R in Maine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6380899/New-way-voting-faces-test-Maine-congressional-district.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP incumbent Bruce Polquin's Maine seat is being decided by a new system which asks voters to rank candidates by preference then counts 2nd and 3rd preferences until one has 50 per cent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents accuse CDC of not reporting children's deaths from polio-like illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/health/cdc-underreported-afm-deaths/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control hasn't reported any deaths in 2018 from acute flaccid myelitis, the polio-like illness which paralyzes healthy children, but CNN has learned of two children who passed away from the disease this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smart toilets' to scan your poop, diagnose disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/ai-toilets-scan-your-poop-to-diagnose-medical-ailments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Micron CEO Sanjay Mehrotra sees smart loos in our future and is anxious to sell the chips they will need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Top Threats to World 'Climate Change', Nuclear War...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2018/11/12/pope-francis-chief-threats-world-climate-change-nuclear-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis highlighted what he considers two main threats to humanity: the “immense crisis” of global warming and nuclear war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI HIT LIST: 85 TRUMP TARGETS... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/house-democrats-subpoenas-trump-administration-cf3ed351-ff11-4498-89f4-cee588145198.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight will test the power of the presidency, Congress and the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mishaps, protests, litigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/105ce13715ae4c9da23ba2adf5cafae0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — After Republicans, including President Donald Trump, made unsubstantiated accusations of illegal activity, a judge on Monday urged the warring sides in the Florida recount to "ramp down the rhetoric," saying it eroded public confidence in the election for Senate and governor. The state's law enforcement arm and elections monitors have found no evidence of wrongdoing, but lawyers for the Republican party and the GOP candidates joined with Trump in alleging that irregularities, unethical behavior and fraud have taken place since the polls closed last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  STARS LOSE HOMES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/woolsey-fire-miley-cyrus-gerard-butler-lose-home-1203025964/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive wildfires that continue to rage in California have forced hundreds of thousands in Southern California to evacuate from their homes. Miley Cyrus, Gerard Butler, and Neil Young are among…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: Squeezed to frame, texts 'out of context?'</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/usworld/world/14284978-74/roger-stone-associate-jerome-corsi-expects-to-be-charged-in-mueller-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative author Jerome Corsi said Monday that he expects to be indicted by prosecutors working for Special Counsel Robert Mueller on a charge of lying to investigators probing Russian interference in the 2016 campaign. Corsi, a writer who has promoted political conspiracy theories, provided research during the race to longtime ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST DEM IN:   OJEDA ANNOUNCES BID FOR PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/11/11/richard-ojeda-2020-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I'm not trying to throw stones at people that are rich, but once again, we will have a field that will be full of millionaires,” Ojeda said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAINTING TO MAKE HISTORY?</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/quartzy/1460361/a-david-hockney-painting-at-christies-will-likely-break-auction-records-at-80-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It will displace "Balloon Dog" by Jeff Koons as the most expensive artwork sold at auction by a living artist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Brown Blames Climate Deniers...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/news-and-politics/jerry-brown-climate-change-deniers-definitely-contributing-to-the-new-abnormal-of-wildfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're getting caught up here in a changed world that not so many people were aware of or thinking about... the chickens are coming home to roost," says California governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Music In Middle Of Night Plagues NJ Communities, Perplexes Police...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/11/09/mysterious-music-plaguing-several-south-jersey-communities-in-middle-of-night-leaves-authorities-perplexed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a noise that's plagued Salem County residents along the Delaware River for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if Harvey walks free?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/12/what-if-harvey-weinstein-walks-free/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What seemed unthinkable one year ago is on the verge of happening: Harvey Weinstein will probably walk. Last Monday, Weinstein’s attorneys filed a motion to dismiss the entire criminal case against…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL's $100 Million Bust...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/12/i-gotta-get-the-f-k-outta-here-jon-grudens-raiders-are-lost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2018 Raiders are what nightmares are made of. Following Oakland’s fifth straight loss Sunday, which dropped it to 1-8 on an already disastrous season, the $100 million coach said the curr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O: Like, Like, You Know, Like, Dude, You Know?</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-michelle-o-you-know-dude-you-know</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I was like, dude, you're cute'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Firms ready to microchip THOUSANDS of employees..</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/12/uk-firms-ready-to-microchip-thousands-of-employees-8129303/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies are 'in talks' with a Swedish microchipping company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow To Host CBS Series 'MILLION DOLLAR MILE' From LeBron...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/lebron-james-tim-tebow-million-dollar-mile-cbs-1202499894/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NFL quarterback Tim Tebow has landed a new gig as host of the forthcoming CBS physical competition series Million Dollar Mile from executive producers Allison Grodner and Rich Meehan with Fl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke Plumes May Extend To East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/12/california-wildfires-smoke-plumes-new-england/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite imagery shows just how massive the fires are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New blazes fan fresh fears in California as some return home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cbcaf374df5e4bb6bd82c8894053d2a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MALIBU, Calif. (AP) — The sky was black and flames on the next ridge were fast approaching when Paul Rasmussen, his pregnant wife and 6-year-old daughter fled their mountainside Malibu home Friday for what they thought might be the last time. His only hope that the large home, once billed in real estate listings as "Shangri-La," would survive was that his next-door neighbor, Randy Berkeley, would not only protect his own house, but also Rasmussen's. On Monday, after driving a winding road across charred slopes and past smoldering ruins of other houses in Decker Canyon, Rasmussen wrapped Berkeley in a bear hug of thanks after finding their two houses still standing untouched by fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida election recount underway, tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0451d4eefaec481aaaa3293379fb9a69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Mishaps, protests and litigation dominated Florida's first day of recounting the vote for pivotal races for governor and Senate, bringing back memories of the 2000 presidential fiasco. Much of the drama on Sunday centered on Broward and Palm Beach counties, home to large concentrations of Democratic voters. In Broward County, the recount was delayed for several hours Sunday morning because of a problem with one of the tabulation machines. That prompted the Republican Party to slam Broward's supervisor of elections, Brenda Snipes, for "incompetence and gross mismanagement."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi Predicts Mueller Indictment Likely In Days...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-counsel-witness-expects-charged-mueller-probe/story?id=59148352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Infowars Washington bureau chief tells ABC News that the special counsel has now indicated he will be charged in within a matter of days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAN LEE DEAD AT 95...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/11/12/stan-lee-dead-dies-marvel-comics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stan Lee, the man responsible for much of the Marvel Universe, has died ... Stan's daughter tells TMZ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Kim and Kanye Hire Private Team, Save Neighbors...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/11/12/kim-kardashian-kanye-west-save-neighborhood-fire-hire-private-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian and Kanye West getting major props from neighbors for helping to stop the spread of the Woolsey Fires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Showbiz, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authentic. Unfiltered. Fearless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters tells Trump to 'keep his mouth shut'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/mad-maxine-tells-trump-to-keep-his-mouth-shut-over-california-fires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Maxine Waters, who has criticized President Donald Trump and Republicans for their “rhetoric,” has been cranking up her tone since Democrats won the U.S. House of Representatives last week. During an interview on Sunday on MSNBC’s “AM Joy,” the California Democrat claimed that the Republican Party fears “strong, black” women like her. She also said she …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Nancy Pelosi foes struggle to find a leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Abrams files new suit in GA governor's race...</title>
      <link>http://www.onlineathens.com/nationworld/20181111/democrat-abrams-files-new-suit-in-georgia-governors-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA | Stacey Abrams' Democratic campaign filed a federal lawsuit Sunday asking a judge to delay vote certifications in Georgia unsettled governor's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain — and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official Website of The Sean Hannity Show. Sean Hannity is a multimedia superstar, spending four hours a day every day reaching out to millions of Americans on radio, television and the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health department raids parks, pours bleach on food being given to homeless...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/kansas-city-health-department-pours-bleach-on-food-meant-for-homeless-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, MISSOURI (Fox 32 News) - The Kansas City Health Department threw away and poured bleach on food meant for homeless people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News is dedicated to the best in journalism under standards it pioneered at the dawn of radio and television and continues to set in today’s digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rachel Maddow Show was No. 1 across all of cable TV on Friday in total viewers. Fox News remained No. 1 across cable news by dominating the 8 and 10 p.m. hours. CNN beat MSNBC in the demo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, womenâ€™s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman steals live lobster from tank, flees restaurant...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/drunk/red-lobster-heist-186531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An intoxicated Florida Woman plucked a live lobster from a tank at a Red Lobster and bolted from the St. Petersburg restaurant with the purloined crustacean, according to police. Kimberly Gabel, 42,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stonezone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Guide to Restaurants, Fashion, Nightlife, Shopping, Politics, Movies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM: NOT GOING TO BE SHUSHED</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/11/12/count-vote-candidates-election-recount-rick-scott-bill-nelson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As election departments across the state begin the process of recounting the votes from the 2018 midterm elections, the candidates whose races will be decided by the count are speaking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap produces a wide range of news contents and provides print, broadcast media as well as state and private institutions with real-time news products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/columnists/howie_carr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
