<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Libertarian candidate Jo Jorgensen advocates end to big govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article244996385.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY corralled virus. What's California's excuse for surge?</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/new-york-corralled-coronavirus-whats-californias-excuse-for-case-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts and those with ties to both states say New Yorkers gained a healthy respect for the virus’ deadly potential after it hammered the state in the spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convention season set to begin, with [virtual] spotlight on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-convention-season-set-begin-201227357.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Democrats on Monday open an unprecedented virtual convention, the party&amp;#39;s disparate factions are projecting a united front behind Joe Biden, brought together by their common determination to defeat Donald Trump in November&amp;#39;s election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First major Mediterranean cruise liner sets sail since pandemic... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-major-cruise-line-set-082146808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first major cruise ship to resume tours of the Mediterranean since the coronavirus pandemic hit Europe set sail from the Italian city of Genoa on Sunday, as the industry tries to regain ground after a bruising hiatus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND NIGHT OF ROLLING BLACKOUTS IN CALI...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-worst-power-shortage-years-130019359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People staying home with air conditioners blasting, plus a dearth of power from other states results in the worst statewide energy shortage in nearly 20 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy closes nightclubs as cases rise among young...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200816173142-jjf0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY-NIGHTCLUBS (PIX):Italy closes nightclubs as coronavirus cases rise among young</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival rallies face off in Warsaw over gay rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200816160439-m28p6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nationalists burnt a rainbow flag, while the LGBT activists painted one on the street</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey in a Stir Over Old Biden Remarks Backing Erdogan Ouster...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/turkey-stir-over-old-biden-133025340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- An old video of Democratic presidential hopeful Joe Biden calling for the removal of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has set off a furor in Turkey while earning U.S. President Donald Trump a shout-out.In a Dec. 16 meeting with New York Times editors, Biden called Erdogan an “autocrat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst heatwave in 70 years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-faces-second-night-blackouts-020525955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- First, it was the prospect of wildfires that took down large swaths of California’s power grid. Now, it’s the worst heat wave in 70 years.Climate change is contributing to increasingly extreme weather in California. Less than a year ago, millions of people were plunged into darkness in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New White House virus doc has no expertise in public health or infectious diseases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/886b59d445a3d20739e2f77600976ea0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has found a new doctor for his coronavirus task force — and this time there's no daylight between them. Trump last week announced that Dr. Scott...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm Determined UK Students' Grades. Chaos Ensued...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/an-algorithm-determined-uk-students-grades-chaos-ensued/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's A-Levels, the high-stakes exams taken in high school, were canceled due to the pandemic. The alternative only exacerbated existing inequities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest woman in USA celebrates turning 116 with drive-thru birthday...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-8632493/Oldest-woman-200-grandchildren-celebrates-116th-birthday-style.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hester Ford, from Charlotte, North Carolina, blew out 116th candles this weekend. The great grandmother, who has 200 great-grandchildren, is believed to be the oldest person living in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universities drastically reshaped...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/16/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The return to college campuses this month has offered a preview into how the coronavirus pandemic has drastically reshaped the university experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter films own arrest at Proud Boys rally...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/16/michigan-reporter-filmed-arrest-at-proud-boys-rally-in-kalamazoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Jesus — I’m being arrested!” Samuel Robinson suddenly cried, his camera shaking as officers were shown around him. He repeatedly shouted, “I’m media!” bef…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems in conservative S.C. see opportunity for gains...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-conservative-c-see-opportunity-122218359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#39;s been nearly 15 years since a Democrat won a statewide office and 44 years since a Democratic presidential candidate claimed the state. In the U.S. Senate race, Democrat Jaime Harrison has raised more money than GOP incumbent Lindsey Graham for two quarters in a row. A Democrat captured a longtime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama 'uses loopholes to bypass coastal protection laws in Hawaii' to build compound...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8631723/Planning-loopholes-bypass-coastal-protection-laws-Hawaii-compound-tied-Obama.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials and community members confirmed to ProPublica that Obama plans to reside in the compound on Oahu, which was purchased for $8.7 million by his close friend Marty Nesbitt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KODAK loan: Insider trading in new garb?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/512174-the-kodak-loan-insider-trading-in-a-new-garb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DFC loan to Kodak is the first of its kind under the Defense Production Act, and so it is not surprising that it raised a number of new issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden looks to make inroads with evangelicals...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/511809-biden-looks-to-make-inroads-with-evangelical-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden is seeking to make inroads with evangelical voters, a demographic that overwhelmingly sided with President Trump during the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's Been Pacifist for 75 Years. Missile Proposal Challenges That...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/16/japans-been-proudly-pacifist-for-75-years-a-missile-proposal-challenges-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO — Shinzo Abe is facing some of the toughest challenges of his record-setting tenure as Japan’s prime minister, with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no balloon drops, what's a convention for?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/08/16/joe-biden-kamala-harris-keys-to-democratic-convention/3368123001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Joe Biden, the to-do list at this week's virtual convention includes spanning a political spectrum from John Kasich to AOC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defund police? Already happening thanks to Covid-19 budget crunch...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/15/defund-the-police-coronavirus-budget-395665</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision about how much spending needs to be cut, and from where, will be up to each state’s bank balance and the political makeup of its government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian surfer punches shark to save wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200816-australian-surfer-punches-shark-to-save-wife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian surfer punches shark to save wife</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fire tornado' warning? Weather service issues what could be first...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fire-tornado-warning-weather-issues-001717718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Fire tornadoes happen, but the issuance of a tornado warning on one is a first.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Cult of Priests Who Hate Pope Francis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/this-secret-cult-of-priests-still-wont-recognize-pope-francis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A priest in Sacramento, California, has been excommunicated for not accepting Pope Francis as the real pope. He’s not the only one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA clears saliva test opening door to wider testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/08/15/fda-clears-saliva-test-for-covid-19-opening-door-to-wider-testing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA granted emergency use authorization for a saliva test for the virus that causes Covid-19, which could improve testing capability in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND NIGHT OF CALI ROLLING BLACKOUTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article244996275.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington QB Alex Smith cleared to play after horrific injury...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29671320/washington-qb-alex-smith-cleared-football-activity-team</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Football Team quarterback Alex Smith, who suffered a leg injury in 2018 that nearly cost him his life, will be cleared for football activity and be activated off the physically unable to perform list, a source told ESPN's John Keim on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea Warns of New Mass Infection After Church Flareup...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/south-korea-confirms-279-new-covid-19-cases-most-since-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korea Warns of New Mass Infection After Church Flareup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telephone service begins between UAE, Israel amid deal...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/middle-east/2020/08/telephone-service-begins-between-uae-israel-amid-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Telephone service between the United Arab Emirates and Israel has begun as the two countries open diplomatic ties. Associated Press journalists in Jerusalem and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's brother dies aged 71...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/robert-trump-president-younger-brother-022805753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump&amp;#39;s younger brother, Robert Trump, a businessman known for an even keel that seemed almost incompatible with the family name, died Saturday night after being hospitalized in New York, the president said in a statement. The president visited his brother at a New York City hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffered brain bleeds that began after recent fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/robert-s-trump-the-presidents-younger-brother-dies-at-71/ar-BB180r9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffered brain bleeds that began after recent fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/15/us/politics/robert-s-trump-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A loyal spokesman for the family, he shunned the spotlight and had “zero sense of entitlement.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney slams administration over death toll... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/No-way-to-spin-that-Romney-says-of-U-S-15486939.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Mitt Romney, R-Utah, offered rare Republican criticism of the Trump administration's coronavirus response Friday, saying the federal government dismissed the virus's threat and failed to protect Americans as infections spiraled out of control.  "Short term, I think it's fair to say we really have not distinguished ourselves in a positive way by how we responded to the crisis when it was upon us," Romney said in a video interview with the Sutherland Institute. "And the proof of the pudding of that is simply that we have 5 percent of the world's population but 25 percent of the world's deaths due to covid-19.  "And there's no way to spin that in a positive light," Romney added.  At least 166,000 people nationwide have died of coronavirus-related complications - about 21 percent of the worldwide death toll. An additional 1,222 U.S. deaths were reported Friday and 1,218 were reported Saturday as of late evening.  Here are some other significant developments:  - The number and rate of infections in children under 17 have increased since March, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said in recently updated guidance, underscoring the risk for young people and their families as schools weigh whether to reopen with in-person instruction. Although the virus is far more prevalent and severe among adults, the true incidence of infection in U.S. children remains unknown because of a lack of widespread testing, according to the agency.  - The Food and Drug Administration granted emergency-use authorization Saturday to a saliva-based coronavirus test, developed by Yale University researchers, that aims to reduce turnaround times in commercial laboratories.  - New York continued to report progress against the virus after experiencing the country's most severe outbreak in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Crisis Ripples Across Nation as Election Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/usps-postal-workers-slowdown-2020-election-2c0d3cf8-38d1-459b-9c21-07e9e637c82b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This isn't a just a potential threat — it is happening before our eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia, Anti-Facists Face Off in Tense Stone Mountain Protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/protesters-clash-in-stone-mountain/3ZXGYQQJWFB6VAMZSZR74B4DXE/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters clash in Stone Mountain. Far-right militia, leftist groups faced off as police held back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX and UPS warn they cannot deliver votes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/video/ups-fedex-warn-cannot-carry-174229060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the fight over voting by mail grows in the U.S. leading up to November’s presidential election, on Friday private delivery companies UPS and FedEx shot down social media calls that they step in to deliver mail-in ballots from the U.S. Postal Service.        This comes as USPS warned states of potentially &amp;quot;significant&amp;quot; delays.        In a statement exclusively to Reuters, UPS said (quote):        “State ballots must be postmarked to be considered valid and only the USPS has lawful postmarking status. Therefore UPS, FedEx and other private parties cannot technically be involved in shipping ballots.”        While FedEx responded (quote):        &amp;quot;FedEx does accept individual ballots, and we advise that customers planning to return their ballots via FedEx should closely review their state&amp;#39;s guidelines on absentee voting and deadlines for ballots or related election documents.&amp;quot;        All this taking place while President Donald Trump on Thursday said he opposed providing funds for the struggling Postal Service for mail voting, which is expected to surge to 50% as the coronavirus pandemic rages ahead of the Nov. 3 presidential election.        The Postal Service said on Friday it has written to 46 states and the District of Columbia warning there is a significant risk voters will not have enough time to complete and return their ballots.        There are other hurdles that these private companies would face…        While the USPS touches every U.S. mailbox six days a week, other companies visit only when they have a delivery or a pre-arranged pickup.        The other issue is cost...        According to Tammy Patrick, a former Arizona election official and senior advisor to the Democracy Fund foundation, domestic costs would skyrocket, since delivery firms charge significantly more for deliveries than the price of a 55-cent stamp while international costs would be “astronomical.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEFT VS RIGHT BATTLE IN MICHIGAN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1316052/proud-boys-group-brawl-antifa-protests-kalamazoo-michigan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RALLY organized by far-right group Proud Boys in Kalamazoo, Michigan, escalated into violence when they were met by a peaceful church vigil. The First Congregational Church hosted a gathering of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING BLACKOUTS CALI...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2020-08-15-california-heat-wave-power-outages-rolling-blackouts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is sweltering under a late summer heat wave that's led to rolling blackouts and warnings about air quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trigger Oakland Estuary Sewage Spill...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/08/15/rolling-power-outage-triggers-oakland-estuary-sewage-spill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boaters were being warned Saturday to stay away from the Oakland Estuary after an estimated 50,000 gallons of raw sewage spilled during a power outage Friday night at the East Bay Municipal Utility District wastewater treatment plant in West Oakland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxe Quarantine Lives of Silicon Valley Elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/08/luxe-quarantine-lives-of-silicon-valley-elite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travis Kalanick is throwing (outdoor) parties, private-jet owners are hopping from safe zone to safe zone, and dinner party hosts are administering 15-minute COVID-19 rapid tests—all business as usual. “Coronavirus is a poor person’s virus,” says one source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Apocalypse: The rich and famous are fleeing in droves...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8631063/Hollywood-Apocalypse-rich-famous-fleeing-droves.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAROLINE GRAHAM: The pandemic has made many in Hollywood realise they don't need to live in LA - or anywhere near it - to keep working.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney slams administration over death toll... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/15/romney-slams-trump-administration-over-us-coronavirus-death-toll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah Sen. Mitt Romney criticized the Trump administration's early response to the coronavirus outbreak, saying they didn't immediately "ring all the alarm bells."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracing Trump's Postal Service obsession  --  from 'loser' to 'scam' to 'rigged election'... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Tracing-Trump-s-Postal-Service-obsession-from-15486836.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Soon after taking office in 2017, President Donald Trump seized on the U.S. Postal Service as an emblem of the bloated bureaucracy. "A loser," he repeatedly labeled one of America's most beloved public institutions, according to aides who discussed the matter with him.  Allies coddled Trump by telling him the reason he lost the popular vote to Hillary Clinton in 2016 was widespread mail-in balloting fraud - a conspiracy theory for which there is no evidence - and the president's postal outrage coarsened further.  Then Trump complained to senior White House advisers that Jeff Bezos - a presidential foe in part because he owns The Washington Post, whose news coverage the president thought was unfair and too tough on him - was "getting rich" because Amazon had been "ripping off" the Postal Service with a "sweetheart deal" to ship millions of its packages, one of them recalled. They explained that this was not true and that the Postal Service actually benefited from Amazon's business, the adviser added, but the president railed for months about what he described as a "scam."  And now Trump has fixated again on the Postal Service, this time trying to make it a tool in his reelection campaign by slowing mail service, blocking an emergency infusion of federal funds and challenging the integrity of mail-in balloting. The president acknowledged last week that his opposition is rooted in his desire to restrict how many Americans can vote by mail.  The breathtaking moves by the Trump administration this summer to disrupt a Constitutionally mandated government service during the coronavirus pandemic - under the argument that it will boost operational efficiencies - represent the culmination of Trump's grievance-fueled crusade against the Postal Service that dates to the start of his presidency. Many of his complaints...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioters Tear Down George Washington Statue at L.A. City Hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/08/14/watch-rioters-tear-down-george-washington-statue-at-l-a-city-hall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rioters tore down a statue of George Washington near Los Angeles City Hall on Thursday evening, the latest monument to fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Military Posts Video of Air Defense Drills as Warning to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2020/08/14/chinese-military-posts-video-hong-kong-air-defense-drills-warning-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese military publishes a short video of air defense drills seen as a warning to the U.S. against interfering in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing mailbox in Baltimore latest symbol of turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/politics/bs-md-pol-usps-signs-20200815-dy6sstao7bemliolecgh6gkvvi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More signs of the turmoil at the U.S. Postal Service emerged in Maryland this weekend after at least one of the service’s iconic blue mailboxes was removed from a Baltimore street corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong journalists harassed, arrested and losing press freedoms under new law...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-journalists-harassed-arrested-120007846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The raid this week of Apple Daily&amp;#39;s newsroom and leadership changes at broadcaster iCable highlight the shrinking space for independent journalism as Beijing exerts more control over a once freewheeling Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA says President not entitled to extra protection from grand-jury subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-subpoena/manhattan-da-says-trump-not-entitled-to-extra-protection-from-grand-jury-subpoena-idUSKCN25A1Z1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump is not entitled to greater protection from a grand-jury subpoena for his tax returns just because he is president, the Manhattan district attorney said in a court filing on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey will send ballots to all active registered voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/coronavirus/2020/08/everybody-gets-a-ballot-murphy-says-nj-to-have-mostly-mail-in-voting-in-november-election-because-of-covid-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Phil Murphy is expected to discuss the issue more Friday afternoon at his latest coronavirus briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Fun Police Should Stand Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-fun-police-should-stand-down/ar-BB17ZH48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorching temps in Southwest shatter records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/15/weather/weekend-heat-record-california-and-texas/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 80 million people are under excessive heat alerts this weekend with records possible in over 10 states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds developing corona strain for human 'challenge' trials...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-developing-coronavirus-strain-human-220417655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US scientists are developing a strain of the coronavirus that could be used to deliberately infect volunteers in so-called &amp;quot;challenge studies,&amp;quot; a government agency said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NEWSWEEK apologizes for op-ed questioning Kamala eligibility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fe4e75db0007c1854e98cb6f2d3488c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Newsweek has apologized for an op-ed that questioned Sen. Kamala Harris’ U.S. citizenship and her eligibility to be Joe Biden’s running mate, a false and racist conspiracy theory...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police move in...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cc42ee6ff8cb1c05278a1e2d7f045a2e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STONE MOUNTAIN, Ga. (AP) — After several hours of mostly peaceful demonstrations Saturday in an Atlanta suburb that's home to a giant Confederate memorial, large numbers of police moved in to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans brave open sea on tubes, fishing for survival...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/025a5e913ae0e6f7537c55cae8e48569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA GUAIRA, Venezuela (AP) — The biggest fear is a fishhook puncturing the inner tube that keeps them afloat far from shore. Then come sharks grabbing their catch and maybe biting their legs. And...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
