<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>10 hospitalized after flu shot turns out to be insulin...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/11/08/flu-shots-insulin-oklahoma-10-hospitalized/2529395001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bartlesville, Oklahoma facility had contracted with a pharmacist to administer the vaccine, but all received injections of insulin instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's Online Crackdowns Inspire World's Dictators...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/11/06/germany-online-crackdowns-inspired-the-worlds-dictators-russia-venezuela-india/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anti-hate speech law written in Berlin has been copy-pasted by authoritarian regimes from Caracas to Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.I. voice assistant  -- your new best friend?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2019/11/08/alexa-google-assistant-ai-robots-become-substitute-friends/4057885002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The promise is that companion robots and voice assistants such as Alexa and the Google Assistant will be our "friends." Can AI solve loneliness?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearings likely to draw high TV ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment-tv-factbox/factbox-trump-impeachment-hearings-likely-to-draw-high-ratings-in-new-era-of-political-tv-idUSKBN1XI1EJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public impeachment hearings for U.S. President Donald Trump next week will mark ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Removes News Reports Mentioning Alleged Whistleblower's Identity...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/11/08/facebook-removes-any-news-reporting-on-or-even-mention-of-who-the-whistleblower-is-alleged-to-be/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media companies including Facebook have launched a crackdown against accounts that publish the name of the alleged Ukraine whistleblower, Eric Ciaramella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAL TECH scientist thinks we all exist in multiple universes... </title>
      <link>https://thenextweb.com/science/2019/11/08/meet-the-scientist-who-thinks-we-all-exist-in-multiple-universes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenextweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The increasingly popular theory of Many Worlds suggests every fundamental event has multiple possible outcomes and splits the world into various realities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar on Bloomberg bid: We don't need anyone telling us 'we aren't enough'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/469615-klobuchar-weighs-in-on-bloomberg-bid-we-dont-need-anyone-coming-in-and</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Amy Klobuchar (D-Minn.) was the latest Democratic presidential candidate to weigh in on billionaire Michael Bloomberg's possible entrance into the 2020 Democratic primary race Friday at a campaign stop in Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman, 95, dies in dog attack at home of animal activist...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/woman-95-dies-dog-attack-173627854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 95-year-old Connecticut woman has died from injuries she suffered when she was attacked by a dog at the home of a former lawmaker who is also an animal rights activist. Authorities say Janet D'Aleo, of Enfield, was found with life-threatening injuries Wednesday and brought to a Massachusetts hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First case of dengue spread by sex confirmed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-case-dengue-spread-sex-confirmed-spain-174218209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spanish health authorities confirmed Friday a case of a man spreading dengue through sex, a word first for a virus which until recently was thought to be transmitted only by mosquitos. The case concerns a 41-year-old man from Madrid who contracted dengue after having sex with his male partner who picked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange may soon die in jail, father warns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/assange-may-die-jail-father-warns-165954491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The father of WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange said Friday he worried his son would die in prison after nine years of "persecution" for daring to reveal US "war crimes". John Shipton told reporters in Geneva that he had visited his son in a British prison two days ago and needed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traumatic tale of 16-year-old virgin forced to be sex slave at Auschwitz told in new book...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/10301773/book-auschwitz-sex-slaves-holocaust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHE was just a girl when she was deported to Auschwitz-Birkenau concentration camp. But 16-year-old Cilka Klein’s beauty so entranced the camp commandant that he made her his sex slave. Cilka, a vi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous author's 'WARNING' portrays presidency on brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Anonymous-author-s-Warning-portrays-a-14818890.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Senior Trump administration officials considered resigning en masse last year in a "midnight self-massacre" to sound a public alarm about President Donald Trump's conduct, but rejected the idea because they believed it would further destabilize an already teetering government, according to a new book by an unnamed author.  In "A Warning" by Anonymous, obtained by The Washington Post ahead of its release, a writer described only as "a senior official in the Trump administration" paints a chilling portrait of the president as cruel, inept and a danger to the nation he was elected to lead.  The author - who first captured attention in 2018 as the unidentified author of a New York Times opinion column - describes Trump careening from one self-inflicted crisis to the next, "like a twelve-year-old in an air traffic control tower, pushing the buttons of government indiscriminately, indifferent to the planes skidding across the runway and the flights frantically diverting away from the airport."  The book is an unsparing character study of Trump, from his morality to his intellectual depth, which the author writes is based on his or her observations and experiences. The author claims many other current and former administration officials share his or her views.  The 259-page book - which was published by Twelve, an imprint of Grand Central Publishing/Hachette Book Group, and goes on sale Nov. 19 - does not re-create many specific episodes in vivid detail, which the author writes was intentional to protect his or her identity.  At a moment when a stream of political appointees and career public servants have testified before Congress about Trump's conduct as part of the House impeachment inquiry, the book's author defends his or her decision to remain anonymous.  "I have decided to publish this anonymously because...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He stumbles, slurs, gets confused, easily irritated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7665031/Anonymous-author-raises-questions-Donald-Trumps-mental-fitness.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anonymous author of a tell-all tome on the Donald Trump administration raises questions about the president's mental fitness to hold office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military ops in Syria getting complicated for Washington...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-military-ops-syria-getting-complicated-washington-161457844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is facing tough questions about the US military's role in Syria. Troops are now limited to a smaller, tougher to defend zone, and focused on protecting oil fields that legally belong to Damascus. On October 6, US President Donald Trump announced that the 1,000 soldiers deployed in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tax Case Should Be an Easy Supreme Court Call...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tax-case-easy-supreme-153735710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Some observers are wondering whether the Supreme Court will let President Donald Trump keep his tax records secret. With respect to presidential prerogatives, many fundamental issues remain open. Perhaps the current court will resolve this one in his favor?That's unlikely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG DREAMS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/461efe170a174c4fb9446951c164537e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLUFFTON, S.C. (AP) — All is not well in the Democratic Party's quest for a presidential nominee. Just ask Michael Bloomberg. The New York billionaire, whose career in business and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearings likely to draw high TV ratings...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191108103132-71wbw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-TV (FACTBOX):FACTBOX-Trump impeachment hearings likely to draw high ratings in new era of political TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Weinstein fawned over by fans at club...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/08/harvey-weinstein-returns-to-club-where-he-allegedly-assaulted-a-tv-anchor-is-fawned-over-by-fans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alleged sexual predator Harvey Weinstein was fawned over by fans and friends on Thursday during a night out at an exclusive SoHo lounge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC CHAOS: Video shows 'peacekeepers' scramble to break up subway brawl...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/08/a-train-chaos-video-shows-peacekeepers-scramble-to-break-up-subway-brawl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of brave “peacekeepers” scrambled to break up a wild fight aboard an A train this week, disturbing footage shows. The recording captured the chaos inside the northbound train be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of microchipping: Ready for technology to get under skin?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/nov/08/the-rise-of-microchipping-are-we-ready-for-technology-to-get-under-the-skin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As implants grow more common, experts fear surveillance and exploitation of workers. Advocates say the concerns are irrational</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD hosts 'Anal Sex 101,' 'Oral Sex 101' and 'fatphobia' workshops...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/harvard-hosts-anal-sex-101-oral-sex-101-and-fatphobia-workshops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annual, student-led Sex Week tradition returns to Ivy League institution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters call for 'revenge' after 22-year-old student dies in fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-11-08/hong-kong-protesters-call-for-revenge-after-22-year-old-student-dies-in-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The student who died had been in hospital since Sunday, after falling from a multi-story parking garage during a confrontation between protesters and police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outed CIA officer has advice for whistleblower under fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-08/outed-cia-officer-has-advice-for-whistle-blower-under-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Valerie Plame was outed as a covert CIA officer in 2003, a White House aide was convicted, a reporter went to jail, and her career in intelligence ended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly teases interview with ABCNEWS Epstein whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7664915/Megyn-Kelly-helps-fired-CBS-employee-woman-leaked-ABCs-Amy-Robach-hot-mic-revelation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com can reveal the staffer is Ashley Bianco, 25, an Emmy-winning producer, who contacted Megyn Kelly directly, a source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Denied Bodily Resurrection of Christ?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/michael-w-chapman/scalfari-pope-denied-jesus-bodily-resurrection-says-it-was-semblance-spirit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his new book and in the periodical he founded, La Repubblica, Eugenio Scalfari, a long-time friend of Pope Francis and frequent papal interviewer, claims that the Pope told him that Jesus Christ did not rise bodily from the dead but "in the semblance of a spirit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba: Jailed Dissident Forced to Drink Fecal Water, Eat Rotten Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/11/08/cuba-jailed-dissident-forced-to-drink-semi-fecal-water-eat-rotten-food/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;José Daniel Ferrer, the head of the largest dissident organization in Cuba, is nearing death after a month in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly teases interview with ABCNEWS Epstein whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/megyn-kelly-teases-interview-with-abc-news-epstein-whistleblower</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalist Megyn Kelly teased an interview with the woman who leaked a video of an ABC News reporter discussing how the network shut down her story about a Jeffrey Epstein accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic blast expected to break 170 records across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/08/weather-arctic-blast-next-week-midwest-east-south-cold-temperatures/2518984001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for a taste of January next week. The incoming Actic blast will bring cold temperatures to the Midwest, Plains, East Coast and Deep South.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She slammed courtroom door on way out. Judge sentenced her to 10 days in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/news/crime/vp-nw-slammed-courtroom-door-20191107-6fgpkrib3zg5lch5yxrop6s7ua-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 18-year-old woman came to the Virginia Beach courthouse to support her boyfriend. She ended up in handcuffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil braces for release of ex-president Lula after court ruling...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-braces-release-ex-president-lula-court-ruling-134519738.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters of Brazilian leftist icon Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva gathered outside a prison Friday waiting for the ex-president's release following a court ruling that threatens to deepen political divisions. Lula is among several thousand convicts who could be freed after the Supreme Court's decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires' wealth falls for first time since 2015...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-wealth-billionaires/billionaires-wealth-falls-for-first-time-since-2015-idUSKBN1XI0L9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's richest people became a little less well off last year, accordi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Will Betray President?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/11/08/trump-impeachment-republicans-congress-229904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump knows there are potential traitors in his midst. His presidency could depend on keeping them at bay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Homebuyers Vanish...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/news/home-young-us-rits-older/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothel swaps humans for sex robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/swiss-brothel-swaps-women-sex-20836948</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arsenal 51 brothel in Switzerland offers a sex doll for half the price of prostitutes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even Super Rich Rethink Yacht Buying Amid Economic Uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-08/even-super-rich-rethink-yacht-buying-amid-economic-uncertainty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA ON IMPEACHMENT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3282d6331648444aa85ea4c04ad71b6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RABAT, Morocco (AP) — Ivanka Trump on Friday echoed her father's view that the House impeachment investigation is an attempt to overturn the 2016 election. But, in an interview with The Associated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reshapes global meat markets as swine fever rages...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191108063137-udxyk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-MEAT/ASF (PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):China reshapes global meat markets as swine fever rages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky-high selfies: Japan warns USA over 'outrageous' antics of military pilots...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/08/sky-high-selfies-japan-warns-us-over-outrageous-antics-of-military-pilots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine corps pilots took photos and read books while flying, according to a US military investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL CREDIT: Chinese facial recognition puts name, photo on billboard if jaywalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/creepy-chinese-facial-recognition-system-20839261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Writer Matthew Brennan tweeted a shocking video of the strange system, although it remains unclear where it was filmed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOPAMINE FASTS: SILICON VALLEY AVOIDING FOOD, TV, SEX, MUSIC, EXERCISE, EYE CONTACT...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/dopamine-fasts-silicon-valley-sex-food-happy-a9194141.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot, crowded, secret room now part of lore...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9aa24db2ceb40ed9f89fefabb721806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It's "excruciating." It smells like a "locker room." And what happens there is supposed to stay there. When history is written about President Donald Trump's presidency, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAST FOOD RAMPAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10302459/racist-tirade-popeyes-attack-restaurant-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RACIST man was beaten up and had his beloved chicken sandwich stolen after going on a sick N-word tirade inside a Popeyes fast-food restaurant. The incident took place in Silver Spring, Maryland …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Starring In Horror Film Charged In Real-Life Murder -- Day After Filming Wraps!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/07/horror-film-actress-charged-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moore-Reed was originally charged with manslaughter and a year later, while out on bail, was cast as a lead role in an indie horror film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo visitor waves at bear and is stunned when it waves back!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7661719/Zoo-visitor-waves-bear-stunned-friendly-creature-waves-back.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage was recorded by Maxim Gavrilenko during a visit to a zoo near Moscow, Russia. He began recording the large brown bear after he spotted it sitting patiently in its enclosure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's demands came down to three words: 'Investigations, Biden and Clinton'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-demands-of-ukraine-came-down-to-three-words-investigations-biden-and-clinton-officials-testimony-states/ar-BBWqL2p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Fatigue? Maddow Beats MAGA Rally in Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-fatigue-rachel-maddow-beats-trump-rally-in-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC's Rachel Maddow saw a huge win in the ratings Wednesday, actually beating out a President Donald Trump rally in both overall audience numbers and well over half a million viewers in a key demo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPEYE'S CHAOS: ANGRY AMERICANS FIGHT OVER COVETED CHICKEN SANDWICH...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/popeyes-chaos-angry-americans-fight-over-coveted-chicken-sandwich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People are yelling, throwing objects at each other and dying over a piece of breaded chicken served in a bun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE'S BACK!  Sessions announces Alabama Senate bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/jeff-sessions-trump-first-ad-alabama-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Attorney General Jeff Sessions is using his first campaign ad as a 2020 Senate candidate in Alabama to try moving past his strained relationship with President Trump, saying the president “has my full support.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARNINGS BEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/07/disney-dis-fiscal-q4-2019-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's fiscal fourth-quarter earnings come just days before Disney+ is set to launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems unveil proposal for 'millionaires surtax'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/469443-dems-unveil-proposal-for-millionaires-surtax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Don Beyer (D-Va.) and Sen. Chris Van Hollen (D-Md.) on Thursday rolled out a proposal for a “millionaires surtax,” amid a growing interest from Democrats in increasing taxes on the wealthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launches 'calculator for the billionaires'... </title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/469496-warren-campaign-launches-a-calculator-for-the-billionaires-after-gates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren’s (D-Mass.) presidential campaign hit back at criticism from billionaire Bill Gates over her wealth tax by releasing a “calculator for the billionaires.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi king hosts CIA chief after TWITTER charges...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-king-hosts-cia-chief-twitter-charges-214625199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia's King Salman hosted the Central Intelligence Agency's director Thursday, state media said, after three people were charged in the United States with spying on Twitter users critical of the royal family. The king and Gina Haspel "discussed a number of topics of mutual interest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan threatens to open Europe gates for refugees...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/erdogan-threatens-open-europe-gates-refugees-173416181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on a visit to EU member Hungary repeated his threat Thursday to "open the gates" for millions of refugees eager to flee to Europe unless more international support was provided. Erdogan held talks with Hungarian nationalist Prime Minister Viktor Orban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over Las Vegas ban on sleeping in streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anger-over-las-vegas-ban-sleeping-streets-012554603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with a growing number of homeless people, Las Vegas has passed a controversial law that bans sleeping on the street and imposes punishments of a $1,000 fine and six months in prison. Sleeping on the streets of the gambling hub will only be illegal in downtown Las Vegas and residential areas --</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON TO DEFY WHITE HOUSE, TESTIFY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/bolton-willing-to-defy-white-house-and-testify-if-court-clears-the-way-according-to-people-familiar-with-his-views/ar-BBWq6CC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG PREPPING PRESIDENTIAL RUN</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/07/bloomberg-preparing-to-file-for-alabama-presidential-primary-000322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-secret govt center admits crippling Virginia garage door openers...</title>
      <link>https://www.insidenova.com/headlines/top-secret-government-center-admits-interference-with-fauquier-garage-door/article_b09dd948-0116-11ea-b4d6-db45151e2c1c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insidenova.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top-secret and secure federal government facility just northwest of Warrenton admitted this week it may be responsible for crippling dozens of garage door openers in two nearby subdivisions, FauquierNow.com's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45 original productions within a year...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/disney-streaming-service-quarterly-earnings-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney+ debuts on Nov. 12 and will cost $6.99 per month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM SHAKEUP</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/07/mike-bloomberg-prepares-to-enter-at-least-one-democratic-primary-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg has previously flirted with running for president in several election cycles. Earlier this year he had said he would not seek the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texts delayed from February mysteriously delivered overnight...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/11/7/20953422/text-messages-delayed-received-overnight-valentines-day-delay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one’s sure what happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANSCRIPT:  State Dept official describes Rudy's 'campaign of lies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/07/politics/george-kent-transcript-released/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A State Department official told lawmakers that Rudy Giuliani's attacks on the then-US ambassador to Ukraine were part of a "campaign of lies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems' new goal: Impeachment by Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/07/politics/democrat-impeachment-timeline/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are signaling they are now on a fast-track in their impeachment proceedings, avoiding court battles that could delay their inquiry and limiting the number of witnesses at public hearings -- all signs that President Donald Trump could be impeached as soon as next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Nursing Home Employee Took Photos Of Dead Residents...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/11/07/berks-heim-nursing-home-employee-stephanie-thomas-took-photos-dead-residents-ex-boyfriend-liked-that-kind-of-thing-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Thomas, 28, of Muhlenberg Township, now faces corpse abuse charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 3 San Fran residents wants out...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/expensive-san-francisco/article/leaving-sf-survey-moving-out-of-bay-area-14814850.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a third of San Franciscans can't see themselves staying in San Francisco much longer, according to none other than the city itself.  The survey, conducted by San Francisco's Office of the Controller, found that 35% of respondents were either "very likely" or "somewhat likely" to move out of San Francisco in the next three years. Residents under the age of 35 were the most likely to want to leave and - no surprise here - renters were about twice as likely as homeowners to be thinking of bailing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Pence running for president in 2024?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/07/mike-pence-president-2024-067313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds deploy armored military vehicle for Queens operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.ny1.com/nyc/all-boroughs/news/2019/11/06/ice-immigration-and-customs-enforcement-armored-vehicle-spotted-queens-ridgewood-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ny1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The armored vehicle was spotted in Ridgewood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 'SEINFELD' Actor Found Dead -- Partially Eaten By Vultures...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/2019/11/07/seinfeld-actor-charles-levin-found-dead-70-partially-eaten-by-vultures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this year, the body of 70-year-old Seinfeld actor Charles Levin was found in Oregon, and [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing kicks off work on 6G...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/business/china-kicks-off-work-on-6g-5g-research-state-media-12072078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHANGHAI: China has officially started researching sixth-generation telecoms technology, state media reported on Thursday (Nov 7), a move it ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO brain dead, says Macron...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-50335257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French president laments a lack of commitment by the United States, Nato's main guarantor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese surveillance goods illegally sold to US...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b7eeb297a0394b4784d5155e50cd954c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A Long Island firm sold tens of millions of dollars in Chinese-made surveillance and other sensitive security equipment to customers, including the U.S. military, by falsely...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems discussing multiple articles of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/democrats-discussing-mutiple-articiles-impeachment-trump/story?id=66822206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are discussing at least three articles of impeachment and they could go beyond Ukraine to include obstruction of Congress and the Mueller investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ characters on TV are at an all-time high...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/schitt-s-creek-batwoman-lgbtq-characters-u-s-tv-are-n1078246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There's a lot of great numbers to celebrate, but there's still work to be done," Megan Townsend of GLAAD said. "Progress is also still found in clusters."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whoopi Snaps At Audience: 'The Booing Is F***ing Us Up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/booing-is-fing-us-up-view-melts-down-donald-trump-jr-visit-1253109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guests clashed with hosts and hosts clashed with audience members at the ABC show on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Greenwald Slapped Live On Air By Brazilian Journalist...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/07/glenn-greenwald-slapped-brazil-on-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalist Glenn Greenwald was slapped in the face on air by a Brazilian journalist, shown in a video posted to Twitter Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders President to pay $2M for misusing charitable foundation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/president-donald-trump-ordered-pay-2m-collection-nonprofits/story?id=66827235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has been ordered by a New York State judge to pay $2 million to a group of nonprofit organizations as part of a settlement in a civil suit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
