<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Covid Puts Lie to Los Angeles Exceptionalism'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/12/covid-puts-the-lie-to-los-angeles-exceptionalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Late last March, after the appearance of the coronavirus prompted a first shutdown here, I put up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Nikki Haley's Time for Choosing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2021/magazine-nikki-haleys-choice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2024 hopeful can’t decide who she wants to be—the leader of the post-Trump GOP or a “friend” to the president who tried to sabotage democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military unaware of danger to Pence's 'nuclear football'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/11/politics/military-officials-were-unaware-pence-nuclear-football-riot/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military officials overseeing the authorization process to launch nuclear weapons were unaware on January 6 that then-Vice President Mike Pence's military aide carrying the "nuclear football" was potentially in danger as rioters got close during the violent Capitol insurrection, according to a defense official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans see trial ending shot at future office...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/538565-even-with-acquittal-gop-sees-trial-ending-trumps-shot-at-future-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans, including those who do not plan to vote to convict former President Trump, say this week’s impeachment trial has effectively ended any chance of him becoming the GOP presidential nominee in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All we have left': Dating apps on frontline of loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/left-dating-apps-frontline-loneliness-085740712.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dating apps are booming in lockdown -- no longer just a way of hooking up but also of simple interaction at a time when the coronavirus inflicts loneliness on millions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caged in court, Navalny mocks Putin and chases fans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/caged-court-navalny-mocks-putin-104214835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confined in a glass box in a Moscow courtroom, Alexei Navalny berated the judge, mocked a prison official and sparred with the prosecutor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Look of Spring Break...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/12/the-new-look-of-spring-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, Covid-19 crashed the spring break party, but not before mass gatherings on the beaches of Florida, Texas and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'News Media Bargaining Code'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-media-google-analysis/analysis-google-partners-brace-for-hit-as-search-giant-threatens-australia-exit-idUSKBN2AC0IK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's threatened shutdown of its search engine in Australia over a proposed content licensing law would ripple across industries, saddling partners like Apple with a sudden revenue gap and retailers as varied as affordable Kmart to upmarket David Jones with a supply of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2021 Looks Like Black Hole for Battered Tourism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/2021-looks-like-a-black-hole-for-battered-european-tourism/ar-BB1dCl1r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across Southern Europe’s tourist hotspots, all they can do is get ready and hope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH'S LATEST BILLIONAIRE:  BUMBLE BOSS AT 31...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-9251481/Bumble-dating-app-founder-Whitney-Wolfe-Herd-billionaire-31.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whitney Wolfe Herd's wealth jumped from £362m to £1.1bn as her firm celebrated a stellar first-day trading performance on Wall Street, with shares soaring nearly 80 per cent on the stock market debut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omar takes leadership post on House Foreign Affairs Committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/rep-ilhan-omar-takes-leadership-post-in-house-foreign-affairs/600021954/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota Democrat will become vice chair of House panel that oversees Africa policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo's taxpayer-funded gifts to dinner guests: $10,000 in engraved pens from China...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/article249178695.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As secretary of state, Pompeo emphasized a tough approach to China as an organizing principle for the former Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top editor walks back controversial comment on race...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/11/media/new-york-times-dean-baquet-town-hall/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top editor of The New York Times on Thursday, aiming to quell mounting scrutiny from both employees and outside critics, walked back a controversial comment he and the newspaper's managing editor made last week in which they said the newspaper does not "tolerate" the use of racist language "regardless of intent."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dems decided to fast-track...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Impeachment-Speed-headline-here-and-here-15944313.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Capitol was still littered with the wreckage left by the violent mob of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines Withdraw Planes From Service in Reversal of Recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/airlines-withdraw-planes-from-service-in-reversal-of-recovery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines Withdraw Planes From Service in Reversal of Recovery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Mayor Pushes Crypto With Offer to Pay Workers in Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/miami-mayor-pushes-crypto-offer-223833772.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Miami Mayor Francis Suarez proposed paying municipal workers and collecting taxes in Bitcoin, expanding a campaign to promote cryptocurrencies.The mayor wants to allow the City of Miami’s workers to choose to receive all or a portion of their pay in Bitcoin, according to a resolution passed by the city’s governing commission. In addition, the mayor proposed allowing people to pay all or part of property taxes or city fees in crypto.Although the commission approved the resolution 4-1, it significantly dialed back its original wording. It only agreed to study the practicality of such steps, rather than taking action, as the original proposal had suggested.Suarez has been courting Silicon Valley investors and technology companies for months, and adopting Bitcoin is a critical part of that plan. “I think we’re on the cusp of seeing a major titanic shift on this,” Suarez told the city commission. ”It’s an industry that’s boisterous, vociferous and growing, and this would send the right signal.”Suarez also wants the city to analyze the feasibility to invest a some government funds in Bitcoin, the resolution said. It’s not clear how much of that is actually possible: Florida statutes have strict limitations on how local governments can invest surplus funds, generally restricting investments to low-volatility instruments such as those issued by the U.S. government. In the past year alone, Bitcoin has shown it can double in price -- or lose half its value -- in a month’s time.Suarez doesn’t seemed fazed by volatility: Miami, the mayor’s original resolution said, “is committed to promoting the emergence of Bitcoin as it continues to gain mainstream acceptance.”Some city commissioners cautioned against embracing Bitcoin without a close study of the risks. “Let’s analyze this before we jump in,” said Manolo Reyes, a commissioner. “Maybe you’re ahead of your time, maybe you’re right, but let’s analyze it.”New IdeasSuarez, who is up for re-election this year, has portrayed himself as someone who is willing to consider and promote new ideas. Late in 2020, he started engaging with Silicon Valley technology investors on Twitter, and his efforts to lure them to Miami have become a viral sensation.While Suarez’s Twitter campaign may have given him new influence, the mayor of the City of Miami doesn’t control the budget or municipal workforce or get a vote on the commission. He asked voters to give him more managerial power, but the initiative failed.The proposal comes in a week when Tesla Inc. disclosed it had made a $1.5 billion investment in Bitcoin, a big vote of confidence from the world’s leading electric-carmaker. Mike Novogratz, the billionaire founder of cryptocurrency investment firm Galaxy Digital, said in an interview Monday that “it’s the messaging that matters,” even if the investments themselves are relatively small.In the resolution, the mayor described Bitcoin as an increasingly popular asset for people, corporations and major investors. The plan is part of a campaign to make Miami a city that “embraces new technologies,” the resolution said.Ken Russell, vice-chairman of the city commission, said he’s “certainly not opposed” to the idea of integrating Bitcoin into the city’s business, but it’s important to ensure “we all know what we’re getting into.”“What needs to be done is diligence, and not just from the legal perspective,” he said in an interview Wednesday. “It’s not just a currency, it’s a concept.”(Adds passage of proposal, comments from mayor and city commissioners.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Helped Government Identify Rioters From Photos...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-helped-government-identify-capitol-180342835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc. has been “helping” law enforcement identify people who posted photos of themselves at the Jan. 6 riots at the U.S. Capitol, “even after the attack was over,” said Monika Bickert, the company’s head of global policy management.Bickert said Facebook removed posts from several militant groups in the lead-up to the violent event and continued to remove content celebrating the riots and planning future violence after Jan. 6. The company said it didn’t use its facial recognition software to help the government identify people, but passed along data in response to requests.In the days following the attack, Chief Operating Officer Sheryl Sandberg said the riots were planned mostly on other social media platforms. But reporters quickly found evidence that Facebook and Instagram, which the company also owns, were mainstream tools for coordinating and spreading the word about the events.Facebook disclosed the government coordination as part of its Community Standards Enforcement Report, where it also revealed an increased reliance on artificial intelligence in removing content that violates Facebook rules.(Updates with Facebook explanation about facial recognition in the second paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some rioters believed they answered God's call...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/Some-Capitol-rioters-believed-they-answered-God-s-15942977.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten weeks before the election and four months before then-President Donald Trump summoned...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus mutates several times -- in same patient...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-had-active-coronavirus-infection-for-5-months-that-mutated-several-times-researchers-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 45-year-old man’s case has drawn attention from researchers about the potential role similar scenarios could have played in the emergence of new coronavirus variants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ says Oath Keepers leader waited for Donald's direction before attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/11/politics/oath-keeper-justice-trump-capitol/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is now making clear that a leader among the Oath Keepers paramilitary group -- who planned and led others in the US Capitol siege to attempt to stop the Biden presidency -- believed she was responding to the call from then-President Donald Trump himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne enters new lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210212015432-aj9v7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Melbourne enters new lockdown, crowds barred from Australian Open</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says Trump 'did not do his job' on corona vaccination program, urges patience...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211225326-a1lgq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BIDEN (UPDATE 3, PIX, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 3-Biden says Trump 'did not do his job' on coronavirus vaccination program, urges patience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House has made 'no decisions' on any new travel restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211213823-pf76d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FLORIDA (UPDATE 2, PIX, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 2-White House has made 'no decisions' on any new COVID-19 travel restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convict Trump or face dire democracy damage, prosecutors say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trump-impeachment-trial-video-b2550fd54083b27a5bc40f0f89bd052c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Dire harm from Donald Trump’s false and violent incitements will vex American democracy long into the future unless the Senate convicts him of impeachment and bars him from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law firm details sexual misconduct by global ministry leader...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ravi-zacharias-sexual-misconduct-4b285e38282c4de13d651a1706853668</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ravi Zacharias, who died in May after a high-profile career leading a global Christian ministry, engaged in sexual misconduct with massage therapists and carried on many amorous...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT to launch outside probe amid new revelations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-0eab9919c555150a78e6ac083b1b06a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Lincoln Project, one of the best-known and best-funded organizations in the so-called Never Trump movement, announced plans late Thursday to launch an external investigation to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fever got you down? Smash up stuff at the rage room!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-new-york-coronavirus-pandemic-elohim-0cc737f6bc1fc27f47d85fc4396b60a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WESTLAKE VILLAGE, Calif. (AP) — After nearly a year of being trapped in pandemic isolation, some people just want to pick up a sledgehammer and smash something to smithereens. “That felt...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears scores first legal victory against her dad!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/2319454/britney-spears-first-legal-victory-dad-jamie-conservatorship-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears scored her first legal victory against father Jamie Spears during a tense court battle over the singer’s ongoing conservatorship.  On Thursday, a judge ruled that Jamie will no longe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS 'THROUGH NEXT YEAR'</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/ABC/status/1359985372860719116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN CLAIMS 600 MILLION DOSES BY SUMMER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vaccine-biden-600-million-doses-july-b7845a7d0f709199265d9243598b629e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BETHESDA, Md. (AP) — President Joe Biden said Thursday that the U.S. will have enough supply of the COVID-19 vaccine by the end of the summer to inoculate 300 million Americans. Biden made...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million-Dollar Pardon Offer at Trump Hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-million-dollar-pardon-offer-at-the-trump-hotel/ar-BB1dzFCd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corey Lewandowski allegedly wanted a hefty fee in exchange for helping a government whistleblower win a pardon from the former president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER BANS PROJECT VERITAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9251245/Twitter-PERMANENTLY-bans-Project-Veritas-locks-founder-James-OKeefe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspensions reportedly stem from a video the group shared on Wednesday which featured Facebook's Vice President of Integrity, Guy Rosen, a screenshot shared by Project Veritas showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept. botched response to diplomats' brain injuries in Cuba, secret report found...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/state-dept-botched-initial-response-diplomats-brain-injuries/story?id=75805795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department mishandled its initial response to the mysterious health incidents that have affected U.S. personnel in Cuba, according to a newly released review.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC says no quarantine for vaccinated people
...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/no-more-quarantine-cdc-says-vaccinated-people-not-isolate-after-covid-exposure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These new recommendations apply to recipients who are within the first three months of receiving their final COVID-19 vaccine dosage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE DON GOLFS...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-golf-impeachment-trial-videos-b1801183.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president has refused to testify in person at the impeachment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Dog Pulled From Wreckage...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/11/dog-pulled-out-of-wreckage-deadly-i-35w-pileup-fort-worth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chopper 11 captured video of a dog being pulled out of the massive I-35W pileup and taken to safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jazz great Chick Corea with 23 Grammy Awards dead at 79...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-gary-burton-jazz-music-herbie-hancock-3fe2b6b98850454a1470e24fc4f653a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Chick Corea, a towering jazz pianist with a staggering 23 Grammy Awards who pushed the boundaries of the genre and worked alongside Miles Davis and Herbie Hancock, has died. He was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He Can Do This Again' If Not Convicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/trump-impeachment-trial-live-updates/2021/02/11/966984248/he-can-do-this-again-rep-lieu-warns-of-future-attacks-on-democracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House impeachment managers are rebutting claims from Trump's defense team that the trial is politically motivated because Democrats don't want to face Trump in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Sicker Than Acknowledged With Covid...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/11/trump-was-sicker-than-acknowledged-with-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Donald J. Trump was sicker with Covid-19 in October than publicly acknowledged at the time, with extremely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Apple A Day Keeps Alzheimer's Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/apples-brain-alzheimers-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experiments on mice discovered grey matter increased after they were injected with phytonutrients, which are abundant in fruits and vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems rest prosecution with Donald's 'lack of remorse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/11/trump-impeachment-trial-live-updates-day-3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is CNBC's live blog covering Day 3 of former President Trump's second impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry customers show up at ROBINHOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/11/angry-customers-show-up-at-robinhoods-headquarters-in-the-wake-of-gamestop-chaos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Robinhood clients are driving to the start-up's headquarters in California and in some cases, vandalizing the property, according to police reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managers say acquittal could embolden extremists...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/11/trump-impeachment-trial-day-3-468588</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment managers intend to rest their case Thursday after discussing Trump's "lack of remorse."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expose 'hypocrisy' of Democrats...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/11/trump-impeachment-lawyer-schoen-vows-to-expose-dem-hypocrisy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — One of former President Donald Trump’s lead impeachment attorneys said Thursday that his presentation Friday will lay bare the “hypocrisy” of House impeachment …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-staffer kills himself in front of Texas lawmaker's home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/2021/02/11/us-rep-van-duyne-shocked-after-man-killed-himself-outside-of-her-irving-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who shot and killed himself out of U.S. Rep. Beth Van Duyne’s Irving home Wednesday was a former staffer and GOP activist, the Irving Police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BLOOMBERG Lay Offs, Including Longtime Editors...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/bloomberg-news-layoffs-editors-1234906168/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg News on Thursday began notifying a group of employees they were being terminated, according to three people familiar with the matter, the latest in an ongoing string of layoffs at media c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's Cities Empty. What Will Bring People Back?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-pandemic-emptied-europe-s-cities-what-will-bring-people-back/ar-BB1dBj9B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — When the coronavirus exploded across Europe in March, it realigned city life, shifting office workers to their homes, shuttering the hospitality sector and reshuffling life for millions. Unshackled from offices — many for the first time in their working lives — city dwellers throughout Europe began to leave, some to avoid the virus but others to to escape cramped and pricey apartments and to connect more with the natural world. Now,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal debt to exceed size of economy -- NOT counting new stimulus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/11/deficit-projected-at-2point3-trillion-for-2021-not-counting-additional-stimulus-cbo-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal budget deficit is projected at $2.3 trillion in the 2021 fiscal year, a drop from last year but well ahead of anything the U.S. has ever seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal debt to exceed size of economy -- NOT counting new stimulus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/02/11/cbo-deficit-debt-stimulus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBO’s deficit projections comes the day after the Federal Reserve chairman warned of the dangers of high unemployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  40% of USA could have been prevented...</title>
      <link>https://www.southbendtribune.com/coronavirus/roughly-40-of-the-usa-s-coronavirus-deaths-could-have-been-prevented-new-study-says/article_2d98da88-6c87-11eb-b531-0b35421d42d8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.southbendtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 40% of the nation’s coronavirus deaths could have been prevented if the United States’ average death rate matched other industrialized nations, a new Lancet Commission report has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children Dosed By September?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-vaccine-kids-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci offered an optimistic prediction as vaccine clinical trials expand to include children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US marshals kill more, but face less scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/investigations/2021/02/11/investigation-us-marshals-kill-more-people-but-face-less-scrutiny/4397533001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Marshals Service teams have killed an average of 22 suspects and bystanders each year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pigs can be taught how to use joysticks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/11/world/pigs-joystick-scli-intl-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The intelligence of pigs has long been renowned -- and scientists in the US have now found that they are clever enough to be able to use computer joysticks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing bans BBC for 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/china-bans-bbc-for-fake-news-on-xinjiang-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK foreign secretary calls move ‘an unacceptable curtailing of media freedom.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to reinstate border controls over virus variant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/czech-republic-austria-germany-coronavirus-pandemic-318558bbf1d722c2704b4b03bc7835bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The German government decided Thursday to temporarily reinstate border controls along its southeastern frontier after designating the Czech Republic and parts of Austria as “mutation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Was visibly swaying back and forth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9248977/Bruce-Springsteen-busted-DWI-one-shot-tequila-taking-pictures-fans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arrest allegedly occurred in Sandy Hook when the rock veteran pulled over to take a picture with fans, accepted a tequila shot offered by one of them and took it in full view of police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 REPUBLICAN SENATORS MAY VOTE TO CONVICT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/538386-the-gop-senators-likely-to-vote-for-trumps-conviction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senators say as many as a half-dozen GOP lawmakers could vote with Democrats to convict former President Trump for inciting an insurrection on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis defends maskless crowds in FL...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/538441-desantis-defends-maskless-crowds-after-buccaneers-win-amid-covid-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) attacked the media for what he said was a double standard with how large marches for social justice were covered as opposed to celebrations in Tampa following the Buccaneers' Super Bowl win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frigid weather blankets huge swath of USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211162627-bpbom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/ (TV):From icy Texas to snowy Seattle, frigid weather blankets huge swath of U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine passports 'inevitable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/13979757/vaccine-passport-holiday-cost-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PASSENGERS needing a vaccine passport to go on holiday will be “inevitable” according to one travel expert, following warnings that Brits may face a £30 charge from GPs for it. A string…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Prices Post Record Gain, Topping Peak From 2005...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/us-home-prices-post-149-jump-in-pandemic-real-estate-rally/ar-BB1dBuao</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. home prices, fueled by the lowest mortgage rates in history, surged in the fourth quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A racist slur, a groundbreaking coming out and country music's future hanging in the balance...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/A-racist-slur-a-groundbreaking-coming-out-and-15942811.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You won't find the full story of what happened in country music last week in the video...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coyotes Roam Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/10/coyote-spotted-in-central-park-but-officials-say-theyre-not-there-to-chases-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recently a snowy owl ruffled many feathers. Now coyote sightings have hairs standing on end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is coughing a crime? Danish court hears appeal against conviction...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211152521-cymck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DENMARK-CRIME (REPEAT, PIX):REPEAT-Is coughing a crime? Danish court hears appeal against pandemic-linked conviction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops hunting for umbilical cord thief!</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/umbilical-cord-thief-285096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 11-Pennsylvania cops are hunting for an umbilical cord thief, records show. Investigators say that an “unknown suspect” cut the lock on a storage unit and made off with an umbilical cord, e</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House looks at domestic travel restrictions as virus mutation surges in Florida... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article249154715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outbreaks of the new variants have lent urgency to a review of potential travel restrictions within the United States, an official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCHING YOU: CITIES SELL DATA FROM 'SMART' STREETLIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/smart-cities-street-lights-859992a6-6931-48e5-81ba-7f0a0b8058d9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Smart" LED fixtures could one day be able to find you a parking space and announce an oncoming thunderstorm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where's John Roberts?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/966168/most-important-person-impeachment-trial-missing-isnt-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why John Roberts' refusal to preside is more significant than many have acknowledged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer programmer downloaded streams as PARLER went offline...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/538422-anonymous-programmer-downloaded-key-impeachment-trial-videos-before-parler</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the video footage presented by House impeachment managers in former President Trump’s Senate trial was downloaded from Parler by an anonymous programmer before the platform went offline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies by suicide in front of Texas lawmaker's home...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/538425-man-dies-by-suicide-in-front-of-texas-lawmakers-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man died by suicide on Wednesday in front of Rep. Beth Van Duyne’s (R) home in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget deficit hits ANOTHER record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/1923752000000-federal-spending-sets-record-through-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government spent a record $1,923,752,000,000 in the first four months of fiscal 2021 (October through January), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For decades Trump bullied Palm Beach to get his way. Now he's determined to make it home...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/article/For-decades-Donald-Trump-bullied-Palm-Beach-to-15942737.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One night in late January 1994, fireworks sparkled in the sky above Mar-a-Lago, a grand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Prophets on Rise. What Happens When They're Wrong?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/11/christian-prophets-are-on-the-rise-what-happens-when-theyre-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeremiah Johnson, a 33-year-old self-described prophet, was one of the few evangelical Christians who took Donald J. Trump’s political future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pileup Involving 100 Vehicles Traps Drivers, Shuts Down TX Interstate...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/11/pileup-100-cars-trucks-trapped-drivers-interstate-35w-fort-worth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fort Worth police spokesperson Officer Daniel Segura has confirmed at least 3 people were killed in the crash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperation grows in battered Honduras, fueling migration...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/honduras-hurricane-iota-mexico-storms-immigration-3cf340e556ee767d1dd3dce351c934b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN PEDRO SULA, Honduras (AP) — Nory Yamileth Hernández and her three teenage children have been living in a battered tent under a bridge on the outskirts of San Pedro Sula since Hurricane Eta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems will wrap prosecution with Donald's 'lack of remorse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/congress/democrats-will-wrap-prosecution-with-trumps-lack-of-remorse-after-capitol-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats will conclude a final day of arguments in former President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial by highlighting his “lack of remorse,” following the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol by hundreds of his supporters, and the impact of the deadly and destructive incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-day-3-2021-02-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment managers plan to examine the aftermath of the Capitol attack on the third day of the trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Prices Post Record Gain, Topping Peak From 2005...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-02-11/u-s-home-prices-post-14-9-jump-in-pandemic-real-estate-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson Sponsors Face New Boycott Calls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tucker-carlson-floyd-boycott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlson asserted on his Wednesday night Fox News primetime program that George Floyd died of a drug overdose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Shelley Duvall: Reclusive Icon on Fleeing Hollywood and Scars of Making 'SHINING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/searching-for-shelley-duvall-the-reclusive-icon-on-fleeing-hollywood-and-the-scars-of-making-the-shining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After leaving L.A., and making only one public appearance since — on a widely condemned mental illness episode of 'Dr. Phil' — the complicated actress sat down for a conversation with The Hollywood Reporter about her legacy and the trauma of the Stanley Kubrick film: "To wake and realize that you had to cry all day, I don’t know how I did it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden ghosting Bibi?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/israelis-ask-why-hasn-e2-80-99t-the-us-president-called-their-prime-minister-yet/ar-BB1dBbXe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three weeks into Biden’s term, some are ready to declare a diplomatic snub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ZOOM Town Boom in Bozeman, Montana...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-02-11/the-zoom-town-boom-in-bozeman-montana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal from 'habitable planet' found by scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/alien-hope-signal-habitable-planet-23483061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential planet is in a "habitable zone" of Alpha Centauri, a binary star system 4.37 light-years away from Earth, and could have liquid water on its surface</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheap old homes draw millennials escaping pandemic cages...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211115836-p6nqm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHEAP HOMES (TV, PIX):Cheap old homes draw millennials escaping pandemic cages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Actress fired from 'MANDALORIAN' after social media post...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-gina-carano-social-media-the-holocaust-16a438e51f1c0fd1ca96ba163021caf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Lucasfilm says Gina Carano is no longer a part of “The Mandalorian” cast after many online called for her firing over a social media post that likened the experience of Jews...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S3F1vZYpH8c&amp;t=2s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creating convincing digital humans has traditionally been hard, slow, and expensive. With MetaHuman Creator, the time to create a unique digital human of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 4 In 10 Republicans Say Violence May Be Necessary...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/11/966498544/a-scary-survey-finding-4-in-10-republicans-say-political-violence-may-be-necessa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poll shows significant support in the U.S. for political violence. Most white evangelicals and Republicans say Biden's election was illegitimate and Trump was not behind the attack on the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now out of office, The Don may face tax questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/now-out-of-office-trump-may-have-to-face-tax-questions/ar-BB1dB2mE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether or not Trump is convicted at his impeachment trial, he faces an IRS decision on a massive refund and may no longer be able to conceal his tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company just made it shockingly easy to create lifelike people...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90603474/the-company-behind-fortnite-just-made-it-shockingly-easy-to-create-life-like-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Realistic-looking humans are becoming easier and easier to make from thin air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED PLANET: Mars mission inspires growing fan base back in China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-beijing-china-planets-mars-77509554dcb24ebd5b7bf5c155515cfe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Cui Tingting dyed her hair Mars red for the arrival of China’s spacecraft at the planet known in Chinese as the Fire Star. “This is a great era for space, and the future of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How leading anti-Trump group ignored crisis in its ranks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-b14be5f06588b8f1d78125d4141394cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Last June, the Lincoln Project was on a high. Led by several prominent former Republican consultants, its slickly produced ads attacking President Donald Trump made it...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
