<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China Elite Hand Xi Victory, Paving Way for Indefinite Rule...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/xi-jinping-ensures-future-resolution-144755471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Thursday, only two Communist Party leaders have been powerful enough to rewrite China's history. Xi Jinping is now the third.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Expensive Gasoline in America Close to Record Highs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-expensive-gasoline-america-close-210705656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- California’s gasoline prices are only two cents away from hitting an all-time high as fuel prices have soared nationwide just two weeks ahead of the Thanksgiving holiday. Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesFarmers Take on ‘Post-Apocalyptic’ Food CrisisGreece’s Popular Islands Are Crowded — With PlasticDo Prisons Deserve a Second Chance?Retail prices in the state of California were averaging $4.65 per gallon, just two cents shy of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court temporarily blocks Jan. 6 committee from obtaining Trump records...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-district-of-columbia-capitol-siege-bdc8568b074dfefed8d11b883118dc76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal appeals court on Thursday temporarily blocked the release of White House records sought by a U.S. House committee investigating the Jan. 6 insurrection, granting — for now — a request from former President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN SET TO MAKE PUBLIC RETURN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/16707622/queen-will-attend-remembrance-sunday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen WILL attend Remembrance Sunday commemorations – as she returns to official duties after doctors ordered her to take a break. Her Majesty, 95, has been hoping to lead the Royal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costner's 'YELLOWSTONE' Was Most Watched Anything Last Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/11/11/home-hit-kevin-costners-red-state-comfort-food-yellowstone-was-the-most-watched-anything-last-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Nov. blizzard warning issued in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/first-blizzard-warnings-season-issued-powerful-storm-crosses-country-rcna5250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winter alerts were up Thursday morning for 2 million people across the Northern Plains and the Upper Midwest, which included the first blizzard warnings of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China opens first clinic for trans youth...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nbc-out/out-health-and-wellness/china-opens-first-clinic-transgender-youth-rcna5313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking with its usual practices on LGBTQ rights and issues, China launched its first medical clinic to treat transgender children and adolescents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Nov. blizzard warning issued in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/581183-rare-november-blizzard-warning-issued-in-midwest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people living in the Midwestern region of the U.S. received their first blizzard warnings of the season on Thursday, NBC News reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARSTOOL Portnoy fires back over violent sex allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/11/barstool-sports-dave-portnoy-fires-back-over-alleged-abusive-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barstool Sports founder Dave Portnoy went on an online rant, slamming Business Insider for an explosive “slander piece” on his alleged penchant for abusive and violent sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Putin's 'conveyor belt of torture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/europe/leaked-footage-reveals-prisoners-horrific-rape-and-abuse-inside-notorious-russian-jail/news-story/3849c86596b818dc70be82436f3ad7c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disturbing, leaked footage has revealed the systematic torture, sexual abuse and degradation of prisoners inside a brutal Russian jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venture Capitalist Gave Fake Spy $2M For Hoax CIA Missions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/venture-capitalist-gave-fake-spy-2m-for-hoax-cia-missions/ar-AAQBjOq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To the uber-rich venture capitalist Michael Goguen, it was apparently an enticing idea: a supposed former CIA agent named Matthew Marshall wanted to conduct an “off the books” paramilitary operation in Mexico. According to court papers, Marshall planned to lead assault teams on rescue missions and other expeditions. He just needed Goguen’s help to fund his plans. To further bolster his credibility, Marshall allegedly also claimed that he had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court temporarily blocks Jan. 6 committee from obtaining Trump White House records...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-asks-appeals-court-temporarily-block-release-jan-6-records-n1283732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jan. 6 select committee was scheduled to obtain the records on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bracing For Winter Surge...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/11/newsom-california-winter-covid-19-surge-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has begun positioning equipment and locking in contracts with temporary health care workers in preparation for another possible winter surge of coronavirus cases, Gov. Gavin Newsom said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERS:  'Not Easy to Put Brakes On Here'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/11/ex-treasury-secretary-biden-behind-the-curve-on-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists having sex in dunes ruining Spanish beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/gran-canaria-tourist-sex-dunes-maspalomas-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maspalomas beach is a nature reserve in Gran Canaria, Spain. But tourists having sex on its famous shifting dunes is destroying the environment, says a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Budget Problems About to Get Worse...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/11/inflation-will-make-government-budget-problems-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of interest on the national debt will soon be a huge chunk of change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists Keep Getting Killed in Mexico After Posting on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epxdq7/mexican-journalists-on-facebook-getting-killed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of the eight journalists murdered in Mexico this year posted on Facebook hours before they were killed. Nearly all of them relied on the platform to publicize their stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rents climbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/11/homes/manhattan-rents-rising/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rents in Manhattan rose at the highest rate in more than a decade in October, with increases especially impacting the upper end of the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia pharmacy incorrectly administers doses to 112 kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/11/virginia-pharmacy-incorrectly-administers-covid-vaccine-to-112-kids-officials-pull-remaining-doses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas investigates whether porn available in schools...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/581157-texas-governor-orders-education-officials-to-investigate-whether</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unclaimed soldier: Thousands of veterans die alone every year...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/veterans/2021-11-11/unclaimed-soldier-veterans-vietnam-era-deaths-3583003.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no requirement for local governments — who are responsible for unclaimed bodies — to report them to any national authority, so there is no official count. But tens of thousands of lives in the United States end this way each year, according to a Washington Post investigation. A striking number — thousands every year — served in the military, especially during the Vietnam War.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>110 now suing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/astroworld-lawsuit-110-plaintiffs-travis-scott-drake-live-nation-1234871896/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Antonio lawyer who filed the first lawsuit last weekend over the tragic events at the Astroworld Festival now says he has over 100 clients who are part of the legal action. “I represe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9th Victim Passes...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/bharti-shahani-astroworld-victims-texas-am-student-dies-what-happened-at-festival/11224693/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bharti Shahani had shown no brain activity while she was hospitalized following the Travis Scott concert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffers blame themselves: 'We killed Herman Cain'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/we-killed-herman-cain-trump-staffers-say-they-blame-themselves-for-cain-s-covid-19-death-after-he-attended-tulsa-rally/ar-AAQAA3p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cain tested positive for COVID-19 days after he attended Trump's Tulsa rally on June 20, 2020 and died due to complications with the virus on July 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why groceries keep getting more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/10/business/grocery-prices-inflation-meat/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You've probably realized that shopping for food and household basics is more expensive these days. Expect to keep paying more for groceries in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrities targeted in spate of follow-home robberies, LAPD says...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/celebrities-among-those-targeted-spate-165220067.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LAPD says robbers are following people home to break into their houses; recent targets include Terrence Jenkins and Dorit Kemsley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrities targeted in spate of follow-home robberies, LAPD says...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-11-11/follow-home-robbery-spike-in-la-sweeps-up-celebrities-too</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LAPD says robbers are following people home to break into their houses; recent targets include Terrence Jenkins and Dorit Kemsley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel unveils new defensive electronic warfare systems...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/iai-unveils-new-defensive-electronic-warfare-systems-684703</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel Aerospace Industries unveiled a family of new electronic warfare systems to combat a range of threats with targeted beams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterans' memorial vandalized with 'obscene graffiti'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4045686/veterans-day-memorial-vandalized-graffiti/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VETERANS memorial has been vandalized with “obscene graffiti” just days before the US honors those have served the country. Shocking pictures show the damage to the monument in Rock F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime-ravaged Seattle now so dangerous own workers no longer protected...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10191185/Downtown-Seattle-dangerous-city-employees-security-guard-escorts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle has become so dangerous that the city can no longer protect its own employees, with security guards now escorting them after they finish work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN SET TO MAKE PUBLIC RETURN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-10190731/Charles-smiles-meets-Princes-Trust-young-entrepreneurs-Brixton.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen will attend the annual Remembrance Day Service at the Cenotaph on Sunday after Prince Charles insisted today that his mother was 'all right'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Warns Troops May Plan Ukraine Invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/10/politics/blinken-ukrainian-presser/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Secretary of State Antony Blinken said Wednesday that the United States is "concerned by reports of unusual Russian military activity" and the possibility that Russia may be "attempting to rehash" its 2014 invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOP THE DIANA DRAMAS:  TIME TO LEAVE PRINCESS ALONE...</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/opinion/princess-diana-films-tv-spencer-the-crown-ban-1294164</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adaptions of the Princess of Wales' life are getting out of hand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Citizens Urged to Leave Haiti Amid Gas Shortages, Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-urges-citizens-to-leave-haiti-amid-deepening-turmoil/ar-AAQAO4J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — The U.S. government is urging U.S. citizens to leave Haiti because of the country’s deepening insecurity and a severe lack of fuel that has affected hospitals, schools and banks. Gas stations remained closed on Thursday. The rare warning from the U.S. State Department comes as Haiti’s government and police are struggling to control gangs that have blocked fuel distribution terminals for several weeks. “Widespread...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving air travel on track to exceed pre-pandemic levels...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/581121-thanksgiving-flight-bookings-on-track-to-exceed-pre-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanksgiving air travel is on track to exceed pre-pandemic levels, signaling a busy holiday season for airlines, according to a new analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk breaks promise never to sell any TESLA stock...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/11/elon-musk-other-execs-sell-billion-tesla-stock-twitter-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon’s brother, Kimbal, dumped $109 million worth of Tesla stock before the Twitter poll went live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderna Defends Shot as Questions on Heart Risks Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/moderna-defends-covid-shot-as-questions-on-heart-risks-mount/ar-AAQAFSO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna Inc. held a brief conference call to defend the safety of its Covid-19 shot from a barrage of questions about associated heart risks in young people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure builds on Meadows to cooperate with Jan. 6 committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pressure-builds-on-meadows-to-cooperate-with-jan-6-committee-as-white-house-rejects-his-executive-privilege-claims/ar-AAQAimR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Mark Meadows he has been “engaged” with investigators to negotiate the terms of his deposition and turning over of documents, the pace of these discussions has caused the committee to weigh more aggressive measures against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freezing pies, boiling beans: Coping with rising prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/11/politics/high-inflation-economy-groceries-gas/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though Thanksgiving is still two weeks away, Travis Moffatt and his fiancée, Britnie Walston, have already purchased three apple pies for their family dinner and socked them away in the freezer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA Bank Infor, Staff Social Security Numbers Leaked by Russian Hackers...</title>
      <link>https://thereload.com/nra-bank-account-information-staff-social-security-numbers-leaked-by-russian-hackers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thereload.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thieves have exposed sensitive personal and financial information in the latest round of NRA internal document dumps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: FBI Raid of James O'Keefe House Blow to Press Freedom...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/11/james-okeefe-fbi-raid-project-veritas-biden-diary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus: Consumer prices surge, a Virginia school district talks openly about burning books, and more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>110 now suing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/astroworld-lawsuit-110-plaintiffs-travis-scott-drake-live-nation-1234871896/#recipient_hashed=a059e5746446ee317b5c0d1bcc6e37f1c4d9f97e87dfd056ab1271a040e5441c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Antonio lawyer who filed the first lawsuit last weekend over the tragic events at the Astroworld Festival now says he has over 100 clients who are part of the legal action. “I represe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disappearing shorts: As stocks soar, skeptics surrender...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-stock-markets-stock-prices-f4ec3a4aa0bab5f6ed347fecd55731ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The skeptics on Wall Street have gone missing. As the stock market has surged to records — unbowed by recession, pandemic or warnings of a dangerous bubble — activity has dwindled to a nearly two-decade low for the traders known as short sellers, who make their money betting stocks will fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clapton anti-vax statements have friends and fans asking what happened...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/music/news/what-happened-to-eric-clapton/ar-AAQAkkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 56 years, the guitar icon remained silent about politics. But when covid struck, the guitarist took a forceful — and controversial — stand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals in West Under Siege as Patients Packs ICUs...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/health-law-and-business/hospitals-in-western-u-s-under-siege-as-covid-19-packs-icus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals in some parts of the U.S. are already starting to see the impact of an autumn wave of Covid-19 infections, the latest sign that the health-care system still faces serious pressure from the virus, even in places that have achieved relatively high vaccination rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIVIAN mega IPO is good test of meme stock craze...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/11/22774719/rivian-ipo-meme-stock-tesla-reddit-wallstreetbets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rivian’s IPO hasn’t spurred any feverish online posting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever use of tree DNA in prosecution sends poacher to prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trees-fight-back-First-ever-use-of-tree-DNA-in-16612182.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trees are fighting back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bond market showing worry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-5fa9cd69a09996c3ccace84942476e8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Things look great across most financial markets, with everything from stocks to Bitcoin near record highs. That’s not the case in the market often seen as the most steady and sober of them all: government bonds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farms Completely Out Of Turkeys...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/10/supply-chain-issues-thanksgiving-turkeys-stuffing-cranberry-sauce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two weeks before Thanksgiving, Bob's Turkey Farm in Lancaster is out of fresh turkeys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia sends nuke bombers on patrol over Belarus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/european-union-moscow-belarus-poland-russia-99656920fa8d12adee6043fac4d9b546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia sent two nuclear-capable strategic bombers on a training mission over Belarus for a second straight day Thursday in a strong show of Moscow's support for its ally amid a dispute over migration at the Polish border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You sanction us again? We'll freeze you, Lukashenko warns Europe, threatening to cut gas supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/you-sanction-us-again-we-e2-80-99ll-freeze-you-lukashenko-warns-europe-threatening-to-cut-gas-supply/ar-AAQAiS5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Belarusian leader ordered a tough response if the European Union imposes new sanctions over a migration crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Back in Vogue...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gold-back-vogue-bulls-loving-110016664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For much of this year, rising inflation has been bad news for gold. Now it’s giving the metal a shot in the arm. Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesFarmers Take on ‘Post-Apocalyptic’ Food CrisisDo Prisons Deserve a Second Chance?Greece’s Popular Islands Are Crowded — With PlasticWhile bullion is often bought as a way to protect wealth when consumer prices are climbing, this year’s inflation had weighed on the metal as investors b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man earns Ph.D., fulfills dream of being physicist -- at 89...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-lifestyle-united-states-rhode-island-europe-2c4ba11a5cad6542c580f57e662074ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — An 89-year-old Rhode Island man has achieved a goal he spent two decades working toward and nearly a lifetime thinking about — earning his Ph.D. and becoming a physicist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUSTRIA LOCKDOWN FOR UNVAXXED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-europe-austria-health-1188b65ea3d8d80c40e40d3e13aea0a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Austria's chancellor on Thursday stepped up threats of lockdown measures for unvaccinated people, as new coronavirus cases in the Alpine country are soaring. Austria has taken a series of measures in recent weeks in an effort to curb the spread of COVID-19 and encourage more people to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The mutant kids of Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4044467/elon-musk-mars-children-mutations-skin-bones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk’s plan to move mankind to Mars could end up with “Martian” children suffering an array of mutations such as “green” skin, brittle bones and poor eyesight. Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Collections Set ANOTHER Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/283927000000-federal-tax-collections-set-record-october</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government, according to the Monthly Treasury Statement, collected a record $283,927,000,000 in total taxes in October, which was the first month of fiscal 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Number Robot Workers Added...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/north-american-companies-rush-add-robots-demand-surges-2021-11-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies in North America added a record number of robots in the first nine months of this year as they rushed to speed up assembly lines and struggled to add human workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern Europe, facing covid surge, also battles vax hesitancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/eastern-europe-facing-covid-surge-also-battles-vaccine-hesitancy/ar-AAQAeud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases have soared across Central and Eastern Europe, despite the widespread availability of vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL HOLDS COVID WAR GAMES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-holds-e2-80-98war-games-e2-80-99-to-prepare-for-more-lethal-covid-strain/ar-AAQzQDK </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Rush to Discount Stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.fa-mag.com/news/inflation-pinched-shoppers-are-turning-to-discount-stores-ahead-of-the-holidays-64839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fa-mag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that relief programs have expired, Americans are hunting for deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation turns political nightmare for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/11/politics/president-joe-biden-inflation-politics/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's next political nightmare is inflation, a force that can destroy family budgets and political careers and is being driven by domestic and global factors tough for a president to quickly fix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany mulls new measures amid explosion in virus cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/germany-mulls-new-measures-amid-explosion-in-covid-cases-01636624508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany needs further coronavirus restrictions to combat a record surge in infections and "get through this winter", would-be chancellor Olaf Scholz said on Thursday, calling a meeting with state premiers to decide new curbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christie taunts The Don...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-hbo-chris-christie-donald-trump-2191cfcd-ff3a-4da5-ac7c-b887d46f63e6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the opening clash of the 2024 Republican presidential race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD GERMAN CASES</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-11-germany-covid-cases-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany registered a record 50,196 new COVID-19 infections Thursday, according to health authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS warns extremists pushing violence against Congress, health officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/domestic-extremists-pushing-violence-against-congress-school-health-officials-dhs-n1283672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new DHS anti-terror bulletin also noted how both foreign Islamic terrorists and domestic extremists want to exploit the U.S. exit from Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Elite Hand Xi Key Victory, Paving Way for Indefinite Rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-11/china-s-xi-wins-party-backing-for-doctrine-enabling-third-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Forbidden for Muslims, Religious Council Rules...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-forbidden-muslims-indonesia-religious-090931799.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesFarmers Take on ‘Post-Apocalyptic’ Food CrisisDo Prisons Deserve a Second Chance?Greece’s Popular Islands Are Crowded — With PlasticThe use of crypto assets as a currency is forbidden for Muslims, according to Indonesia’s council of religious leaders.The National Ulema Council, or MUI, has deemed cryptocurrency as haram, or banned, as it has elements of uncertainty, wagering and harm, Asrorun Ni</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcists, Demonologists Break Down Satanic Activity At Rapper Concert...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/11/10/astroworld-exorcist-satanic-influence-travis-scott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic Church Exorcists and Demonologist experts explain the Satanic and demonic aspects of the Astroworld tragedy that left eight dead and hundreds injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Threatens to Return to Politics in Replay of 1980...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/inflation-threatens-to-return-to-us-politics-in-replay-of-1980</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report Wednesday (Nov 10) showed that consumer prices surged at a 6.2% annual pace in October.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEWINSKY SEXLESS.</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bill-clinton-monica-lewinsky-oral-sex-scenes-impeachment-american-crime-story-not-included/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TCA 2021: Writer Sarah Burgess tells TheWrap those "graphic sexual" details were "something that much of the audience already knew"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DULL.</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/tv/tv-reviews/impeachment-american-crime-story-review-1218870/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fat suits, bad accents, and two-dimensional characters spoil the latest season of Ryan Murphy’s docudrama anthology series</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans have never been in so much debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/09/economy/fed-household-debt-inflation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American households are carrying record amounts of debt as home and auto prices surge, Covid infections continue to fall and people get out their credit cards again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER PRICES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/10/consumer-price-index-october.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consumer price index surged 6.2% from a year ago in October, the most since December 1990.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AND DISNEY!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/impeachment-star-says-series-aimed-232755010.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A television series debuting next month delves into the impeachment of former U.S. President Bill Clinton, and star Beanie Feldstein said she hopes it might "redeem" Monica Lewinsky in the eyes of some viewers. Lewinsky had an unusual level of involvement in "Impeachment: American Crime Story," producers said on Friday ahead of the Sept. 7 premiere on Walt Disney Co's FX network. Feldstein said she developed a friendship with Lewinsky, meeting once in person just before the COVID-19 pandemic hit, and exchanging texts and videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA extends Covid state of emergency past 2 year mark...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/newsom-extends-covid-state-of-emergency-california-1234871981/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Gavin Newsom today extended for the third time the state of emergency in California related to the threat that Covid poses. Today’s executive order stretches declaration through Marc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOOD BANKS STRUGGLE TO FEED HUNGRY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-oakland-thanksgiving-health-a3d8f4ed0c4842fc3927710f11207c9e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — U.S. food banks already dealing with increased demand from families sidelined by the pandemic now face a new challenge — surging food prices and supply chain issues walloping the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Evading CIA -- and White House Worried...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-11-10/china-under-xi-is-tough-target-for-cia-spies-hurting-biden-s-beijing-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
