<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>End of Theaters? 'IRISHMAN' Opens in Less Than Half of Country...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/10/31/the-end-of-theaters-the-irishman-opens-tomorrow-in-less-than-half-the-us-one-theater-only-in-most-places-concentration-in-new-york-and-los-angeles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it the beginning of the end for movie theaters? Tomorrow, Netflix opens Martin Scorsese’s epic “The Irishman” — highly touted for the Academy Awards — in just a han…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mankind's belief in evil 'caused by disease'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/scientists-discover-mankinds-belief-evil-20762415</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A potentially-massive breakthrough in our understanding of evil may have been found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Live pigs used as crash-test dummies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7634193/Live-pigs-used-crash-test-dummies-killed-China.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifteen immature pigs (some of which are seen in their car seats) were strapped in for high-speed simulations in a study carried out in China which killed seven of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Fertility Crisis Has Govts Scrambling for Answer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2019-global-fertility-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS Manager Suing Company for Discrimination Against White People...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/10/31/former-center-city-starbucks-manager-suing-company-for-alleged-discrimination-against-white-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former regional manager of a Center City Starbucks where two black men were arrested last year for sitting inside the store is suing the company for allegedly discriminating against white people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The city preparing for collapse of capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/oct/31/us-city-preparing-itself-for-the-collapse-of-capitalism </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a festival that helps artists trade work for healthcare to a regional micro-currency, Kingston is trying to build an inclusive and self-sufficient local ecosystem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?465765-1/us-house-debates-impeachment-inquiry-resolution</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House debates and votes on a resolution that lays out the next steps in the impeachment investigation of President Trump, including public hearings, and rights for the president and minority…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Veteran Catherine Herridge Moves to CBS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/catherine-herridge-cbs-news-fox-news-channel-1203389192/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catherine Herridge, a Fox News Channel veteran who has been with that network since it was founded in 1996, is moving to rival CBS News. She will work as a senior investigative correspondent out of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In swing state Ohio, are workers still on President's side?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/swing-state-ohio-workers-still-trumps-side-022912827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Rust Belt state of Ohio, where Donald Trump unexpectedly earned significant support in 2016, some voters are wondering why the "greatest economy in American history" is passing them by. Workers for General Motors spent more than a month on the picket line here, carrying signs and huddling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants on Greek islands 'on edge of catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/migrants-greek-islands-edge-catastrophe-council-europe-110646687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The situation for migrants in camps on Greek islands is "explosive" and "on the edge of catastrophe", the Council of Europe's Commissioner for Human Rights said Thursday. Greece has once again become the main point of entry for people seeking asylum in Europe and it is struggling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUVRE in push to display 'missing' Da Vinci...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/louvre-push-display-missing-da-vinci-culture-expert-115742325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Louvre museum has made an "offer" to the owner of the world's most expensive painting to allow it to be displayed in a Leonardo da Vinci exhibition in Paris, a French cultural body chief said Thursday. The world-famous Salvator Mundi has not been seen in public since it was sold for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House to formalize Trump impeachment investigation... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-formalize-trump-impeachment-investigation-061523863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats laid out a formal roadmap for President Donald Trump's impeachment Thursday as they accumulated more evidence to support charges that he improperly pushed Ukraine to boost his own 2020 electoral prospects. One day after a decorated army officer told Congressional investigators he witnessed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists say quarter of all pigs could die of swine fever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4d525760e304520899eb10a7b084ea2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY (AP) — Around a quarter of the world's pigs are expected to die from African swine fever as authorities grapple with a complex disease spreading rapidly in the globalization era, the World...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires spare Reagan library but menace homes in SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a5c14ddf1dd4130bf02c5a33f21c379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIMI VALLEY, Calif. (AP) — Santa Ana winds were expected to linger for a final day Thursday after driving more than a dozen wildfires through California, sending thousands fleeing and burning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog helps police ID pedestrian hit by vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/dog-helps-police-id-pedestrian-hit-vehicle-66659341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in New Jersey say a dog helped officers find the home of a pedestrian who was struck by a vehicle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People always running late happier...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/study-people-always-running-late-are-happier-and-healthier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who usually run late also tend to be happier and live longer, this according to a new study from Harvard University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory loss set by age 8...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/10/30/memory-loss-mental-decline-old-age-largely-decided-age-eight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memory loss and mental decline in old age is largely decided by the age of eight, a new study has shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Harper trolled after NATS win without him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/world-series-bryce-harper-trolled-on-twitter-after-nationals-win-world-series-without-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nationals unlikely October run ended in a title</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Bans Online Material 'Inciting Violence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/h-k-court-bans-online-materials-inciting-violence-report-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;H.K. Court Bans Online Materials Inciting Violence, Report Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How Rudy May Cost President Dearly...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5714722/rudy-giuliani-transformation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is going on with Giuliani?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Vote to Open Intense Public Phase of Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-inquiry-vote-show-080000555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Democrats hold a historic vote on Thursday to kick off the public phase of an inquiry of President Donald Trump that moves significantly closer to a vote to impeach him.The vote, which is expected to break down mostly along party lines, doesn’t make his conviction and removal from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Boasts on Economy Undercut by Weak Pay Gains...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-boasts-economy-undercut-weak-080000204.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.President Donald Trump boasts that a robust economy will protect him from impeachment and ensure his re-election, but it’s an argument resting on a shaky foundation.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia set to disconnect from Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/russia-disconnect-internet-tomorrow-test-20763305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The test will see Russia revert to an internal version of the web called ‘RuNet’ which is isolated from the networks of other nations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORGET BUGS, PEOPLE NOW EATING 'HUMAN BLOOD SAUSAGE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/forget-bugs-some-people-are-now-eating-human-blood-sausage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, really.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divisive docket to test Supreme Court ahead of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/468224-divisive-docket-to-test-supreme-court-ahead-of-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court is poised to rule on a range of controversial political issues in its current term, potentially putting the high court's broad popularity with the public to the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Republicans shift tone on impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/468246-senate-gop-shifts-tone-on-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are taking the House impeachment proceedings against President Trump more seriously as damaging revelations against the president mount and the possibility of a quick dismissal of the charges shrinks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires 2 missiles amid stalled talks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed0a113001fb40ff95a854bf3c176f49 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea on Thursday fired two projectiles into its eastern sea, an apparent resumption of weapons tests aimed at ramping up pressure on Washington over a stalemate in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2-HOUR WAITS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7633481/Chaos-LAX-ban-curbside-Uber-Lyft-pickups-leaves-thousands-passengers-stranded.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures were high into the seventies in LA yesterday afternoon, but the sizzling Autumnal heat did little to compare to the boiling tempers of the travelers stuck in heavy traffic in LAX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Campaign Holds 'Witch Hunt' Halloween Party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-campaign-holds-witch-hunt-021941396.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joyce Bollini, in a tall black witch hat, gestured at her yellow T-shirt when asked why she and her friend Cynthia Lane, attended a Trump campaign Halloween “Witch Hunt Party” in Lancaster County, Pennsylvania, on a drizzly Wednesday evening.The T-shirts worn by Bollini and Lane had the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX apologizes after UBER policy causes gridlock...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/oct/30/lax-uber-lyft-rideshare-pickup-shuttle-traffic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ban on curbside rideshare pickups leads passengers to report wait times longer than the flights themselves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton Fuels Rumors of Hillary 2020:  'She May or May Not'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/10/bill-clinton-fuels-rumors-of-a-hillary-2020-run-she-may-or-may-not-run-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House lawyer moved to classified server...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-lawyer-moved-transcript-of-trump-call-to-classified-server-after-ukraine-adviser-raised-alarms/ar-AAJC8D7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE DIVIDED ON PARTY LINES...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-hoped-theyd-win-over-republicans-on-impeachment-but-its-not-looking-that-way-so-far/ar-AAJC2PN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD SERIES TRIUMPH!</title>
      <link>https://www.mlb.com/news/nationals-win-2019-world-series</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Down Howie Kendrick reached and off it went. Carrying far, slicing right, pinging the yellow-coated steel screen of the foul pole in right field. The Washington Nationals were trailing until they weren’t. They were, true to form, down but not done.   The late-May misfits and National League Wild</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak feared in Bahamas as nation put on 'high alert'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ebola-outbreak-feared-bahamas-nation-20762175</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus has killed thousands of people in Africa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing club of very powerful countries steering away from dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/31/de-dollarization-russia-china-eu-are-motivated-to-shift-from-using-usd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The greenback's status as the world's major reserve currency could come under threat, as a group of countries seeks to undermine its importance, according to Anne Korin of the Institute for the Analysis of Global Security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent Crime, Robberies Surge in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2019/10/30/statistics-show-paris-violent-crime-robberies-surging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crime statistics in Paris show a continued surge in violent crime, with some areas seeing as much as a 70 per cent rise in violent incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keystone pipeline leaks oil in North Dakota...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/832aca2a059f471c993a55788a3fc719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BISMARCK, N.D. (AP) — A pipeline that carries tar sands oil from Canada through seven states has leaked an unknown amount of crude oil over more than quarter-mile swath in northeastern North...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK reports record revenue...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Facebook-reports-record-revenue-14577228.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook shrugged off months of criticism from regulators and privacy experts Wednesday with record quarterly revenue, revealing advertisers are still flocking to the site.  Facebook, which also owns Instagram and WhatsApp, said its third-quarter revenue grew by 29 percent to $17.7 billion. The company's revenue is driven almost entirely by advertising. Those numbers beat estimates from S&amp;P Global Market Intelligence of $17.35 billion. Net profit grew 19 percent from the same period a year earlier to $6.1 billion.  The number of users on all of Facebook's platforms combined has grown more slowly than revenue. In the third quarter, monthly active users were up 8 percent to 2.45 billion year-over-year. The company's daily active user numbers beat expectations slightly with 9 percent growth year-over-year to 1.62 billion.  "Now we have a clear path forward, not just in terms of product and business but in terms of guidance from regulators which sets clear expectations and gives us a foundation to build on," chief executive Mark Zuckerberg said during a call with analysts.  On the earnings call, Zuckerberg said the company will continue to accept political ads, which he estimated will constitute 0.5 percent of the company's revenue next year. His comments came the same day Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey announced that the platform would ban all political ads, beginning in November.  Zuckerberg insisted that the policy is based on its commitment to free speech, not concerns about its bottom line. Democratic presidential candidates and others criticized Facebook this month for declining to remove a Trump campaign ad that contained falsehoods.  "In a democracy, I don't think it's right for private companies to censor politicians or the news," he said.  "This isn't about free...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment on collision course with possible shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/impeachment-collision-course-possible-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress could navigate a shutdown and an impeachment inquiry if lawmakers and the administration can’t reach a funding deal in the next three weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump without the Trumpiness would win reelection in landslide... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/opinion/article/Trump-without-the-Trumpiness-would-win-reelection-14575603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A thought experiment: Imagine that the president of the United States was a man named Ronald Stump, not Donald Trump. Suppose he was known, before reaching the Oval Office, for delivering thoughtful remarks at the Council on Foreign Relations, rather than for starring in a cartoonish "reality" TV show. Picture him communicating through the White House press office instead of an inflammatory Twitter feed, and cool rather than fiery, and careful as opposed to rash.  Now give this anti-Trump, this Ronald Stump, the same record on which to run for reelection as our real-life President Trump. Give him a persistently strong stock market, record-low unemployment, tame inflation, below-average gasoline prices and bragging rights in a Delta Force raid to administer justice to the founder of the Islamic State. Add to that a passionately happy base of voters savoring a tax cut, a deregulation crusade and a growing army of conservative judges, as promised.  Ronald Stump would be riding high as he enters his reelection campaign. The markers of a two-term presidency are there: a growing economy, a happy political base, a chastened enemy. And given his background and temperament, Stump offends almost no one; he's a uniter, not a divider; he says "Yes, we can" and "Si, se puede." He is affirmative, inspiring. Minus the Trumpiness, President Stump would be thinking in terms of historical landslides.  Trump without the Trumpiness is a fantasy once cherished, but long abandoned, by the conflicted individuals formerly known as Republicans. They've reluctantly come to understand that chaos is intrinsic to this perpetual one-man news cycle. The cartoon-villain vibe, the crazy Twitter feed, the geopolitical rashness and the crude bully-boy are all so baked into Trump's personality that they will matter just as much (maybe more) over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON SET TO TESTIFY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7632107/John-Bolton-evidence-closed-door-impeachment-hearing-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bolton will testify in Donald Trump's impeachment inquiry next week as Democrats will look for the former national security adviser to burn the president in his deposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rules against husband in frozen-embryo divorce case...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/news/connecticut/hc-news-supreme-court-frozen-embryos-20191030-20191030-lx7zxgdu35ew3ftu4yt4jhshsm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state Supreme Court dodged questions about when life begins Wednesday when it ruled in a divorce case that previously frozen embryos a couple had created during their marriage are marital property and can be destroyed over the husband’s objection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie-Omar rally moved to bigger arena due to high demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/10/30/bernie-sanders-ilhan-omar-rally-moves-to-bigger-arena-due-to-high-demand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanders' November 3 Minneapolis rally, with an appearance from Ilhan Omar, had to be moved to a different venue due to high demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Offers Upbeat Forecast While Profit Continues to Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-50242291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of the iPhone fell about 10% from the same period in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles and San Francisco Don't Lose Power Even When Their Suburbs Do...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/los-angeles-san-francisco-don-210710766.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Swaths of Southern California are being plunged into darkness on purpose to prevent power lines from sparking fires during the state’s latest windstorm.But the lights are staying on in Los Angeles.Just like San Francisco, L.A. has avoided the intentional blackouts that have upended daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested on 10th DUI charge...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/drunk/tenth-dui-arrest-102569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 30--A Washington State man whose rap sheet includes nine drunk driving convictions was arrested on his 10th DUI charge after being spotted driving a minivan erratically, police report. David</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer rates rise among war veterans who fought in Iraq, Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article236413328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP: 1.9%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/30/us-gdp-q3-2019-first-reading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growth in GDP was slightly slower than in the second quarter as business investment declined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump on 1.9% GDP in 2012: 'Economy is in deep trouble'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/875233/trump-celebrates-19-percent-gdp-growth-criticized-exact-same-number-under-obama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To quote everyone in President Trump's Twitter replies, "there's a tweet for everything." Trump on Wednesday celebrated the news that the U.S. GDP's growth rate had fallen from 2 percent to 1.9 percent. To Trump, that slight drop quantifies "the greatest economy in American history!" The Greatest Economy in American History! â€” Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) October 30, 2019 Compare that with how the economy performed back in 2012, when GDP growth similarly dropped to a revised 1.9 percent in the first quarter of the year. That was under former President Barack Obama, so Trump had another opinion on the matter. Kathryn Krawczyk Q1 GDP has just been revised down to 1.9% http://t.co/tX9ij8KQ The economy is in deep trouble. â€” Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) May 31, 2012</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reagan Library 'safe' as flames race nearby...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/801090af71c14dba976549932bf4c79e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIMI VALLEY, Calif. (AP) — A wind-whipped outbreak of wildfires outside Los Angeles on Wednesday threatened thousands of homes and horse ranches, forced the smoky evacuation of elderly patients in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  'Whistleblower' Exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearinvestigations.com/articles/2019/10/30/whistleblower_exposed_close_to_biden_brennan_dnc_oppo_researcher_120996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearinvestigations.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Paul Sperry, RealClearInvestigationsOctober 30, 2019, 4:21 PM Eastern For a town that leaks like a sieve, Washington has done an astonishingly effective job keeping from the American public the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Director Leaving White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/10/30/774815627/trumps-russia-director-to-leave-national-security-council-amid-impeachment-inqui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Morrison, a White House official asked to testify Thursday in the impeachment inquiry into President Trump, is expected to leave the National Security Council imminently, three sources told NPR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon releases footage of raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7632435/Pentagon-releases-video-raid-ISIS-leader-al-Baghdadis-Syrian-compound.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine Corps General Kenneth F. McKenzie Jr, commander of U.S. Central Command, released the footage at a press conference on Wednesday at the Pentagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reagan Library 'safe' as flames race nearby...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/10/30/getty-fire-kincade-fire-california-extreme-winds/2502402001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gusty winds threatened to spread the Kincade and Getty fires on Wednesday, putting thousands on alert as mass power outages continue in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depleted Uranium Causes Hazmat Scare At NJ Synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/10/30/depleted-uranium-causes-scare-leads-to-hazardous-material-response-at-new-jersey-synagogue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The marble-sized substance was discovered at Temple Sha'arey Shalom on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Spooked Horses Desperately Try To Escape Flames...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/10/30/watch-horses-try-to-escape-flames-as-easy-fire-scorches-simi-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Samaritans attempted to corral the horses as they galloped across Tierra Rejada Road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caught in love triangle, teens hatched murder plot. It couldn't have gone worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Caught-in-a-love-triangle-teens-hatched-a-murder-14573939.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roaring up to the Ki-Be Red Apple Market in a Dodge pickup truck, Dalton Pullum and Matthew Phalen had no idea they were about to watch a poorly conceived murder plot unravel before their eyes.  The two high school seniors just wanted to grab lunch in between classes in Benton City, a farming community in the rural eastern half of Washington. But when they pulled up to the grocery store on Nov. 15, 2017, they noticed a strange man skulking around the parking lot in broad daylight. He kept crouching down to hide between parked cars, and, even more suspiciously, was wearing a hoodie and a mask that looked as if someone had cut eye holes in a red T-shirt.  "It was like he didn't have time to get a real mask," Pullum, then 18, told the Tri-City Herald. "Like it was hastily done."  As it turned out, the teens had inadvertently stumbled into a bungled attempt to execute one of their own classmates. A group of fellow students at Kiona-Benton City High School had hatched an ill-fated plot to kill 18-year-old Ryan Vaughn with a kitchen knife during their lunch break, only to be thwarted by freshmen on scooters. The bizarre saga culminated on Monday, when Fe Hadley, Vaughn's ex-girlfriend, was found guilty of conspiracy to commit first-degree murder.  The half-baked plan started out as a joke, the Herald reported. Several weeks before the failed murder attempt, a group of teenagers were sitting around, griping about their dislike of Vaughn, then a senior. "What if he died?" someone asked facetiously.  A few members of the group took the question seriously. Hadley, then 16, had briefly dated Vaughn. And Jeremiah Cunningham, who had once dated Hadley, still harbored feelings for her.  Vaughn would later tell detectives that he broke up with Hadley because Cunningham was too protective and overbearing, putting a wedge in their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems closing ranks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/30/democrats-impeachment-vote-061735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3rd Israeli Election 'Likely' As Coalition Talks Deadlock...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Third-election-looking-likely-with-coalition-talks-at-a-deadlock-606356</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Events of the last week have pushed Blue and White away from the Likud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER bans political ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/30/twitter-bans-political-ads-after-facebook-refused-to-do-so.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, by contrast, said it would not fact-check or remove ads placed by politicians, sparking backlash from lawmakers and employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama rips 'woke culture'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/30/obama-rips-woke-culture-at-foundation-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama lashed into “woke culture” at his Obama Foundation Summit in Chicago Tuesday. “This idea of purity and you’re never compromised and you’r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians try to ban naked Joan of Arc show...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/christian-group-ban-naked-joan-arc-oratorio-66630746</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Christian group is trying to prevent the La Monnaie opera house in Brussels from staging a production of Arthur Honegger's oratorio "Joan of Arc at the Stake" in which the heroine appears dressed in men's clothes and at one point naked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/30/kamala-harris-campaign-layoffs-061112</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never Before Seen Autopsy Photo...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/exclusive/exclusive-never-before-seen-autopsy-photo-of-jeffrey-epsteins-broken-bones-released/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAN FURY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10241849/george-michael-fadi-fawaz-bizarre-twitter-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Michael’s former lover has claimed the singer was HIV positive and “never wrote his own music” in a bizarre Twitter rant today. Former hairdresser Fadi Fawaz, 46, made a nu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Retirement Speeds Up Cognitive Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/if-you-rest-you-rust-study-finds-early-retirement-may-speed-up-cognitive-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study conducted at Binghamton University finds that an early retirement can accelerate the usual rate of cognitive decline among the elderly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police blew up an innocent man's house. Too bad, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-blew-up-an-innocent-mans-house-in-search-of-an-armed-shoplifter-too-bad-court-rules/ar-AAJzs8t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Cuts Rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/30/fed-decision-interest-rates-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors expected the U.S. central bank to cut its benchmark interest rate by a quarter point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi 'Davos in desert': Glitz, smiles, hidden name cards...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-davos-desert-glitz-smiles-hidden-name-cards-092911150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street titans smiled and schmoozed at a Saudi investment conference widely shunned last year over a critic's murder, but as wariness lingers some delegates kept their name cards discreetly out of sight. Thousands of policy-makers and executives from over 30 countries packed into Riyadh'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Spy: ISIS Growing in Strength Despite Killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-10-30/isis-remains-potent-deadly-despite-baghdadis-death-top-spy-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Arab Spring unfolding in the Middle East?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-50219821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seething anger on the streets of Arab countries has the air of revolution, says Jeremy Bowen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top diplomat willing to go public...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2019/10/30/politics/bill-taylor-willing-testify-publicly/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top US diplomat in Ukraine, Bill Taylor, is willing to return to Capitol Hill to testify publicly, according to a source familiar with his thinking, making him a potential key early witness for Democrats as they shift their impeachment inquiry into a public phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer worried Trump will force shutdown to impede impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/schumer-worried-trump-will-force-shutdown-to-impede-impeachment-2019-10-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top Democrat in the U.S. Senate said Tuesday he’s worried that President Donald Trump will shut down the federal government in an effort to impede the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady -- To CHARGERS In 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-brady-focused-only-on-the-present-but-expect-him-to-eye-los-angeles-if-he-leaves-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brady hasn't made any indications he's thinking about the future, but here's why some think L.A. is in play</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority of students want PUNISHMENT for 'offensive' Halloween  costumes...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=13923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the numbers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcript gaps...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nyt-vindman-trump-ukraine-memo-edited-claim-09eeefff-44f9-40c8-8ce8-c6b117337854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ellipses in the transcript have long caused worries among Trump officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAYPAL De-Platforms Conservative Street Artist Sabo, Confiscates Funds for Six Months...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/paypal-de-platforms-conservative-street-artist-sabo-holds-his-funds-for-six-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday evening, the conservative street artist Sabo announced that PayPal had de-platformed him and will be holding his money for six months before refunding him. He warned that this might make him homeless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Biden Edge Over Trump Wanes...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/10/30/bidens-edge-over-trump-wanes-polling-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s pitch for the Democratic presidential nomination has rested in no small part on the idea that he’s the most electable candidate -- that he’ll beat President Donald Trump “like a drum” if given the chance. But polling shows that argument is weakening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Denver Record Broken As Temperatures Plunge To Near Zero...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/10/30/denver-weather-record-cold-temperature-broken-plunge-near-zero-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The temperature in Denver officially dropped to 3 degrees above zero early Wednesday morning. It was cold enough to shatter the previous record low for October 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zh-RiVX88Fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This footage was filmed by Nene Angulo while on his way to work near Broadway &amp; 8th avenue in Downtown San Diego in California. In the footage we can see thi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Slapped With Mere $644,000 Fine Over Cambridge Analytica Breach...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/facebook-pays-644000-uk-fine-over-cambridge-analytica-case-doesnt-admit-fault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has agreed to pay the Information Commissioner's Office a £500,000 fine over its Cambridge Analytica data leak, but did not admit any wrongdoing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Lohan's Bizarre Friendship With MBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-lindsay-lohan-and-mbss-bizarre-friendship </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress’ father says his daughter has a “platonic and respectful” friendship with the unpredictable Saudi royal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studio Chief Summit: All 7 Top Film Executives, 1 Room, Nothing Off-Limits...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/hollywood-reporter-executive-roundtable-7-major-studio-chiefs-1250718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, Warner Bros.' Toby Emmerich, Paramount's Jim Gianopulos, Disney's Alan Horn, Universal's Donna Langley, Sony's Tom Rothman, Amazon's Jennifer Salke and Netflix's Scott Stuber gather to debate streaming service ratings, movie star value, China censorship, onscreen violence and the future of a fraught movie business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once one of America's favorite pastimes, greyhound racing eats dust...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/once-one-of-america-s-favorite-pastimes-greyhound-racing-eats/article_76dd15d2-b3f0-5c7f-9909-82063e453893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Rick Bartley once raced the greyhounds he breeds in Kansas all over the country, but the past decade has slowly stripped him of his livelihood. As state laws</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists discover Aztec tunnel world hidden beneath Mexico City...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1197419/archaeology-latest-Aztec-mexico-tribe-history-mexico-city-scientists-underground-tunnel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARCHAEOLOGISTS have discovered a secret Aztec tunnel world nestled below the busy streets of Mexico’s capital city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael's ex claims singer was HIV positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/george-michael-was-hiv-claims-20755151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fadi Fawaz's Twitter account has claimed George Michael was HIV positive in a string of explosive early morning posts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby born in space 'could become real-life Superman...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/10/30/babies-born-in-space-could-become-a-real-life-superman-11003387/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A space society run by a billionaire and a former Lib Dem MP hopes to change society forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackles rise as Chicago teachers strike drags into day 9...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/21204993c556437db1bc91846423ad5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Chicago's mayor on Tuesday accused leaders of the city's powerful teachers union of using its "political agenda" to hold up a contract agreement to end a strike that will keep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulvaney left in dark on al-Baghdadi operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/mulvaney-was-left-dark-al-baghdadi-operation-n1073731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extraordinary move by Trump to leave out his chief of staff suggests that Mulvaney is increasingly sidelined inside the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man seen falling while livestreaming climb up Mt. Fuji on YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-10-30/japan-livestream-fall-mount-fuji</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Shizuoka, one of two prefectures that include Japan's highest mountain, found a body after receiving calls from some viewers of the livestream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosion in Antarctic sea ice levels may cause another ice age?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/explosion-antarctic-sea-ice-ice-age</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upside-down "rivers" of warm ocean water may be one of the causes of Antarctica's ice shelves breaking up, leading to a rise in sea levels. But a new study suggests an increase in sea ice may lead to a much more devastating change in the Earth's climate — another ice age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specter of Nixon impeachment looming over Republican Party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/468068-specter-of-nixon-impeachment-looming-over-republican-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results of the election over four decades ago haunt lawmakers more than ever today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Texas Hit Hard By Shale Slowdown...</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Energy-General/Texas-Hit-Hard-By-Shale-Slowdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As oil prices continue to remain low, Texas banks are turning away independent oil producers looking for loans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSIVE FIRE SIMI VALLEY</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/10/30/brush-fire-erupts-in-simi-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze broke out before 6 a.m. in the area of the 118 Freeway and Madera Road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRUSTRATION RISES WITH ANOTHER ROUND OF BLACKOUTS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/64fdb75d7e434722bd0229e1b458eebc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A new large wildfire broke out Wednesday in Southern California amid gusty winds, forcing the evacuation of the Ronald Regain Presidential Library and nearby homes. The...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
