<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Iran threatens USA over potential Revolutionary Guard terror designation...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/7/iran-threatens-retaliation-over-potential-revoluti/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in Tehran over the weekend vowed retaliation if the Trump administration moves ahead with a plan to label Iran’s Revolutionary Guard a terrorist organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandinavian Banks' Clean Reputations Threatened by Dirty Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/why-scandinavian-banks-clean-reputations-are-threatened-by-dirty-money/ar-BBVG8oJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY: Dems will 'never' see president's tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/437729-mulvaney-democrats-will-never-see-trumps-tax-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney said Sunday that Democrats will "never" see President Trump's tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man fears feds will kill event...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/burningman/article/Burning-Man-begs-festival-goers-to-help-stop-BLM-13746797.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burning Man organizers are pleading with festival-goers to write to the Bureau of Land Management (BLM) and urge them to reconsider a number of new requirements for the festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE: LET FELONS IN PRISON VOTE</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2019/04/06/bernie-sanders-says-states-should-felon-voting-rights-election-2020-iowa-caucus/3388679002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator was asked whether the imprisoned should have the right to vote. Only his home state and Maine allow felons to vote from behind bars. "I think that is absolutely the direction we should go," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65 get pizza shop logo tattooed for free food...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/2019/04/06/blaze-pizza-restaurant-des-moines-iowa-ia-offers-free-pizza-logo-tattoo-flame-twisted-ink/3387288002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $40 flame tattoo comes with 24 free pizzas and the $65 Blaze name logo comes with 48 free pizzas as part of the promotion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats know they need white male voters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/79fefc13c5a54b089da12c7007e98ac8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPPER ST. CLAIR TOWNSHIP, Pa. (AP) — When he moved to Pennsylvania about five years ago, it was a coin toss which party Brian Heitman would register with. No longer. Since Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop shows up intoxicated to breathalyzer training...</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/region/detroit/detroit-police-officer-shows-up-intoxicated-to-msp-breathalyzer-training</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Detroit Police officer is at the center of an internal investigation after he showed up under the influence of alcohol to training in Lansing, Detroit Police Chief James Craig told reporters Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In extreme wildfire era, firefighting aircraft 'increasingly ineffective'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-aircraft-increasingly-ineffective-against-california-wildfires-20190407-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is poised to spend $273 million on new firefighting aircraft, but the tools won't help fight the most devastating kinds of blazes California has seen of late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Surreal' Pyongyang marathon in spotlight as tensions ease...</title>
      <link>https://whtc.com/news/articles/2019/apr/07/athletics-surreal-pyongyang-marathon-in-spotlight-as-tensions-ease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whtc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Karolos Grohmann (Reuters) - North Korea's Pyongyang marathon may be among the most complicated to enter but an easing of tensions on the Korean peninsula has made it a stage to highlight the power of sport amid growing interest for the race. Athletes can only register through one operator, Koryo Tours, for a chance to run through the capital...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE legend attacked by audience member during Hall of Fame speech...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wwes-bret-hart-attacked-man-york-city-hall/story?id=62228075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 26-year-old man was arrested on Saturday for punching Bret "The Hitman" Hart during a Hall of Fame speech at the Barclay Center in Brooklyn, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative takeover of Supreme Court stalled by Roberts-Kavanaugh bromance...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/04/07/supreme-court-bromance-john-roberts-brett-kavanaugh-tie-up-court/3342377002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative takeover of the Supreme Court under Donald Trump is stalled by a bromance between Chief Justice John Roberts and Brett Kavanaugh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhino poacher trampled to death by elephants then eaten by lions...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8807049/rhino-poacher-dead-elephants-lions-kruger-national-park-south-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POACHER hunting rhinos in the Kruger National Park met a gruesome end after being trampled to death by an elephant and then eaten by a pride of hungry lions. Four other poachers who fled the game…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest female python ever captured...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/this-is-the-biggest-female-python-ever-captured-in-the-everglades-big-cypress-researchers-say/ar-BBVGEnb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker dies setting up Coachella Festival...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/worker-dies-fall-setting-coachella-festival-62225759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get breaking national and world news, broadcast video coverage, and exclusive interviews. Find the top news online at ABC news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In possible first, Cuba allows march by animal activists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1fbc4c9865b4c398f5f1e1f5bd5e9b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — On Sunday morning a group of animal-lovers will march a mile down one of Havana's main thoroughfares waving placards calling for an end to animal cruelty in Cuba. Short,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Election Ads, to Stir up the Base, Anything Goes... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/03/world/middleeast/israel-election-ads-netanyahu-gantz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are some commercials riling up voters on social media. They are in Hebrew and Arabic, but need no translation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Agents Granted Wide Latitude Trying To Catch Drivers Seeking To Enter Illegally...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trapped-in-a-deadly-chase/ar-BBVBO50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince William delves into secretive spy world ...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1110843/royal-news-prince-william-mi5-gchq-spy-terror-threat-kate-middleton-princess-charlotte</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE William has spent the last three weeks secretly embedded with Britain’s intelligence services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhetoric gets tougher...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/media/As-Trump-struggles-to-curb-unauthorized-1479843.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD to scrap some crime data programs after criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2f53080e081042fc82fa00178b0f7dd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A newspaper reports Los Angeles Police Chief Michel Moore plans to make changes to a controversial program that uses data to identify people who are most likely to commit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhetoric gets tougher...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/as-trump-struggles-to-curb-unauthorized-immigration-his-rhetoric-gets-tougher-but-quick-solutions-are-elusive/2019/04/06/8780ac92-57b7-11e9-814f-e2f46684196e_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is grasping to deal with an unprecedented spike in migrant families without a well-defined strategy and with significant divisions roiling Trump’s team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA: Military intervention 'very serious option'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/us-military-intervention-on-the-table-for-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A military intervention to oust Venezuelan strongman Nicolás Maduro remains “a very serious option” for the United States, according to President Trump’s national security team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PM May says final choice between leaving EU with deal or no Brexit at all...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/apr/06/furious-tory-mps-will-bid-to-oust-may-if-uk-fights-euro-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime minister says Brexit could ‘slip through our fingers’ as Tory party fears that taking part in EU election would boost far right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America deals with new kind of candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-Pete-Buttigieg-America-deals-with-a-new-kind-13747087.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST HOLLYWOOD, Calif. - Pete Buttigieg sat in the back of a black SUV with a couple of staffers, sipping a still-steeping cup of tea to ease the fatigue from his suddenly frenetic schedule, when he looked out the window and interrupted himself.  "Man," said Buttigieg, taking in the rainbow-hued signs and colorfully dressed passersby that signaled he had entered West Hollywood, Los Angeles' de facto gay neighborhood. "It got real gay real quick out there."  Few Democratic presidential candidates could assess their surroundings so bluntly without seeming painfully out of line. But Buttigieg is not like any other Democratic presidential candidate - in part, if not exclusively, because he is gay.  He was also a Rhodes Scholar, a McKinsey &amp; Co. consultant who pored over grocery prices and a military officer in Afghanistan. He was a mayor at 29 and re-elected at 33. All of those experiences, he says, have chiseled him into the surprising presidential candidate he is at 37, barely beyond the constitutional age requirement for the job.  So has the fact, Buttigieg says, that he needed the Supreme Court to give him the freedom to marry his partner, Chasten Glezman. Same-sex marriage was illegal in Indiana until 2014, and he cites that to illustrate how government alters lives; his marriage exists, he tells voters at every stop, "by the grace of one vote on the Supreme Court."  Buttigieg's emergence gives Americans their second openly gay presidential candidate - activist Fred Karger sought the GOP nomination in 2012 - but the first, by far, to earn so much attention. Many gay Americans are celebrating Buttigieg's quick climb as a sign of tangible progress. Others, mainly outside that community, wonder whether talking about Buttigieg's candidacy as historic means undermining the notion that sexuality doesn't matter.  "I don't...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans march to demand power, water and end to Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/venezuelans-march-to-demand-power-water-and-end-to-maduro-idUSKCN1RI0L1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After weeks of power cuts and limited access to water, tens of thousands of Vene...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-abortion film a surprise boxoffice success...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-anti-abortion-film-surprise-box-office-success-010603753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A movie produced by a Christian studio about a former employee of an organization that provides abortions who became a "pro-life" activist is proving to be a surprising box office hit. "Unplanned" comes amid a resurgent campaign in the United States by opponents of abortion, which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN expert to visit Assange, assess violation of privacy claims...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-expert-visit-assange-assess-violation-privacy-claims-172848295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An independent rights expert will visit WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange at the Ecuadoran embassy in London to assess whether privacy violation claims involving him merit investigation, the UN rights office said Thursday. "The Special Rapporteur on the right to privacy, Joe Cannataci, plans to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is 'threat to world' says dissident writer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-threat-world-says-dissident-writer-063237464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dissident writer dubbed the "Chinese Solzhenitsyn" said Friday that his homeland is a "threat for the whole world". Liao Yiwu, who was jailed for writing a poem called "Massacre" about the Tiananmen Square protests, told AFP that it would be better for mankind if the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes erupt as Greek police stop migrants from entering...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190406153610-otfp2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-MIGRANTS/GREECE-BORDER (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Clashes erupt as Greek police stop migrants from reaching border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela street rallies show deep divide in struggle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b5de526e1c034541964a3f2e2a39f717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Rival political factions took to the streets across Venezuela on Saturday in a mounting struggle for control of the crisis-wracked nation, where U.S.- backed opposition...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE, BETO FACE OFF IN IOWA!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af719047b5fc4a6d8cafc7bc1ce59bd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's Bernie versus Beto in Iowa on a busy campaign weekend in the early nominating states. The two 2020 Democratic presidential candidates are holding dueling events just days after Bernie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren says Dems need more than anti-Trump cry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0047c702eec64130b5d0969b27dd8b5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on the 2020 presidential race (all times EDT): 3:45 p.m. Elizabeth Warren says the Democrats running for president will have to do more than campaign on an anti-Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest's 150-Year-Old Heart Being Worshipped in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/new-york/articles/2019-04-06/french-priests-150-year-old-heart-being-worshipped-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avg Person Has Just 4 Hours, 26 Minutes Free Time -- Per WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-average-american-free-time-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How much free time do you get to enjoy each week? If you're like the most people, it's hardly enough to even be excited about. A new survey finds that the average American logs just four hours and 26 minutes of time to themselves in a given week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to designate elite Iranian force terrorist org...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran/u-s-to-designate-elite-iranian-force-as-terrorist-organization-idUSKCN1RH2I4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is expected to designate Iran's elite Revolutionary Guard...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generational challenges lie ahead for Joe, Mayor Pete...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Generational-challenges-lie-ahead-for-Joe-Biden-13746930.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes the confluence of unrelated events provides a moment of clarity in politics. So it is with the recent travails of former Vice President Joe Biden and the recent emergence of Pete Buttigieg in the 2020 presidential race. They highlight the challenges that generational politics will play as Democrats select a nominee to run against President Donald Trump.  The two men are virtually bookends in the Democratic race. At 76, Biden is more than twice the age of Buttigieg, who at 37 is just two years past the constitutional requirement to stand for the presidency. Americans have never elected a president as young as Buttigieg, just as the nation has never elected a president as old as Biden.  Biden brings longer experience than anyone else in the field. He has been in the public arena for more than half his life, having been elected to the Senate at an age younger than Buttigieg is. That experience will be a principal attribute as he tries to make the case to Democrats that he is their party's most electable candidate and, if he were to win the nomination, that he is capable of settling down the country and able to be president from day one.  Biden served eight years at the right arm of President Barack Obama, chaired two of the most important committees in the Senate (Judiciary and Foreign Relations), has been in the middle of many of the important domestic policy fights and in the forefront of the most significant foreign policy issues over the past few decades. He has been on the winning and losing side of these debates, and, given how events played out, on the right side and the wrong side of history as well. He has admirers and critics for the positions he has taken.  Buttigieg, the mayor of South Bend, Indiana, offers a far shorter résumé, but one that nonetheless is marked by accomplishment. After graduating...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher faces suspension for showing videos with nudes...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/south-florida-teacher-faces-suspension-for-showing-videos-with-nudes/article_50b23ce2-92e1-5b34-8a3b-f40757616708.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pictures displayed by a high school art teacher showed nudity, for sure. The question is whether they were artistic or obscene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-US Sen 'Fritz' Hollings dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/48ba0b0130d14b97998b1e65a220ad23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — Ernest F. "Fritz" Hollings, the silver-haired Democrat who helped shepherd South Carolina through desegregation as governor and went on to serve six terms in the U.S. Senate,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For American Jews, Trump key figure...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/202753dd5041400daeeb5012f5c550b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Donald Trump isn't on the ballot for Israel's national election, yet he's a dominant factor for many American Jews as they assess the high stakes of Tuesday's balloting. At...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg could hurt Trump in Rust Belt...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/06/how-pete-buttigieg-could-beat-trump-in-his-bases-backyard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg is many things. At just 37, he is the mayor of South Bend, Indiana. He is a military veteran and a deeply religious gay man who is married but also enjoys sandwiches from the (anti-g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Y2K Revisited as GPS Reset May Send Devices Haywire...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apos-y2k-revisited-gps-reset-171424753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to a quirk in how Global Positioning Systems keep track of time, some devices are due to have their calendars reset at 7:59 p.m. EDT on Saturday. Fortunately, the glitch only affects older GPS systems or ones that haven’t been updated, and the U.S. Department of Homeland Security says it isn’</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
