<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Severed cat head at Graydon Carter's home amid Epstein reporting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/23/vanity-fairs-graydon-carter-found-severed-cat-head-outside-home-amid-jeffrey-epstein-reporting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vanity Fair editor-in-chief Graydon Carter made a disturbing discovery on his front lawn — the severed head of a cat — just after he assigned a reporter to dig into Jeffrey Epstein’s alleged sexual…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to train against AI avatars...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/23/armys-close-combat-units-to-train-against-ai-avata/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Army officials say an augmented reality training system created by Microsoft will be ready for prime time by 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite dangers, MO docs can OK marijuana for pregnant women...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/business/health-care/article234009157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg visits hospital for tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7387385/Ruth-Bader-Ginsburg-86-visits-hospital-tests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, 86, was seen leaving the Howard Laboratory at the Memorial Sloan Kettering Hospital on the Upper East Side on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS XI ENEMY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/23/bad-sign-for-trade-talks-trump-calls-china-president-xi-enemy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My only question is, who is our bigger enemy, Jay Powell or Chairman Xi?" Trump wrote amid a series of tweets that rattled markets Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Deep Fake must be stopped before we no longer know what's real...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/opinion/jordan-peterson-deep-fake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can tell you from personal experience how disturbing it is to discover a website devoted to making fake audio clips of you — for comic or malevolent purposes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top publishers sue AUDIBLE for copyright infringement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e2078e81c5ca42a9bcde6aeea678b129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Some of the country's top publishers are suing Audible, citing copyright infringement as they ask a federal judge to enjoin the audiobook producer-distributor's planned use of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines Considering Flying U.S. F-35Bs Off of Japan Warships...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2019/08/23/marines-considering-flying-u-s-f-35bs-off-of-japans-largest-warships</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON – Officials in Tokyo have requested Marines deploy F-35B fighters aboard Japan’s largest warships, a U.S. defense official confirmed to USNI News on Friday. The service is now studying the feasibility of deploying short take-off vertical landing (STOVL) fighters from JS Izumo (DDH-183) and JS Kaga (DDH-184), Japan’s 24,000-ton big deck amphibious. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian President Abbas: Millions Of Fighters Will Take Over Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/pa-president-abbas-millions-of-fighters-will-take-over-jerusalem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PA President Mahmoud Abbas threatened this week that "million of fighters" would swarm Jerusalem and topple the Jewish state's capital city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS:  Trump 'Orders' American Businesses to Find Alternative to China...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190823155042-k15dh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA-TRUMP (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Trump presses U.S. companies to close China operations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -400</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/23/us-stocks-wall-street-monitors-speech-from-fed-chair-jerome-powell.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks dropped after Donald Trump ordered that U.S. companies find alternatives to their operations in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Chair doesn't commit to deep interest rate cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Fed-Chair-Powell-vows-to-sustain-the-expansion-14373128.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON HOLE, Wyo. - Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell said Friday that the trade war is a "complex, turbulent" situation and he vowed the central bank will "act as appropriate to sustain the expansion," suggesting another interest rate cut may be coming but not the large decline President Donald Trump has urged.  "Our economy is in a favorable place," Powell said, according to prepared remarks, but he added that there are "significant risks," especially from trade policy uncertainty.  Twice during his speech here at the Kansas City Fed's annual monetary policy symposium, Powell reiterated that the Fed's overriding goal is to ensure the economy continues to grow and the central bank would do what was necessary to make that happen.  "Our challenge now is to do what monetary policy can do to sustain the expansion so that the benefits of the strong jobs market extend to more of those still left behind," Powell said.  Trump has lashed out at the Fed almost daily, calling on Powell to lower interest rates a full percentage point from just shy of 2.25% now down to 1.25%, the type of action that is typically done when the economy is in a recession or dangerous situation.  "Now the Fed can show their stuff!," Trump tweeted shortly before Powell's speech Friday morning.  In his remarks, Powell repeatedly characterized the U.S. economy as in a good place with low unemployment, solid growth and strong consumer spending, painting a picture of an economy that could possibly use a small boost but does not need massive aid.  "The U.S. economy has continued to perform well overall, driven by consumer spending," Powell said. "It will be appropriate at times for us to tilt policy one way or the other because of prominent risks."  Wall Street investors now predict a 96% chance the Fed will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves, Tsujihara and Art of Hollywood Self-Sabotage...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/les-moonves-kevin-tsujihara-art-hollywood-sabotage-1233956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even before the #MeToo era, there was a long tradition of Tinseltown executives destroying their own careers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEFFEN YACHT SNAPS BECOME TOP STATUS IN MEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-david-geffens-yacht-photos-became-a-status-thing-hollywood-1233154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A voyage on Rising Sun is summer’s "most coveted" vacation for A-listers with Oprah Winfrey, Chris Rock, Steven Spielberg, Leonardo DiCaprio and even Jeff Bezos popping up on the mogul’s Instagram feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDMA, Or Ecstasy, Shows Promise As PTSD Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/mdma-or-ecstasy-shows-promise-as-a-ptsd-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MDMA, the psychoactive ingredient in the club drug known as molly or ecstasy, is being tested in combination with therapy as a treatment for severe trauma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying for new body: Why so many deaths from plastic surgery tourism?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/aug/23/americans-plastic-surgery-dominican-republic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers flock to the Dominican Republic for cheaper plastic surgery procedures, but not all of them return home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army may help fight as condemnation mounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-politic-president/brazils-bolsonaro-says-army-may-help-fight-amazon-fires-as-global-condemnation-mounts-idUSKCN1VD19T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's President Jair Bolsonaro said on Friday the army may be enlisted t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Circular craft' filmed flying next to passenger plane over Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/kentucky-ufo-circular-craft-video-18990049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The object appeared to be following the plane as it flew overhead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-US marine says injured by Russian prison guards...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ex-us-marine-says-injured-russian-prison-guards-094848922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former US marine who was arrested in Moscow on espionage charges said Friday he has been injured by guards in the prison where he is being held awaiting trial. "I was injured in the prison... the prison doesn't want to tell you," Paul Whelan told journalists from an accused's cage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tribe looks on helplessly as rainforest is destroyed by man and fire...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/08/23/amazon-tribe-looks-helplessly-rainforest-destroyed-man-fire-10617538/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We need the forest and our children need the forest.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Negative Rates Coming for Your Savings...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/negative-rates-coming-savings-050005475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- First they came for central banks, then they came for government bonds, then they came for rich depositors. Then they came for me.Negative interest rates are coming for us all, in one form or another, as central banks redouble their efforts to avert a global economic slowdown that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Burning Man events: Sensual hot dog eating, Bob Ross, more...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/burning-man-activities-orgy-food-event-what-to-do-14371372.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The events range from the innocuous (dodgeball brunch, bachata dance class, fruit smoothies) to the X-rated (let's just say, there are 40 search results for "orgy"), to the ... somewhere in between? We're not sure where to sort "sensual hot dog eating contest."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro accuses Macron of 'colonialist mindset' after calls for action...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/23/brazils-bolsonaro-hits-back-at-frances-macron-over-amazon-fires.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro hit back at French leader Emmanuel Macron, after he urged dialogue among G-7 leaders on the rising number of fires in the Amazon rainforest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenny Kravitz is still ripped, rocking and 'letting love rule'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/lenny-kravitz-is-still-ripped-rocking-and-letting-love-rule/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been 30 years since Lenny Kravitz first introduced his flower-child rock with “Let Love Rule,” his debut album released on Sept. 6, 1989. But the New York native is still always on the run: Af…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Risks Recession as Second-Quarter GDP Revised Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/mexico-economy-gdp/update-1-mexican-second-quarter-gdp-revised-down-to-show-flat-economy-idUSL2N25J07U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Adds comparison to preliminary data)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbance on Florida doorstep gets 60% chance of development...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/news/20190823/just-in-disturbance-on-floridarsquos-doorstep-has-70-chance-of-development</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An area of low pressure just east of the upper Florida Keys has a 70 percent chance of developing into a tropical cyclone over the next five days, but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebs spreading disinformation?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190823-amazon-fires-how-celebrities-are-spreading-disinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon fires: how celebrities are spreading disinformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Yellow vests, anarchists put French police on alert...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/3954/yellow-vests-anarchists-put-french-police-g7-alert-doc-1jp4ko1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skin in the game: Hong Kong protesters get inked...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/skin-game-hong-kong-protesters-inked-072003706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a tattooist's black ink fills the petals of Hong Kong's Bauhinia flower on her upper thigh, 'C' says the indelible act of rebellion will forever serve as a reminder of the city's summer of defiance. From umbrellas and Chinese calligraphy, to gas masks and helmets, people are getting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing WIKILEAKS associate 'had kayak accident in Norway'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/missing-wikileaks-associate-had-kayak-accident-norway-police-105614719.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dutch WikiLeaks associate who went missing under mysterious circumstances a year ago probably had a kayaking accident, Norwegian police said Friday, adding that his body had not yet been found. Arjen Kamphuis, a cybersecurity expert then aged 47, had not been seen since he left his hotel in the northern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Riles Bolsonaro, Setting Up G-7 Fight Over Amazon Fires...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/macron-riles-bolsonaro-g-7-063544219.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Emmanuel Macron said Group of Seven leaders gathering in Biarritz, France, Saturday must tackle head on the fires in the Amazon jungle, establishing the summit’s first flash point.“Our house is burning. Literally,” the French president wrote in a tweet late Thursday. “It is an international</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamers take aim at Trump's criticism of virtual violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gamers-aim-trumps-criticism-virtual-violence-094930468.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamers at the industry's biggest fair in Europe have taken aim at US President Donald Trump's assertions that violence in video games was partly to blame for recent mass shootings. Experts and fans alike at the Gamescom trade fair in the German city of Cologne rejected the link between popular</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOG OWNERSHIP LINKED TO BETTER HEART HEALTH...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-08-heart-friend-dog-ownership-cardiovascular.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owning a pet may help maintain a healthy heart, especially if that pet is a dog, according to the first analysis of data from the Kardiozive Brno 2030 study. The study examines the association of pet ownership—specifically dog ownership—with cardiovascular disease risk factors and cardiovascular health. The results are published in Mayo Clinic Proceedings: Innovations, Quality &amp; Outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart attacks halved by daily 'polypill', strokes reduced too: study...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/europe/heart-attacks-halved-by-daily-polypill-strokes-reduced-too-study-1.1566554872779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cheap, once-a-day pill combining aspirin with other drugs cuts cardiovascular diseases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Find Europe Dug In Against 'Maximum Pressure' on Iran...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/europe-dug-against-trump-iran-080002594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump wants America’s closest allies to ratchet up the pressure on Iran. But this weekend in France he’ll find they’re still reluctant to join him.Divisions over Iran will be on full display when Trump meets his European peers at a Group of Seven meeting starting Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin orders reciprocal response to U.S. missile test...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190823093444-5phk4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PENTAGON/MISSILES-RUSSIA (URGENT):Putin orders reciprocal Russian response to U.S. missile test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Act of insanity to stay in U.S.:' Why 63-year-old ditched Massachusetts for Panama...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/it-is-an-act-of-insanity-to-stay-in-the-us-why-this-63-year-old-teacher-ditched-massachusetts-to-retire-in-the-highlands-of-panama-2019-08-23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can live on about $2,000 a month, experts says, and Panama has a generous ‘pensionado program.’ But there are drawbacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Biblical city where Jesus healed blind man 'unearthed' in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ancient-biblical-city-jesus-healed-18988836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ancient city is referenced in the New Testament</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gentleman jailbreak: 270 inmates who bolted during riot -- return to finish sentences...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gentleman-jailbreak-convicts-return-indonesia-prison-072828529.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 270 inmates -- including convicted murderers -- who bolted from a prison torched during violent riots in Indonesia's Papua region have returned to finish their sentences, a corrections official said Friday. The convicts are even helping build a temporary office for their jailers, he added</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny, Released From Jail, Says Anti-Putin Protests Will Intensify...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190823072057-vhort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Freed Kremlin critic Navalny predicts bigger opposition protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY TO RUMBLE</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2019/08/22/g-7-braces-for-its-next-encounter-with-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aides say the president plans to 'frankly' discuss trade, a digital services tax and NATO spending obligations during the summit this weekend in France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life-like robots closer to reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/technow/life-like-robots-closer-to-reality-945405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Bristol have demonstrated a new way of embedding computation into soft robotic materials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT contractors listening to children through XBOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/43kv4q/microsoft-human-contractors-listened-to-xbox-owners-homes-kinect-cortana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple contractors working for Microsoft explain how they listened to audio captured by Xbox consoles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST LEAD FRIDAY:  White House internal warnings about economic slowdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-month-trump-e2-80-99s-economy-faltered/ar-AAGbKV8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes will get day in court against TWITTER. Will  case be dismissed?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/regional/the-west/article234221712.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miley Cyrus Was Fired from SONY Movie for Penis Cake Photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/miley-cyrus-was-fired-hotel-transylvania-penis-cake-photos-1233931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I got kicked off 'Hotel Transylvania' for buying Liam [Hemsworth] a penis cake for his birthday and licking it," she tweeted Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethnic studies bill delayed a year in California amid controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/state-nation-world/ethnic-studies-bill-delayed-a-year-in-california-amid-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A measure that would require all California high school students take an ethnic studies course is on hold for at least a year after pro-Israel groups and other critics raised concerns about the curriculum. The decision was announced Thursday by the author of the bill, Assemblyman Jose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanists battle for religious freedom...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-49392867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The documentary shining a new light on the Satanic Temple and its battle for religious freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farming moves indoors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-49052317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vertical farming is fast-expanding but the costs are high and the food range is limited - for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Attempt To Edit DNA In Human Sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/08/22/746321083/scientists-attempt-controversial-experiment-to-edit-dna-in-human-sperm-using-cri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NPR visited the only lab in the world known to be trying to use the powerful gene-editing tool CRISPR to modify the DNA in human sperm. If successful, it could be used to prevent genetic disorders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pump Prices Could Fall Below $2 in the South!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbc12.com/2019/08/22/cheap-crude-oil-paves-way-cheaper-gas-this-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbc12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AAA forecasts the national average to drop to $2.40 or lower this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies by suicide after video goes viral of him defending relationship with trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/maurice-willoughby-died-by-suicide-after-viral-video-defending-transgender-girlfriend-20190822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation into Willoughby’s death is still pending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy hunter turned to mush as 11ft alligator savages him...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/trophy-hunters-bones-turned-mush-18987291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Perchalski had shared pictures of dead animals on Facebook from his hunting sessions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  Raise capital gains tax back to 39.6%...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/biden-capital-gains-tax-we-should-raise-tax-back-396-percent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden calls for doubling of capital gains tax rate&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Democrat presidential candidate Joe Biden said he’d like to raise the capital gains tax rate to 39.6 percent, a near doubling of the current 20 percent. &amp;#13;&amp;#13;Biden made the remarks on Wednesday, August 21 during an interview with Iowa Public Television: &amp;#13;&amp;#13;“I believe we should, in fact, the capital gains tax should be at what the highest minimum tax should be, we should raise the tax back to 39.6 percent instead of 20 percent,” Biden said yesterday.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Raising the capital gains tax would harm Americans’ ability to build a nest egg and h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Macron seeks to be mediator in G-7 hard times...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7cb2611f95aa4e68be00e088ddf893be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French President Emmanuel Macron hosts the G-7 summit this weekend fresh off a meeting with Russia's Vladimir Putin, hoping to maintain his image as a global mediator at a time of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Man crushed by falling elevator in NYC building...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/video-shows-moment-man-crushed-by-elevator-at-manhattan-promenade-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horrifying video obtained by The Post shows the moment a Manhattan man is crushed under the weight of his luxury high-rise’s malfunctioning elevator and dragged to his death into the darkness…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Risks Recession as Second-Quarter GDP May Be Revised Down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-risks-recession-second-quarter-172410979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Economists expect Mexico’s second-quarter gross domestic product to be revised slightly down on Friday, with some going as far as to predict a negative number that would mean Latin America’s second-largest economy slipped into technical recession this year.The median estimate of economists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY MOVES TO BAN SLEEPING NEAR SCHOOLS, PARKS...</title>
      <link>https://laist.com/2019/08/22/los-angeles-homeless-sit-lie-sleep-law.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;laist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposed changes would outlaw sleeping on public space within 500 feet of schools and parks, and within 10 feet of any building entrance or driveway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems less likely to get Trump's tax returns before 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://hamodia.com/2019/08/22/house-democrats-less-likely-get-trumps-tax-returns-2020-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hamodia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats appear increasingly unlikely to secure President Donald Trump's tax returns before the 2020 presidential election, according to interviews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas governor meets with tech officials about quelling extremism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f0c1ce26cf104ba897ac205c9d5b91a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas Gov. Greg Abbott on Thursday met in Austin with officials from some of the world's biggest tech giants to discuss ways of combatting extremism in the wake of a mass...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global worry over Amazon fires escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1b052a0ffb34217aef47d20e960a410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Amid global concern about raging Amazon fires, Brazil on Thursday said it was the target of a smear campaign by critics who contend President Jair Bolsonaro is not doing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term mortgage rates near historic lows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a8e2d9164ad4cb5b192d542a2b9abbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. long-term mortgage rates are near historically low levels, with the average on the benchmark 30-year loan falling this week to its lowest level since November...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see opening on economy, risk cheering recession...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4a0e49f91c6043119e8b4ba4c510ae31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROLE, Iowa (AP) — Campaigning under the stifling August sun, Joe Biden assailed President Donald Trump's trade war with China, accusing him of squandering a strong economy and putting Americans'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female backers sell his message...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2f5a348dca974cb79526fd2a7edf5894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — President Donald Trump's campaign is rallying and training a corps of female defenders, mindful that Trump's shaky standing with women could sink his hopes of reelection...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women open fires on LA Skid Row; 4 injured...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190822204643-hm297</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-SHOOTING/SKIDROW:Four people wounded in Los Angeles Skid Row shooting, female suspect at large</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NBC Sports Pro Football Talk' turns into Trump bash-fest...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/22/chris-simms-uses-nbc-sports-pro-football-talk-to-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC Sports Pro Football Talk turned into a venue for bashing President Trump and conservatives when Mike Florio and Chris Simms said they had to expose “hypocritical sports fans” and media personalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor, who went to school with Kavanaugh, sues HUFFPOST...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/news/politics/2019/08/22/mississippi-man-sues-huffington-post-over-story-brett-kavanaugh-illegal-drugs-party-david-kennedy/2078341001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawsuit says that claims that Mississippi professor, then a student, helped supply illegal drugs were "outrageously false and defamatory."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Kicks Off Massive War Games, Unveils Russian Missile System...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-kicks-off-massive-war-games-unveils-homemade-russian-missile-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iranian Revolutionary Guard Corps' ground forces kicked off a "massive" set of war drills Thursday as the country unveiled its own version of the S-300.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/ci38996632/executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.0 Mag Quake Shakes Death Valley...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/50-earthquake-strikes-inyo-county-usgs-says/5486495/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A preliminary-magnitude 5.0 earthquake struck Inyo County, centered in the region that experienced two major temblors in early July, the U.S. Geological Survey said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Guitars. Buy Rocker's Childhood Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/forget-guitars-buy-rocker-childhood-202456158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why would you buy Bob Dylan, Kurt Cobain or Tom Petty's childhood homes? The new owners explain how they're trying to keep legacies alive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims' Lawyer Claims Epstein Was Murdered...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9757129/jeffrey-epstein-did-not-commit-suicide-murdered-lawyer-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAWYER for Jeffrey Epstein’s victims says he has obtained new information that suggests the billionaire paedo did NOT commit suicide but was murdered. Spencer Kuvin, who accurately predicte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Nazi salute video stirs reminders of dark Orange County history...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nazi-salute-video-stirs-reminders-of-dark-history-in-increasingly-diverse-orange-county/ar-AAGbezv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President kills plan to cut billions in foreign aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/22/white-house-backs-off-foreign-aid-cuts-1472130</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers objected to the plan, complaining that it would hurt foreign aid programs while also jeopardizing the massive budget deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein to be arraigned on new charges weeks before trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7384531/Harvey-Weinstein-arraigned-NEW-charges-Manhattan-Criminal-Court-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson for the Manhattan District Attorney's Office said that Weinstein's appearance has been scheduled for Monday, August 26 , and he will be called at 9:30am</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Doing housework could substantially lower risk of 'early death'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/doing-housework-could-substantially-lower-risk-of-early-death-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doing light physical activity such as cooking or washing dishes each day is enough to substantially lower the risk of early death, a study suggests. Researchers say people can raise their chances o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Divided Over More Cuts...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/trump-economy-interest-rates-federal-reserve-split-on-next-move-2019-8-1028467749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffes move closer to endangered species protection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8839637123514ace82f80f526f2ff0e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — Nations around the world moved Thursday to protect giraffes as an endangered species for the first time, drawing praise from conservationists and scowls from some sub-Saharan African...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
