<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Many experts think Americans can ditch masks soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210513-why-many-covid-experts-think-americans-can-ditch-their-masks-soon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why many Covid experts think Americans can ditch their masks soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang sits atop mayoral field vying to revive battered NYC...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210513085243-ov3bq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK-ELECTION/MAYOR (PIX):Yang sits atop mayoral field vying to revive a battered New York City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges pushed anew for reparations for slavery, racism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ma-state-wire-philanthropy-slavery-race-and-ethnicity-education-bff4488c36de6c7beb3f7696da07d77d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — For Brown University students, the Ivy League college's next step in its yearslong quest to atone for its legacy of slavery is clear: Pay up. Nearly two decades after the Providence, Rhode Island, institution launched its much-lauded reckoning, undergraduate students this spring &lt;a href="https://www...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach preparing for possible Trump indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook/2021/05/13/how-palm-beach-is-preparing-for-a-possible-trump-indictment-492836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And a meeting today will tell us how far apart the parties are on infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communal violence erupts in cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/12/middleeast/israel-palestine-violence-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Israeli military and Palestinian militants in Gaza exchange deadly airstrikes and rocket bombardments, rioting and violent clashes have also swept through several Israeli cities between Arab and Jewish citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Greene aggressively confronts Ocasio-Cortez, causing congresswoman to raise security concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/rep-greene-aggressively-confronts-rep-ocasio-cortez-causing-new-york-congresswoman-to-raise-security-concerns/ar-BB1gG3bZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (Ga.) followed Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) off the House floor and accused her of supporting “terrorists and antifa.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$365 BILLION WIPED OFF CRYPTO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/13/bitcoin-btc-price-falls-after-tesla-stops-car-purchases-with-crypto.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk said Tesla would suspend car purchases using bitcoin, wiping off billions of dollars of value from the cryptocurrency market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uruguay, once a corona model, struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/uruguay-once-a-coronavirus-model-struggles-against-a-deadly-wave/ar-BB1gFfjG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South America leads the world in new cases and deaths per capita. Uruguay leads South America in both.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETBLUE passenger who blew nose into blanket faces $10,500 fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-maskless-airline-passenger-blew-his-nose-into-a-blanket-he-now-faces-a-2410500-fine/ar-BB1gFnid?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest fines come under the Federal Aviation Administration's "zero-tolerance policy" for passengers who disobey flight crew instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI learns to type on phone like humans...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2021-05-ai-humans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Touchscreens are notoriously difficult to type on. Since we can't feel the keys, we rely on the sense of sight to move our fingers to the right places and check for errors, a combination of tasks that is difficult to accomplish simultaneously. To really understand how people type on touchscreens, researchers at Aalto University and the Finnish Center for Artificial Intelligence (FCAI) have created the first artificial intelligence model that predicts how people move their eyes and fingers while typing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O opens up about coping with depression: 'Don't wallow in your low'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/michelle-obama-opens-coping-depression-171708137.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On 'The Late Show With Stephen Colbert,' former First Lady Michelle Obama talked about how she has dealt with anxiety and depression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL NOT PAY RANSOM</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210512195700-2wvda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PRODUCTS/COLONIALPIPELINE-RANSOM (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Colonial Pipeline has no plan to pay ransom to hackers -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 rockets fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/latest-news/around-1500-rockets-fired-towards-israel-from-gaza-army/news-story/cb3d411ca736192a9b398d6d6a0eb086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theaustralian.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 1,500 rockets have been fired from Gaza into Israeli cities since hostilities escalated between Hamas militants and Israel earlier in the week, Israels army said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA BAILS ON BITCOIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/elon-musk-tesla-bitcoin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The problem is the cryptocurrency's environmental impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawl Over Line-Cutting...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article251353113.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video of the fight has made international news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob 'lynching of Arab' aired live on TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mob-lynching-of-arab-aired-live-on-israeli-tv/ar-BB1gFrB8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of a far-right Israeli mob attacking a man near Tel Aviv they believed to be an Arab was aired live on television Wednesday night, as the Israel-Palestinian conflict raged on. Demonstrations by far-right activists broke out Wednesday night in several cities, leading to clashes with police and sometimes Arab Israelis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governor Announces Million Dollar Lottery For Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ohio-governor-announces-a-million-dollar-lottery-for-adults-who-have-gotten-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio Governor Mike DeWine announced a million-dollar lottery for people who have gotten vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeGeneres to End Daytime Talk After 19 Years...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/ellen-degeneres-ending-daytime-talk-show-1234971355/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen DeGeneres is ending her long-running daytime talk show, Variety has confirmed. “The Ellen DeGeneres Show” will officially end after the upcoming 2021-22 season. DeGeneres has host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL, GAZA VIOLENCE ESCALATES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-africa-gaza-middle-east-violence-cb885f54369c7f4799aff0d8e421212c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Israel on Wednesday pressed ahead with a fierce military offensive in the Gaza Strip, killing as many as 10 senior Hamas military figures and toppling a pair of high-rise towers housing Hamas facilities in a series of airstrikes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Ailments Said to Be More Widespread Among U.S. Personnel...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/05/12/us/politics/havana-syndrome.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has begun more aggressively investigating episodes that left spies, diplomats, soldiers and others with brain injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE RESTARTS AFTER HACK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/colonial-pipeline-restarts-after-hack-but-supply-chain-wont-return-to-normal-for-a-few-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC says 28 blood clot cases, 3 deaths may be linked to J&amp;J...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/cdc-says-28-blood-clot-cases-3-deaths-may-be-linked-to-jj-covid-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women who were 30- to 39-years old accounted for the biggest risk group who developed rare blood clots following J&amp;J's Covid vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Admits Slave Labor Fuels China's Green Energy Supply Chain...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/kerry-admits-slave-labor-fuels-chinas-green-energy-supply-chain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden administration climate envoy John Kerry admitted before Congress on Wednesday that slave labor plagues the globe's green energy supply chain, potentially complicating the administration's efforts to source materials from top human rights abusers like China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE WILL NOT PAY RANSOM</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joewalsh/2021/05/12/colonial-pipeline-reportedly-wont-pay-hacker-ransom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colonial, which normally carries almost half of the East Coast’s gasoline supply, hopes to restore data from a backup instead of paying off hackers, the Washington Post reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of Dying: $20,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/dying-america-funerals-cost-5bb4dc9e-797d-4ffd-94a5-39b8ac953bb9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average cost of funerals and end-of-life care is nearly $20,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady 'fearful' of what comes after football...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/11/tom-brady-a-little-fearful-of-what-comes-after-football/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seven-time Super Bowl champion, in a new podcast interview, discussed the latter half of his football career, and what lies ahead when he finally decides to walk away from the game for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Docs Show Police Charged Thousands For Petty Violations...</title>
      <link>https://mtracey.substack.com/p/new-documents-show-police-charged</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mtracey.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In March and April of last year, drastic emergency measures were imposed by federal, state, and local government authorities for the stated purpose of curbing the spread of COVID-19. By March 16, 2020, all states had declared a State of Emergency, and by April 7 all states except four had imposed a “Stay at Home” order of some kind. Counties and municipalities also decreed their own separate COVID-related orders. As usual in the US, the details greatly varied by jurisdiction — some measures were far more stringent than others. But in general, a new legal regimen had taken hold across the country, in the name of combatting what was described as a once-in-a-lifetime public health crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools ditch student mask requirements in growing numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcax.com/2021/05/12/schools-ditch-student-mask-requirements-in-growing-numbers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debates have been emotional and highly divisive around the country, in some cases leading to the involvement of police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS WHACKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/11/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The selling intensified after the S&amp;P 500 fell below Tuesday's low, a level traders were watching closely because of the intraday rebound one day ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gasoline pipeline shutdown tests Biden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-government-and-politics-cdfa22ac10a52a07fefbe30de9b88472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cyberattack last week on a primary gasoline pipeline has created new political and economic risks for the Biden administration, which is working to keep the fuel flowing as prices spike. Officials laid out plans Wednesday to address transportation issues and price pressures after ransom-seeking hackers last week shut down the Colonial Pipeline, which delivers about 45% of the East Coast's gas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE WILL NOT PAY RANSOM</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2021/05/12/gas-shortage-colonial-pipeline-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fuel prices creep up and states of emergency are now in place in Florida, North Carolina, Georgia and Virginia in the aftermath of the Colonial Pipeline cyberattack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS: Lynchings, right-wing riots...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/right-wing-rioters-smash-windows-of-arab-owned-businesses-in-bat-yam-667993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Riots spread across several cities throughout Israel with mixed Arab and Jewish populations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bikini-clad Florida woman claims cops called by someone 'jealous her body looked good'...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2021/05/12/bikini-clad-florida-woman-claims-cops-were-called-by-someone-jealous-that-her-body-looked-good/#//</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman arrested on a disorderly intoxication charge claims the only reason that the cops were called while she was at a hotel pool was because the manager saw her in a bikini and was “jealous that her body looked good,” according to the Ocala Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain chip allows paralyzed man to write...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210512-mind-over-matter-brain-chip-allows-paralysed-man-to-write</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mind over matter: brain chip allows paralysed man to write</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA driver arrested after being seen riding in backseat...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/tesla-driver-arrested-after-being-seen-riding-in-backseat-on-bay-area-freeway-chp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A motorist was arrested after an officer observed him in the backseat of a Tesla traveling on a San Francisco Bay Area freeway, the California Highway Patrol said. Param Sharma, 25, was arrested fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Into Philly!</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/12/gasoline-shortage-creeping-into-philly-region-delaware-shell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gas shortage appears to be creeping into the Philadelphia area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive resort wants to turn sewage into snow...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/az-state-wire-business-lifestyle-wastewater-e7b9bf2dcef9dc4a5c2c13cb23b634e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exclusive Montana resort wants to turn sewage into snow so that its rich and famous members can ski its slopes in a winter season that’s shrinking because of climate change. The Yellowstone Club— a ski and golf resort just north of Yellowstone National Park that counts Bill Gates, Justin Timberlake and Jessica Biel among its members— has asked the Montana Department of Environmental Quality for a permit to allow it to use wastewater for snowmaking operations on its ski slopes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TYSON blames underperforming roosters for chicken shortage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/12/tyson-blames-underperforming-roosters-for-us-chicken-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Underperforming roosters that aren’t producing as many chicks as expected are partly to blame for the US poultry shortage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in flames at LA homeless encampments a growing crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/24-fires-day-surge-flames-120009728.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the three years since the Los Angeles Fire Department began tracking them, fires related to homeless camps have more than doubled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opioid-related overdose deaths soar among Blacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/opioids-race-and-ethnicity-coronavirus-pandemic-health-72819bfb2c6eed9760bdd4a91a0ffe67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — While there was a slight increase in the overall number of confirmed and suspected opioid-related drug overdose deaths in Massachusetts in 2020 amid the coronavirus pandemic, overdose deaths among Black men soared by almost 70%, state health officials said Wednesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent clashes between Israeli and Palestinian protesters in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/2872083/israeli-palestinians-violently-clash-nyc-protests-erupt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAELI and Palestinian protesters violently clashed in New York City on Tuesday as demonstrations erupted across the US and cops struggled to separate the warring crowds. Scuffles broke out outsid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF KILLS HAMAS COMMANDERS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210512123247-s5sah</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-Senior Hamas commander killed as Israel strikes Gaza, Palestinians fire rockets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effort to oust Netanyahu stalls during crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/lapid-bennett-coalition-talks-stall-netanyahu-4554c851-c86b-48df-a3ad-efbde94c835f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the crisis continues, it could be impossible to reach a coalition deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Inside Nasty Battle Between Silicon Valley and Journalism...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/05/tech-vs-journalism-silicon-valley-reporters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silicon Valley feels picked on by “woke” journalists “who can’t code.” Reporters feel picked on by petty zillionaires with anger-management problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's Just Not A Challenge Anymore'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/ellen-degeneres-show-end-1234951571/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen DeGeneres is signing off. Daytime’s most recognizable face has decided her upcoming season, the show’s nineteenth, will be the last. The decision, which fell to DeGeneres, is said to have bee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mice 'raining' from sky as 'biblical plague' sweeps Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/horrifying-video-shows-mice-raining-24090384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both dead and live mice are seen falling to the ground in a terrifying clip after a silo was being cleaned out on farmland, with the rodents continuing to fall out of the pump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay 'BACHELOR' says he was blackmailed over nudes before coming out...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/features/colton-underwood-the-bachelor-netflix-1234970331/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colton Underwood didn’t plan on ever telling the world that he was gay. After all, he’d starred as “The Bachelor” in 2019 to scout for a wife on national television, searching for love among 30 asp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN more opinionated, emotional. Can it still be 'most trusted name in news'?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-new-CNN-is-more-opinionated-and-emotional-16171187.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the first presidential debate of the 2020 general election came to a close last fall,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She's hero': Liz down but not out in Wyoming...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210512045237-zlshu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CONGRESS/CHENEY-WYOMING (PIX):'She's a hero': Liz Cheney down but not out in Wyoming after crossing Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 in 4 Stations Dry in Southern Cities...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/three-four-gas-stations-dry-134459308.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- More than three-quarters of gasoline stations in some southern U.S. cities have run out of gasoline as a massive pipeline shutdown stretches into a fifth day.In Spartanburg, South Carolina, 78% of outlets were out of gasoline, while Pensacola, Florida, and Charlotte, North Carolina, had 73% and 71% outage rates, respectively, according to data from retail tracker GasBuddy.About 65% of filling stations in Norfolk, Virginia, have sold out of gasoline, the data showed.Florida cities south of the panhandle, where most of the state’s population lives, are “looking good” as far as gasoline supplies are concerned, GasBuddy analyst Patrick DeHaan said.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney Declares War on Trump Moments After Ouster...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cheney-declares-war-on-trump-moments-after-her-ouster-will-do-all-i-can-to-ensure-he-never-gets-near-the-oval-office-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After House Republicans voted to remove Rep. Liz Cheney (R-WY) as chair of the conference, the lawmaker pledged to ensure Donald Trump would never get "near the Oval Office" again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if America's falling fertility rate isn't reversible?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/982103/doomloop-falling-fertility-rate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why America is powerless to reverse its plummeting fertility rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: 200 Workers At NJ Hindu Temple Forced Into Manual Labor $1 An Hour!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/05/11/robbinsville-baps-hindu-temple-lawsuit-manual-labor-human-trafficking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agents raided the sprawling site of a Hindu temple Tuesday morning in Robbinsville, just east of Trenton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Computer Broke Human Body...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3dda7/how-the-personal-computer-broke-the-human-body</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades before 'Zoom fatigue' broke our spirits, the so-called computer revolution brought with it a world of pain previously unknown to humankind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors fear vaccines messing with mammograms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/doctors-fear-covid-19-vaccines-are-messing-with-mammograms/ar-BB1gEfBO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radiologists have discovered a new side effect of COVID-19 vaccines: They make it more difficult to interpret mammogram results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS CANCEL CHENEY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9570721/Liz-Cheney-Republicans-remove-Wyoming-representative-leadership.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republicans planted themselves firmly in the camp of Trump when they removed Rep. Liz Cheney from their leadership team in a closed-door meeting in the basement of the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: COVID In Penile Tissue, May Lead To Erectile Dysfunction...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/virility-the-virus-covid-found-in-penile-tissue-may-even-lead-to-erectile-dysfunction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have, for the first time ever, discovered traces of COVID-19 within penile tissue. They say it may even lead to erectile dysfunction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-liner Ahmadinejad again seeks to be Iran president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-2b0497dfd2773eaa39c719cc91d10bbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's former hard-line President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad registered Wednesday to run again for the Islamic Republic's presidency, raising the possibility that the populist leader who rapidly advanced Tehran's nuclear program to challenge the West could return to the country's top civilian post...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS TOPS $3/GALLON</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/national-average-for-gasoline-tops-3-a-gallon-amid-pipeline-shutdown-rush-to-buy-in-southeast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colonial Pipeline is expected to make a full restart decision by the end of the day on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION SURGES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/consumer-price-index-april-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAKE: No greater offense than honesty in today's GOP...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/553034-flake-no-greater-offense-than-honesty-in-todays-republican-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Sen. Jeff Flake (R-Ariz.) is calling out GOP lawmakers for their plan to oust Rep. Liz Cheney (R-Wy.) from the party’s leadership in the House, arguing that “today there is no greater offense than honesty” among Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Republicans threaten to form new party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/553037-dozens-of-influential-republicans-threaten-to-form-new-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of Republicans are planning to call for reforms amid escalating divisions within their party, and threaten to form a separate group if GOP members do not break away from former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami appoints chief heat officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/facing-rising-temperatures-miami-appoints-chief-heat-officer/ar-BB1gDUd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Gilbert, the city’s new chief heat officer, says she will put together a task force of experts to address the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLONIAL Faces Deadline to Decide on Hacked Pipeline Restart...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gas-stations-run-dry-pipeline-100859225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Colonial Pipeline Co. told federal officials it will know by late Wednesday whether it’s safe to restart gasoline and diesel flows that have been on hold since criminal hackers targeted the company last week.The promise comes as frustration grows among political leaders over scant details about when the biggest North American fuel pipeline will recover, while fuel shortages spread rapidly across the South and East. U.S. Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm said that even if Colonial can restart on Wednesday, it’ll take days longer to “ramp up operations.” With a full restoration of the pipeline system potentially taking weeks, U.S. retail gasoline jumped to the politically sensitive level of $3 a gallon for the first time in six years.Facing increasing pressure, the White House announced several measures Tuesday to blunt the growing crisis that threatens to hobble the post-pandemic economic recovery. The Biden administration will give a House briefing on the cyberattack at 6 p.m. Washington time on Wednesday.“This is something that demands really serious federal attention,” Florida Governor Ron DeSantis said on Tuesday, prior to declaring a state of emergency. “The U.S. government needs to be involved, they need to help mitigate this. My fear is, you have these gas shortages, it’s going to cause a lot of problems for people.”The Colonial pipeline is the most important conduit for distributing gasoline, diesel and jet fuel in the U.S., connecting Gulf Coast refineries to population centers from Atlanta to New York and beyond. Each day, it ships about 2.5 million barrels (105 million gallons), an amount that exceeds the entire oil consumption of Germany.The national average retail gasoline price rose to $3.008 a gallon, the first time it’s exceeded $3 since October 2014, according to auto club AAA data on Wednesday. The premium for wholesale gasoline in the New York area reached its widest in three months.The vital economic lifeline has been shut since late Friday, prompting a run on filling stations by panicked motorists in several states. In addition to Florida, Virginia and North Carolina are under states of emergency. U.S. average retail gasoline prices have risen to their highest since late 2014 due to the disruption, almost touching $3 a gallon. That could add to broader inflationary pressures as commodity prices from timber to copper also surge.The situation across the southeastern states is “rapidly deteriorating,” Brad Jenkins, a senior vice president at truck-stop owner Pilot, said in an email.The White House relaxed some environmental rules across 12 states and Washington D.C. to help bring in more fuel, even as some Gulf Coast refiners were forced to curtail output to cope with logjams of fuel they can’t send to eastern markets. The Department of Transportation also announced initial steps that could permit foreign tankers to transport gasoline and diesel to East Coast ports.The Wednesday deadline on a decision over the pipeline’s restart was given by Colonial Chief Executive Officer Joe Blount to Granholm. The energy secretary said she’s been in regular contact with the CEO in recent days to track the company’s progress in neutralizing the ransomware attack.“By the end of business tomorrow, Colonial will be in a position to make the full restart decision,” she said.“We have been providing daily and sometimes twice daily updates to our shippers, and have been in close contact with law enforcement and federal agencies to relay information on our restoration efforts,” Colonial’s media relations office said earlier in the day. “We will continue to keep all of our stakeholders informed and appreciate the outpouring of support we have received throughout the industry.”Even when the pipeline is restored to full service, however, it’ll take about two weeks for gasoline stored in Houston to reach East Coast filling stations, according to the most recent schedule sent to shippers. For diesel and jet fuel, the transit time is even longer -- about 19 days -- because they are heavier and move more slowly.More than four days into the crisis, Colonial has only managed to restart a small segment of the pipeline as a stopgap measure. Meanwhile, fuel shortages continued to worsen. In Atlanta, 20% of filling stations were dry by Tuesday afternoon, according to retail-fuel tracker GasBuddy.Two of the nation’s largest truck-stop owners --- Love’s Travel Stops &amp; Country Stores Inc. and TravelCenters of America Inc. -- confirmed that fuel is scarce is some states. Both companies said they’re taking extraordinary measures to replenish tanks.The Biden administration issued an order on Sunday extending the amount of time truck drivers can spend behind the wheel when transporting fuel across 17 states and the District of Columbia. On Tuesday evening, the Transportation Department said 10 states could allow heavier-than-normal truck loads of gasoline and other fuels.Federal transportation regulators also took the first step toward waiving the 101-year-old Jones Act that prohibits foreign-flagged and -staffed ships from hauling products from one U.S. port to another. Fuel traders have so far redirected at least one international cargo of gasoline, and another of diesel, toward the U.S. East Coast, according to shipping data compiled by Bloomberg.Gasoline isn’t the only oil-derived product under threat. In an effort to bolster jet-fuel inventories, Southwest Airlines Co. has begun flying supplies to Nashville, Tennessee, and other cities. So far, no Southwest flights have been affected by the pipeline closure; rather, the airline said it’s “actively managing” fuel stockpiles.United Airlines Holdings Inc. loaded extra fuel on flights to preserve local supplies in places like Baltimore and Greenville-Spartanburg, South Carolina. Problems are “relatively minor so far,” however, Chief Executive Officer Scott Kirby said at the Resources for the Future Forum.What BloombergNEF Is SayingBloombergNEF expects additional supply this week to come primarily from storage inventories, increased East Coast refinery run, other pipelines and shipments from Canada. Cargoes from Europe could also help alleviate lingering shortages next week.-- Anastacia Dialynas, BNEF analystRead the full report here.The Environmental Protection Agency moved to allow the sale of gasoline that doesn’t satisfy requirements meant to help combat smog in certain areas. An initial order allowed the sale of conventional gasoline in areas where reformulated gasoline is required across Maryland, Pennsylvania, Virginia and the District of Columbia. A second order went further by waiving low-volatility requirements governing conventional and reformulated gasoline in those areas, as well as nine other states.Emergency shipments of gasoline and diesel from Texas are already on the way to Atlanta and other southeastern cities via trucks, and at least two Gulf Coast refineries began trimming output amid expectations that supplies will begin backing up in the nation’s oil-refining nexus.(Updates with vessel diversions in 17th paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Used Male Doll in Joke. Now Accused of Sexual Harassment...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/12/she-used-a-male-doll-in-a-joke-now-shes-accused-of-sexual-harassment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Park Na-rae, a comedian, grabbed a male doll, placed its plastic arm between its legs and made a suggestive remark.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
