<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hospital staff must swear off TYLENOL, TUMS to get religious exemption...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/09/hospital-staff-must-swear-off-tylenol-tums-to-get-religious-vaccine-exemption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospital CEO aims to educate staff on the full scope of what they're claiming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama endorses Trudeau in Canadian election...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/obama-endorses-trudeau-in-the-canadian-election/600097815/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama endorsed Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau on Thursday in the Canadian election, calling him an effective leader in a rare endorsement of a candidate in a Canadian election by a former American president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Outraged by U.S. Nuclear Sub Deal With Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/france-is-outraged-by-u-s-nuclear-submarine-deal-with-australia/ar-AAOvXGS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — France reacted with fury on Thursday to President Biden’s announcement of a deal to help Australia deploy nuclear-powered submarines, calling it a “unilateral, brutal, unpredictable decision” that resembled the rash and sudden policy shifts common during the Trump administration. The angry words from Jean-Yves Le Drian, the foreign minister, in an interview with Franceinfo radio, followed an official statement from him and Florence...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese state-run newspaper claims warships could 'soon' be near Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2021/09/15/chinese-state-run-newspaper-claims-warships-could-soon-near-hawaii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newspaper said warships could be on their way following claims that the US Navy challenged international waters near Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body composting 'green' alternative to burial, cremation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-lifestyle-religion-environment-and-nature-health-014a5d0bc4f4039181d9863527334ebe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAFAYETTE, Colo. (AP) — In a suburban Denver warehouse tucked between an auto repair shop and a computer recycling business, Seth Viddal is dealing with life and death. He and one of his employees have built a “vessel” they hope will usher in a more environmentally friendly era of mortuary science that includes the natural organic reduction of human remains, also known as body composting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCID Beats TESLA, Going 520 Miles on Charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Lucid-Beats-Tesla-in-Range-Going-520-Miles-on-a-16464007.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lucid Motors, a startup automaker, has unseated Tesla, the dominant maker of electric...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key senators eye exits ahead of '22 midterms:...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/16/politics/senators-eye-exits-midterms/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Thune, the No. 2 Senate Republican, is struggling with a crucial decision: Whether to ask South Dakota voters for six more years in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FOX Exec Set to Clean Up ABC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/former-fox-exec-peter-rice-is-supposed-to-clean-up-abc-news-but-angry-staffers-say-hes-failing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney exec Peter Rice had promised to address the network’s cultural issues, but angered staffers said they now feel abandoned by him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin says 'several dozen' in inner circle test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/16/europe/russia-putin-coronavirus-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday morning that "not just one or two but several dozen people" from his inner circle had contracted coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia ramps up pressure on foreign tech firms on election eve...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210916154528-e5w1s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-ELECTION/IT (PIX):Russia ramps up pressure on foreign tech firms on eve of election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell raises ethics questions after Fed presidents' multimillion-dollar investments...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/fed-chief-powell-orders-ethics-review-after-multimillion-dollar-trades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed Chair Powell directed staff to review the central bank's rules after filings showed officials made multimillion-dollar trades in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small agency, big job: Biden tasks OSHA with vaccine mandate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-henry-mcmaster-f33acd986ad5045e48088a832c6f9903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Occupational Safety and Health Administration doesn’t make many headlines. Charged with keeping America’s workplaces safe, it usually busies itself with tasks such as setting and enforcing standards for goggles, hardhats and ladders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objects at Solar System Edge Influenced by Something Mysterious?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qj8qeb/objects-at-the-solar-systems-edge-are-being-influenced-by-something-mysterious</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery of hundreds of new objects in the outer solar system confirms weird gravitational effects that could be caused by “Planet Nine.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought Haves, Have-Nots Test How to Share Water in West...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2021-09-16/drought-haves-have-nots-test-how-to-share-water-in-the-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oregon farmers who grow 60% of the world’s carrot seed have been without irrigation water for weeks as drought ravages the American West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone served Capitol riot suit during live interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/roger-stone-capitol-riot-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone, a longtime friend of former president Donald Trump, was served a lawsuit related to the Jan. 6 Capitol Riot Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK keeps researching own harms -- and burying findings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/facebook-keeps-researching-its-own-harms-e2-80-94-and-burying-the-findings/ar-AAOvQpK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of leaked internal reports shows Facebook knows far more than it lets on. That’s by design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like a sunset' -- Developers propose Hollywood office tower with bold design...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/home-and-garden/like-a-sunset-e2-80-94-developers-propose-a-hollywood-office-tower-with-a-bold-sculptural-design/ar-AAOvWyb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Developers are proposing a visually stunning $500-million office tower on Sunset Boulevard in the heart of Hollywood called the Star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS TURN SOUR</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow slipped Thursday despite better-than-expected August retail sales, as the latest weekly jobless claims report pointed to a mixed economic picture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes changing porn...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/deepfakes-have-disturbing-implications-for-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artifical Intelligence has been heralded as ‘the future’ for as long as I can remember. The excitement is understandable: scientists may one-day be able to create an AI that is so efficient it can substitute the manual work of humans, replacing doctors, engineers and even journalists. But professional occupations are not the only area AI [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring utility bills alarm Europe, raise fears for winter...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-prices-d783b16fe0a5a2c87e909b15822253ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Wholesale prices for gas and electricity are surging across Europe, raising the prospect of increases in already-high utility bills and further pain for people who have taken a financial hit from the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Happiness Benefits of Walking...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/09/happiness-walking-pilgrimage/620075/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What I learned about transcendence from a very boring 100-mile trek</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gray wolf may be re-listed as endangered after Trump removed protections...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/572555-fish-and-wildlife-service-to-review-trump-era-removal-of-gray-wolf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Interior Department will review the Endangered Species Act status of the American gray wolf after the Trump administration delisted it as endangered, the department announced Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 56% Americans Can Name All 3 Branches Of Govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/knowledge-the-first-amendment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual poll of more than 1,000 people finds 56 percent of Americans are now capable of naming all three branches of government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Furious; 'Stabbed in Back'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/french-furious-at-biden-for-cutting-them-out-of-submarine-deal/ar-AAOvpka</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s top diplomat unleashed a stream of invective against President Joe Biden after the U.S. and the U.K. announced a new security alliance for the Pacific region which will cost the French defense industry some A$90 billion (56 billion euros).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piers Morgan Joins NEWS CORP...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3674043/piers-morgan-the-sun-news-corp-tv-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIERS Morgan is joining The Sun and News Corp in a global deal that’s a “bigger comeback than Cristiano Ronaldo.” Britain’s powerhouse journalist is returning to his roots and com…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 1 In 6 Will Quit Job If Not Allowed To Work From Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/remote-work-in-person-policies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;44 percent know at least one person who has quit their job or is planning to quit because their boss is requiring them to restart in-person work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure grows to prescribe fresh produce as medical care...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/16/food-medicine-covid-health-care-511169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure is growing to prescribe fresh produce as part of medical care. Will the health care system respond?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals in West struggle to find beds for critically ill amid surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/idaho-hospitals-west-face-covid-surge-struggle-transfer-patients-rcna1997</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idaho has allowed its hospitals to establish crisis standards of care, which means doctors can triage patients dependent on bed space availability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan defense minister draws red line in island dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/15/asia/japan-defense-minister-kishi-china-interview-intl-hnk-ml/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan is drawing a red line around an island chain also claimed by China, pushing back at Beijing's increasingly aggressive military posturing, and setting the stage for a potential showdown between the region's two biggest powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada's tight election heads into final stretch...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/canada-s-tight-election-heads-into-final-stretch/ar-AAOuQha</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions are mounting four days ahead of Canada's legislative elections as Liberal Prime Minister Justin Trudeau called on citizens to "vote strategically" to block a Conservative surge as he faces a potential defeat at the hands of rookie Tory leader Erin O'Toole. According to polls, the two major parties that have ruled Canada since its 1867 confederation are in a statistical dead heat, each garnering the support of 32 percent of respondents,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: Retail Sales Unexpectedly Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/retail-sales-unexpectedly-rise-0point7percent-in-august-vs-expected-decline-of-0point8percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists surveyed by Dow Jones expected retail sales to decline by 0.8% in August and for initial jobless claims to total 320,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jay-Z NFT Feud Spotlights Legal Peril in Hot Investment Trend...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/jay-z-s-nft-feud-spotlights-legal-peril-in-hot-investment-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay-Z’s NFT Feud Spotlights Legal Peril in Hot Investment Trend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutal Realities of Supply Chain Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-09-16/supply-chain-issues-shortages-and-delayed-shipping-through-2023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Logistics managers are battling the pandemic, a labor shortage, and huge demand to get goods to your front door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In showdown over masks in K-12 schools, who will blink first?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/education/572173-in-the-showdown-over-masks-in-k-12-schools-who-will-blink-first</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unless the federal government or courts take action, state bans on masks will place schoolchildren with disabilities at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Digital Privacy Reshaping Internet...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/16/the-battle-for-digital-privacy-is-reshaping-the-internet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — Apple introduced a pop-up window for iPhones in April that asks people for their permission to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Merkel prepares to leave office, many think Germany 'golden age' over...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/germanys-golden-age-is-over-most-europeans-think-as-merkel-leaves.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Europeans believe the Germany's "golden age" is over just as Chancellor Merkel prepares to leave office — including a majority of Germans, a poll shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin keeps Washington guessing on what he wants...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/572504-manchin-keeps-washington-guessing-on-what-he-wants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight over Democrats' $3.5 trillion spending bill is reviving one of Washington’s most perennial questions: What does Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) want?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 101, she's still hauling lobsters with no plans to stop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-oddities-maine-61b5c7bd559a5636e840c206cb990a32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCKLAND, Maine (AP) — When Virginia Oliver started trapping lobster off Maine’s rocky coast, World War II was more than a decade in the future, the electronic traffic signal was a recent invention and few women were harvesting lobsters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CRY MACHO' Test: Will Clint Eastwood's Fans Choose Theaters or Streaming?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cry-macho-will-clint-eastwoods-loyal-fans-choose-theaters-or-hbo-max/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eastwood's films have historically attracted older moviegoers from red states, but his core audience might take the streaming option this time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit's historic female genital cutting case is in limbo...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2021/09/15/detroit-female-genital-mutilation-case-doctor-jumana-nagarwala/8343451002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government is seeking to revive its historic female genital mutilation case with new charges. But the defense is pushing back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea release images of missiles being launched from train...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/north-korea-releases-terrifying-images-24995680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The images come after North Korea launched two deadly ballistic missiles towards Japan on Wednesday. Intelligences agencies are investigating the testing but no one was harmed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump still wins elections  -- for Dems?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/newsletter/2021-09-15/national-lessons-from-californias-recall-essential-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recall campaign offered insights that will inform strategies over the next 14 months. Here are three:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Newsom defeated recall: Early leads in suburbs, overwhelming margins in big cities...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-defeated-recall-early-leads-172700965.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of the more than 9.1 million votes tabulated as of early Wednesday, nearly 64% were in favor of keeping Gov. Gavin Newsom in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, Australia, UK unveil new security partnership as Beijing expands military, influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/us-uk-australia-unveil-new-security-partnership-as-china-expands-military.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new trilateral security partnership seeks to strengthen stability in the Indo-Pacific region as China expands its military might and influence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gymnasts offer scathing assessment of FBI...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/572452-us-gymnasts-offer-scathing-assessment-of-fbi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star U.S. gymnasts offered stark criticism Wednesday of the FBI's handling of its investigation into sexual assault and harassment in the U.S. gymnastics program, prompting criticism from lawmakers of the Department of Justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Clinically Dead For 45 Minutes Miraculously Brought Back To Life...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/09/14/baltimore-county-woman-is-brought-back-to-life-after-a-medical-miracle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Baltimore County woman is calling it a medical miracle after being brought back to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German police responding to possible synagogue threat... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/german-police-say-they-are-responding-possible-threat-synagogue-2021-09-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Germany said they had received information about a possible threat to a synagogue in the western town of Hagen and had put appropriate measures in place to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENDEAVOR's Growing Pains...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/endeavor-ipo-ari-emanuel-public-1235065405/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Endeavor defied its critics and the odds by successfully pulling off a public offering in April, but the company — a hodgepodge of live-events brands and talent representation — is facing major obs…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-national security officials funded by big tech claim antitrust laws would hurt USA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/15/ex-national-security-officials-claim-antitrust-laws-would-hurt-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former officials argue the measures could undermine the US in its competition with China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major NFT Marketplace Admits Employee Did Insider Trading...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxj43/major-nft-marketplace-admits-employee-used-insider-knowledge-to-profit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An OpenSea employee bought NFTs before they were promoted on the marketplace's homepage, which angered traders have compared to insider trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalio says if bitcoin really successful, regulators will 'kill it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/ray-dalio-says-if-bitcoin-is-really-successful-regulators-will-kill-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ray Dalio said regulators would ultimately take control of bitcoin if the cryptocurrency gains mainstream success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Australian fires boost carbon-capturing algae...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australian-fires-boosted-c02-carbon-171926968.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devastating Australian wildfires released twice as much climate-warming C02 than previously thought -- but also triggered vast algae blooms thousands of miles away that may have soaked up significant extra carbon, according to studies published Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Strategy Offers Republicans Warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/newsom-s-anti-trump-recall-strategy-offers-a-warning-for-2022-midterms/ar-AAOsJy0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN LEANDRO, Calif. — California basks in its clairvoyance. “The future happens here first,” says Gov. Gavin Newsom, calling his state “America’s coming attraction.” By emphatically turning back the effort to recall him from office, however, Mr. Newsom made clear that California’s cherished role presaging the politics of tomorrow was not as significant as another, larger factor in Tuesday’s results: the tribal politics of today. The first-term...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops face discipline for selfies with rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article254245798.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘If you want to take a photo, I’m not going to say no because we are always told to interact and keep the situation calm,’ one officer told investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER pushes for boosters...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pfizer-covid-vaccine-boosters-fda-approval-69ff9870-5e9a-4099-98ff-24085091cc7f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA's advisory committee is expected to review Pfizer's clinical trials on Friday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
