<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Brain Age' Stays Younger When Blood Pressure Optimal...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/brain-age-healthy-blood-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors say participants with high blood pressure had older, less healthy brains and a much higher risk of heart disease, stroke, and dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 90 rattlesnakes found under California home...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/more-90-rattlesnakes-found-under-california-house-n1281628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Sonoma County Reptile Rescue official said the number of snakes living in the foundation was likely because it is such a rocky area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biohackers at the gate: How DIY experimenters waged war on COVID...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biohackers-gate-untold-story-diy-090058088.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The untold story of how disruptors and biohackers behind this $1.8 billion robot company helped battle the pandemic and revolutionize America's diagnostics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers Warn Of Turkey Shortage Ahead Of Holidays...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/10/14/farmers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenyan mob lynches 'bloodthirsty vampire' child killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kenyan-mob-lynches-bloodthirsty-vampire-child-killer/ar-AAPyhBa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kenyan villagers on Friday lynched a man believed to be a "bloodthirsty vampire" child murderer, days after the self-confessed serial killer escaped from police custody, officials said. Police spokesman Bruno Shiosho told AFP they have launched a forensic investigation into the identity of the lynched man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A wary Beirut reels after deadly gun battle raises fears of renewed conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-wary-beirut-reels-after-deadly-gun-battle-raises-fears-of-renewed-conflict/ar-AAPyQwH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fighting between Hezbollah and other armed groups over the appointment of an investigative judge killed seven people and brought back memories of Lebanon's terrible civil war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden out to flex muscle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-travel-new-jersey-elections-048183f2439126d0165e585e66a151eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — First lady Jill Biden is set to campaign Friday for Democrats in governors' races in Virginia and New Jersey, her most overt foray into politics since arriving at the White House nine months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How people who quit are making ends meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/getting-by-in-the-great-resignation-how-people-who-quit-or-retired-are-making-ends-meet/ar-AAPvYe5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record number of workers are quitting or taking early retirement from jobs where they feel disrespected and burned out in what is being called "The Great Resignation." Here's how they are getting by financially.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORSCHE Electric Taycan Pulls Ahead of Iconic 911 in Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/porsche-s-electric-taycan-edges-past-iconic-911-sports-car</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porsche’s Electric Taycan Pulls Ahead of the Iconic 911 in Sales</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student test scores fall first time in national test's history...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/576870-student-test-scores-fall-for-first-time-in-national-tests-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Math and reading test scores for the country's 13-year-olds have dropped sharply in comparison to numbers from 2012 as some of the lowest scoring test takers fell the furthest behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big businesses siding against Texas in mandate fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/576853-big-businesses-are-siding-against-texas-in-mandate-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight over vaccine mandates between the White House and Texas Gov. Greg Abbott (R) is putting businesses in the middle. But many are picking the White House’s preferred policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today's Must-Have Amenity? A Little Green Space...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/15/todays-must-have-amenity-a-little-green-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move toward incorporating more outdoor spaces in luxury buildings was underway before the pandemic struck. But life in lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe's Other Obstacle in Virginia Race: Dem Apathy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/15/terry-mcauliffes-other-obstacle-in-virginia-race-democrats-apathy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. — Terry McAuliffe doesn’t do subtext well. So when Mr. McAuliffe appeared on “Morning Joe” on MSNBC this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Experts Sound Alarm on APPLE and EU Phone Scanning Plans...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/14/cybersecurity-experts-sound-alarm-on-apple-and-e-u-phone-scanning-plans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen prominent cybersecurity experts on Thursday criticized plans by Apple and the European Union to monitor people’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital life encroaches on 'quiet zone' refuge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/digital-life-encroaches-us-quiet-013451574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yvonne Wallech loves the digital respite and sense of community in her tiny US town, where cell phone service is effectively barred and outsiders come seeking the shelter of that quiet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tipping Point for Trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/22722357/dave-chappelle-the-closer-netflix-backlash-controversy-transphobic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chappelle’s latest Netflix special, The Closer, may be a tipping point for trans people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanted temporarily in post-Brexit Britain: 800 foreign butchers to slaughter 120,000 pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/wanted-temporarily-in-post-brexit-britain-800-foreign-butchers-to-slaughter-some-120000-pigs/ar-AAPxHed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shortage of slaughterhouse workers has created what Britain’s pig lobby calls its biggest crisis in over two decades, with roughly 120,000 pigs waiting to be slaughtered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses say morale has hit low...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/emotionally-physically-mentally-tired-e2-80-99-nurses-say-morale-has-hit-a-pandemic-low/ar-AAPyqfj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nurses repeatedly call themselves resilient but say they're hitting the limits of that strength. In interviews, they describe plummeting morale during the latest pandemic surge, marked by utter exhaustion and growing workloads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among South Florida doctor's mistakes: Removing fat instead of appendix...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article254947547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of surgical errors alleged in a state complaint, including misidentifying an appendix and a gallstone, led to a Coral Springs surgeon being restricted from laparoscopic surgeries by the Florida Board of Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College students struggle with mental health as pandemic drags on...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/College-students-struggle-with-mental-health-as-16534094.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People handed flowers to strangers on campus this week, and wrote encouraging notes in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eerie lights of nearby Chinese squid fleet keep Taiwan islanders on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Eerie-lights-of-nearby-Chinese-squid-fleet-keep-16534829.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MATSU, Taiwan - As dusk falls, green lights appear one by one along the horizon off...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY UNREST OVER COVID RULES</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/protests-blockades-greet-italy-covid-082537348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters gathered at Italian ports on Friday as the country braced for widespread disruption over new coronavirus requirements for workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adele releases soul-stirring comeback single 'EASY ON ME'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/adele-releases-soul-stirring-comeback-100103809.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British soul diva Adele on Friday released comeback single "Easy On Me", in which she shares with the world details of the traumatic six years she has endured since last releasing a record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER SUED OVER SAUDI SPIES ON PAYROLL...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/saudi-dissident-twitter-lawsuit-spies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prominent human rights activist is accusing Twitter of failing to protect him against Saudi spies inside the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Bill Clinton in hospital for infection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-california-university-of-california-university-of-california-irvine-cff527736edf82da0ac0d2bd84034cfb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former President Bill Clinton was admitted to a Southern California hospital Tuesday with an infection but he is “on the mend,” his spokesman said Thursday. Clinton, 75, was admitted to the University of California Irvine Medical Center on Tuesday evening for a non-COVID-related infection, Angel Ureña said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No More Martinis: Queen Advised to Give Up Daily Drinking...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2021/10/the-queen-advised-to-give-up-daily-drinking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the advice of her doctors, the 95-year-old will forgo her evening cocktail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema opposes?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-say-they-have-no-sense-of-what-kyrsten-sinema-wants-in-biden-s-safety-net-package-as-she-opposes-tax-hikes/ar-AAPxdCD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinema is fundraising abroad while talks around Biden's spending plan stall, partly over her opposition to corporate and individual tax hikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON Watkins Looks Like He's Prepping Bid for Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7e5jj/q-anon-ron-watkins-might-run-for-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ron Watkins, a prominent QAnon figure, appears to have filed a “statement of intent” to run for Congress with the Arizona Secretary of State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School leader tells teachers to balance Holocaust books with 'opposing' views...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/southlake-texas-holocaust-books-schools-rcna2965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top administrator with the Carroll Independent School District in Southlake, Texas, warned teachers about having one-sided books about the Holocaust in their classrooms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals debate their role as political activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/meet-the-press/news/evangelicals-debate-their-role-political-activists-trump-era-n1281422</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Meet the Press Reports”: White evangelical congregations are debating how closely to mix religion and politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WH:  'HIGH CLASS PROBLEMS'</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/white-house-inflation-supply-chain-woes-high-class-problems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House chief of staff Ron Klain endorsed former Obama administration economist Jason Furman's claim that the country's inflation, supply chain, and other economic problems only affect a small part of the U.S. population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Cop Fatally Shoots Her Ex-Girlfriend's New Lover, Wounds Ex...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/10/14/police-officer-shoots-ex-girlfriend-yvonne-wu-jamie-liang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources said Wu waited inside her ex-girlfriend's home, which they shared at one time. Wu allegedly opened fire when her ex arrived with another woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to let troops cast ballots over internet draws opposition...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2021/10/14/plan-to-let-troops-cast-ballots-over-the-internet-draws-opposition-from-security-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A provision included in a draft of the annual defense authorization bill would look into a new system for troops to cast their votes online instead of through mailed-in paper ballots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist sues newly-freed Bill Cosby over '90 hotel encounter...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-pennsylvania-lawsuits-new-jersey-fbbdffde36353380f075a902b6074f08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — A prominent Bill Cosby accuser filed suit Thursday against the actor over a 1990 hotel room encounter in Atlantic City, New Jersey, before the state's two-year window to file older sexual assault claims expires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sotomayor slams Supreme Court justices; 'Missing' diversity...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/sonia-sotomayor-says-supreme-court-justices-are-sorely-missing-diverse-experience-and-that-leaders-aren-t-paying-enough-attention/ar-AAPwRXK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sotomayor said the Supreme Court justices lack experience in legal areas such as civil rights and immigration, which greatly affect the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan 6 panel to recommend criminal contempt citation for Bannon...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/jan-6-committee-recommend-criminal-contempt-citation-trump-adviser-steve-n1281562</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The panel's chairman said that the vote comes after Bannon has refused to comply with a subpoena for documents and his testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy to Discharge All Sailors Refusing Jab -- Without Exemption...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/10/14/new-navy-guidance-will-discharge-sailors-refusing-covid-19-vaccination-without-exemption</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This story has been updated with additional information about the Navy vaccine mandate. All active-duty Navy personnel must be vaccinated by Nov. 28 or face separation, according to a Navy administrative message released Wednesday. Any active-duty Navy service members who do not get fully vaccinated or do not have an approved or pending exemption will …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly Discovered Bat Viruses Give Hints to Origins...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/newly-discovered-bat-viruses-give-hints-to-covid-s-origins/ar-AAPwqmZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the summer of 2020, half a year into the coronavirus pandemic, scientists traveled into the forests of northern Laos to catch bats that might harbor close cousins of the pathogen. In the dead of night, they used mist nets and canvas traps to snag the animals as they emerged from nearby caves, gathered samples of saliva, urine and feces, then released them back into the darkness. The fecal samples turned out to contain coronaviruses, which the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summers Slams Woke Fed for Risking Losing Control of Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/summers-slams-woke-fed-for-risking-losing-control-of-inflation/ar-AAPuq9I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Treasury Secretary Lawrence Summers castigated monetary policy makers in the U.S. and elsewhere for paying too much attention to social issues and not enough to the biggest risk to inflation since the 1970s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada buckles up for mass health-care firings...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/first-reading-buckle-up-for-the-mass-health-care-firings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle police staffing woes prompt emergency dispatch plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-police-seattle-0f3abe25a903c8695faa5117b5da8716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Seattle’s police department is sending detectives and non-patrol officers to respond to emergency calls because of a shortage of patrol officers that union leaders fear will become worse because of COVID-19 vaccine mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Craig Reveals He Dislikes Aggression of Hetero Spaces...</title>
      <link>https://www.out.com/celebs/2021/10/13/daniel-craig-loves-gay-bars-says-hes-sick-hetero-bars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.out.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater mystery on Canada's coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/travel/article/20211013-an-underwater-mystery-on-canadas-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of wooden stakes poking up from British Columbia's shoreline have smashed a long-held stereotype of Canada's First Nation people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MO gov vows criminal prosecution of reporter who found flaw in state website...</title>
      <link>https://missouriindependent.com/2021/10/14/missouri-governor-vows-criminal-prosecution-of-reporter-who-found-flaw-in-state-website/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;missouriindependent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missouri's governor promises to seek prosecution of a reporter and news outlet that discovered a privacy flaw in a state website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BOND' DOES GAY BARS:  Actor Craig Reveals He Dislikes Aggression of Hetero Spaces...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/oct/14/daniel-craig-says-he-goes-to-gay-bars-to-avoid-fights-at-straight-venues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bond star says he dislikes the aggression of hetero spaces, and gay bars were a good place to meet women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIDERS QB:  Open Up All NFL Private Texts, Emails!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/derek-carr-suggests-nfl-open-up-everything-in-team-correspondence-after-jon-gruden-resignation/ar-AAPw7p2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Vegas Raiders quarterback Derek Carr suggested in his first comments since Jon Gruden resigned that all communication from front office personnel and coaches be made available. Gruden resigned as head coach of the Raiders on Monday evening after a New York Times report that he'd sent hateful homophobic, racist and misogynistic emails over the course of a decade. The communication was found and subsequently leaked as part of the 10-month...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10,000 JOHN DEERE workers on strike after rejecting contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/10000-john-deere-workers-on-strike-after-rejecting-contract/ar-AAPw2gW?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The walkout is the latest by an emboldened labor movement and affects 14 plants in Iowa, Illinois, Kansas, Colorado and Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg building AI that sees, hears, and 'understands' everything we do...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/facebook-building-ai-sees-hears-25214407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social media giant reportedly wants to train its artificial intelligence to understand the world just like humans do, by feeding it video recordings from augmented reality glasses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic quickens GOP populism tilt from old pro-business brand...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/government/covid-quickens-gop-populism-tilt-old-pro-business-brand</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business groups and the companies they represent say vaccines and other measures are crucial to spurring the economic recovery. But many of their traditional allies—Republican pols—see it differently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARANDOS DOUBLES DOWN...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/ted-sarandos-dave-chappelle-defense-1235088647/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix Co-CEO Ted Sarandos sent a lengthy missive to the entire company following the mounting controversy around a new original special from comic Dave Chappelle. After addressing top leadership …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid becomes No. 1 killer of Americans age 35-54...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/coronavirus/1006016/covid-19-was-the-no-1-killer-of-americans-aged-35-to-54-last-month-and-no-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see an opening with vaccinated, frustrated Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/coronavirus/article254985632.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccinated Republicans have expressed rising levels of anger about unvaccinated Americans in voter focus groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shoplifting skyrockets in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/calls-for-change-as-shoplifting-skyrockets-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some New York City stores are responding to the increase in shoplifting by locking up inventory like aspirin, toothpaste and ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S to test burger created with 'Beyond Meat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/14/mcdonalds-to-test-mcplant-burger-created-with-beyond-meat-in-the-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald's will test the meatless McPlant burger created as part of its partnership with Beyond Meat in eight U.S. restaurants next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lurching Between Crisis and Complacency': Was This Last Covid Surge?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/14/lurching-between-crisis-and-complacency-was-this-our-last-covid-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a brutal summer surge, driven by the highly contagious Delta variant, the coronavirus is again in retreat. The United</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia marks pandemic high of infections, deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-russia-moscow-vladimir-putin-68b9c1702fd7cfb1daa9a11d0b6d45a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia on Thursday recorded the highest daily numbers of coronavirus infections and deaths since the start of the pandemic, a rapidly surging toll that has severely strained the nation's health care system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A more comfortable goodbye? Vets bring pet euthanasia home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-new-york-pets-health-b41d4f3eceaae7dce484fce76d103a0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Clarence the giant schnauzer came into Penny Wagner's life as a puppy nearly eight years ago, at a traumatic time for her family. She and her husband, Steve, had recently lost their 21-year-old daughter in a car accident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to meet with pope, push for global tax at G20 in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biden-g20-idUSKBN2H41Q9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will meet with Pope Francis on Oct. 29 before attending a two-day summit of G20 leaders in Rome where he hopes to reach agreement on a Global Minimum Tax of 15%, a White House official told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRICES SKY HIGH</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/10/14/consumer-prices-rising-covid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price increases have hit certain industries particularly hard over the last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT to shut down LINKEDIN in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/14/microsoft-to-shut-down-linkedin-in-china.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft halts LinkedIn China to launch standalone jobs app</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIXCEO under fire for defending Chappelle special...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/576719-netflix-ceo-under-fire-for-defending-chappelle-special</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of Netflix is taking heat for repeatedly defending Dave Chappelle's controversial special, saying that the company believes that transphobic remarks by the comedian won't result in "real-world harm."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL ECONOMY PERFECT STORM</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/price-pinch-global-economy-caught-095406458.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From beef bowls in Tokyo to fried chicken in London, consumers are beginning to feel the pinch from the surge in costs coursing through the global economy. The rebound in economic activity as coronavirus restrictions are eased has exposed shortages across supply chains, with companies scrambling to find workers, ships and even fuel to power factories, threatening the recovery. Britain's biggest chicken producer warned that the country's 20-year cheap food binge is coming to an end and said food price inflation could hit double digits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bumble bees have disappeared from 8 states. Now face extinction...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/10/14/american-bumble-bees-disappeared-8-states-face-extinction/8448637002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American bumble bee may soon face extinction after they have disappeared from 8 states and their population has dwindled across the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's chicken king says 20-year binge on cheap food over...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/britains-binge-cheap-food-is-over-biggest-chicken-producer-says-2021-10-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's 20-year binge on cheap food is coming to an end and food price inflation could hit double digits due to a tidal wave of soaring costs that are crashing through the supply chain, Britain’s biggest chicken producer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami mayor wants to pay city workers with bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/576706-miami-mayor-wants-to-pay-city-workers-with-bitcoin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami Mayor Francis Suarez (R) says he is moving forward with a proposal to pay city workers in bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kristof Leaves NYT as He Considers Political Run...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/14/nicholas-kristof-leaves-new-york-times-as-he-considers-a-political-run/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 37 years at The New York Times as a reporter, high-level editor and opinion columnist, Nicholas Kristof is leaving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 50 Harmful Effects Linked To Social Media Use...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/50-harmful-effects-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 3.6 billion people, about half the global population, use social media networks such as Facebook and Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: World's Rich and Powerful Stashing $500 Billion in SDakota...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/the-world-s-rich-and-powerful-are-stashing-500-billion-in-this-tax-haven/ar-AAPw6Ny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Dakota has no members in the Bloomberg Billionaires Index of the world’s richest 500 people, yet it shelters some half a trillion dollars of wealth in trusts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims below 300,000 first time since pandemic began...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/14/us-jobless-claims-total-293000-vs-318000-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial claims for unemployment insurance for the week ended Oct. 9 were expected to total 318,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Americans Revert to Favoring Reduced Govt Role...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/355838/americans-revert-favoring-reduced-government-role.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans once again say the government is doing too many things that should be left to individuals and businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesale prices rose record 8.6% ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-producer-prices-prices-inflation-728488dd62aec4d09527c7ba9779944f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Inflation at the wholesale level rose 8.6% in September compared to a year ago, the largest advance since the 12-month change was first calculated in 2010. The Labor Department reported Thursday that the monthly increase in its producer price index, which measures inflationary pressures before they reach consumers, was 0.5% for September compared to a 0.7% gain in August.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
