<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Let's Go Brandon' Crypto Coin Turns Into Dumpster Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lets-go-brandon-crypto-coin-turns-into-total-dumpster-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MAGA-themed coin with dreams of sponsoring a NASCAR team is now circling the drain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida militia movement grew for years before emerging at heart of Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article257480309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI:  LA 66% CHANCE OF WINNING...</title>
      <link>https://thespun.com/more/top-stories/espns-computer-model-releases-final-super-bowl-prediction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thespun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to ESPN's Football Power Index, the Los Angeles Rams have a 66.3 percent chance to win Sunday's Super Bowl against the Bengals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  PLACE YOUR BETS!</title>
      <link>https://sports.nbcsports.com/2022/02/13/2022-super-bowl-odds-picks-spread-line-rams-vs-bengals-predictions-nfl-betting-favorite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2022 Super Bowl between the Rams and Bengals is right around the corner. Check out the game's odds, line, spread, NFL picks and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Will Pay $0 Federal Tax Despite Profit of $5.5 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2022/02/tesla-2021-federal-corporate-tax-elon-musk-personal-income/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla has no taxable income to report in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump going to war with Republicans. Again...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2022/02/10/politics/donald-trump-gop-incumbents-impeach-votes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as party leaders try to turn the focus of the country to President Joe Biden and his first two years in office, Donald Trump just keeps fighting the last war -- going after Republican incumbents who either voted to impeach him or otherwise wronged him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry bombshell book to 'shake monarchy to core'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/prince-harrys-book-shake-royals-26215261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry's friends predict the Duke of Sussex won't hold back on his stepmother, the newly announced future Queen Consort, in his forthcoming memoirs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODDS:  LA 66% CHANCE OF WINNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/game/_/gameId/401326638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get a summary of the Los Angeles Rams vs. Cincinnati Bengals football game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hip Hop Halftime Could Be Real Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/super-bowl-snoop-dogg-nfl-bel-air-review-inventing-anna-everythings-gonna-be-all-white-show-you-have-to-watch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to a weekend with the Super Bowl on, the choice of what to watch on the small screen should be pretty straightforward. Yet, despite Sunday’s face-off between hometown Los Angeles Rams…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandals, firings, 'tabloid-like' news. This is CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2022/feb/13/cnn-jeff-zucker-chris-cuomo-fox-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The departures of Jeff Zucker and Chris Cuomo are the latest examples of how those at the top of US networks assume the rules don’t apply to them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey to lowest point in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-parks/article/journey-to-California-Badwater-Basin-16847958.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My first sight of the lowest point in North America was from the top of a mountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow says warship chased off US sub...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-696268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's defense ministry summoned the US military attache on Saturday after complaining of an incident in which it said a US submarine violated its territorial waters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry bombshell book to 'shake monarchy to core'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10506709/Prince-Harrys-bombshell-book-shake-monarchy-core.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friends of Prince Harry have warned his long-awaited book will lay bare his true feelings towards his step-mother Camilla and is likely to 'shake the monarchy to its core'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest protesters as key US-Canada bridge remains shut...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/canada-police-arrest-protesters-as-key-bridge-to-u-s-remains-shut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future variants could be more deadly, scientists warn...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/13/future-covid-strains-could-be-more-deadly-scientists-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New COVID-19 variants that emerge could cause more serious illness and fatalities than previous strains, some scientists warn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selling Trump: Profitable Post-Presidency Like No Other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/selling-trump-profitable-post-presidency-170703308.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early December, Donald Trump put on a tuxedo and boarded the private jet of a scrap-metal magnate and crypto-miner for a short flight across Florida, touching down at an airport in Naples. There, a long red carpet marked the pathway into a Christmas-decorated hangar filled with supporters of Trump who had paid $10,000 to $30,000 for the privilege of attending a party and taking a photo with him. The event had all the trappings of a typical high-end fundraiser: a giant American flag, a lectern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Tehran police chief linked to rights abuses spotted working out at Toronto gym...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/iran-morteza-talaei-richmond-hill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside McConnell's Campaign to Thwart The Don...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/13/inside-mcconnells-campaign-to-take-back-the-senate-and-thwart-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX — For more than a year, former President Donald Trump has berated Gov. Doug Ducey of Arizona, savaging him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest protesters as key US-Canada bridge remains shut...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-canada-blockades-65453655bfffcd349388c283d14f972a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDSOR, Ontario (AP) — Police moved in to clear and arrest the remaining protesters near a key U.S.-Canadian border bridge early Sunday, trying to end one of the main demonstrations that have broken out across Canada and the world against COVID-19 vaccine mandates and other restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McVay hints at early retirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/2022-super-bowl-rams-sean-mcvay-says-he-wont-make-it-coaching-until-60-hints-at-early-retirement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McVay, 36, is part of the youngest coaching matchup in Super Bowl history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle-Age Angst vs. the Vitality of Youth...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/super-bowl-lvi-pits-matthew-114744398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Luis G. Rendon/The Daily Beast; GettyThis Sunday’s Super Bowl LVI marks the showdown of the century: the angst of middle age vs. the vitality of youth. Who will you, a middle-age person, choose?Once, LA Rams QB Matthew Stafford was young. “Stafford is likely the most ‘ready to play right away’ quarterback in this class and most naturally gifted passer in this class.” The year is 2005, and someone is writing about high school senior quarterback Matthew Stafford for ESPN.com’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burrow's Lovable Underdogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/super-bowl-2022-bengals-vs-rams-game-has-real-underdog-ncna1288994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someday, if Joe Burrow becomes the next Tom Brady, we may regret considering him and his lovable Cincinnati brothers underdogs. But not on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stafford's Hollywood Ending...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/matthew-stafford-has-set-the-stage-for-a-hollywood-ending-during-super-bowl-lvi/ar-AATMtSc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  SUPER BOWL LVI...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/2022/2/13/22930053/super-bowl-lvi-bengals-rams-eye-could-be-one-and-done-shot-at-title-joe-burrow-mvp-matthew-stafford</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This isn’t like Tom Brady’s 2001 Patriots or Patrick Mahomes and the Chiefs arriving two years ago. Neither the Rams nor Bengals are presumably at the start of a dynasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTS TO UKRAINE HALTED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-russia-europe-moscow-dce9b30db290a6e82f5aaa0f35a3125a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Some airlines have canceled or diverted flights to Ukraine amid heightened fears that an invasion by Russia is imminent despite intensive weekend talks between the Kremlin and the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran RAMS take on upstart BENGALS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/los-angeles-rams-cincinnati-bengals-nfl-sports-super-bowl-1bba14dbf940c8e0e6e05fe3b49a900c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across both Super Bowl rosters, there is a great divide. The Rams are the team loaded with veterans and the Bengals are the new kids on the block. Los Angeles has the star power, which figures with Hollywood next door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMED AND READY</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4677703/russia-attack-helicopters-ukraine-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin “doesn’t give a s**t about sanctions” Russia’s ambassador to Sweden has said, as the nation moved a fleet of attack helicopters to its border with Ukraine. Vi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing censors 'FRIENDS' in crackdown on 'immoral content'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4676411/china-censors-friends-remove-lesbian-jokes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has censored Friends to remove lesbian jokes and sexually suggestive punchlines amid a crackdown on ‘immoral content’, prompting millions to complain. Fans of the popular TV comed…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron becomes NBA's 'unofficial' points king...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/sports/lebron-james-kareem-abdul-jabbar-nba-points-scored-time-record-rcna16030</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron has 44,152 points, three more than Karmeem’s regular and postseason total, and he did that in 181 fewer games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China building nuke power plant in Argentina as turns to Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3166763/china-building-nuclear-power-plant-argentina-it-looks-latin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New deal is the latest Chinese effort to engage with countries in the region using its cutting-edge clean energy technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic seed vault to receive rare deposits...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/arctic-seed-vault-receive-rare-101008106.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Svalbard Global Seed Vault, on Spitsbergen island halfway between mainland Norway and the North Pole, is only opened a few times a year to limit its seed banks' exposure to the outside world. On Monday, gene banks from Sudan, Uganda, New Zealand, Germany and Lebanon will deposit seeds, including millet, sorghum and wheat, as back-ups to their own collections. The International Center for Agricultural Research in Dry Areas (ICARDA), which moved its headquarters to Beirut from Aleppo in 2012 because of the war in Syria, will deposit some 8,000 samples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb Security Beef Up; Violent Crime Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/02/13/super-bowl-private-security-help-protection-celebrities-la-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private security companies are seeing an uptick in requests in Los Angeles for Super Bowl weekend, as a result of recent violence in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Case of Evaporating Sub-Neptune World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-mysterious-case-of-the-evaporating-sub-neptune-world/ar-AATMzfR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Seeds of Political Violence Being Sown in Church...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/the-seeds-of-political-violence-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new insurrection is being organized, in a sanctuary near you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Soda Tax -- Great for Beer Sales?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/02/12/study-seattles-soda-tax-has-been-great-forbeer-sales/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study is pouring cold beer on Seattle's soda tax. The study, published in the peer-reviewed journal PLoS ONE, reveals...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
