<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ASHLEY MADISON cyber-breach: 5 years later, users targeted with 'sextortion' scams...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/31/ashley-madison-breach-from-2015-being-used-in-sextortion-scams.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2015 Ashley Madison breach affected individuals with corporate and government email addresses, which could make them particularly vulnerable to bribery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases May Be Undercounted -- Even With 3,000% Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/china-virus-cases-surging-3-000-may-be-undercounting-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Virus Cases May Be Undercounted Even With 3,000% Surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Crisis Hits Heartland...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/the-u-s-housing-crisis-is-making-its-way-to-the-heartland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Housing Crisis Is Making Its Way to the Heartland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's war zone': Why generation of rappers dying young?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2020/jan/31/war-zone-music-industry-confronts-a-generation-of-rappers-dying-young</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overdoses or violent crime have claimed Mac Miller, Juice WRLD and Nipsey Hussle. ‘It’s not a fairytale lifestyle,’ admits an insider – but should the business do more to protect its stars?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone army deployed to spray disinfectant across cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-drone-army-deployed-spray-21399569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One drone managed to spray disinfectant across 16,000 square metres in just one morning in the latest attempt by Chinese authorities to combat the spread of coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three ways end could play out...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/480807-three-ways-the-end-of-the-impeachment-trial-could-play-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday will be a make-or-break moment in President Trump’s impeachment trial, as Republicans try to bring the proceedings to a close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars of 'HOMELAND' Get Final Debriefing...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/01/31/the-stars-of-homeland-get-their-final-debriefing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a chilly January afternoon, Claire Danes and Mandy Patinkin arrived safely at the Library at the NoMad Hotel, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIMBAUGH:  Dems Know They've Been Beaten Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.rushlimbaugh.com/daily/2020/01/30/democrats-will-back-down-if-gop-stands-firm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rushlimbaugh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSH: I think there are a lot of people on the left, Democrats, secretly happy about this... Trump is gonna win this one, folks. He's gonna win this one, like he won the Mueller episode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acquittal Friday?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/30/republicans-confident-defeat-witness-vote-trial-109603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Lamar Alexander, a key swing vote, is sticking with the GOP. And now Trump could get acquitted by Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Alexander says 'no need for more evidence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/gop-sen-lamar-alexander-key-impeachment-vote-reveal-decision-witnesses-n1127056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP Sen. Susan Collins of Maine, another swing vote, said Thursday she supports hearing from witnesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNSTEIN:  A Shameful Episode in Our History...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/a-shameful-episode-in-our-history-carl-bernstein-scorches-senate-for-cover-up-after-alexanders-likely-trial-ending-no-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a cover-up. That's what the Senate has now done."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:   'This is a happy period'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/480817-trump-insists-he-isnt-worried-about-impeachment-this-is-a-happy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump used a campaign rally in Iowa Thursday night to air grievances against House Democrats over his impeachment while describing a “happy period” for the Republican Party despite what he lambasted as a partisa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dershowitz quits trial... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7949285/Trump-defense-claims-acts-help-reelection-not-impeachable.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Jeffrey Epstein attorney turned up in Miami amid a firestorm over his legal theory that if the president believed his re-election was in the public interest, anything he does is permitted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY:  Defense is just one big lie... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/opinion/article/Trump-s-defense-is-just-one-big-lie-15018316.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's lawyers this week floated their catch-all impeachment defense, one tailor-made for President Donald Trump. It is, in essence, that a narcissistic president can do no wrong.  Like most of the president's arguments, it's erroneous. But no argument could have presented the issue more starkly to Republican senators: Will they follow their oaths to defend the Constitution and to do impartial justice? Or will they once again show fealty to Trump personally, thereby accepting his conflation of his personal interests with those of the nation?  The Trump lawyers' challenge to the Senate began with their answer to the very first question from senators. Republican Sens. Susan Collins of Maine, Lisa Murkowski of Alaska and Mitt Romney of Utah asked: What if the president had a mixed motive - if he thought he was acting both "in pursuit of a personal political advantage" and in "promotion of national interests"? White House Deputy Counsel Patrick Philbin responded without caveat. That "cannot possibly be the basis for an impeachable offense," he said.  Leave it to Alan Dershowitz to drive the point home with the subtlety of a sledgehammer. If "a president does something which he believes will get himself elected in the public interest, that cannot be the kind of quid pro quo that results in impeachment," Dershowitz contended.  For a president psychologically incapable of distinguishing between his own personal interests and the nation's, that amounts to the ultimate get-out-of-impeachment-free card. Trump already believes that "I have an Article II" - Article II of the Constitution - "where I have the right to do whatever I want as president." This self-described very stable genius, he of "I alone can fix it," is convinced that his reelection, achieved by whatever means necessary, serves the interests of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish family who were kicked off flight for 'extremely offensive body odor' now suing for discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7949871/Jewish-family-kicked-American-Airline-flight-body-odor-suing-discrimination.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yehuda Yosef Adler and his wife Jennie are seeking unspecified damages in the suit filed in the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of Texas Houston Division against American Airlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAN A TIE?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7949505/Republicans-rush-wrap-Donald-Trumps-impeachment-four-hours-debate-Friday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican leadership in the Senate is working on a plan that will guarantee defeating a motion to call more witnesses and wrap up Donald Trump's impeachment trial by the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cipollone was camera-shy everyman before trial made him famous...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/Cipollone-was-a-camera-shy-everyman-before-15018274.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In August 2016, the conservative pundit Laura Ingraham brought an unassuming, 50-year-old corporate attorney to a presidential debate-prep session for then-candidate Donald Trump.  Long before that day, Ingraham had grown close to Pat Cipollone. He'd been her spiritual mentor as she converted to Catholicism, and he had become her godfather, a special honor in the church meant to forge a lifelong bond. But in her professional world - the realm of high-octane, highly public political combat - Cipollone had made no footprints.  "No one knew who he was," said a person close to Cipollone, speaking on the condition of anonymity to describe a closed-door campaign gathering.  Here was a Washington everyman, one of the faceless masters of the universe in the capital city who quietly turn the wheels of power, influence, the law and business - pointedly, and by design, without ever generating a headline.  That brief encounter would set in motion one of the more curious pairings in modern American politics, something approaching the knitting of a sinner and a saint. A twice-divorced president with a penchant for extramarital dalliances, name-calling and celebrity magazine spreads aligned with a preternaturally private father of 10 whose great passions trend more to devotional trips to the Vatican and Catholic charitable endeavors.  The impression Cipollone made on the day of Trump's debate prep - the future president and his team viewed this unknown quantity as a man of discretion, of "judgment, intellect and modesty, not a leaker," as one attendee put it - would linger. Nearly 2 1/2 years later, Trump would select Cipollone as his White House counsel and more recently as the lead attorney in the impeachment trial that has played out for the past two weeks in the Senate chamber.  Cipollone's central role in the defense...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of performing illegal c-sections on dogs in his kitchen...</title>
      <link>https://www.modbee.com/news/local/crime/article239817538.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narrow majority favors 'Medicare for All'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kff.org/health-reform/poll-finding/kff-health-tracking-poll-january-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kff.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This month’s KFF Health Tracking poll examines public opinion and knowledge of Medicare-for-all and a public option, President Trump’s approval on health care programs and issues, the p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm bankruptcies jumped 20% despite federal aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.fb.org/market-intel/the-verdict-is-in-farm-bankruptcies-up-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fb.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the 2019 calendar year there were 595 Chapter 12 family farm bankruptcies, up nearly 100 filings from 2018 and the highest level since 2011’s 637 Chapter 12 filings. Given that there are slightly more than 2 million farms in the U.S., the 2019 bankruptcy data reveals a bankruptcy rate of approximately 2.95 bankruptcies per 10,000 farms, slightly below the rate of 2.99 filings per 10,000 farms in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hired BLACK CUBE to Kill Stories...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/567a1f4d8f1f725b89e6d9ff5e16a63a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Harvey Weinstein is defending his use of a private spy agency that allegedly dug up dirt on his accusers, saying Thursday he did it “for days like this.” The unscripted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilots, flight attendants demand flights to China stop as virus fear mount worldwide...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200130232450-em6gu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/AIRLINES (WRAPUP 2, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 2-Pilots, flight attendants demand flights to China stop as virus fear mount worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI probes use of Israeli firm's spyware in personal and government hacks...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200130224046-60daf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CYBER/NSO (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-FBI probes use of Israeli firm's spyware in personal and government hacks -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris to declare 'dawn of new era' as Britain leaves  EU...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10859141/boris-johnson-brexit-new-era/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson will declare “the dawn of a new era” for Britain as the nation leaves the EU at 11pm tonight. In an address to the nation from No10, the PM will describe the historic moment as the be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skipping LA traffic in a helicopter; Elite way of transportation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/skipping-la-traffic-in-a-helicopter-not-a-poor-mans-way-of-transportation/ar-BBZtNlA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Harvey Weinstein trial, prosecutors try to overcome image of 'harmless old man'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-nz/news/world/at-harvey-weinstein-trial-prosecutors-try-to-overcome-image-of-a-harmless-old-man-in-court/ar-BBZuA4o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge says jail staff acted with 'indifference' when woman gave birth alone in cell...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/judge-says-jail-staff-acted-with-indifference-when-woman-gave-birth-alone-in-cell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge issued an opinion, criticizing the Alameda County Sheriff’s office for their “indifference” when a woman gave birth in a jail cell alone, screaming for hours in 20…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes filed six lawsuits in 2019. Where are they now?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/regional/the-west/article239564228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority supports decriminalizing sex work...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/other/480725-poll-majority-supports-decriminalizing-sex-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of U.S. voters support decriminalizing sex work, according to an analysis released Thursday by left-leaning think tank Data for Progress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR:  Beware the Revenge Impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beware-revenge-impeachment-195925165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Former Solicitor General and federal judge Kenneth Starr made a simple argument this week on behalf of President Donald Trump’s impeachment defense. We are living in the “age of impeachment,” he said on Monday, urging the Senate to acquit Trump and “return to norms” that counsel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating apps face Feds over underage use...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a93a6e2b02b7f979efca92ea7266e9f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A House subcommittee is investigating popular dating services such as Tinder and Bumble for allegedly allowing minors and sex offenders to use their services. Bumble,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toughest game to pick in years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/61967c1bec6a84210f2b39768bafe42d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Even the oddsmakers aren't sure about this Super Bowl. That's how close the Kansas City Chiefs and San Francisco 49ers match up. The Chiefs are a 1-point favorite, which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will chief justice expand his role?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1544c83c96cfdcc4c7ba36c5562109a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Chief Justice John Roberts is the picture of judicial modesty at President Donald Trump's impeachment trial, wearing his unadorned black robe and wielding an ivory gavel as he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testimony coming? Abrupt acquittal? Trump trial edges on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/12cbb6666003300732c9182fd9e636b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate jurors peppered President Donald Trump's defenders and accusers with final questions at his impeachment trial Thursday ahead of a crucial vote on calling witnesses, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO DECLARES EMERGENCY</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200130224918-c4gqz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):WRAPUP 1-China virus death toll rises to at least 212 as WHO declares global emergency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry loses battle with UK newspaper...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/prince-harry-loses-complaint-uk-newspaper</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry has lost his battle with U.K. newspaper, Mail on Sunday, which began back in 2019 when the Duke of Sussex posted an Instagram photo that the paper claimed intentionally misled his more than 5 million followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO DECLARES EMERGENCY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/30/who-declares-china-coronavirus-a-global-health-emergency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement came just hours after the U.S. confirmed its first human-to-human transmission of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Adds $13.2 Billion to Fortune -- in Minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-30/bezos-adds-13-2-billion-to-fortune-in-minutes-with-amazon-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney, Man Alone...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/01/30/mitt-romney-a-man-alone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — It’s been one of those spectacle weeks on Capitol Hill, the likes of which history might just stop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wary of irking China, Trump offers rosy take...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c2b286be3024aa6781035dc5e56491d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump regaled a friendly New Jersey campaign crowd with his thoughts about with his thoughts about impeachment, the economy, the border wall, local politics and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASES SPIKE TENFOLD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f0f07b30c8cdd2b0f30c6081acc7599</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The World Health Organization declared the outbreak sparked by a new virus in China that has spread to more than a dozen countries as a global emergency Thursday after the number of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES pilots sue to stop flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/30/american-airlines-pilots-sue-over-china-flights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pilots’ union at American Airlines sued to block the carrier from flying to China and told members not to operate flight there because of the spreading coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 million Prime subscribers...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/amazon-earnings-return-to-growth-in-holiday-season-sending-stock-soaring-toward-1-trillion-valuation-2020-01-30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. defied its own disappointing forecast and returned to earnings growth in the holiday quarter with more than $3 billion in profit, sending...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children joining self-defense militia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/30/americas/children-self-defense-militias-in-mexico-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a remote, mountainous region of Mexico's Guerrero state, a group of uniformed young boys lined up on a basketball court. "Attention! Lift up your weapons now," their trainer yelled as the kids rushed into position, hands firmly holding onto their rifles. The littlest ones are training with sticks, faces covered with colored bandanas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing arguments set...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/480754-impeachment-closing-arguments-to-begin-friday-afternoon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are planning for four hours of closing arguments in President Trump’s impeachment trial starting Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: DEMS NEVER FOUND THEIR HERO...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/01/democrats-schiff-impeachment/605803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Adam Schiff played every card he had in the impeachment inquiry into President Trump, but none seemed to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New recording shows access Rudy associates had at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-recording-shows-access-lev-parnas-and-igor-fruman-had-to-trump-at-mar-a-lago-donor-event/ar-BBZuBz0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON soars after huge earnings beat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/30/amazon-amzn-q4-2019-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon beat on both the top and bottom lines for the fourth quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department authorizes personnel to evacuate China...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/state-department-staff-evacuate-china-coronavirus-05f55f0b-25e7-4fa3-b344-b9c5d245ec7d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outbreak was declared a Global Health Emergency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine ordered for American passenger on military base...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/health/quarantine-ordered-for-american-flown-from-china-coronavirus-zone-who-tried-to-leave-riverside-military-base/5892089/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A quarantine order was issued Thursday for one of the nearly 200 Americans who evacuated the Chinese city at the center of the coronavirus outbreak and arrived at March Air Reserve Base in Riverside after officials say the person tried to leave the base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden quietly pouring money into Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/30/us/politics/joe-biden-fundraising.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mr. Biden barnstorms the state in the final days before the caucuses, he is chasing more than voters and delegates. The biggest stakes for him might just be cash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman bites off inch of man's tongue while kissing...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article239803723.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit evacuation plan risks infecting healthy citizens...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/coronavirus-brit-evacuation-plan-risks-infecting-healthy-citizens-former-health-secretary-warns-11921887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lord Lansley's warning comes as Sky News understands that the Britons being repatriated will be quarantined on the Wirral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New recording shows access Rudy associates had at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/new-recording-shows-access-lev-parnas-and-igor-fruman-had-to-trump-at-mar-a-lago-donor-event/2020/01/30/a11cb354-437e-11ea-abff-5ab1ba98b405_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video of the April 2018 gathering came 10 days before the two men would dine with the president at his Washington hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts won't read question from Rand naming whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7948669/John-Roberts-DECLINES-read-question-Rand-Paul-naming-alleged-whistleblower.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts declined to read a question from Republican Senator Rand Paul on Thursday that would name the alleged whistleblower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel bars flights...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-bars-flights-china-over-virus-fears-health-185155408.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's health minister said Thursday that the country would bar all flights from China over the coronavirus epidemic, as fears of global contagion grew. "We shall not allow any flight in the near future from China to land in this country, not one," Yaakov Litzman said at a televised</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUMMER making comeback -- with electric...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/88664c30da1a142126794def35f69138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — The Hummer, once a gas-guzzling target for environmentalists, is making a comeback. But this time around it won't burn fuel or spew greenhouse gases. General Motors announced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal worker rented storage unit to hold 5,000 pieces of undelivered mail...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/us-postal-service/mail-stashed-in-storage-unit-714036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A time-strapped United States Postal Service worker who was unable to complete deliveries on his Virginia route rented a $49-a-month storage unit into which he dumped about 5000 pieces of undelivered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images show Wuhan's empty streets...</title>
      <link>https://graphics.reuters.com/CHINA-HEALTH-WUHAN-SATELLITE/0100B5B93B4/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;graphics.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images show Wuhan's empty streets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spying On Accusers Becomes Topic At Trial...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-black-cube-to-spy-on-accusers-rape-trial-1202846724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein’s hiring of Black Cube, a private intelligence agency run largely by former officers of Mossad and other Israeli intelligence agencies, became a key topic on an otherwise sub…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago woman transmits to husband...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/01/30/first-human-to-human-transmission-of-coronavirus-in-u-s-documented-in-illinois/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first human-to-human transmission of coronavirus in the United States has been documented in Illinois.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSES TRUMP GOAL</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy/u-s-economy-misses-trumps-3-growth-target-in-2019-idUSKBN1ZT0CA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy missed the Trump administration's 3% growth target for a s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commerce secretary Wilbur Ross:  Virus will help bring jobs back!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/wilbur-ross-touts-coronavirus-economic-benefits-u-s-after-saying-n1126366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think it will help to accelerate the return of jobs to North America," Trump's commerce secretary said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless encampment forms own government...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/homeless-community-at-east-austin-camp-creates-committee-for-the-homeless-run-by-the-homeless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The once mostly empty lot off U.S. 183 and Montopolis in East Austin has become home to more than 100 people without another place to go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10498694/results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE POLL...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10498694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Republicans more fired up for 2020, Dems anxious...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4daf1b154eeff75b97b886e2fe8c1d29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to the 2020 presidential election, Democrats are nervous wrecks and Republican excitement has grown. That's according to a new poll by The Associated Press-NORC Center for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise fueling internal fight as some fear November wipeout...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-01-30/sanders-democrats-division</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats increasingly worried about the prospect of Bernie Sanders winning their nomination are pushing harder to block him, galvanizing his backers in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Thought it was end of world!' Space debris lights up sky in SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7947543/I-thought-end-world-Space-debris-lights-sky-Southern-California.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media users posted 'crazy' meteor videos from Southern California on Wednesday but the American Meteor Society believe the event was caused by space debris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK stock plunges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/30/facebook-plunges-at-open-wiping-out-more-than-50-billion-in-market-value.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drop comes after Facebook reported a 51% rise in expenses compared with its total in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Net Worth Tumbles $4 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-30/zuckerberg-s-net-worth-tumbles-4-billion-after-facebook-dive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7,000 Quarantined On Cruise Ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10853820/coronavirus-passengers-cruise-ship-chinese-couple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORONAVIRUS fears have sparked on a cruise ship after two holidaymakers fell ill, leaving around 7,000 passengers and crew trapped on the vessel in an Italian port. A husband and wife, reportedly f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scenes of Racy 'Oscars of Porn'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/behind-the-scenes-of-the-racy-oscars-of-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 37th annual AVN Awards, recognizing the best of the adult industry, was held on Jan. 25 in Las Vegas. It’s preceded by a week of debauched fun. And we were there to capture it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentary on Michael Vick seeks to add context to dogfighting saga...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/ESPN-documentary-on-Michael-Vick-seeks-to-add-15016059.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You don't have to forgive Michael Vick for dogfighting, but ESPN wants you to understand the context.  "Vick," a two-part "30 for 30" documentary set to air Jan. 30 with the second half premiering the following Thursday, Feb. 6, takes a deep dive into the factors that surrounded the former NFL quarterback's midcareer imprisonment, including race, poverty and sudden stardom and wealth. Among the complexities of his saga are the differing ways communities reacted to his arrest and lengthy sentence, and what to make of his football legacy.  Perhaps the biggest question, though, was raised by the documentary's director, Stanley Nelson, in a phone interview Wednesday with The Washington Post: "How does something that so many of us see as horribly cruel and torturous, how does anybody not see that?"  "And how, to some people, does this seem like something that's not wrong?" Nelson added. "So we wanted to examine that."  Unlike the recent Netflix series on former NFL star Aaron Hernandez, whose tale bears some similarities with Vick's - including a degree of misfortune in being drafted by teams located too close to their old stomping ground for their own good - the latter is alive to offer his take on what happened.  Vick, who has apologized numerous times and worked as an animal rights advocate since his 2009 release from prison, himself appears somewhat at a loss to explain it.  "I was really, really competitive, and I loved dogs," he says in the documentary, "and somehow, some way, that got intertwined, and I never got away from it, never walked away from it."  The "I loved dogs" line could have some viewers rewinding to make sure they heard it correctly, but Vick says it more than once, as do a pair of childhood friends and cohorts in Bad Newz Kennels, a dogfighting operation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wilbur Ross suggests will help bring jobs back...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/892627/wilbur-ross-suggests-coronavirus-help-bring-jobs-back-north-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross says he doesn't 'want to talk about a victory lap' regarding the coronavirus outbreak. 'But...' Ross during a Fox Business appearance Thursday morning discussed the Wuhan coronavirus, the death toll of which has reached 170 as more than 7,700 cases have been confirmed in mainland China. While Ross said that 'every American's heart has to go out to the victims' and 'I don't want to talk about a victory lap about a very unfortunate, very malignant disease,' his thought didn't end there. 'But the fact is, it does give businesses yet another thing to consider when they go through their review of their supply chain,' Ross said. '...It's another risk factor that people need to take into account. So I think it will help to accelerate the return of jobs to North America, some to U.S., probably some to Mexico as well.' Host Maria Bartiromo, unphased by Ross' observation, quickly responded, 'Ah, that's a good point, actually. Yeah.' The Washington Post notes in response to this comment that 'White House officials so far have been careful in how theyâ€™ve talked about the economic implications of the health scare in China,' but Ross? Not so much. Brendan Morrow Secretary Wilbur Ross says coronavirus will be good for [checks notes] American jobs: 'I think it will help to accelerate the return of jobs to North America.' pic.twitter.com/Y4SbDIcTi4 â€” Aaron Rupar (@atrupar) January 30, 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Butterfly Activist Found Dead in Rainwater Tank...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/30/homero-gomez-gonzalez-prominent-butterfly-activist-in-mexico-found-dead-in-a-well/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homero Gómez González, a former logger who transformed into one of the most vocal defenders of central Mexico's monarch butterfly population, disappeared on Jan. 13.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possibility of epic tie...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/29/john-roberts-trump-impeachment-trial-109109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spotlight will fall on the chief justice if the Senate deadlocks on a critical trial vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs show team already preparing dozens of executive orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/sanders-prepares-to-sign-dozens-of-executive-orders-upon-taking-office-we-cannot-accept-delays-from-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the orders include an immediate halt of border wall construction, removing a limit on accepting refugees, and reinstating the Obama-era DACA program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pee-wee Herman 'Dark' Reboot: Paul Reubens Ready to Stage Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/pee-wee-hermans-dark-reboot-paul-reubens-is-ready-stage-a-comeback-1273962</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three decades after 'Pee-wee’s Big Adventure' and a career-threatening scandal, the 67-year-old has become a comedy cult hero with a shocking new Pee-wee script: "I make the rules about when I'm coming back."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP 2019: 2.3%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/30/us-gdp-q4-2019-first-reading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2.3% growth in U.S. gross domestic product for the full year well below the White House's projections following the 2017 tax revamp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes Set For Biggest NFL Contract Ever?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/agents-take-what-super-bowl-2020-starter-patrick-mahomes-could-make-on-potentially-biggest-nfl-contract-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mahomes could have 'basketball money' on the horizon when he signs an extension</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll finds Sanders faring best against Trump in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign-polls/480643-poll-sanders-best-challenge-to-trump-in-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) fares best against President Trump in a head-to-head matchup in Texas, according to a new poll released Wednesday by Texas Luyceum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear in age of outbreak: Chinese not welcome...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/fear-in-the-age-of-coronavirus-chinese-no-longer-welcome</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (BLOOMBERG) - Hong Kong suspends travel from China. Schools in Europe uninvite exchange students. Restaurants in South Korea turn away Chinese customers.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurse charged with attempted killing of five babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-crime/nurse-in-germany-charged-with-attempted-killing-of-five-babies-idUSKBN1ZT1AW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in southwestern Germany detained an intensive care nurse on Wednesda...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS FALL FURTHER ON SICKNESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/30/us-futures-point-to-sharply-lower-open-on-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Futures fell as the death toll from the coronavirus continues to rise in China, stoking fears about the virus' impact on the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Kochs vs. Mercers in Right's Big Tech Brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/big-tech-fight-brews-between-the-right-s-kochs-and-mercers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Itâ€™s Kochs vs. Mercers in the Rightâ€™s Big Tech Brawl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican economy suffers first contraction in decade...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200130115834-u1j7m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-ECONOMY/GDP (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Mexican economy suffers first contraction in a decade in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game security shows easy-going 1960s long gone...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200129230150-5d3iv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOOTBALL-NFL-SUPERBOWL/SECURITY:Super Bowl security shows the easy-going 1960s are long gone</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
