<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Zoo bans chimp-loving fan who blows kisses to ape...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3514361/zoo-bans-woman-chimp-visiting-blow-kisses-antwerp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ZOO has banned a woman who “loves” one of its chimps after she and the ape would blow kisses and wave to each other during weekly visits. Adie Timmermans has been left heartbroken by …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Marines cradle Afghan babies as evacuees airlifted to safety...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3514040/us-marines-cradle-babies-afghan-air-lift-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEART-warming pictures of Marines tending to Afghani children have gone viral as evacuations continue following the Taliban’s takeover of the country six days ago. The images, taken by a US s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside horrific 'Children of God' cult...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3513885/children-of-god-cult-david-berg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEARING a woman walk through the door, 11-year-old Verity Carter prayed she would finally be saved from the ‘uncle’ who was raping her. But her ‘rescuer’ turned and quietly walked away, leaving her…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PICTURES:  World's worst zoo attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3496211/worlds-worst-ever-zoo-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FROM the other side of a zoo cage, most animals look tame and arguably approachable – but rest assured, these are still very much wild creatures with feral instincts. Just this month a woman …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS stars 'betrayed' with ban on porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/3511692/onlyfans-courtney-tillia-betrayed-explicit-content-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONLYFANS model Courtney Tillia says she feels “betrayed” after the social media platform kept its creators in the dark about banning explicit content, she told The Sun exclusively. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORNING AFTER:  Jerusalem could have all gone up in smoke in latest wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jerusalem-could-have-all-gone-up-in-smoke-in-latest-wildfire-677221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENVIRONMENTAL AFFAIRS: One of the country’s worst fires devastated areas around Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Iowa, Marjorie Taylor Greene tests her national appeal...</title>
      <link>https://omaha.com/news/in-iowa-marjorie-taylor-greene-tests-her-national-appeal/article_52ced3bf-5971-5576-a865-0b22980e7bac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa. — She rattled off pullups at the Iowa State Fair, trailed by a pack of reporters and onlookers. She dodged questions about her political future. And she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach suspends law used by cops to arrest people who film them; Training ordered...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-beach-suspends-law-used-210908289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami Beach police say they have stopped enforcing a new law that critics believe has emboldened officers to arrest bystanders using their phones to film police on duty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recall candidate Larry Elder draws fire for N-word comedy clip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/larry-elder-draws-fire-n-021039847.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The clip, which was recorded in the 1990s, was recently unearthed by KBLA radio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variants likely to bring a fall and winter of mandates, anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/delta-variant-likely-bring-fall-120056591.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many health experts believe mask mandates and tougher vaccine requirements will be needed in the coming months to avoid more serious coronavirus surges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid oxygen shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wesh.com/article/orlando-mayor-to-hold-newser-on-unprecedented-event-requiring-community-assistance/37359831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wesh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dyer explained that many COVID-19 patients require liquid oxygen for their treatment. OUC has used liquid oxygen to treat the water supply for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Most Face Masks WILL NOT Stop Covid; Cloth Only Filters 10% Of Exhaled Aerosols...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/masks-wont-stop-covid-indoors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite wearing a mask, the study finds a large buildup of aerosol droplets suspended in the air coming from wearers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toddler, 1, survives three nights in forest with bears and wolves...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/toddler-girl-survives-three-nights-24808291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyuda, the daughter of a nuclear physicist, was miraculously located after three nights in an area of thick forest, around two-and-a-half miles from her home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mad House Getting Off Cape Cod!</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/08/20/tropical-storm-henri-cape-cod-preparations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harbormasters, residents, and business owners on Cape Cod are preparing for Tropical Storm Henri to hit the area hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  HENRI NEW ENGLAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/henri-long-island-new-england-northeast-landfall-hurricane/1003672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been nearly 36 years since a hurricane has made landfall on Long Island. Plus, New York City was under a tropical storm warning as Henri picked up speed on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.weathernerds.org/satellite/?initsatsrc=On&amp;initsatname=GOES16&amp;initsattype=wv&amp;initcscheme=ir1&amp;initimdimx=1050&amp;initimdimy=764&amp;initrange=37.750:-79.750:29.250:-65.750&amp;initloop=True&amp;initnframes=20&amp;initlightning16=On&amp;initlightning17=Off&amp;initltngfed=Off&amp;initltngtoe=Off&amp;initinterstates=On&amp;initwarnings=On&amp;initlatlon=On&amp;initascata=Off&amp;initascatb=Off&amp;initascatc=Off&amp;initascatamba=Off&amp;initascatambb=Off&amp;initascatambc=Off&amp;initsst=Off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weathernerds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST HIT IN 30 YEARS?</title>
      <link>https://www.ny1.com/nyc/all-boroughs/weather/2021/08/20/live-blog-henri-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ny1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest updates as the storm heads north.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADVISORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211148.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Extremely worrisome'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-hurricanes-9c64eb1be8ccdf184861a53161e4d5f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLYMOUTH, Mass. (AP) — Parts of the Northeast could begin to feel the effects of Tropical Storm Henri as soon as late Saturday, as the system that is expected to become a hurricane by the end of the day barrels toward the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  HENRI NEW ENGLAND...</title>
      <link>?https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/henri-long-island-new-england-northeast-landfall-hurricane/1003672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full FDA approval of PFIZER as early as Monday...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/20/fda-approval-pfizer-covid-shot-506472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision would apply to people 16 and older. Officials hope it will convince some vaccine holdouts to get inoculated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE HILL Bought by TV Giant for $130 Million...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/the-hill-acquired-nexstar-media-1235045896/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political digital media company The Hill has been acquired by Nexstar Media, a broadcast TV and internet media company, for $130 million. Nexstar, which operates TV stations in 116 markets and 120 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 arrested in student's killing at Denver Jewish school...</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/news/local/4-people-arrested-in-killing-of-student-outside-denver-jewish-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police investigating a crime spree that stretched along Colfax and included the shooting death of a student outside Yeshiva Toras Chaim have arrested for four suspects, FOX31 News has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maker of Popular Covid Test Told Factory to Destroy Inventory...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/maker-of-popular-covid-test-told-factory-to-destroy-inventory/ar-AANxYP6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For weeks in June and July, workers at a Maine factory making one of America’s most popular rapid tests for Covid-19 were given a task that shocked them: take apart millions of the products they had worked so hard to create and stuff them into garbage bags. Soon afterward, Andy Wilkinson, a site manager for Abbott Laboratories, the manufacturer, stood before rows of employees to announce layoffs. The company canceled contracts with suppliers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece completes border wall extension to deter potential Afghan migrants...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210820201734-gfs82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/GREECE-TURKEY (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Greece completes border wall extension to deter potential Afghan migrants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demand for antibody drugs soars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-ad87808ad28f29c6cb5f1b98e478c6db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People infected with COVID-19 were captured in a photo this week lying on the floor in pain while waiting for antibody infusions at a treatment site set up inside the library in Jacksonville, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol cop who shot Ashli Babbitt exonerated in internal probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/capitol-police-officer-who-shot-ashli-babbitt-exonerated-internal-probe-n1277336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Capitol Police memo obtained by NBC News says “no further action will be taken in this matter” after the officer was exonerated for use of force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Paying Parents $700 To Drive Kids Amid Bus Driver Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/08/19/wilmington-charter-school-paying-parents-to-drive-students-amid-driver-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid a nationwide school bus driver shortage, a Wilmington school is paying its students' teachers to take the wheel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo artist morphs into devil look-alike...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/cna-lifestyle/sinister-attracted-me-brazilian-tattoo-artist-morphs-devil-look-alike-2127291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO :   Brazilian tattoo artist Michel Faro Prado has taken body modification to a new level by transforming himself into a devil look-alike.Prado, known on social media as Diabao Praddo or Devil Praddo, changed his appearance by tattooing 80per cent of his body, reducing his nose size and removing on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admits he doesn't know how many are left...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3511802/joe-biden-live-speech-forgets-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden forgot a reporter’s question in his live speech on Afghanistan after the White House boasted about his interviews. While answering questions from a handful of journalists, the presi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines pull baby over barbed wire to safety...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/2021/08/20/marines-in-afghanistan-pull-baby-over-barbed-wire-to-safety/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An update on the baby pulled over barbed wire in viral video:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Study About Honesty -- Based On Fake Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/stephaniemlee/dan-ariely-honesty-study-retraction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Renowned psychologist Dan Ariely literally wrote the book on dishonesty. Now some are questioning whether the scientist himself is being dishonest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak shuts entire police force in Illinois...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/20/covid-outbreak-shutters-entire-police-department-in-illinois/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COVID-19 outbreak has infected every member of the police department in Venice, Illinois, Mayor Tyrone Echols said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China military nuclear orders rise fourfold...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3145851/chinas-military-nuclear-orders-rise-fourfold-push-catch-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasing nuclear capability is a natural course of action in the face of challenge posed by the US and its strategy of suppression, military expert says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Britain's Gypsies survive?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/08/can-britains-gypsies-survive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new law could extinguish centuries of tradition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE 'founder' admits he created revenge site against estranged wife...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/20/google-founder-created-revenge-site-against-estranged-wife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Hassan and his ex-wife, Allison Huynh, are about to battle in California court over an estate worth more than $1 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flights Grounded for Last 8 Hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/mideast/no-rescue-flights-have-taken-kabul-airport-least-eight-hours-n1277317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qatar, where the first batch of evacuees were taken, does not have the capacity to take any more, sources told NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon unlivable as crisis deepens: 'Hell on earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210820-hell-on-earth-lebanon-unlivable-as-crisis-deepens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Hell on earth': Lebanon unlivable as crisis deepens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS:  Biden and Pelosi Set to Impose Tax Hikes on Small Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/biden-and-pelosi-set-impose-tax-hikes-small-businesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During his campaign, President Biden promised the American people that he would not raise taxes on small businesses. Now he is violating that promise, and next week House Democrats will vote on the framework to make the tax hikes possible.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Biden's small business tax promise was made on Feb. 20, 2020 before a national audience during a Democratic debate hosted by MSNBC:&amp;#13;&amp;#13;MSNBC's Hallie Jackson: "I want to ask you about Latinos owning one out of every four new small businesses in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 In 4 Employees Want To Work From Home Forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/employees-remote-work-from-home-forever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two in five say a company’s policy on remote work is now their number one desired workplace perk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent gives Nazi salute during mask school meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/parent-gives-nazi-salute-during-debate-about-masks-in-classrooms-at-birmingham-school-board-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My great grandparents' siblings perished in the Holocaust. They literally were taken out of their homes, into a Polish field, and were forced by Nazis to dig their own graves up until the point where the Nazis shot them to death in those graves,” Sen. Jeremy Moss said. “That was the Holocaust. A Birmingham School Board Meeting is not the Holocaust.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICAN CONGRESSWOMAN CALLS PRESIDENT OF UNITED STATES 'PIECE OF SHIT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5gn8x/marjorie-taylor-greene-called-joe-biden-a-piece-of-shit-over-afghanistan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Georgia representative, who last month voted against granting visas to Afghans who helped U.S. troops, made the comments in a video she posted on Gettr, the far-right Twitter alternative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/storminfo/08L_tracks_latest.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tropicaltidbits.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE ALLOWS CHILD PORN LAWSUIT AGAINST TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/fosta-twitter-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision was a rare ruling on the impact of carveouts to Section 230.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOUBLE JEOPARDY:   Host Canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-reviews/mike-richards-jeopardy-host-out-1234999713/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The embattled host announced he's stepping down, production on the new season has been suspended and the search for a new permanent daytime host will begin again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC concert to celebrate recovery still on despite surging cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/we-love-nyc-the-homecoming-concert-to-feature</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's concert to celebrate its recovery from the coronavirus pandemic despite surging cases and hospitalizations, is set to take place Saturday, August 21 in Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK BOT TO 'END HUMAN WORK'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-unveils-5-ft-24801285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk has announced a five foot eight "Tesla Bot", a humanoid robot prototype, that will be unveiled next year - some people have criticised the announcement as nothing but a "dream"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sentenced for beheading his grandmother...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wwjnewsradio/news/local/michigan-man-sentenced-for-murdering-beheading-grandmother</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Monroe County man was sentenced after being found guilty of murdering and beheading his grandmother. Kenny Wayne McBride, 45 of Temperance, was sentenced to life without parole on a first-degree murder charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  HURRICANE NEW ENGLAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/hurricane-watches-in-northeast-as-henri-moves-northward/1002669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters say a landfall in New England is increasingly likely later this weekend -- and they break down what conditions the region could face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST HIT IN 30 YEARS?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2021-08-20-tropical-storm-hurricane-henri-northeast-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Henri is expected to strengthen in the western Atlantic and may track close to eastern New England. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELON SEES UNIVERSAL INCOME FOR ALL</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2021/08/19/musk-the-tesla-bot-is-coming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember that weird Will Smith movie about robots? Yeah, neither do we. But Elon Musk does. Tesla is developing a 5’8” Tesla Bot, with a prototype expected sometime next year. The news comes during Tesla’s inaugural AI Day, which was streamed on the company’s website Thursday night. The bot i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>48% Want Govt to Restrict 'Misinformation' on Socials...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/08/20/48-of-americans-want-the-government-to-restrict-misinformation-on-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pew Research Center found that support for censorship is increasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman In Ski Mask Opens Fire Into HARRY POTTER Store On Fifth Avenue...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/20/harry-potter-store-shots-fired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said a security guard inside the store heard noise, then saw a man wearing a ski mask standing in the front glass window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Aloe a Sham?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/20/is-aloe-a-sham/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As ongoing heat waves extend beach weather for many in the United States, you may find yourself sporting a bad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movers seen at mansion as Cuomo prepares to leave office...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-5f064d9b8053be53632590eb946f12a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — A moving van was at the governor's mansion in Albany on Friday and workers were seen carrying out boxes and artwork as Gov. Andrew Cuomo prepared for his last day in office. The Democrat is scheduled to have a last full day as governor Monday, giving way to Lt.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
