<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Working From Home Makes MORE Productive...</title>
      <link>https://www.theedgemarkets.com/article/yes-working-home-makes-you-more-productive-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theedgemarkets.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(April 22): The great work-from-home experiment occasioned by the pandemic has divided opinion in the corporate suite and sparked endless debates about whether employees work as effectively from the kitchen table as they do from the office.A new study finds that, in fact, remote work does indeed make us more productive.The work-from-home boom will lift productivity in the U.S. economy by 5%, mostly because of savings in commuting time, the study says. The findings suggest the rapid adoption of new</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Automated Checkout Coming to Full-Size Supermarkets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/amazon-e2-80-99s-automated-checkout-is-coming-to-full-size-supermarkets/ar-BB1fVAhL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Widespread adoption could fuel charges the company aims to eliminate cashiers. Amazon denies that, saying it created thousands of grocery jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,700 detained at pro-Navalny rallies across Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210422-over-1-700-detained-at-pro-navalny-rallies-across-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 1,700 detained at pro-Navalny rallies across Russia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron Faces Backlash Over Warning To Ohio Officer Who Shot Black Teen...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/lebron-james-faces-backlash-over-youre-next-tweet-about-ohio-police-officer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns West of harsh response if crosses 'red lines'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/21/putin-warns-against-crossing-russias-red-lines-talks-up-military.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his annual State of the Nation speech, Russian President Vladimir Putin warned against provoking his country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden opening summit with ambitious climate pledge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-climate-climate-change-summits-d27b869add251860acc82f58e2750fd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden will open a global climate summit with a pledge to cut at least in half the climate-wrecking coal and petroleum fumes that the U.S. pumps out, a commitment he hopes will spur China and other big polluters to speed up efforts of their own. Biden is offering Americans and the world a vision of a prosperous, clean-energy United States where factories churn out cutting-edge batteries for export, line workers re-lay an efficient national electrical grid and crews cap abandoned oil and gas rigs and coal mines. His commitment to cut U.S. fossil fuel emissions up to 52% by 2030 — similar to pledges from allies — will come at the launch Thursday of an all-virtual climate summit for 40 world leaders, marking a return by the U.S. to global climate efforts after four years of withdrawal under President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Citizenship Renunciation To Rise Dramatically?</title>
      <link>https://www.wealthbriefing.com/html/article.php?id=190932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wealthbriefing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA extracts breathable oxygen from Martian air...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/science/nasa-extracts-breathable-oxygen-thin-martian-air-2021-04-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air defense system fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/alarms-sound-in-south-of-israel-665953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SA-5 flies from Syria all the way to Negev in longest-range attack by Syria. Patriot missile activated in response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes targets in Syria after missile lands near nuke reactor...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20210422-israel-strikes-targets-in-syria-after-missile-lands-near-nuclear-reactor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Syrian surface-to-air missile exploded in southern Israel on Thursday, the Israeli military said, in an incident that triggered warning sirens in an area near the secretive Dimona nuclear reactor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Sales Surging. When Does Music Stop?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/22/u-s-home-sales-are-surging-when-does-the-music-stop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As housing omens go, beware the trending Google search. In the first week of April, U.S. search interest in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom launches effort to deal with drought; Emergencies declared...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2021-04-21/california-drought-newsom-mendocino-sonoma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Newsom has declared a drought emergency in Mendocino and Sonoma counties but said he was not prepared to issue statewide water-use restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California case rate now lowest in USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-coronavirus-case-rate-now-184916537.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's latest seven-day new case rate — 40.3 per 100,000 people — is dramatically lower than the nationwide rate of 135.3 over that same time period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah's life coach on how to be much happier:   'Let yourself be quirky'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2021/apr/21/oprah-winfrey-life-coach-martha-beck-how-be-happier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martha Beck survived abuse, went to Harvard, left her husband – then began working with the world’s biggest TV star. She discusses self-help, nonconformity and the power of truth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Republicans running for Virginia governor wary of vote-counting software...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/three-republicans-running-for-virginia-governor-wary-of-vote-counting-software/ar-BB1fUkRd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rivals teamed up on a letter to the state GOP calling for a hand count of ballots at the party’s nominating convention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 55% of Republicans agree with guilty decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/04/21/chauvin-verdict-poll-majority-approve-guilty-finding/7316788002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the hours a verdict was announced in the Derek Chauvin murder trial, a USA TODAY/Ipsos snap poll found 71% of Americans agreed Chauvin was guilty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US spy planes keep unusually close eye on China amid live-fire military exercises...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3130500/us-spy-planes-keep-close-eye-china-amid-live-fire-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American aircraft goes unusually near naval base on east coast, think tank says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump admin awarded firm $1.3 billion to make syringes. Where are they?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-care/trump-administration-awarded-firm-1-3-billion-make-covid-vaccine-n1263872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Covid vaccines are here, but the ApiJect syringe is not yet approved by federal regulators and a new factory in North Carolina is not yet built.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT ESCAPE:  Demand may soon exceed supply says CEO of biggest hotel groups...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/demand-may-exceed-supply-as-ceo-of-one-of-the-worlds-biggest-hotel-groups-sees-surge-in-bookings-11618999201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotel and airline industry will begin to bounce back by second half of 2021, according to the chief executive of InterContinental Hotels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bennett new PM?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/likud-attacks-bennett-again-665867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu says he'd be opposition leader, won't seek presidency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH TIMES:  Entrepreneurs becoming marijuana moguls...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/marijuana-moguls-grow-in-ranks-as-states-legalize-cannabis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the movement to legalize marijuana for medicinal and recreational use sweeps the country the cannabis industry is creating new jobs and raking in millions of dollars in legal profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEENS RUNNING FROM INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90627938/nike-and-chick-fil-a-are-winning-the-hearts-of-american-teens-instagram-is-losing-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snapchat is king. Beyond Meat is tasty. A new report from Piper Sandler offers insight into the hearts, minds, and wallets of generation Z.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's deadliest cartel uses drones to drop bombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mexicos-violent-jalisco-new-generation-23955985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's powerful Jalisco New Generation Cartel is run by El Mencho who reportedly ramped up attacks on police following the extradition of his son Rubén Oseguera González to the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Lost on Mountain Follows Hikers to 10,000-ft Summit for Company, Comfort...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/pets/cat-lost-on-swiss-mountain-joins-hikers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lost cat followed two hikers to the top of Mt. Britsen in Switzerland before eventually getting the help she need to reunite with her family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU MOVES TO REGULATE AI</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-government-and-politics-artificial-intelligence-data-privacy-5226382bb316f8aad4cbc5637f03a44c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Risky uses of artificial intelligence that threaten people’s safety or rights such as live facial scanning should be banned or tightly controlled, European Union officials said Wednesday as they outlined an ambitious package of proposed regulations to rein in the rapidly expanding technology. The draft regulations from the EU's executive commission include rules for applications deemed high risk such as AI systems to filter out school, job or loan applicants. They would also ban artificial intelligence outright in a few cases considered too risky, such as government “social scoring” systems that judge people based on their behavior. The proposals are the 27-nation bloc’s latest move to maintain its role as the world’s standard-bearer for technology regulation, as it tries to keep up with the world's two big tech superpowers, the U.S. and China. EU officials say they are taking a four-level “risk-based approach” that seeks to balance important rights such as privacy against the need to encourage innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 arrested at Navalny rallies in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-180-reported-arrest-alexei-navalny-demonstrations-b0fd8e696c86792b5cb1a291fb6338e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Police arrested nearly 1,500 people Wednesday during a day of demonstrations throughout Russia calling for freedom for imprisoned opposition leader Alexei Navalny, whose health reportedly is in severe decline after three weeks of hunger striking, according to a group that monitors political detentions. The largest of the protests took place in Moscow, where thousands marched through the center city. Some of the people arrested were seized before the protests even began, including to top Navalny associates in Moscow. Navalny’s team called for the unsanctioned demonstrations after weekend reports that his health is deteriorating and his life was in danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY AFTER:  SUICIDE WATCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9494507/Derek-Chauvin-45-taken-maximum-security-prison-placed-suicide-watch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota Department of Corrections released the new booking photo on Wednesday morning as Derek Chauvin woke up from his first night at MCF-Oak Park Heights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California declares emergency in state's most water-starved region...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/2021-04-drought-Sonoma-Mendocino-counties-16118321.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor said he's targeting a region where conditions are most urgent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Mends Physical Damage From Broken Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drug-mend-damage-broken-heart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study finds, in western nations, broken heart syndrome almost exclusively affects women, especially after menopause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLITARY CONFINEMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/derek-chauvin-is-being-held-in-solitary-confinement-for-23-hours-a-day/ar-BB1fTSls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Derek Chauvin is being held in solitary confinement for 23 hours a day in Minnesota’s only maximum-security prison after he was convicted of murdering George Floyd and led out of a courtroom in handcuffs, according to authorities. Mr. Chauvin, 45, the former Minneapolis police officer who knelt on Mr. Floyd’s neck for more than nine minutes last May, was sent to the prison, in Oak Park Heights, Minn., a suburb of St. Paul, after the verdict was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron targets officer: 'YOU'RE NEXT' -- but deletes tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/lebron-james-ohio-police-shooting-tweeting-photo-officer-youre-next</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the jury was deliberating Tuesday the fate of ex-Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin, another police-involved shooting was taking place in Columbus, Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Kansas counties turn down doses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kansas-coronavirus-health-c60d9f3070426e9964f1eaecb0fd3268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — About three-quarters of Kansas counties have turned down new shipments of the coronavirus vaccine at least once over the past month and several for four straight weeks, state date shows. “It is kind of stalling. Some people just don’t want it," said Stacey Hileman, a nurse with the health department in rural northwest Kansas' Decatur County, where only about 29% of the county's 2,900 residents have received at least one vaccine dose. Her county is among six that have rejected allocations for all four weeks. Thirty-three other counties paused shipments from the state for one week, 26 for two weeks and 16 for three weeks. Only 24 counties, mostly the larger ones such as Shawnee, Johnson and Sedgwick, haven't turned down any shipments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Reveal New Bodycam Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/police-reveal-new-bodycam-video-of-columbus-ohio-shooting-at-press-conference/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Columbus, Ohio have released body cam footage showing the moment when Ma’Khia Bryant was shot dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA will limit use of disposable napkins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-limit-disposable-napkins-utensils-190840262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A.'s ordinance would prohibit providing or offering disposable items to dine-in and takeout customers, except when requested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernard Goldberg Quits HBO 'REAL SPORTS' After 22 Years, Trashes Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/bernard-goldberg-quits-hbos-real-sports-after-22-years-trashes-shows-far-left-politics-in-scathing-interview-with-bill-oreilly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After quietly departing HBO’s Real Sports earlier this year, longtime reporter Bernard Goldberg joined Bill O’Reilly to explain his unceremonious decision to leave a show he now says is driven by “cowardice.” Goldberg worked on the show for more than two decades. “You are looking at diversity on the show, I literally am diversity,” the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groups see new openings for digging up dirt on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/549284-groups-see-new-openings-for-digging-up-dirt-on-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public interest groups determined to stay focused on the Trump administration say they have new openings for unearthing information now that the past government’s political appointees have departed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publisher pauses release of new Philip Roth biography...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/blake-bailey-philip-roth-biographies-arts-and-entertainment-entertainment-d95be8f46e5570766bcaae10a92e2aac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The publisher of a new, bestselling biography about Philip Roth has temporarily halted the book’s shipping and promotion as its author, Blake Bailey, faces multiple allegations of sexual harassment and abuse. “These allegations are serious. In light of them, we have decided to pause the shipping and promotion of ‘Philip Roth: The Biography’ pending any further information that may emerge,” according to a statement provided Wednesday to The Associated Press by W.W. Norton &amp;amp; Company. Existing copies remain widely available, including on Amazon.com, where the 800-page book ranked No. 812 on the print bestseller list as of midday Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite NFL prospect discloses epilepsy...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/04/21/justin-fields-told-nfl-teams-he-is-managing-epilepsy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quarterback Justin Fields has shared some medical information with teams ahead of next week’s draft. NFL Media reports that Fields has informed teams that he is managing epilepsy. The neurological condition can cause seizures and is usually treated with medication, although different cases can call for different medical approaches. Per the report, Fields has not [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI ZOOM COURT: Butt injection during virtual hearing...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/DavidOvalle305/status/1384867018508312578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man mulling mandatory jabs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arts-and-entertainment-cultures-lifestyle-government-and-politics-81405fb48db2e911a7f8ebcedce8c1f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. (AP) — Burning Man organizers have said that they are considering requiring attendees to prove they have been vaccinated for COVID-19 if the organizers move forward with plans to hold this year’s counter-culture festival in the Nevada desert. The organizers backed off an earlier statement indicating that they had already decided to make the shots mandatory. They say they won’t decide for sure until the end of the month whether the event that was canceled last year because of the pandemic will take place this summer. Burning Man CEO Marian Goodell said in a video message posted on the group’s web site on April 8 that “vaccines will be required to come to Burning Man.” She erroneously said at that time that the state of Nevada requires that people have proof of vaccination at large gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine commandant reveals new mission preparing for conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/21/marine-commandant-reveals-new-mission-preparing-ch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine Corps Commandant Gen. David H. Berger has revealed new plans for shifting the Corps’ mission to prepare for a future conflict with China: scouting and screening operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New rules allowing small drones to fly over people in U.S. take effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-drones/new-rules-allowing-small-drones-to-fly-over-people-in-u-s-take-effect-idUSKBN2C82FH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said that final rules announced in December took effect on Wednesday allowing for small drones to fly over people and at night, a significant step toward their eventual use for widespread commercial deliveries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service running 'covert operation' to monitor social posts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/the-postal-service-is-running-a-running-a-covert-operations-program-that-monitors-americans-social-media-posts-160022919.html?soc_src=social-sh&amp;soc_trk=tw&amp;tsrc=twtr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The law enforcement arm of the U.S. Postal Service has been quietly running a program that tracks and collects Americans’ social media posts, including those about planned protests, according to a document obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverted cop funding goes to mental health center...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-mental-health-364365482f58133842e2d710f6e71072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANHAM, Md. (AP) — Officials in a Washington suburb marked the groundbreaking this week of a mental health treatment center funded by money diverted from a police training facility. Prince George's County redirected the $20 million for the facility after the police killing of George Floyd , The Washington Post reported . The facility at Doctors Community Medical Center in Lanham will help address a long-standing disparity in access to mental and behavioral health care in the county, County Executive Angela Alsobrooks said at a news conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans, amid medicine scarcity, turn to herbal remedies, bartering...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/cubans-medicine-scarcity-turn-herbal-remedies-bartering-rcna737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba is suffering acute shortages of basic medicines as it grapples with its worst economic crisis in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Black soldiers harassed by IHOP patron...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/04/21/4-black-soldiers-harrased-by-ihop-patron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unnamed patron unloaded racially charged comments at a group of soldiers at IHOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems push $25B to electrify school buses, a Biden priority...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-health-technology-environment-and-nature-business-78082d303d5152c3a0d06eeba53ae7d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic lawmakers on Wednesday unveiled legislation that would invest $25 billion to convert the nation’s fleet of gasoline- and diesel-powered school buses to electric vehicles, aiming at a component of President Joe Biden’s $2.3 trillion infrastructure plan to improve children’s health. The legislation led by Sen. Alex Padilla , D-Calif., seeks to build on the administration’s effort this week to promote the electrification of school buses, which Biden sees as an important step in addressing climate change and economic inequities. School buses make up 90% of the nation’s total bus fleet and typically carry nearly 25 million children each day. Emissions from diesel engines may contribute to respiratory illnesses in children, studies have found, and have been linked to poor academic performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX 'close call' crash suddenly becomes much more mysterious...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/elon-musk-spacex-oneweb-satellite-collision-mystery-b1835045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX claims OneWeb was ‘demonstrably inaccurate’ as satellites passed over 1000 meters - not 60 - from each other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore plant with contaminated J&amp;J jabs had multiple failures, unsanitary conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/baltimore-plant-with-contaminated-johnson-26-johnson-vaccines-had-multiple-failures-unsanitary-conditions-fda-says/ar-BB1fTtnO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan to Stop Prosecuting Prostitution...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/21/manhattan-to-stop-prosecuting-prostitution-part-of-nationwide-shift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney’s office announced Wednesday that it would no longer prosecute prostitution and unlicensed massage, putting the weight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Human being, not political cause': Will death, conviction spur reforms?</title>
      <link>https://www.wenatcheeworld.com/news/human-being-not-a-political-cause-will-floyd-s-death-chauvin-conviction-spur-reforms/article_949932be-a24c-11eb-84e0-d7aec10c2934.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wenatcheeworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — Racial justice advocates and legal experts on Tuesday hailed former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin’s murder conviction in the killing of George Floyd, expressing hopes the case could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christie gears up for 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/chris-christie-2024-presidential-election-4eac5391-8239-4a92-93e1-4f0fb5b367ab.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Absent another run by former President Trump, the field would be wide open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Releasing Long-Awaited Update To Restrict Apps From 'Tracking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iphone-ios-privacy-update/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New mobile platform has privacy controls to limit how advertisers and companies like Facebook can track you online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Mixing Human Body Parts With Robots, Monkeys. What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2021/04/21/scientists-are-mixing-human-body-parts-with-robots-and-monkeys-we-dont-want-to-see-whats-next/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent scientific experiments reveal a dangerous desire — and the increasing ability — to alter the fundamental elements of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin crackdown on Navalny allies as he fights for life...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210421121015-yheep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-PUTIN/PROTESTS-DETENTIONS (URGENT):Police detain more than 100 people at protests in support of Navalny - protest monitor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUILTY, GUILTY, GUILTY</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/04/20/derek-chauvin-jury-reaches-verdict-george-floyd-death-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following nearly a year of protest, introspection and raw emotion, former Minneapolis officer Derek Chauvin has been found guilty of second-degree murder and two other charges in Floyd's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ TO PROBE POLICE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/george-floyd-verdict-police-reform-doj-e24dd1a390a781af3495fa1e0271f492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General Merrick Garland is expected to announce that the Justice Department is opening a sweeping investigation into policing practices in Minneapolis after the guilty verdict in George Floyd's death, a person familiar with the matter told The Associated Press on Wednesday. The announcement comes a day after former officer Derek Chauvin was found guilty of murder and manslaughter in Floyd's death last May, setting off a wave of relief but also sadness across the country. The Black man's death prompted months of mass protests against policing in the U.S.  The Justice Department is already investigating whether the officers involved in Floyd's death violated Floyd's civil rights. The investigation announced Wednesday is known as a “pattern or practice" and will be a more sweeping probe of the entire department and may result in major changes to policing there, the official said. The official had direct knowledge of the matter but was not authorized to speak publicly about the upcoming announcement, planned for Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER-MUTANT COULD PROLONG PANDEMIC?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14667687/scientists-world-most-mutated-covid-strain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have detected what is believed to be the world’s mutated Covid strain as fears grow new super variants may prolong the pandemic. The team of experts revealed their findings in a pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Who Drink 3-5 Cups Of Coffee Daily Have Better Memory?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drink-coffee-more-alert-memory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coffee drinkers had a more "efficient" brain, with quicker connectivity in the cerebellum, the right precuneus, and the right insular.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran celebrates 'explosion' at 'sensitive Israel missile factory'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-media-celebrates-explosion-at-sensitive-israel-missile-factory-665875</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports indicate the explosion happened near Ramle at a routine test at the Tomer factory for advanced weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry over TV show that has 'ISIS' kidnap celebs, tell them they'll be executed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9495115/Outcry-Iraq-TV-fake-ISIS-fighters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TV show in Iraq has sparked outcry over fake ISIS fighters 'kidnapping' celebrities, strapping fake suicide vests to them and telling them they will be executed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research finds new variant potentially resistant to antibodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/research-finds-new-coronavirus-variant-potentially-resistant-to-antibodies-665836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During lab tests, research showed that "several neutralizing antibodies are ineffective in controlling other variants with the same genetic markers as BV-1," the university said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang Wins Endorsement from Left-Wing Rival...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/21/andrew-yang-wins-endorsement-from-left-wing-rival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang may be leading early polls in the New York City mayor’s race, but he has nonetheless faced skepticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES crisis deepens as former president expelled, advisers resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/apr/21/golden-globes-crisis-philip-berk-former-president-expelled-and-advisors-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Foreign Press Association expels Philip Berk after he shared article calling Black Lives Matter a ‘racist hate group’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian sub missing after torpedo test...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/indonesia-submarine-missing-53-on-board-after-expected-torpedo-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say they lost contact with the 40-year-old submarine's crew north of Bali, and they've asked Singapore and Australia for help finding it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
