<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Taunts Bill Maher... </title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-labels-bill-maher-wacko-comedian-who-tells-so-many-lies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He is right about one thing, though," Donald Trump said of Bill Maher. "I will win again in 2020. Otherwise, he pays 95% in taxes!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Proud Boys, antifa showdown mark tipping point for Portland?</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2019/08/will-proud-boys-antifa-showdown-mark-a-tipping-point-for-portland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We’ve been sitting on a powder keg and everything is kind of coming to a head.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jeffrey Needed Three Orgasms A Day'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/08/09/epstein-three-orgasms-per-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who served as one of Jeffrey Epstein's personal masseuses testified that the accused sex trafficker needed to have multiple orgasms a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Couple Caught Having Sex In Car Parked In Police HQ Lot...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/autoeroticism/parking-lot-romance-634809</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are going to get naked and have sex with your partner in the back seat of an automobile, your car should be located anywhere but the parking lot of the local police department. That important</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Tyson opens up: 'I hurt everybody'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaaf/sec/2019/08/09/mike-tyson-alabama-football-players-advice-nick-saban/1968601001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former heavyweight boxing champion Mike Tyson, talking to Alabama football players, urges them to love themselves and manage anger in a healthy way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hepatitis A breaking out across country...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/08/10/hepatitis-vaccine-outbreak-spreads-shadows-opioid-epidemic/1967284001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the opioid crisis, the hepatitis A virus is spreading in more than half the states and making its way into the general public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Williamson says 'powerful forces' on left out to end campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/marianne-williamson-powerful-forces-left-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insurgent Democratic presidential candidate Marianne Williamson claims that “powerful forces” of the left are to keep her away from the third Democratic debate next month with smears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia nuke leak: Footage of hazmat officials escalates radiation panic...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1164125/Russia-nuclear-leak-radiation-Putin-iodine-hazmat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILLING footage from Russia has intensified fears of a nuclear radiation accident after ambulances were spotted lined with protective chemical sheets and hospitals workers were seen wearing hazmat suits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broke and sleeping rough, he fibbed way into tryout -- then scored 86-yard run!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/09/us/nfl-rookie-sheehy-guiseppi-touchdown-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cleveland Browns rookie wide receiver Damon Sheehy-Guiseppi stole the show Thursday in the team's first preseason game with an 86-yard punt return for a touchdown against the Washington Redskins. But even the most diehard fans didn't know his name before that play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with placing hidden camera in airplane bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/houston-man-charged-placing-hidden-camera-airplane-bathroom/story?id=64897031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Malaysian man, and Halliburton employee, is facing charges of video voyeurism after he allegedly planted a hidden camera in an airplane bathroom earlier this year. Choon Ping Lee is accused of planting the video camera on United Airlines flight 646 from San Diego to Houston on May 5. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICA: Rise In 'Doomsday Prepping'; Mainstream 'Culture Of Fear'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-finds-rise-in-doomsday-prepping-due-to-mainstream-american-culture-of-fear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Doomsday prepping" or stockpiling food, medicine, weapons and other supplies in case of an apocalyptic scenario has long been considered peculiar behavior only exhibited by conspiracy theorists and other extremists in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Museum of Death, every day like Manson anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/la-me-museum-of-death-manson-2019-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Museum of Death, interest in Manson isn’t heightened. It’s never really gone away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is film 'THE HUNT' misfire or direct hit in left-right divide?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/456950-is-the-film-the-hunt-a-misfire-or-a-direct-hit-in-our-left-right-divide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universal Pictures just jumped into the culture wars with both feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the All-Digital Actor...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/behind-screen/rise-all-digital-actor-1229783 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This fall's 'Gemini Man' and 'The Irishman' are just the tip of the iceberg for how studios will look to capitalize on de-aging VFX techniques: "It's safer and cheaper than plastic surgery."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' $90 MILLION OPENING?</title>
      <link>https://www.cinemablend.com/news/2477895/how-much-money-joker-could-make-in-its-opening-weekend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cinemablend.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’re two months way from the Clown Prince of Crime taking the spotlight for himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Recent political rhetoric has echoed 'Hitler in 1934'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/456936-pope-francis-cautions-against-nationalism-says-recent-political</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Friday said he was “concerned” about recent political rhetoric, cautioning against nationalism and saying that recent political speeches he’s heard “resemble those of Hitler in 1934.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flying shame' movment growing in Sweden...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/swedes-are-switching-planes-trains-here-s-why-n1027666</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Flight should be seen as a precious gift, to be used wisely and sparingly, not blown on cheap weekend jaunts,” a climate academic told NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKOUT MYSTERY IN UK: FURY AS BRITAIN BROUGHT TO KNEES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7343681/Government-launches-probe-mysterious-power-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Energy watchdog Ofgem has demanded an urgent report from National Grid after a major power cut yesterday caused travel chaos and cut electricity for almost one million people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin covering up nuclear disaster?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7340445/Putins-6-000-mph-hypersonic-missile-exploded-test-causing-radiation-spike-north-Russia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spike in radiation in Russia yesterday may have been caused when one of Vladimir Putin's top secret Zircon hypersonic missiles exploded during tests, according to news reports in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires 2 projectiles into sea...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190809210922-cm34s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (URGENT):N.Korea fires two projectiles into sea off eastern coast -Yonhap</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
