<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Plan to Start Building Wall Monday Crumbles in Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/federal-judge-blocks-trump-from-using-2-5b-in-military-funds-for-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California federal judge issued a ruling blocking Trump from using $2.5 billion in military funds to build a wall along the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman banned from WALMART for eating half a cake, refusing to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/06/29/walmart-ban-texas-woman-reportedly-banned-police-cake-theft/1604324001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six months after a Texas woman was banned by Wichita Falls police for drinking wine from a Pringles can, a second has been banned for taking the cake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hero 9/11 first responder with cancer dies; Testified to Congress with Jon Stewart...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/hero-9-11-first-responder-dies-53-congress-jon-stewart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 9/11 first responder has died two weeks after appearing on Capitol Hill with Jon Stewart, according to a report Saturday. He was 53.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sabotage? Space clean-up drones could have military implications...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/science/space/space-junk-or-sabotage-space-cleanup-drones-could-have-military-implications/news-story/e2cbbb479ea620a64a43ddc0d860c30c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China calls them scavengers, Russia calls them inspectors and the US calls them threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summit still relevant?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190629-who-needs-g20-question-gets-louder-osaka</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who needs the G20? Question gets louder in Osaka</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMZ diplomacy? Trump outreach to Kim for border rendezvous...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/12c0389ada294c158ff1989bc7049cad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recreational Drug Use Surges Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/recreational-drug-surges-worldwide-un-130000996.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Some 271 million people globally, or more than one in 20 of the population aged 15 to 64, used recreational drugs in 2017, according to newly released data from the United Nations World Drug Report. That’s a 30% increase from 2009.The use of cannabis, cocaine, amphetamines and prescription</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott by Whites of SAfrican Restaurant Reflects Growing Sense of Grievance...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/29/world/africa/south-africa-spur-boycott.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Afrikaners are spurning a once-cherished restaurant chain to protest its banning of a white man. The boycott has drawn “an eye roll” among many black South Africans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside horrors of dog festival where animals are boiled ALIVE to make stew...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-horrors-yulin-dog-festival-17264832</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING CONTENT: The defenceless dogs whimper and howl in terror before they are boiled and burned alive at the festival in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: U.S. Oil Output Tops 12 Million Barrels a Day for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-oil-output-tops-12-120000720.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. crude output soared to new heights in April, highlighting OPEC’s dilemma just days before the producer group meets amid growing geopolitical threats.A government report on Friday showed U.S. production grew 2.1% in April to 12.16 million barrels a day. Booming shale production from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING 737 Max Software Outsourced to $9-an-Hour Engineers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boeings-737-max-software-outsourced-204657048.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It remains the mystery at the heart of Boeing Co.’s 737 Max crisis: how a company renowned for meticulous design made seemingly basic software mistakes leading to a pair of deadly crashes. Longtime Boeing engineers say the effort was complicated by a push to outsource work to lower-paid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Godzilla' Divorce Approaches With $38 Billion Bezos Breakup...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/38-billion-divorce-jeff-mackenzie-100000923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- One of the biggest wealth transfers in history is expected in coming days.With the flick of a judge’s pen, a $38 billion stake in Amazon.com Inc. will pass to MacKenzie Bezos as part of her separation from company founder Jeff Bezos.“This is the Godzilla of all divorces,” said Peter Walzer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FOX Staffer Drops $750 Million Suit Over SHOWTIME's 'LOUDEST VOICE'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/laurie-luhn-roger-ailes-suit-loudest-voice-1203256223/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurie Luhn, the former Fox News staffer who made sexual abuse allegations against Roger Ailes, has dropped a $750 million lawsuit against Showtime over the forthcoming miniseries “Loudest Vo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL HOTEL reservations sell out in 2 minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/hotels/2019/06/27/taco-bell-hotel-reservations-sell-out-in-2-minutes/1587139001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hotel pop-up experience in Palm Springs, California, will be Taco Bell-themed to the extreme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  FISH OIL DOES NOTHING TO BOOST BRAIN HEALTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9398518/over-50s-who-buy-fish-oil-supplements-to-boost-brains-are-wasting-their-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLDER Brits should not waste their money buying brain-boosting supplements such as fish oil, experts warn. Instead they should invest in a pair of walking shoes and eat plenty of salmon and trout, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beneath the smiles and handshakes, tensions simmer as world leaders meet for G20...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3016538/beneath-smiles-and-handshakes-tensions-simmer-world-leaders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Xi Jinping makes beeline to shake hands with Donald Trump before traditional ‘family photo’ at start of Osaka summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA ADDRESSES WORLD LEADERS IN OSAKA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7191497/Ivanka-Trump-joins-father-meets-world-leaders-including-Russias-President-Putin-G20.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's senior White House adviser Ivanka has been pictured  with her husband and colleague Jared Kushner attending crucial talks in Osaka, Japan, today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants now soundstage for our national politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Restaurants-are-now-a-soundstage-for-our-national-14059927.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent weeks, we've witnessed two high-profile collisions between the food service industry and an unwelcome potential patron. In the first, Cracker Barrel - the Tennessee-based chain best known for its simpler-times decor and crowd-pleasing portions - came out with a forceful statement barring Grayson Fritts, the sheriff's detective-cum-Baptist preacher who advocated the arrest and execution of LGBTQ people, from holding an event at one of its restaurants in Cleveland, Tennessee.  In the second instance, a server at Aviary, an upscale Chicago cocktail bar, was briefly detained by the Secret Service after allegedly spitting in the face of Eric Trump while the president's son was visiting the city on business.  Happily, there was more widespread support for Cracker Barrel than for the spitting server. A hatemonger with murderous intent doesn't deserve anyone's hospitality. But no one in the industry condones the physical assault of a patron.  Yet, in whatever way we regard these events, the fact remains that restaurants are now part of the soundstage for our ongoing national spectacle. Whether the bar or restaurant serves merely as the backdrop, as in the cases last year of Kirstjen Nielsen, Stephen Miller and Mitch McConnell, or takes an active role in the drama, as was the case with Cracker Barrel, Aviary or my own restaurant last June, the business involved inevitably comes under attack. A portion of the public will scold owners and managers about "staying in their lane" and express chagrin at the loss of a perceived "politics-free zone."  The comments tend to fall into one of two camps: either that it's illegal to discriminate against a person for his or her political stance or that it violates some imaginary unwritten universal service-for-all hospitality industry code.  Neither is quite right. Eateries have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Missiles Found in Libyan Rebel Compound...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/american-missiles-found-in-libyan-rebel-compound/ar-AADAofz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of guns, grenades mailed to South America are seized in crackdown on Florida ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article232029987.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carter Calls Trump Illegitimate President...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/jimmy-carter-says-trump-is-an-illegitimate-president-he-didnt-actually-win-the-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Jimmy Carter said he believes President Donald Trump's election was illegitimate and "he didn't actually win the election in 2016."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED WARNING ITALY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7191493/Boy-dies-heat-exhaustion-Spain-country-battles-wildfires-rest-Europe-sizzles.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The temperature was recorded in the southern village of Villevieille and beat the previous record for France of 111.4F (44.1C) recorded in Saint-Christol-les-Ales and Conqueyrac in 2003.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngstown's paper closes after 150 years... </title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/news/2019/06/the-vindicator-youngstowns-daily-newspaper-will-close-after-150-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Youngstown Vindicator told employees Friday afternoon it will end production in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE HOTTEST DAY IN HISTORY!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/heat/news/2019-06-26-record-breaking-heat-wave-europe-june-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All-time record highs for June have already been topped, but all-time records for any month of the year could be threatened by this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Williamson decries 'aggressive energy'  of event...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/marianne-williamson-spell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot babies tackling teenage pregnancies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/robot-babies-tackling-teenage-pregnancies-colombia-233437713.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caldas (Colombia) (AFP) - "Anthony" cried so hard at night that Susana Ortegon couldn't sleep. "This experience was pretty tough, it's not easy being a mommy or a daddy," Ortegon told AFP. It's a voluntary program launched in schools by the Caldas municipality, just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crunch time at G20 as US-China trade showdown looms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crunch-time-g20-us-china-trade-showdown-looms-200737060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a first day dominated by public shows of bonhomie, all eyes at the G20 turned Saturday to a pivotal trade showdown between economic rivals China and the United States. Trump and China's Xi Jinping will meet at around 11:30 am (0230 GMT) in a bid to thrash out a truce in a long-running trade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince feted at summit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b2ff24266d47483abf5fb92cf50ade5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES mechanics defying court order, continue work slowdown; Disrupting flights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7eb99124b7aa4ff9aa03f659eb18fd7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands gather at Stonewall 50 years after LGBTQ uprising...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3454ab8c6b254a679afbfd8b25e1f9f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Dems  in a Bubble on Immigration...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/_pages/cjxg9ymru007yl6y6zstts42l.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debates proved that they are fundamentally out of touch with the difficult realities of the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Silicon Valley's UFO Hunters...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/597ebn/meet-silicon-valleys-ufo-hunters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small group of venture capitalists and technologists believe that humans can capture and reverse-engineer UFOs—and that trying to do so might be a good investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai leader's wife dramatically leaves him, flees country...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9395501/dubai-wife-princess-flees-31-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE wife of Dubai’s ruler Sheik Mohammed bin Rashid al-Maktoum has left him — and taken £31million to start a new life, it is understood. Princess Haya, who had not been seen since February, is sai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Urges Universities To Monitor Chinese Students, Scholars...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/06/28/728659124/fbi-urges-universities-to-monitor-some-chinese-students-and-scholars-in-the-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As suspicion toward China spreads to academia, the FBI has advised at least 10 U.S. universities to monitor academics associated with certain Chinese institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant African Snails found in luggage at Atlanta airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/article232070387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  McConnell relishes role as 'Grim Reaper'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c842a0bcecc840628a991092da3e7ce3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right group 'used police data to compile death list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jun/28/german-far-right-group-used-police-data-to-compile-death-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists linked to military and police suspected of preparing terror attack, reports say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  'DeepNude' app to 'undress' women shut down after furor...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190628-deepnude-app-undress-women-shut-down-after-furor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'DeepNude' app to 'undress' women shut down after furor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Mess Causing Countless Internet Outages...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/bgp-route-leak-internet-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may not have heard of the Border Gateway Protocol, but you definitely know when it goes wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest year-on-year drop in Bay Area home prices in 7+ years...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/business/networth/article/Bay-Area-home-prices-fell-1-7-in-May-biggest-14056290.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After home sales rose at double-digit rates in the first half of last year, growth began slowing in the second half to almost a crawl this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best first half of year for S&amp;P 500 in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/28/stock-market-trump-xi-meeting-at-the-g-20-summit-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks closed higher on Friday, boosted by bank shares, as investors looked ahead to a key meeting between President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping. Wall Street also wrapped up its best first half to a year in two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska Now Crime Capital of America...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2019/06/28/us-attorney-general-announces-10-million-in-emergency-funds-to-support-public-safety-in-rural-alaska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement comes a month after William P. Barr visited the state to hear concerns about a lack of police in rural communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian convicted of impaired operation of canoe...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/in-a-case-that-made-canadian-legal-history-ontario-man-convicted-of-impaired-operation-of-a-canoe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is easy to laugh at the idea of drinking and canoeing. But the Sillars case shows how devastating the consequences of a boating accident can be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Additional US fighter jets sent to Gulf amid Iran tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d0a8fe7f91924bb69a6c5936e3acd30f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sulfuric acid leaked from derailed train car... </title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/train-derails-in-commercial-tunnel-between-michigan-canada/511951622/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 13,700 gallons of sulfuric acid has spilled from one of about 40 freight train cars that derailed in an international tunnel connecting Michigan and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudists, burkini bathers in heatwave pool standoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/06/27/french-nudists-burkini-bathers-heatwave-pool-standoff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of French nudists are threatening to &amp;quot;bare all&amp;quot; against burkini-clad bathers in an unlikely showdown at public baths in Grenoble as an ongoing row over the body-covering garment has resurfaced in the heatwave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fifth of All European Flights Delayed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/more-than-a-fifth-of-all-european-flights-delayed-in-may-1.1280257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grain-free food linked to dog heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/grain-free-food-may-linked-dog-heart-disease-172221153.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent years have seen a surge in grain-free dog and cat foods, as increasing numbers of pet owners cast aside kibble packed with cheap corn, wheat and barley fillers for what they believe is a healthier alternative. The reality may be more complex, with the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) announcing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor Kamala treats him as hostile witness!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dbf7aa798cf54646a7b8c705c6af27e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Alexa curses customer after he cancels AMAZON Prime...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9390172/alexa-insults-man-cancelled-amazon-prime-subscription/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRTUAL ASSISTANT Alexa told a customer he was a “s**thead” after he asked it to play some music. Michael Slade, 29 was shocking to hear his Amazon Echo Dot call him the rude name a day after he ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster City sees storm warnings every day...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/06/25/disaster-city-sees-storm-warnings-every-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  NJ warns not to swim even touch popular swimming lake amid algae disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/New-Jersey-Warns-Dont-Swim-in-Lake-Hopatcong--Dont-Even-Touch-the-Water-511908612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey environmental officials say people shouldn't swim in Lake Hopatcong or even touch the water because of an extensive harmful algal bloom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami sex fetish club owner convicted of murder after jury sees video of him dumping body...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article231993167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARBY'S Testing 'Meat-Based Plants'...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/06/27/arbys-tests-meat-products-that-look-like-carrots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arby's is turning the plant-based meat craze on its head by testing meat-based plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 MILLION: Round 2 Draws Bigger Crowd... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/06/democratic-debate-ratings-surge-kamala-harris-joe-biden-nbc-1202639418/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second night of the first Democratic debate of the 2020 presidential election season was certainly punchier and snappy than the previous evening. Kamala Harris came out of her corner Thursday i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Hundreds of Haitians, Africans wade through Rio Grande, stroll into USA -- carrying luggage!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-hundreds-of-haitians-africans-wade-through-rio-grande-stroll-into-u-s-carrying-luggage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Groups of hundreds of Africans, Haitians and others from Central and South America continue to trudge across the U.S.- Mexico border in record numbers, despite promises from Mexico to help stop the massive migration. Footage from the Del Rio Sector of the border in Texas shows scores are making their way in mini-caravans, with many …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carter Calls Trump Illegitimate President...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/jimmy-carter-suggests-trump-an-illegitimate-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy Carter said he doesn’t believe President Trump won the 2016 election legitimately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After $50 million price cut, vast Bel-Air property may still languish...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/realestate/hot-property/la-fi-hp-senderos-canyon-bel-air-price-cut-20190628-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senderos Canyon, a tract of 258 undeveloped acres in one of L.A.'s toniest neighborhoods, is relisted for $75 million, or 40% less than in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATINGS: Round 2 Draws Bigger Crowd... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/democratic-debate-part-2-rises-tv-ratings-thursday-june-27-2019-1221677 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary ratings for the second wave of presidential candidates on NBC are up 15 percent over Wednesday's telecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE HOTTEST DAY IN HISTORY!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-06-26-europe-heatwave-germany-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe is sweltering under a deadly record-breaking heat wave. Here's the latest.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
