<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Violent confrontations rock Puerto Rico protests demanding gov step down...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/article232779917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Biden won friends in Hollywood by helping studios get movies into China...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-07-17/joe-biden-money-hollywood-studios-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has delivered more for Hollywood for years longer than any of his rivals. Now industry donors are delivering for him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley Bans Gendered Language; 'Manhole' Now 'Maintenance Hole'...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/07/18/gendered-language-like-manhole-will-soon-be-banned-from-berkeleys-city-codes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon, there will be no more manholes in the city of Berkeley, California. There will also be no chairmen, no manpower, no policemen or policewomen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino Says 'STAR TREK' Film Will Be 'PULP FICTION' in Space...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/07/quentin-tarantino-once-upon-a-time-interview-leonardo-dicaprio-brad-pitt-margot-robbie-star-trek-pulp-fiction-1202647835/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Most times Deadline has done in-depth interviews with Quentin Tarantino, the occasion has been a hot-button moment that begged for clarity. Like the time he (temporarily) scrapped The Ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AD ASTRA' Trailer: Brad Pitt Has Another Oscar Contender With Space Epic...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2019/07/ad-astra-new-trailer-brad-pitt-james-gray</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director James Gray also reveals the layers beneath Pitt’s new role: “He plays someone with schizoid tendencies.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Coffee Shaming...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/07/coffee-financial-advice/594244/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal-finance gurus really hate coffee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shares Plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/18/us-stock-futures-earnings-trade-fears-weigh.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Thursday as investors were concerned about the latest batch of quarterly corporate reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline Fines Unruly Passenger $106,000 for 'Dangerous Behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/18/106000-bill-from-jet2-to-woman-who-tried-to-open-plane-doors-in-air.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two fighter jets were scrambled to escort the plane she was traveling on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malnutrition, disease rising in NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-aid/malnutrition-disease-rising-in-north-korea-aid-organization-idUSKCN1UD0P4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rates of malnutrition and disease are increasing in North Korea as it faces a ha...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate fears lift Greens' chances of running Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-greens-analysis/climate-fears-lift-greens-chances-of-running-germany-idUSKCN1UD1RX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former trampolinist and a children's author have led the Greens to a spec...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES: Homeland Security has gutted programs aimed at detecting WMDs...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-trump-homeland-security-wmd-terrorism-20190830-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security has dismantled or ended multiple programs intended to counter WMD attacks, a Times investigation found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass murderer? Cult leader? Musician? Charles Manson son wrestles with father's legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-07-18/mass-murderer-cult-leader-musician-charles-mansons-son-wrestles-with-fathers-legacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mass murderer? Cult leader? Musician? Charles Manson’s son, Michael Brunner, wrestles with father’s legacy and notoriety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AD ASTRA' Official Trailer: Brad Pitt Has Another Oscar Contender With Space Epic...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2019/07/ad-astra-official-trailer-brad-pitt-james-gray-1202158675/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Once Upon a Time in Hollywood" isn't the only Brad Pitt contender this awards season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling Superpowers, Rival Billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/longform/race-to-the-moon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space-based businesses currently contribute $350 billion to global gross domestic product</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Worked at AMAZON Fulfillment Center; They Treat Workers Like Robots'...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5629233/amazon-warehouse-employee-treatment-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The author of 'On the Clock' investigates the experience of modern low-wage work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TRUTH' to Kick Off Venice Film Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/catherine-deneuve-kore-eda-hirokazu-ethan-hawke-drama-the-truth-venice-film-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film is first that Japanese director Kore-eda Hirokazu has made outside his home country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dropping F-Bomb Increases Pain Tolerance By Third...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dropping-f-bomb-increases-pain-tolerance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that swearing when injured has a measurable effect on pain tolerance. In fact, dropping the F-bomb when in pain increases tolerance by up to 33%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have We Hit Peak Podcast?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/18/style/why-are-there-so-many-podcasts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If past experience (cough, blogs) is any indication, a shakeout is nigh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellphones flight danger? They are on these BOEING jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/are-cellphones-a-flight-danger-they-are-on-these-boeing-jets-1.1288882</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man screaming 'You die!' kills at least 23 at anime studio...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b10907eaf37945889d9ee4339df92aaa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bond Vigilantes Lose Sway Over Govts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bond-vigilantes-lose-sway-over-100100505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Balance of Power newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Politics on Twitter and Facebook for more.Bill Clinton’s political adviser, James Carville, once said he’d like to be reincarnated as the bond market, since “you can intimidate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoid Big Penis supplement, FDA warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/07/17/fda-big-penis-sexual-enhancement-supplement-notice/1764407001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sexual enhancement product Big Penis should be avoided because of a hidden ingredient, the Food and Drug AdministrationÂ warned Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New trailer today...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/it-chapter-two-first-look-kicks-comic-con-1225246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Line's third annual ScareDiego revved up the scares (and laughs) as Conan O’Brien brought out Andy Muschietti, Jessica Chastain, James McAvoy, Bill Hader, and others to share secrets from the horror sequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom wood kennels, memory foam beds: Wild world of pet furniture...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/article/Custom-wood-kennels-memory-foam-beds-The-wild-14102846.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pet furniture has come a long way from teal carpeted cat towers and lumpy plaid dog beds.  For discerning pet owners who treat their cats and dogs like family - in some cases better than family - designers are creating stylish, even glamorous, furniture. Witness the new $5,000 Crystal Clear Lotus Cat Tower by the Refined Feline, with three platforms for lounging and a hideaway cubby at the bottom lined in white faux fur. (You can see one at the trendy Los Angeles cat cafe Crumbs &amp; Whiskers.) And now you and Buddy can catnap or watch DOGTV on matching tufted Chesterfield-style Wayfair Archie &amp; Oscar sofas; his is a $399 miniaturized version of yours in faux-leather scaled with similar nailhead trim and turned legs.  None of these products, however, guarantee that they will keep their paws off your favorite club chair.  Over the past five years, pet furniture has been growing in sophistication and durability, says Phil Cooper, a pet industry expert with more than 50 years in the business. This trend has blossomed with the development of regional pet stores and local pet boutiques, which tend to offer more personalized service than big-box stores, plus the rise of fancy pet product websites, he says. An army of pet experts, behaviorists and designers is looking for ways to make dogs and cats sleep and play more comfortably, stylishly and safely.  "The choices available to pet owners today did not exist even a few years ago," says Steve King, chief executive of the American Pet Products Association.  Jackson Cunningham, founder of Tuft + Paw, just got back from Italy, where he was sourcing partners to develop designer cat furniture. His three-year-old company has appealed to fussy feline owners with sleek gray scratching towers and retro birch litter box furniture.  "Making pet furniture is very interesting because...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Set To Break Box Office Record?</title>
      <link>https://www.flickeringmyth.com/2019/07/it-chapter-two-could-top-deadpools-record-r-rated-box-office-opening-weekend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.flickeringmyth.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It Chapter Two is set to have a massive debut when it arrives in cinemas, with projections of $130 million-plus for its opening weekend. It was a huge critical and commercial success, bringing in a massive $700 million after a $127 million domestic opening weekend. The film is currently the fourth highest-grossing R-rated film of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood-soaked 'IT' sequel jolts Comic-Con...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/blood-soaked-sequel-jolts-comic-con-life-083218150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Diego Comic-Con kicked off with a chorus of shrieks -- and gallons of blood -- as New Line Cinema unveiled spine-chilling footage from "It: Chapter 2," the sequel to the highest-grossing horror movie of all time. The Warner Bros-owned studio used Wednesday's preview night of the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough technique eradicates mosquitoes...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-07-breakthrough-technique-eradicates-mosquitoes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A breakthrough technique harnessing two methods to target disease-carrying mosquitoes was able to effectively eradicate buzzing biters in two test sites in China, according to research published on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You're Going to Vote for Me or You're Going to be So Goddam Poor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/07/president-trump-tells-businessman-youre-going-to-vote-for-me-or-youre-going-to-be-so-goddam-poor-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes of night Trump partied at Mar-a-Lago with Epstein, NFL cheerleaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Behind-the-scenes-of-the-night-Trump-partied-at-14103852.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump was coming off a bruising few years: His casino and real estate business had teetered on the edge of collapse, awash in debt. His marriage to Ivana Trump had disintegrated, and his relationship with model Marla Maples had fallen apart.  In November 1992, eager for a comeback, Trump threw a raucous party with NFL cheerleaders at his Mar-a-Lago estate in Florida and invited NBC to tape the event.  Footage of that party, unearthed and aired by NBC News on Wednesday, shows Trump grabbing dancing cheerleaders and socializing with financier Jeffrey Epstein, who was arrested last week and charged with sex trafficking.  Trump has repeatedly said that he is "not a fan" of Epstein's and that the two had a falling out about 15 years ago. Epstein, who owns a home in Palm Beach near Mar-a-Lago, pleaded guilty in 2008 to soliciting a minor for prostitution.  "I knew him like everybody in Palm Beach knew him," the president said of Epstein this month. "He was a fixture in Palm Beach."  In the video from the 1992 party, the two men appear chummy, chuckling as Trump appears to point out women on the dance floor. At one point, Trump can be seen whispering in Epstein's ear, causing the financier to double over in laughter.  The footage was taken for a feature on Trump that aired on the NBC talk show "A Closer Look" that month. On the segment, host Faith Daniels described Trump's agreeing to come on the show after he kissed the news anchor on the lips in front of photographers at a charity dinner in New York while her husband's back was turned.  Trump's interactions with women at the Mar-a-Lago party - welcome or not - provides visual evidence of the kind of behavior he would later brag about on a 2005 "Access Hollywood" recording that surfaced at the end of the presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Racist,' 'socialist' lines drawn for 2020...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/36f5e67a145c4f0eb7661f2ca453b0a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4IOXhBKoSFg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharing a mix of breaking news, Arizona stories, engaging discussions, and popular culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd chants 'Send Her Back' about Omar...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/07/17/trump_maga_rally_crowd_chants_send_her_back_to_rep_ilhan_omar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attendees at a 'Make America Great Again' campaign rally Wednesday night in Greenville, N.C. chanted "send her back" after President Trump trashed Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-MN), claiming she is not proud of America and that she wouldn't disavow al Qaeda in an interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOKGOOGLE Quietly Tracking You on Sex Websites...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/17/opinion/google-facebook-sex-websites.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study scanned 22,484 pornography sites and found them riddled with trackers from major technology companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY calls heiress remarks about workers 'gross and unfair'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/disney-calls-heiress-s-remarks-about-workers-gross-and-unfair-1.1288729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First look at 'UNTOUCHABLE' doc about Harvey Weinstein's alleged sexual abuse...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/17/first-look-at-untouchable-doc-about-harvey-weinsteins-alleged-sexual-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its harrowing trailer debuted Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  Imagine if We Didn't Have all the Bullshit...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-if-we-didnt-have-all-bullsht-wed-be-much-further-along</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Could you imagine if we didn’t have the time wasted’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stumbles in Effort to Annex the World's Eyeballs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-stumbles-effort-annex-world-214347521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The optimistic scenario about Netflix Inc. goes like this: The company is wise to spend like mad to create a new generation of entertainment service that capitalizes on the inexorable shift of people away from old ways of wasting time like television toward new modes of wasting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance claim denied after giant gator breaks into Florida woman's home...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/pinellas-county/insurance-claim-denied-after-destructive-clearwater-gator-break-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of May, Mary Wischhusen woke up in the middle of the night to find an aggressive, 11-foot-long gator had broken into her Eagles Landing home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-secret locations of 150 US nukes in Europe accidentally leaked in NATO report...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9525421/locations-of-150-us-nuclear-europe-accidentally-leaked-nato-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SECRET sites storing 150 US nukes have been accidentally revealed in a Nato report, it has been reported. The United States and its allies in the Nato military alliance never disclose the locations…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to hold AG Barr and Commerce chief in criminal contempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/house-vote-criminal-contempt-against-attorney-general-barr-commerce-secretary-n1030901?cid=eml_nbn_20190717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wilbur Ross derided the effort as nothing but "political theater" and "silly."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staying ad-free?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netflix-shares-slide-disappointing-q2-subscriber-growth-221855920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix shares plunged in after-hours trade Wednesday after its quarterly update showed weaker-than-expected subscriber growth for the streaming television sector leader. Netflix said it added 2.7 million new subscribers worldwide in the April-June period, well below expectations, as the sector prepared</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak in Congo declared a global health emergency...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ebola-outbreak-congo-declared-global-175202499.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadly Ebola outbreak in Congo is now an international health emergency, the World Health Organization announced Wednesday after a case was confirmed in a city of 2 million people . A WHO expert committee declined on three previous occasions to advise the United Nations health agency to make the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEY GROPING CHARGES DROPPED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a3353b8a69d4226b96d98dacc34a7ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90 degrees or warmer for 90% of Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/07/17/heat-wave-record-breaking-temperatures-bake-central-eastern-us/1754689001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 290 million people will swelter through theÂ hottest weather of the summer asÂ a record-breaking heat wave bakes the central andÂ eastern U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House scuttles effort to impeach Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/house-vote-impeachment-resolution-against-trump-n1030791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The measure was being pushed by Texas Rep. Al Green, who says the president is unfit for office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb squad responds to drone with fireworks on LA building...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/drone-with-fireworks-strapped-to-it-is-found-on-dtla-building/5401910/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Police Department's bomb squad is responding to reports of a drone that has fireworks attached to it and is on top of a building in the downtown Los Angeles area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSFT giving away software to 'guard' voting machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/microsoft-will-give-away-software-guard-u-s-voting-machines-n1030956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech giant says it has tracked more than 700 cyberattacks by foreign adversaries against U.S. political organizations so far this election cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX tanks after whiffing on paid subscribers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/17/netflix-earnings-q2-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company blamed its Q2 content slate and price increases for the subscriber miss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Sued for Selling Customers' Location to Bounty Hunters...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/43j99g/eff-hits-atandt-with-class-action-lawsuit-for-selling-customers-location-to-bounty-hunters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit, which comes after multiple Motherboard investigations into phone location data selling, is seeking an injunction against AT&amp;T which would try to enforce the deletion of any sold data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley bans gas in new homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Berkeley-becomes-first-U-S-city-to-ban-natural-14102242.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berkeley became the first city nationwide to ban the use of natural gas in new buildings in a unanimous vote Tuesday by the City Council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columnist savaged by colleague at going away party...</title>
      <link>https://www.phillymag.com/news/2019/07/17/stu-bykofsky-inga-saffron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.phillymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrested reporter slams conditions at detention centers...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2019/07/arrested-reporter-slams-conditions-at-us-detention-centers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — A Spanish-language reporter who was recently released from immigration custody says he was held for 15 months in detention centers that were plagued by insects and he had to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRUDEN DEAD AT 83...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/17/wes-pruden-washington-times-editor-and-columnist-d/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wesley Pruden would have undoubtedly wanted to spend his final hours at his keyboard, deftly deflating the pompous, entitled and arrogant of the political establishment, and he came awfully close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trials of HIV jab to start after monkey test success...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/792518/hiv-jab-trials-humans-monkey-success-holy-grail-aids-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Stole 18 Cars -- In 24 Hours!</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/07/15/18-car-thefts-in-24-hours-pgpd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;34-year-old Terry Johnson, of no fixed address, is charged with multiple thefts, property damage and other related charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake FERRARI factory raided...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/792473/ferrari-lamborghini-supercar-fake-cheap-brazil-counterfeit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Best Day -- Was His First Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/mattberman/2020-democratic-primary-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And other things you can learn from new data on how many donors Democratic presidential campaigns got each day this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO:  Ebola outbreak now global emergency...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2019/07/ebola-outbreak-in-congo-declared-a-global-health-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The World Health Organization says the deadly Ebola outbreak in Congo is now an international health emergency after the virus spread this week to a city of 2 million people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia launches criminal case over gay couple's adoption...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-launches-criminal-case-over-gay-couples-adoption-172548071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Wednesday said it had opened an unprecedented criminal case accusing officials of negligence for allowing a gay couple to adopt two children. The Investigative Committee, which probes serious cases, said that Moscow social workers were suspected of criminal negligence for allowing the two</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force warns against storming Area 51 as 'event' reaches 1.5 million attendees...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/air-force-warns-storming-area-51-facebook-event/story?id=64389885</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force is warning people against storming Area 51 in Nevada, after a Facebook event page organizing a meet up at the "Alien Center tourist attraction" went viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Drudge's 'Future' Now Realized, And That Has Legacy Media Enraged...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/timothymeads/2019/07/15/matt-drudges-future-is-now-realized-and-that-has-legacy-media-enraged-n2550087</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth not absolute with AI deception technology...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/453395-truth-is-not-absolute-with-ai-deception-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal challenges may help resolve privacy and developmental concerns so that artificial intelligence can be a viable law enforcement tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK raises alarm after mother held by Iran is taken to mental ward...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-raises-alarm-mother-held-iran-taken-mental-153357016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London demanded the immediate release Wednesday of a jailed British-Iranian aid worker whose husband said she has been transferred to the mental ward of a public hospital in Tehran. Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe's case has roiled Britain's relations with the Islamic republic since her 2016 arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE HEAT TEMPS...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_heat.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food delivery droid wants to use bike lanes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/food-delivery-robot-wants-share-bike-lane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Refraction AI, founded by two researchers at the University of Michigan, joins a crowded field of self-driving delivery vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES GETTING BACK ON MOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/07/trump-and-nasas-uncertain-moon-plans/593986/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA wants to put people back on the lunar surface in 2024, but it doesn’t have the budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren gets big bucks from employees of tech companies she wants to break up...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/07/16/elizabeth-warren-tech-donations-facebook-google-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts senator came in second among the Democratic presidential candidates in donations from employees of Amazon, Apple, Facebook, and Google over the last three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion for hire: Americans embrace clothing rental services...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190717-fashion-hire-americans-embrace-clothing-rental-services</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion for hire: Americans embrace clothing rental services</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CBS EVENING NEWS' Ratings Slip On Norah O'Donnell's Debut As Anchor...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2019/07/17/cbs-evening-news-ratings-slip-on-norah-odonnells-debut-as-anchor/#b1fe2b015b09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ratings data compiled by Nielsen show O'Donnell's first night actually delivered lower ratings than the anchor she replaced, Jeff Glor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There's no justice in America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/792492/el-chapo-life-in-prison-sentence-trial-us-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball Coach Ejected for Fight over Robot Umpire...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/atlantic-league-coach-ejected-for-arguing-over-automated-strike-zone-just-one-inning-into-robot-umpire-era/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank Viola will go down as the first victim of the automated strike zone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters Line up at 4:00 AM for NC Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/07/17/watch-trump-supporters-line-up-at-400-am-for-greenville-nc-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump supporters began lining up early for the president's 2020 re-election campaign rally in Greenville, North Carolina, on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tied up wife's lover, cut off penis, deputies say...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/florida-dismemberment-275903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 17--A gun-toting Florida Man broke into the home of his wife’s lover and cut off the man’s penis with a pair of scissors, according to police who said that the intruder fled the residence with t</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
