<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>In Bahamas, hard-hit island beckons again...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhregister.com/lifestyle/travel/article/In-the-Bahamas-a-hard-hit-island-beckons-again-14820327.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tip Burrows dropped a low-grade expletive when she saw the beach by Banana Bay Restaurant, on the south side of Grand Bahama Island.  "Holy (bad word)!" said the islander, peering into a freshly carved trench. "That wasn't here before."  Nearly two months after Hurricane Dorian battered the Bahamas, Tip, who runs the Humane Society of Grand Bahama, was still discovering new evidence of destruction. On this mid-October afternoon, she had unearthed an inlet on Fortune Beach. As if that weren't alarming enough, the storm surge that had swept away a section of the beach had not come from the ocean lapping at Fortune's feet. It had traversed the island from the north and pushed the sand out to sea like a scene from an eco-horror film.  "We lost two feet of beach," said Danilo Rulli, the restaurant's owner, "but it will slowly come back."  And so will the Bahamas, at possibly an even faster clip than Mother Nature.  "We're going to bring the sparkle back to Grand Bahama," said Steven Johnson, an official with the Grand Bahama Tourism Office who is already working on new initiatives, such as expanding the West End as a seafood destination.  To be sure, Dorian was devastating. The strongest storm ever to strike the Bahamas caused at least 65 deaths and damaged or destroyed more than 13,000 homes on Grand Bahama Island and the Abaco Islands, both in the upper reaches of the 500-mile-long archipelago. Economic loss could rise to $7 billion, more than half of the country's gross national product. But the Bahamas are moving forward - rebuilding homes, reopening businesses, and restoring the spirit of the islands and its people.  "We'll be back bigger and better than before," exclaimed a resident who lives in the East End, the hardest-hit area on Grand Bahama Island.  The Bahamas can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hundreds of records could fall in next week's cold snap...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Hundreds-of-records-could-fall-in-next-week-s-14820980.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arctic blast engulfing the eastern half of the Lower 48 will make mid-November feel like mid-January. Between Sunday and Wednesday, temperatures will sink to levels 15 to 30 degrees colder than normal from the Plains to the East Coast.  The National Weather Service is predicting that about 250 cold records will be established as a result of this polar plunge, from the Gulf Coast to the Great Lakes.  Next week's cold is the second and stronger of back-to-back Arctic fronts sweeping across the nation.  The first front raced from the Midwest to the East Coast between Wednesday and Friday this week. It caused temperatures to drop 15 to 20 degrees in 24 hours along the Eastern Seaboard between Thursday and Friday morning and supported the season's first snow flurries in Washington, D.C.  But temperatures are poised to take an even deeper dive as the second front invades.  The cold front will drop into the Northern Plains and Upper Midwest on Saturday night into Sunday, passing through Minneapolis and Chicago.  On Monday morning, the front will have rapidly progressed eastward, stretching from interior New England southwest to Texas, having sliced through Buffalo, Detroit, Cleveland, Kansas City, St. Louis and Oklahoma City.  By Tuesday morning, it will have reached the East Coast, having passed through all but southeast South Carolina and Florida, which it will cross by Wednesday morning.  On Monday, when the core of the cold grips the Upper Midwest and Great Lakes, Minneapolis will not escape the high teens while Chicago hovers in the 20s. Both cities are likely to see their coldest Veterans Day on record.  "Record low-max and record low mins could be in jeopardy of being tied/broken for both Monday and Tuesday," wrote the National Weather Service office serving Chicago....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish with 'human face' spotted swimming in lake...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/fish-human-face-spotted-lake-20846470</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People on social media have been thoroughly creeped out by a video doing the rounds of a fish, with a very human-like face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whips, chains and fancy food: S&amp;M fetish restaurant opens to rave reviews...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/whips-chains-fancy-food-new-20846224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slave collar-wearing waitresses serve food and also engage in bondage-themed displays</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female jihadis filmed slaughtering soldiers in 'Baghdadi revenge strikes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/isis-female-jihadis-filmed-slaughtering-20842411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Militants attacked an army outpost in northern Mali and killed 53 troops and one civilian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: NASA forced to cut ISS feed when UFOs appear...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/government-forces-nasa-cut-iss-20839773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The head of a UFO disclosure group believes NASA is the "victim" of government laws – and that it is possible UFOs are being seen on ISS live feeds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frenchwoman accuses Polanski of raping her as teen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frenchwoman-accuses-polanski-raping-her-teen-204841844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French former model and actress on Friday accused Oscar-winning director Roman Polanski, whose new film on the persecution of French Jewish army officer Alfred Dreyfus premieres next week, of raping her in a Swiss ski resort when she was a teenager. It is the latest accusation against the 86-year-old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global debate gets underway over married Catholic priests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c3cd8c5c7a4b4811b9cc3ba4452a9963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's Catholics reacted enthusiastically when bishops from across the Amazon called for the ordination of married men as priests to address the clergy shortage in that region....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on Texas gov as calls grow to halt execution...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d99026ae9cf4d88b8da8b020162af6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — In his five years as Texas' governor, Republican Greg Abbott has overseen the execution of nearly 50 prisoners while only once sparing a condemned man's life, after a victims'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgian police arrest more than 25 in clashes at gay movie premiere...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191108173745-a5bue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators blocked the road outside a movie theatre ahead of the first screening of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Collective Suicide in Turkey in Week Highlights Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-09/second-collective-suicide-in-turkey-in-a-week-highlights-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci: Trump sees threat...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/469721-scaramucci-trump-sees-bloomberg-as-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci said late Friday that there is “no question” that Michael Bloomberg would be “the No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Red Alert Now Flashing on Bond Trader's Radar Screen...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/red-alert-now-flashing-bright-050001839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A bond-market warning light that glowed green for years is suddenly flashing red. The bad news for bondholders is that the last time this happened, it was accompanied by the biggest sell-off since the aftermath of the global financial crisis.That indicator is the term premium, which, for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM TO START HIDING LIKES IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/digital/news/instagram-likes-like-counts-hidden-1203399222/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instagram likes are about to disappear from public view for many more users: The Facebook-owned photo sharing service is getting ready to hide like counts from U.S. users as early as next week, CEO…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN PLAYS TO EMPTY HALL</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/sahilkapur/status/1192957650742513664?s=21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“ORANGEBURG — Elizabeth Warren takes the stage at an Environmental Justice forum in South Carolina before a sparse audience. Tom Steyer spoke before her; numerous rivals skipped it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PLAYS IT COOL...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloomberg-flirts-white-house-bid-challenge-biden-172847056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York business tycoon Michael Bloomberg has paved the way for a shot at the US presidency, registering as a candidate in the Alabama Democratic primary race before Friday's filing deadline. Although the 77-year-old billionaire has not publicly announced his run, his inclusion among a crowded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth gives him options rivals don't enjoy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a480a660c9e42488662398498e240d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — There are many questions surrounding Michael Bloomberg's potential presidential candidacy. Whether he'll have enough money to sustain a lengthy and bruising campaign is not one...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALS SPREAD WRONG NAME OF 'WHISTLEBLOWER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumpkins-thought-this-man-was-the-whistleblower-they-were-wrong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Obama staffer has been erroneously accused by the pro-Trump internet of blowing the whistle on the Ukraine affair. He didn’t. But now he’s getting death threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO PLAYED WHO?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7666103/DJ-Randy-Credico-says-feared-guy-helped-Trump-win-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Bannon told a federal court Friday that Roger Stone was considered  the Trump Campaign's 'access point' to WikiLeaks and Julian Assange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia far-right protest at gay film premiere...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/georgia-far-groups-threaten-disrupt-gay-film-premiere-101909930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of far-right activists burned a rainbow flag and cried "Shame!" during a protest in the Georgian capital against an Oscar-nominated Swedish-Georgian gay-themed film which premiered amid a heavy police presence. The drama has won worldwide critical acclaim but was denounced by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Detains Nuke Inspector, Bans From Key Atomic Site...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/state-department-slams-iran-for-blocking-nuclear-inspector-from-accessing-contested-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Department officials described Iran's blocking of an international nuclear inspector from accessing key nuclear sites as "outrageous and unwarranted."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White restaurant owner gets 10 years for enslaving black man...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/08/south-carolina-white-restaurant-manager-sentenced-jail-enslaving-black-man/2527814001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white restaurant manager in South Carolina was sentenced to 10 years in prison for enslaving and torturing an African American cook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEN ONLY:  'IRISHMAN' lead actress speaks just SIX words in entire 210-minute film...	</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/10309008/the-irishman-anna-paquin-only-speaks-six-words-netflix-film/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE IRISHMAN viewers have been left outraged after noticing “lead” actress Anna Paquin only speaks SIX words in the three and a half hour Netflix film. The Martin Scorsese movie is the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business braces for 2020 recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/businesses-spending-indicators-recession-533481fc-dba7-4b5c-add4-c11628c335bc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firms are trying to protect themselves, but their spending pullback itself could lead to a recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon testifies Stone was campaign link to WIKILEAKS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/469654-bannon-testifies-that-trump-campaign-saw-stone-as-link-to-wikileaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Bannon, President Trump's former White House adviser and campaign CEO, testified in court on Friday that the campaign saw Roger Stone as a potential intermediary with WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boies Sues  Dershowitz in Clash of Marquee Lawyers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/08/alan-dershowitz-being-sued-by-jeffrey-epstein-accusers-lawyer-for-defamation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Boies filed a defamation suit in Manhattan Supreme Court on Friday — just one day after Dershowitz made accusations against him and his clients in his own suit in federal court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House impeachment hire Bondi winding down foreign work...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d533bfca6c934034be0ed745cad8c611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An agent of the Qataris. Lobbying for a Kuwaiti firm. A decision to steer clear of a lawsuit against Trump University. As she prepares to defend President Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG TO SKIP IA, NH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/653386c5e7e040d09836d0e013558815</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Michael Bloomberg plans to skip early voting states like Iowa and New Hampshire if he launches a presidential bid and instead focus his efforts on the crush of states that vote...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast, cable networks to televise hearings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/44078e878efc4077b59a55ec10de8c2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — ABC, CBS, NBC and PBS will set aside scheduled programming next week to cover the House's first open impeachment hearings on President Trump. The cable news networks CNN, Fox...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OJ Simpson sues Vegas casino, contends he was defamed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a8f45d3164b4b9e82e9c2bd209c7a72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — O.J. Simpson is suing a Las Vegas hotel-casino that banned him in November 2017, alleging that unnamed employees defamed him by telling a celebrity news site he had been drunk,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil braces...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191108221210-00gea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-CORRUPTION/COURT (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-Lula leaves prison, firing up Brazil's left and right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff bootlegging out the back door?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7666295/Chaos-Popeyes-staff-fight-accusations-selling-chicken-sandwiches-side.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers have been filmed fighting at a Popeyes over claims staff bootlegging sandwiches out the back door, as another video shows a woman being body slammed by a worker in a parking lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=87PVEXMN5qE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former ABC producer Ashley Bianco reveals the inside story to Megyn Kelly about the hot mic moment from anchor Amy Robach. #mkInterview #MegynKelly #JeffreyE...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Witnesses Finger Mulvaney In Quid Pro Quo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/key-ukraine-witnesses-finger-mick-mulvaney-in-the-quid-pro-quo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two top national security officials say that the chief of staff was the one who’d outlined the investigations that the Ukrainians needed to launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG journalists 'unnerved'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/08/bloomberg-news-michael-bloomberg-candidacy-068113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Company Claims To Have Cure For HIV, AIDS...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/11/08/maryland-medical-company-claims-to-have-hiv-aids-cure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Maryland medical company has submitted an application to the U.S Food and Drug Administration for a gene therapy it says will eliminate HIV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROJECT VERITAS: SHE'S NOT OUR SOURCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.projectveritas.com/2019/11/08/abc-insider-why-i-alone-released-the-amy-robach-epstein-tape/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.projectveritas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knows About 'Many Relevant Meetings'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/bolton-knows-about-many-relevant-meetings-on-ukraine-lawyer-says/ar-BBWtD5t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press group: Hollywood libel lawsuit could set bad precedent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/521c4445a1fe4aabb00a28200e7d03ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAIRFAX, Va. (AP) — Free press advocates in Virginia are concerned that a libel lawsuit between Hollywood actors Johnny Depp and Amber Heard could set a bad precedent. The Virginia Press...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 hospitalized after flu shot turns out to be insulin...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/11/08/flu-shots-insulin-oklahoma-10-hospitalized/2529395001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bartlesville, Oklahoma facility had contracted with a pharmacist to administer the vaccine, but all received injections of insulin instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's Online Crackdowns Inspire World's Dictators...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/11/06/germany-online-crackdowns-inspired-the-worlds-dictators-russia-venezuela-india/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anti-hate speech law written in Berlin has been copy-pasted by authoritarian regimes from Caracas to Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.I. voice assistant  -- your new best friend?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2019/11/08/alexa-google-assistant-ai-robots-become-substitute-friends/4057885002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The promise is that companion robots and voice assistants such as Alexa and the Google Assistant will be our "friends." Can AI solve loneliness?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearings likely to draw high TV ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment-tv-factbox/factbox-trump-impeachment-hearings-likely-to-draw-high-ratings-in-new-era-of-political-tv-idUSKBN1XI1EJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public impeachment hearings for U.S. President Donald Trump next week will mark ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Removes News Reports Mentioning Alleged Whistleblower's Identity...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/11/08/facebook-removes-any-news-reporting-on-or-even-mention-of-who-the-whistleblower-is-alleged-to-be/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media companies including Facebook have launched a crackdown against accounts that publish the name of the alleged Ukraine whistleblower, Eric Ciaramella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAL TECH scientist thinks we all exist in multiple universes... </title>
      <link>https://thenextweb.com/science/2019/11/08/meet-the-scientist-who-thinks-we-all-exist-in-multiple-universes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenextweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The increasingly popular theory of Many Worlds suggests every fundamental event has multiple possible outcomes and splits the world into various realities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar on Bloomberg bid: We don't need anyone telling us 'we aren't enough'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/469615-klobuchar-weighs-in-on-bloomberg-bid-we-dont-need-anyone-coming-in-and</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Amy Klobuchar (D-Minn.) was the latest Democratic presidential candidate to weigh in on billionaire Michael Bloomberg's possible entrance into the 2020 Democratic primary race Friday at a campaign stop in Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman, 95, dies in dog attack at home of animal activist...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/woman-95-dies-dog-attack-173627854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 95-year-old Connecticut woman has died from injuries she suffered when she was attacked by a dog at the home of a former lawmaker who is also an animal rights activist. Authorities say Janet D'Aleo, of Enfield, was found with life-threatening injuries Wednesday and brought to a Massachusetts hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First case of dengue spread by sex confirmed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-case-dengue-spread-sex-confirmed-spain-174218209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spanish health authorities confirmed Friday a case of a man spreading dengue through sex, a word first for a virus which until recently was thought to be transmitted only by mosquitos. The case concerns a 41-year-old man from Madrid who contracted dengue after having sex with his male partner who picked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange may soon die in jail, father warns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/assange-may-die-jail-father-warns-165954491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The father of WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange said Friday he worried his son would die in prison after nine years of "persecution" for daring to reveal US "war crimes". John Shipton told reporters in Geneva that he had visited his son in a British prison two days ago and needed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traumatic tale of 16-year-old virgin forced to be sex slave at Auschwitz told in new book...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/10301773/book-auschwitz-sex-slaves-holocaust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHE was just a girl when she was deported to Auschwitz-Birkenau concentration camp. But 16-year-old Cilka Klein’s beauty so entranced the camp commandant that he made her his sex slave. Cilka, a vi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous author's 'WARNING' portrays presidency on brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Anonymous-author-s-Warning-portrays-a-14818890.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Senior Trump administration officials considered resigning en masse last year in a "midnight self-massacre" to sound a public alarm about President Donald Trump's conduct, but rejected the idea because they believed it would further destabilize an already teetering government, according to a new book by an unnamed author.  In "A Warning" by Anonymous, obtained by The Washington Post ahead of its release, a writer described only as "a senior official in the Trump administration" paints a chilling portrait of the president as cruel, inept and a danger to the nation he was elected to lead.  The author - who first captured attention in 2018 as the unidentified author of a New York Times opinion column - describes Trump careening from one self-inflicted crisis to the next, "like a twelve-year-old in an air traffic control tower, pushing the buttons of government indiscriminately, indifferent to the planes skidding across the runway and the flights frantically diverting away from the airport."  The book is an unsparing character study of Trump, from his morality to his intellectual depth, which the author writes is based on his or her observations and experiences. The author claims many other current and former administration officials share his or her views.  The 259-page book - which was published by Twelve, an imprint of Grand Central Publishing/Hachette Book Group, and goes on sale Nov. 19 - does not re-create many specific episodes in vivid detail, which the author writes was intentional to protect his or her identity.  At a moment when a stream of political appointees and career public servants have testified before Congress about Trump's conduct as part of the House impeachment inquiry, the book's author defends his or her decision to remain anonymous.  "I have decided to publish this anonymously because...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He stumbles, slurs, gets confused, easily irritated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7665031/Anonymous-author-raises-questions-Donald-Trumps-mental-fitness.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anonymous author of a tell-all tome on the Donald Trump administration raises questions about the president's mental fitness to hold office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military ops in Syria getting complicated for Washington...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-military-ops-syria-getting-complicated-washington-161457844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is facing tough questions about the US military's role in Syria. Troops are now limited to a smaller, tougher to defend zone, and focused on protecting oil fields that legally belong to Damascus. On October 6, US President Donald Trump announced that the 1,000 soldiers deployed in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tax Case Should Be an Easy Supreme Court Call...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tax-case-easy-supreme-153735710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Some observers are wondering whether the Supreme Court will let President Donald Trump keep his tax records secret. With respect to presidential prerogatives, many fundamental issues remain open. Perhaps the current court will resolve this one in his favor?That's unlikely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG DREAMS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/461efe170a174c4fb9446951c164537e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLUFFTON, S.C. (AP) — All is not well in the Democratic Party's quest for a presidential nominee. Just ask Michael Bloomberg. The New York billionaire, whose career in business and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearings likely to draw high TV ratings...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191108103132-71wbw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-TV (FACTBOX):FACTBOX-Trump impeachment hearings likely to draw high ratings in new era of political TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Weinstein fawned over by fans at club...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/08/harvey-weinstein-returns-to-club-where-he-allegedly-assaulted-a-tv-anchor-is-fawned-over-by-fans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alleged sexual predator Harvey Weinstein was fawned over by fans and friends on Thursday during a night out at an exclusive SoHo lounge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC CHAOS: Video shows 'peacekeepers' scramble to break up subway brawl...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/08/a-train-chaos-video-shows-peacekeepers-scramble-to-break-up-subway-brawl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of brave “peacekeepers” scrambled to break up a wild fight aboard an A train this week, disturbing footage shows. The recording captured the chaos inside the northbound train be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of microchipping: Ready for technology to get under skin?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/nov/08/the-rise-of-microchipping-are-we-ready-for-technology-to-get-under-the-skin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As implants grow more common, experts fear surveillance and exploitation of workers. Advocates say the concerns are irrational</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD hosts 'Anal Sex 101,' 'Oral Sex 101' and 'fatphobia' workshops...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/harvard-hosts-anal-sex-101-oral-sex-101-and-fatphobia-workshops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annual, student-led Sex Week tradition returns to Ivy League institution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters call for 'revenge' after 22-year-old student dies in fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-11-08/hong-kong-protesters-call-for-revenge-after-22-year-old-student-dies-in-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The student who died had been in hospital since Sunday, after falling from a multi-story parking garage during a confrontation between protesters and police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outed CIA officer has advice for whistleblower under fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-08/outed-cia-officer-has-advice-for-whistle-blower-under-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Valerie Plame was outed as a covert CIA officer in 2003, a White House aide was convicted, a reporter went to jail, and her career in intelligence ended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly teases interview with ABCNEWS Epstein whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7664915/Megyn-Kelly-helps-fired-CBS-employee-woman-leaked-ABCs-Amy-Robach-hot-mic-revelation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com can reveal the staffer is Ashley Bianco, 25, an Emmy-winning producer, who contacted Megyn Kelly directly, a source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Denied Bodily Resurrection of Christ?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/michael-w-chapman/scalfari-pope-denied-jesus-bodily-resurrection-says-it-was-semblance-spirit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his new book and in the periodical he founded, La Repubblica, Eugenio Scalfari, a long-time friend of Pope Francis and frequent papal interviewer, claims that the Pope told him that Jesus Christ did not rise bodily from the dead but "in the semblance of a spirit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba: Jailed Dissident Forced to Drink Fecal Water, Eat Rotten Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/11/08/cuba-jailed-dissident-forced-to-drink-semi-fecal-water-eat-rotten-food/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;José Daniel Ferrer, the head of the largest dissident organization in Cuba, is nearing death after a month in prison.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
