<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Finds Electrical Issue in New Areas of 737 MAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/boeing-finds-electrical-issue-in-new-areas-of-737-max-cockpit/ar-BB1fJF5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Co. has found potential electrical flaws in two additional areas of the 737 Max’s cockpit, a week after a similar manufacturing defect prompted a temporary flying halt for recently delivered jetliners, said people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Marxist' Black Lives Matter co-founder DEFENDS property empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9479179/BLM-founder-defends-property-empire-reveals-spent-week-security.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrisse Cullors responded to criticism saying it is 'categorically untrue' and 'incredibly dangerous' to suggest she used organization funds for her homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Eye-Popping Auctions, News Outlets Jumping on NFT Gravy Train...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/04/with-eye-popping-auctions-news-outlets-are-jumping-on-the-nft-gravy-train</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times, Time, and the AP have racked up six-figure sales of digital assets that could be a future revenue stream—or the next bubble to burst. “If it doesn’t make sense,” Quartz’s CEO says of the frenzy, “it probably doesn’t make sense.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny terriers chase very large bear out of California home...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/viral-video-bear-dogs-terriers-california-home-16104193.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bear thought he'd struck gold: an empty kitchen and a fridge full of food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracies Supercharging Germany's Far-Right...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbybg/germany-far-right-covid-decade-of-hate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stable economic powerhouse at the heart of the European Union is also home to the continent's biggest, and wildest, anti-lockdown movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Going Vegetarian Lowers Testosterone, Damages Libido In Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/vegetarian-lower-testosterone-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results show vegetarian low-fat diets rank as the worst for men's sexual health; decreasing testosterone by up to 26 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 DEAD IN FEDEX SHOOTING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/shootings-crime-indianapolis-indiana-e92ad3117c56357b3b2c71a2903e68a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — The FBI says that last year it questioned the man who fatally shot eight people at a FedEx plant in Indianapolis. Paul Keenan, the special agent in charge of the FBI’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ERA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/15/americas/cuba-raul-castro-communist-leader-intl-latam/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Raul Castro announced three years ago that he would step down in 2021 as head of Cuba's all-powerful communist party, he surely envisioned the island on firmer economic footing and the transition to a new generation of leadership nearly complete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect ID'd as 19-year-old; Targeted Sikhs?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/16/fedex-shooter-idd-as-19-year-old-brandon-scott-hole/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who killed eight people at an Indianapolis FedEx facility was identified as local former employee 19-year-old Brandon Scott Hole. FedEx said Hole used to work for the company. Authorities a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous YOUTUBEr Jeffree Star hospitalized after 'severe car crash'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/2717086/jeffree-star-hospitalized-injured-car-crash-vehicle-flip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREE Star was hospitalized after being injured in a “severe car crash” after his car “flipped over three times.” The shocking news was revealed on the famous YouTuberR…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castro confirms he is passing Cuban Communist Party leadership to new generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/castro-confirms-he-is-passing-cuban-communist-party-leadership-to-new-generation/ar-BB1fJ6Xk?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUBA-POLITICS/CASTRO (URGENT):Castro confirms he is passing Cuban Communist Party leadership to new generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Detains Man Sitting On Times Sq Bench With Rifle...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/04/16/man-with-rifle-at-times-square-subway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was spotted sitting on a bench near the turnstile of the Times Square subway station at around 12:30 p.m. Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having virus does NOT guarantee immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2021/04/16/having-covid-doesnt-guarantee-immunity-study-of-marine-recruits-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten percent of Marine recruits who had COVID antibodies got COVID again during basic training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First male Marine recruits graduate from all-female boot camp battalion...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2021/04/15/first-male-marine-corps-recruits-graduate-from-previously-all-female-boot-camp-battalion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The depot is now training its 15th coed company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grenades Found In Package At Dept Of Treasury In Philly...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/04/15/inert-grenades-found-in-package-at-department-of-treasury-in-northeast-philadelphia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Treasury building in Northeast Philadelphia was evacuated after a package containing apparent grenades was found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How sex surrogates help injured Israeli soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/stories-56737828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Therapy with surrogate sexual partners is used in Israel to rehabilitate badly injured soldiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome red tape causes bodies to pile up...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/funeral-workers-protest-rome-red-144331961.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Funeral home operators staged a protest in Rome on Friday over a desperate situation they say has left almost two thousand coffins in the Italian capital waiting weeks or even months to be cremated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stole police car moments after release from Arkansas jail, cops say...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/arkansas-car-thief-501378</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 16--Moments after being released from custody, an Arkansas man yesterday stole a police car that was parked in front of the jail, earning him a return trip behind bars, cops say. According to i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to keep cap on refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-administration-will-keep-cap-refugees-trump-administration-levels-n1264320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president had said in February he would raise the limit from 15,000 to 62,500 for this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blowing up own agenda to 'own the libs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/republicans-are-blowing-up-their-own-agenda-to-own-the-libs/ar-BB1fIUFn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, the GOP wants to counter China. Yes, it wants to break up Big Tech. But only if the Democrats get mad about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIBERTY sues Jerry Falwell Jr., seeking millions...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/virginia/2021/04/liberty-sues-jerry-falwell-jr-seeking-millions-in-damages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberty University has filed a civil lawsuit against its former leader, Jerry Falwell Jr., seeking millions in damages after the two parted ways acrimoniously last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's Palace has cryo chamber!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/16/putin-residence-cryo-chamber-navalny-team-alleges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators have released floor plans and photos of expanded residence they say is Putin’s favourite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-Year-Old Dies After Choking Himself For TIKTOK Challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/04/15/12-year-old-dies-choking-blackout-challenge-tiktok.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social media platform has responded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang leads NYC mayor poll!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/16/andrew-yang-leads-new-nyc-mayoral-poll-despite-gaffes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a tough week, top Democratic mayoral hopeful Andrew Yang got a bit of good news from a poll commissioned by a rival political group that shows him well ahead of the pack with the primary just…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech billionaires staying 'very, very quiet' on proposals to tax wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22372857/washington-state-wealth-tax-bill-gates-steve-ballmer-mackenzie-scott-jeff-bezos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is relatively easy for a billionaire to say they support higher taxes. More is on the line if they are asked to do something about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House tries courting local reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-tries-a-time-tested-media-strategy-courting-local-reporters/ar-BB1fJ9OB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s team is launching a new focus on local media, reaching past national outlets to ones that are more trusted in their communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big bulk book-buying machine boosting Republicans on bestseller lists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-gops-big-bulk-book-buying-machine-is-boosting-republicans-on-the-bestseller-lists/ar-BB1fIlU3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The practice has raised ethical concerns. Now, a complaint about Ted Cruz’s own campaign buying his books has triggered questions about self-enrichment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKED MAN TRIES TO ROB HIS GRANDPA, ENDS UP IN HOSPITAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article250721314.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim did not realize it was his grandson, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN: FBI 'going beyond law' breaking into Americans' computers to delete malware...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/Snowden/status/1382738475288510466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid monkey-human embryos created in lab for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2713352/first-human-monkey-embryo-created/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE FIRST part-human, part-monkey embryo has been created by scientists in California despite ethical concerns. Researchers have grown human stem cells in monkey embryos to try and better understan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW: Biden 59% approval...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/politics/2021/04/15/biden-nears-100-day-mark-with-strong-approval-positive-rating-for-vaccine-rollout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The share of Americans viewing illegal immigration as a ‘very big’ problem has increased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to spend $1.7 billion on fighting variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/04/16/988019682/biden-administration-to-spend-1-7-billion-track-spread-of-coronavirus-variants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a more contagious variant now dominant in the U.S., the country's genomic surveillance capacity is getting a major boost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID much deadlier in Brazil than India and no one knows why...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/nation-world/ct-aud-nw-covid-19-deadlier-brazil-india-20210416-iialaw5tlzcvporezl3cajtfqe-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a sudden surge in coronavirus infections, India is once again home to the world’s second-largest outbreak, overtaking Brazil after the latter moved ahead in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unused Doses Piling Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/unused-vaccines-are-piling-up-across-us-as-some-regions-resist/ar-BB1fGFbO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in states where inoculation campaigns have been mostly successful, vaccine gaps remain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogecoin spikes 300% in week, stoking fears of crypto bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/16/dogecoin-doge-price-meme-cryptocurrencys-rise-sparks-bubble-fears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defying all odds, dogecoin is now worth $34 billion, and its price has risen by a whopping 300% in the last seven days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer Under Fire Over Video Showing Forceful Arrest Of 80-Pound Elderly Woman With Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/15/loveland-police-karen-garner-excessive-force-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys representing Karen Garner, who suffers from dementia and sensory aphasia, say the fragile woman experienced a broken arm, dislocated shoulder and sprained wrist following an altercation with Loveland police in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican donors flock to DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/16/desantis-trump-gop-donors-481891</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida governor has cultivated relationships with many of the party's biggest givers, who admire his opposition to strict Covid mitigation policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In secret FACEBOOK groups, America's warriors share racist jabs, QANON theories...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/military/secret-facebook-groups-america-s-best-warriors-share-racist-jabs-n1263985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News reviewed posts from four private, secret Facebook groups that describe themselves as solely for current and former special operations forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORSCHE Electric Taycan Sales on Course to Eclipse Iconic 911...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/porsche-e2-80-99s-electric-taycan-sales-on-course-to-eclipse-iconic-911/ar-BB1fIJSt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porsche buyers are flocking in droves to the brand’s Taycan sedan with sales of the all-electric model almost matching those of the iconic 911 sports car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Biggest Restaurateurs Turning Miami Into Hottest Dining Scene...</title>
      <link>https://robbreport.com/food-drink/dining/why-miami-hottest-dining-city-america-1234607434/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;robbreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Covid hits, and all of a sudden this becomes the Garden of Eden.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon sex therapist faces discipline and possible expulsion from the LDS Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Mormon-sex-therapist-faces-discipline-and-16105639.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sex therapist who has publicly challenged her church's teachings on sexuality is facing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym That Defied Lockdown Linked to at Least 419 Infections, One Death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gym-defied-lockdown-linked-least-101719970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cameron SmithCity officials are trying to figure out how a single Quebec City gym that refused to obey lockdown orders could have been linked to the infection of at least 419 people including one 40-year-old man who died after contracting COVID.Health authorities told CBC that the Mega Fitness Gym had broken at least three public health orders before it was forced to shut down on March 31, just as the city was placed under another lockdown amid surging infection rates. The outbreak has prompted local health authorities to conduct an epidemiological investigation into how the virus was able to spread so rapidly, and whether the infections were caused by the deadly U.K. variant.The gym owner, Daniel Morino, had protested government-mandated business closures by reopening his facility in the middle of a province-wide lockdown last summer. According to CBC, the gym owner had shared social media posts that downplayed the seriousness of the virus and cast doubt over the necessity of wearing face masks.In June, police showed up at Morino’s gym after receiving a complaint that he had hosted a 5 am “grand re-opening” of his family business. Morino told a local daily newspaper that, after touring the business, the police officers left without imposing any fines or ordering him to shut the gym doors.“I was not surprised by the presence of the police and I told them to do their job as I did mine," Marino told Le Journal de Québec, adding that he had taken the necessary precautions to keep his clients safe.“My biggest fear is going bankrupt… I have nothing to lose. If I am fined $50,000, I will add it to my debts. Either way, it won't make a difference since I'm going to go bankrupt. I have invested 25 years of my life in this business and I don't want to go out of business without doing anything. I would regret it all my life. I'm not the people's savior, but I'm just trying to save my business.”Although Marino maintained that he had been adhering to social distancing measures after defying lockdown mandates, Quebec City’s public health director said that, based on the latest inspection, it was clear that the gym had not been taking proper safety precautions.According to the director’s statement, which was reported by CTV, gym-goers were not being screened for symptoms, employees were not wearing proper personal protection gear, and clients were not physically distancing themselves from each other.Morino finally closed the Mega Fitness Gym doors to the public on March 31. But at that point, it was too late. With hundreds infected, one gym client dead, and more casualties likely to come—the outbreak has spiraled into one of Canada’s biggest superspreader events.Addressing Quebec City’s latest lockdown amid Canada’s lagging vaccine rates and staggering third COVID wave, Mayor Régis Labeaume had some choice words aimed directly at Dan Marino.“Bravo, champion,” he said. “Everyone has nice biceps but now people are sick."Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women busted for trying to use $1M bill -- at DOLLAR GENERAL store...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/crime/ny-counterfeit-million-dollar-bill-20210415-57tinj7b2naj5jeejd7fxzwcvu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who wants to be a millionaire?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top seer at India religious mega-festival dies from virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210416-top-seer-at-india-religious-mega-festival-dies-from-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top seer at India religious mega-festival dies from Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPERT: NEURALINK COULD SELL PRIVATE THOUGHTS TO 'HIGHEST BIDDER'...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/neoscope/expert-neuralink-sell-private-thoughts-highest-bidder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine getting targeted ads based on your thoughts and feelings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba readies for life without Castro...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/548567-cuba-readies-for-life-without-castro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in more than 60 years, Cuba is poised to have a government without a single Castro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: INFECTION RATE NEARS PANDEMIC HIGH</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210416071348-1n3ui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO (TV):WHO chief says COVID-19 infection rate approaching highest of pandemic so far</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel says lockdowns, curfews vital to break third wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210416062114-noj6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (URGENT, TV, PIX):Merkel says lockdowns, curfews vital to break Germany's third wave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China GDP hits record 18.3%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/economic-growth-china-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-d7582fd934da5c87e2a5c817bab9c618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China’s economy grew by double digits in the latest quarter but an explosive rebound from the coronavirus pandemic is slowing abruptly as manufacturing and consumer spending return...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz and DeSantis: Friendship that may become liability...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-tallahassee-florida-ron-desantis-campaigns-8c26a4a2c9c98d21e87acd8da4acde3b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — When he launched his campaign to become Florida’s governor in January 2018, few expected Ron DeSantis to prevail in America’s toughest political battleground. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France outlaws sex with children aged under 15...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210415184516-rc21d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The #MeToo movement helped to push France to toughen its rape law over sex with underage children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China GDP to hit record growth...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chinas-q1-gdp-hit-record-230000795.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China releases first-quarter GDP data on Friday (0200 GMT), along with March factory output, retail sales and fixed-asset investment. With the economy back on a more solid footing, China's central bank is turning its focus to cooling credit growth to help contain debt and financial risks, but it is treading cautiously to avoid derailing the recovery, analysts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's hospitals running out of sedatives as Covid rages...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-brazils-hospitals-running-sedatives-195911622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's hospitals were running out of drugs needed to sedate COVID-19 patients on Thursday, with the government urgently seeking to import supplies amid reports of the seriously ill being tied down and intubated without effective sedatives. Health Minister Marcelo Queiroga said Brazil was in talks with Spain and other countries to secure the emergency drugs. Hospitals, he added, were also struggling to get enough oxygen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman with 'mental issues' killed at San Antonio Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9476409/Gunman-mental-issues-killed-opening-fire-San-Antonio-International-Airport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Antonio International Airport was in lockdown after a shooting involving a police officer this afternoon. A man was captured on video being wheeled onto a stretcher by police soon after.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia considers staggered reopening of borders...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210415235128-moso2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (PIX):Australia considers staggered reopening of borders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago releases graphic video of police shooting 13-year-old...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/adam-toledo-chicago-police-shooting-video-0777ebc110898733ee78b91311d71a71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Disturbing bodycam video released Thursday after public outcry over the Chicago police shooting of a 13-year-old boy shows the youth appearing to drop a handgun and begin raising...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Short, fat, ugly': GUCCI family lashes out at cast in new film...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2021/apr/15/gucci-family-criticises-horrible-ugly-casting-biopic-film</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ridley Scott biopic tells story of Patrizia Reggiani’s doomed marriage to Maurizio Gucci</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,800 post-vaccination infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/spring-wave-of-coronavirus-crashes-across-38-states-as-hospitalizations-increase/ar-BB1fGXdU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccines drive down covid-19 mortality, even as the CDC reports 5,800 “breakthrough” infections in people who had received shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  How Justice Dept came to investigate Matt Gaetz...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-the-justice-department-came-to-investigate-rep-matt-gaetz/ar-BB1fH2XQ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stalking case against a Florida tax collector metastasized after authorities arrested him and seized electronic records pointing to the congressman, a prominent ally of former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beloved teacher's double life revealed after he dies in cartel robbery, sheriff says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/beloved-teacher-e2-80-99s-double-life-revealed-after-he-dies-in-cartel-robbery-sheriff-says/ar-BB1fHogV?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Let me say this. Many, many times you don’t really know a person," a sheriff said. "And this is probably one of those examples.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BOOM:  RETAIL SALES SURGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/jobless-claims-fall-to-lowest-level-since-march-2020/ar-BB1fGw3P?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blockbuster economic results powered the Dow above 34,000 for the first time and the S&amp;P 500 to a record finish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network merges news division with local TV stations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/548555-cbs-merges-news-division-with-local-tv-stations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS is merging its news arm with its local television stations to form a new division that will be co-led by a former ABC executive, the network announced on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court expansion bill faces serious blocks across political spectrum...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/04/15/supreme-court-expansion-bill-faces-serious-blocks-across-political-spectrum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four Democratic lawmakers have introduced bill to expand seats on Supreme Court, but party leaders are already playing down that effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Developing 'Algorithmic' Solution To Workplace Injuries...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90625851/jeff-bezos-shareholder-letter-amazon-is-developing-an-algorithmic-solution-to-workplace-injuries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s part of Amazon’s mission to become “Earth’s Best Employer and Earth’s Safest Place to Work.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid monkey-human embryos created in lab for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/hybrid-monkey-human-embryos-created-23922632</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The groundbreaking work could one day lead to a vast increase in the number of available organs for transplant, but some critics say it raises serious ethical questions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sanctions Russia over massive cyberattack and election interference...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-imposes-sanctions-moscow-expels-131700759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States announced sanctions and the expulsion of 10 Russian diplomats Thursday in retaliation for what Washington says is the Kremlin's US election interference, a massive cyberattack and other hostile activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two to a bed in Delhi ICU!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210415113306-smg6a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/INDIA-HOSPITAL (PIX, TV):Two to a bed in Delhi hospital as India's COVID crisis spirals</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
