<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Republican senator 'disturbed' by McConnell's White House coordination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/25/politics/lisa-murkowski-senate-impeachment-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Sen. Lisa Murkowski of Alaska said she is "disturbed" by coordination between Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell and the White House over the upcoming Senate impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Calls for Exemplifying Teachings of Christ...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-celebrates-christmas-by-calling-for-americans-to-unify-and-exemplify-the-teachings-of-christ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"While the challenges that face our country are great, the bonds that unite us as Americans are much stronger."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Warmth On Christmas In Chicago? </title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/12/25/chicago-weather-christmas-day-record-breaking-temperatures-possible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicagoans could see a record-breaking Christmas Day as temperatures rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Less joy in Tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/2019/12/23/donald-trumps-tweets-get-negative-impeachment-2020-election-loom/2601246001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is tweeting more frequently than ever, and his dispatches are increasingly negative, according to a USA TODAY analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undocumented woman marks year inside Maryland church... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Undocumented-woman-marks-a-year-inside-Maryland-14930567.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next to Rock Creek in Bethesda, Maryland, sits a six-acre church campus shrouded by old cedar trees. For a year and two weeks, this has been Rosa Gutierrez Lopez's home, sanctuary and site of confinement. This year, for the second time, it is where she will spend Christmas.  Gutierrez Lopez, 41, was the first undocumented immigrant in the Washington area to seek protection from deportation at a house of worship - one of the "sensitive location" categories where Immigration and Customs Enforcement agents are discouraged from conducting enforcement activities.  According to the nonprofit Church World Service, there are 49 residents in the United States taking refuge in faith communities. Hundreds of these institutions have designated themselves sanctuaries - a form of protest on the Trump administration's increasing crackdown on undocumented immigrants.  Congregants at Cedar Lane Unitarian Universalist Church had not met Gutierrez Lopez, a Fredericksburg, Virginia, resident, before she arrived at their doorstep one early morning in 2018. And she had not heard of Cedar Lane - had not even known about sanctuary - until several days before her scheduled deportation date: Dec. 10, 2018.  Since then, Lopez has not left the premises, fearful of being arrested and sent back to El Salvador, where she says her relatives have been killed by gang members.  Meanwhile, the church's 1,000 or so members have learned to practice what the Rev. Abhi Janamanchi, the senior minister, calls "the fragile art of hospitality." More than 200 volunteers, from Cedar Lane and 26 other D.C.-area congregations, help facilitate the day-to-day lives and logistics of Gutierrez Lopez and her family.  "It has been an adjustment - both for Rosa and for the community," Janamanchi said. "We can talk about these issues, intellectualize, but to see, actually see...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We've never seen spending like this': Bloomberg, Steyer saturate airwaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/25/michael-bloomberg-tom-steyer-2020-ads-084823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg and Tom Steyer have hit the $200 million mark combined, and Bloomberg, at least, is just getting started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman charged after dragging dog behind car...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/crime/article238686693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY AND THE MIDNIGHT MASS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7826469/Giuliani-attends-midnight-mass-St-Patricks-bizarre-drunken-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani attended midnight mass at the Catholic St. Patrick's Cathedral after he slammed liberal financier George Soros by questioning his Judaism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canceled Miami two hour before showtime...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7824863/Madonna-CANCELS-Miami-no-explanation-furious-fans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna canceled her performance Sunday night in Miami two hour before showtime and has yet to give an explanation. The next day her ex husband Guy Ritchie filed a motion in their divorce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock markets gained $17 trillion in value in 2019...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/24/global-stock-markets-gained-17-trillion-in-value-in-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Central banks, trade negotiations and tech stocks have helped push global equities higher in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires support  wealth tax -- as long as they aren't getting taxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/23/millionaires-support-a-wealth-tax-as-long-as-they-arent-getting-taxed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attitudes toward the wealth tax are also strongly dependent on political party rather than wealth levels, according to the CNBC Millionaire Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using fake name, mother fled on private jet after trying to kidnap son, authorities say...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/using-fake-name-mother-fled-on-private-jet-after-trying/article_fbc7129f-904d-58c9-88dd-5900fbc83805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A 55-year-old orthopedic surgeon was charged this week with several felonies after authorities say she tried to kidnap her son — brutally beating a woman in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls for 'deeper understanding and respect'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/475900-trumps-christmas-message-calls-for-culture-of-deeper-understanding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump called for unity and respect in his presidential Christmas message released Wednesday by the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When Web Gets Less American?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/happens-internet-gets-less-american-174355587.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- America is going to have to reckon with an internet that is becoming less American.Some U.S. lawmakers on both sides of the partisan divide have said they are worried about TikTok, the app that lets users record and share short skits or dance routines to music. The app quickly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran starts internet shutdown before new protests... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191225150157-4l1oj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-PROTESTS/INTERNET (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Iran starts internet shutdown before possible new protests - reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X:  Madonna suffering 'indescribable' pain; Delays rest of Tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/12/25/madonna-says-shes-in-indescribable-pain-cancels-last-miami-show-delays-european-dates-to-avoid-irreversible-damage-to-my-body</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna is still on her theater tour, and it’s not going so well. On Sunday she cancelled her final show in Miami because she’s in “indescribable” pain, she says on Instagra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Merry Christmas' bank robber throws cash at passers-by...</title>
      <link>https://www.kktv.com/content/news/Bank-robbed-in-downtown-Springs-566439071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kktv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Witnesses say a robber was doing everything he could to get caught after holding up a downtown Springs bank in the middle of lunchtime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison cameras hacked, live-streamed on YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/prison-camera-hacked-streamed-live-on-youtube</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Thailand say they are investigating an apparent online break-in by a computer hacker that allowed him to broadcast surveillance video from inside a prison in the country's south.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell flexes reelection muscle with $1B gift for Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/475831-mcconnell-flexes-reelection-muscle-with-1b-gift-for-kentucky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is delivering more than $1 billion worth of federal spending and tax breaks to his Kentucky constituents, just in time for Christmas and ahead of a potentially tough reelection campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veiled women make Santa dolls in Gaza Strip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/veiled-women-santa-dolls-gaza-strip-171252475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beit Lahia (Palestinian Territories) (AFP) - The scene on Tuesday morning in the northern Gaza Strip could at first look incongruous -- a group of women in black niqab veils sewing Santa Claus dolls for Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Chinese woman sues over egg freezing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/single-chinese-woman-sues-over-egg-freezing-100529352.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A single woman in China has gone to court challenging rules that forbid unmarried women from freezing their eggs in the first case of its kind in the country. Teresa Xu said she was prompted to take legal action after a top hospital in Beijing declined to freeze her eggs last year, and instead told</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French transport strike enters fourth week...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gloomy-christmas-eve-20th-day-french-strike-172857134.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas Day brought no respite for travellers in France as a transport strike entered its fourth week, ruining the plans of thousands to share a traditional meal and quality time with loved ones. Many scrambled at the last minute to make alternative arrangements as the protest against pension reform</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of UK royals back in spotlight after Queen's year to forget...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cost-uk-royals-back-spotlight-queens-forget-060154217.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a torrid 2019 in which the queen's son Prince Andrew was implicated in an underage sex abuse scandal, many in Britain are again asking if the monarchy has gotten too big -- and rich -- for its own good. The family's year to forget may encourage Prince Charles, set to eventually take over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro says 'fine' now but lost memory after fall...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-says-fine-now-lost-memory-fall-003907068.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro temporarily lost his memory after hitting his head in a fall at his official residence, he said in an interview on Tuesday. "The following day, this morning, I managed to get back a lot of things and now I am fine," Bolsonaro said in a telephone interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON'S END:  Ravens, Saints, 49ers top 3 teams in AP poll...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/66107090272c0ef09254e4029da3b9ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Lamar Jackson and the Baltimore Ravens have already made plenty of history this season. They have won 11 consecutive games, have the NFL’s best record at 13-2 and have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonstop violence as Baltimore nears record homicide rate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/521b92265e24a213b2a3d9218fc5774b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — Baltimore could wrap up 2019 with its highest per-capita homicide rate on record as killings of adults and minors alike for drugs, retribution, money or no clear reason continue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We only learned about this when reporter called us'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/451e897954d3202a19996e367ead9299</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic presidential contender Michael Bloomberg cut ties with a contractor that used prisoners to make calls for his presidential campaign, he said in a statement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope offers hope against darkness in Christmas Day message...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00585ce6767d6bde058dcac77facab3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis offered a Christmas message of hope Wednesday against darkness that cloaks conflicts and relationships in large parts of the world from the Middle East to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA's Ratings Crash Ahead of Christmas Showcase...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/12/24/nbas-ratings-crash-ahead-christmas-showcase/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV ratings for the National Basketball Association are taking a tumble as we approach Christmas week, even as the sports media tries to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged bank robber throws money into air, yells, 'Merry Christmas!'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/24/alleged-bank-robber-throws-money-into-air-yells-merry-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s one way to spread some holiday cheer. A Colorado bank robber tossed fistfuls of cash into the air and exclaimed, “Merry Christmas!” following a stick-up, according to a rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Method to Silence Dissent: Military Service in Arctic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-russian-method-to-silence-dissent-military-service-in-the-arctic/ar-BBYji5j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING document dump shows 'disturbing' picture...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boeing-document-dump-shows-disturbing-picture-737-max-205910958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing provided a fresh batch of incriminating documents on the 737 MAX to regulators and congressional investigators, only hours after announcing a leadership shakeup, officials confirmed Tuesday. The document dump came just before Christmas, when many officials already are on holiday, and "appear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope marks joyful Christmas Eve after less-than-joyful year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/adad91b6d695089d744116b87a7baa58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis assured the faithful on Christmas Eve that God loves everyone — “even the worst of us” — as he celebrated the joyous birth of Christ after a less-than-joyful year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alive Inside: How to reach 'vegetative' patients -- aware of everything...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/alive-inside-how-do-we-reach-vegetative-patients-when-tests-show-theyre-aware-of-everything</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not clear how much Jeff Tremblay knows about the role he’s playing in a revolution in the treatment of the catastrophically brain injured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs process numbers, count their treats...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/a-new-study-shows-dogs-can-process-numbers-and-theyre-counting-their-treats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Our work not only shows that dogs use a similar part of their brain to process numbers of objects as humans do — it shows that they don’t need to be trained to do it’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New BOEING docs show 'very disturbing' concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-boeing-737max/new-boeing-737-max-documents-show-very-disturbing-employee-concerns-u-s-house-aide-idUSKBN1YS1BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Co documents under review by a U.S. congressional panel appear to point t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake, Dangerous Kids Products For Sale On AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/12/24/warning-fake-dangerous-kids-products-are-turning-up-for-sale-on-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was advertised to look like a high end brand, but this car seat is a copycat. Legitimate sellers say it's one of many potentially dangerous kids products sold on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crop duster spreads 100 gallons of holy water on Louisiana town...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/crop-duster-spreads-100-gallons-holy-water-louisiana/story?id=67914735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crop duster spread holy water on a Louisiana town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the REDSKINS Plummeted to Rock Bottom...</title>
      <link>https://www.theringer.com/nfl/2019/12/24/21035742/washington-redskins-rock-bottom-dan-snyder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theringer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The professional football team in the nation’s capital was the hottest ticket in town for decades. But under Dan Snyder’s ownership, the franchise has lost a lot of games and managed to alienate even some of its most dedicated fans. What made one of most unshakable fandoms in America give up on its team?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA plans to dramatically shrink Navy destroyer fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/naval/2019/12/24/pentagon-proposes-big-cuts-to-us-navy-destroyer-construction-retiring-13-cruisers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pentagon proposal sent to the white house would cut five destroyers out of the budget over the next five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI iooking into former KY gov's pardons...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/politics/2019/12/23/matt-bevin-pardons-fbi-asking-questions-situation/2737842001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators are looking into former Kentucky Gov. Matt Bevin's last-minute pardons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW WEINSTEIN CASES BEING REVIEWED BY LA DA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/harvey-weinstein-cases-review-1203451578/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein is set to go on trial next month in New York on charges of rape and sexual assault. But no matter how that case turns out, he will still face criminal jeopardy in Los Angeles. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'God Has Me Right Where He Wants Me': Bieber Announces New Single 'Yummy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/12/24/god-has-me-right-where-he-wants-me-justin-bieber-announces-new-single-called-yummy-for-january-3rd-2020-tour-dates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber released a video announcement today for new music and tour dates. His single, “Yummy,” comes January 3rd. He says, “As humans we are imperfect. My past, my mistakes,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Exploited Prison Labor to Make 2020 Campaign Phone Calls...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/12/24/mike-bloomberg-2020-prison-labor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bloomberg campaign said it ended the arrangement after learning of the prison call centers from an The Intercept inquiry.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
