<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Climate envoy John Kerry allegedly arrives on private plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/conservatives-hit-climate-envoy-john-kerry-for-allegedly-flying-private-plane-to-obama-s-birthday-party/ar-AAN3CE3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Presidential Envoy for Climate John Kerry was rebuked by political opponents for taking a private plane to attend the birthday party of former President Barack Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND:  Shooting leaves 1 police officer dead, another wounded...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/2-chicago-police-officers-shot-2-suspects-nabbed-reports?test=cf8626f70c15e857e061f98f6ee61044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Chicago police officer died and another was critically wounded Saturday night during a confrontation on the city’s South Side, according to reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To shake hands or not? Age-old human gesture now in limbo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-2af72babe298ccb795831dbfa13a9000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the pandemic took hold, a Kansas City-area meeting and event planning business began hawking “I Shake Hands” stickers to help ease awkward social encounters. “We didn’t want the sticker to say, ‘We Don’t Shake Hands’ because that is kind of off-putting,” said John DeLeon, vice president of operations and sales at MTI Events, adding that the idea was that anti-shakers could simply choose not to wear one of the stickers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV ratings plummet 49%...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9873415/Olympics-TV-ratings-plummet-49-compared-2016-games-amid-woke-protests-pandemic-lockdowns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a significant decline in Olympic viewership this year compared to previous games. NBC has seen 'underwhelming ratings' for the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA rallies to top China in Olympics gold medal tally...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/us-rallies-to-top-china-in-tokyo-olympics-gold-medal-tally-061004909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A final day flurry of golds pushed Team USA to the top of the medal table at the Tokyo Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ posts stealth pics of Obama 'epic' birthday bash -- before being forced to delete them...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/08/dj-posts-pics-of-obamas-birthday-party-before-being-forced-to-delete-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manager TJ Chapman gave his Instagram followers an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at President Barack Obama’s 60th birthday party at Martha’s Vineyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could USA Catch China in Gold Medal Race?</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nicholasreimann/2021/08/07/us-surging-in-chase-for-olympic-gold-medal-lead-heres-how-it-could-top-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just hours remain in the 2020 Olympics, but that might be enough for the U.S. to catch China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For couples, sleeping apart could have health benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/for-couples-sleeping-apart-actually-could-have-health-benefits/ar-AAN33C3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you or your partner have sleeping habits or problems that can interfere with slumbering, experts say both of you might get a better nights rest by trying separate beds or rooms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires rampage through forests in Greece; Thousands evacuated... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-middle-east-fires-greece-forests-ad72c1a6cc7db73ec2bf46ac0c3e066e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THRAKOMAKEDONES, Greece (AP) — Wildfires rampaged through Greek forests for yet another day Saturday, threatening homes and triggering more evacuations a day after hundreds of people were plucked off beaches by ferries in a dramatic overnight rescue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Musk put 'sex' into TESLA cars...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/07/how-elon-musk-put-the-sex-into-tesla-and-conquered-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By 2018, it appeared that the auto industry might chew up and spit out startup Tesla, as it had done to so many others before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How He Took Advantage of #MeToo...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/07/how-cuomo-took-advantage-of-metoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two summers ago, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo stared into a camera, signed a bill and made a promise to the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient pharaonic boat taken to Egypt's grand new museum...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210807-ancient-pharaonic-boat-taken-to-egypt-s-grand-new-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancient pharaonic boat taken to Egypt's grand new museum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters in France denounce health pass rules for fourth weekend...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210807140534-q0uq9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-PROTEST (TV):Protesters in France denounce COVID health pass rules for fourth weekend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: First Job May Determine If Develop Heart Disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/your-first-job-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers who spent a longer time in school and quickly went into a professional role as a young adult displayed better cardiovascular health 20 years later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUT BY FALL?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/07/politics/andrew-cuomo-political-fallout/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo is running out of time and friends as he stares down the prospect of being the first New York governor impeached in more than 100 years -- with his own party leading the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The appeal of small Southern towns...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/article/The-appeal-of-small-Southern-towns-16370071.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUNSET, S.C. - Nestled in the foothills of the Blue Ridge Mountains, where pine trees...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: First, five stages of grief...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/07/cuomo-will-resign-once-he-gets-through-five-stages-of-grief/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few short months ago, Gov. Andrew Cuomo was heralded as the noblest, boldest and sexiest governor in American history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team USA shutout by Japan in baseball...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/olympics/team-usa-shutout-japan-settles-baseball-silver-hosts-take-olympic-n1276224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top-ranked host country beat a U.S. squad filled with minor leaguers and free agents in the gold medal match in Yokohama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-Hit Conventions Hope Virus Fades Soon as Shows Cancel Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/hard-hit-conventions-hope-delta-fades-soon-as-shows-cancel-again/ar-AAN39B5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cancellation of the New York Auto Show this week over concerns about the spread of the Covid-19 delta variant sparked “here-we-go-again” fears in the events industry, just when it started booking conferences again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW COVID WARS</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Public-health-collides-with-politics-as-latest-16371547.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty months into the pandemic, the latest wave of the face-mask culture war is in full...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC beloved owl dies after struck by maintenance vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/barry-the-barred-owl-central-park-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barry arrived in Central Park in October, becoming an instant celebrity and a beacon of hope for New Yorkers amid the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German coach disqualified after punching horse...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/sports/germanys-modern-pentathlon-coach-disqualified-after-punching-horse-2021-08-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's modern pentathlon coach Kim Raisner will not be part of Saturday's men's individual competition at the Tokyo Olympics after she hit a horse with her fist and urged rider Annika Schleu to "really hit" the horse when it refused to jump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Cuban protesters still detained, including prominent dissidents...</title>
      <link>https://www.normantranscript.com/region/hundreds-of-cuban-protesters-are-still-detained-including-prominent-dissidents/article_38a8c7a0-6ecb-5b36-a4bb-3336869b0545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.normantranscript.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His screaming face became one of the iconic images of the widespread July 11 protests in Cuba, making the front pages of newspapers worldwide. The photo, taken by an Agence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dixie fire tears through communities, some refuse evacuation orders with guns in hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/as-dixie-fire-tears-through-communities-some-refuse-evacuation-orders-with-guns-in-hand/ar-AAN36Jc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One challenge for fire crews in Plumas County is residents who won't leave their property, forcing firefighters to take risks on their behalf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid tangled Haiti assassination plot, mysterious figure emerges from shadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/haiti/article253278878.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the July 7 assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moïse, the growing cast of shadowy characters swept up in the investigation has resembled a scrambled jigsaw puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebs descend on Martha's Vineyard for Obama bash...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/07/barack-obamas-birthday-bash-at-marthas-vineyard-guest-list-john-legend-chrissy-teigen-dwayne-wade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars such as John Legend, Chrissy Teigen, Dwayne Wade and Gabrielle Union arrived in Martha’s Vineyard to celebrate President Barack Obama’s 60th birthday party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chilling details emerge about execution-style killing of TikTok star at movie theater...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chilling-details-emerge-execution-style-162836544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Barajas, 19, and Rylee Goodrich, 18, were each fatally shot in the head while watching a movie in Corona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA looking for people to 'live on Mars' for year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-oddities-business-science-mars-182cc63732fbabeb7120df2fc637b85a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to find your inner Matt Damon and spend a year pretending you are isolated on Mars? NASA has a job for you. To prepare for eventually sending astronauts to Mars, NASA began taking applications Friday for four people to live for a year in Mars Dune Alpha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THOUSANDS IN STURGIS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-south-dakota-sd-state-wire-b729c1e92cb7e0f74c12343c483f9474</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STURGIS, S.D. (AP) — The Black Hills of South Dakota roared with motorcycles and crowds Friday as the annual Sturgis Motorcycle Rally kicked off, with mostly mask-less rallygoers packed shoulder-to-shoulder at bars and rock shows, despite a rise in COVID-19 cases in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid soaring infections, mask and vax debates continue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-3c41b219cd5419056f4a626eef2ea2f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — When Brack May began requiring proof of COVID-19 vaccination for indoor dining at his restaurant near the Mississippi River levee in New Orleans, some of the reactions were intense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hochul moves into spotlight as scandal roils Cuomo reign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-immigration-5984949e6c5c59063598409eec10ba5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — As New York's lieutenant governor, Kathy Hochul has spent years on the road as the friendly face of the administration, visiting the far-flung coffee shops and factory floors of each of the state's 62 counties for countless ribbon-cutting ceremonies and civic cheerleading events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii, Masked and Vaccinated, Still Falls Prey to Strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/hawaii-masked-and-vaccinated-still-falls-prey-to-delta-strain/ar-AAN1N9h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii has one of the country’s most comprehensive mask mandates and a highly effective vaccine campaign. Despite that, Covid-19 cases on the islands are climbing with a ferocity that’s outstripping every other U.S. state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby airlifted 150 miles because of bed shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/06/us/houston-baby-girl-airlifted-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 11-month-old girl with Covid-19 had to be airlifted to a hospital 150 miles away because of a shortage of pediatric beds in the Houston area, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 20 types of gifts missing from State Dept vault...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/566829-at-least-20-types-of-gifts-missing-from-state-departments-vault</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department’s inspector general is reportedly investigating the disappearance of at last 20 types of items that had been in the agency’s gift vault, with dozens of individual items unaccounted for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo accuser files criminal complaint...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/06/gov-cuomo-accuser-files-criminal-complaint-with-albany-sheriff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former staffer of Gov. Andrew Cuomo who has accused him of groping her in 2019 has filed a criminal complaint against him with the Albany County Sheriff’s Office, The Post has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire rages north of Athens on fifth day of Greece blazes...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210807105930-9pqsh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREECE-WILDFIRES/ (UPDATE 2, PIX,TV):UPDATE 2-Wildfire rages north of Athens on fifth day of Greece blazes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro fans judiciary flames, calls top judge 'son of a whore'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210806202805-vodvd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Brazil's Bolsonaro fans judiciary flames, calls top judge 'son of a whore'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Don't Want Shot. They Don't Want Colleagues to Know...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/07/they-dont-want-the-shot-they-dont-want-colleagues-to-know/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vincent Taranto has felt like less of a pariah at work in the last few days. For more than two</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban Take Second Afghan City in Two Days...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/07/taliban-take-second-afghan-city-in-two-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan — Another provincial capital, the second in two days, all but fell on Saturday in Afghanistan, officials said,</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
