<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Airborne Virus a Threat, CDC Acknowledges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/airborne-coronavirus-is-a-threat-the-c-d-c-acknowledges/ar-BB1gtRBD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal health officials on Friday updated public guidance about how the coronavirus spreads, emphasizing that transmission occurs by inhaling very fine respiratory droplets and aerosolized particles, as well as through contact with sprayed droplets or touching contaminated hands to one’s mouth, nose or eyes. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention now states explicitly — in large, bold lettering — that airborne virus can be inhaled even...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Bill to kill up to 90% of Idaho wolves signed by governor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-idaho-lifestyle-wolves-bills-f83cd2449975c977d167c0509bccab24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — Idaho Gov. Brad Little has signed into law a measure that could lead to killing 90% of the state’s 1,500 wolves in a move that was backed by hunters and the state's powerful ranching sector but heavily criticized by environmental advocates...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Children Who Grow Up Around Nature Less Likely To Have ADHD...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/children-green-spaces-adhd-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities brace for more...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/israel-braces-weekend-violence-after-spate-shootings-eviction-protests-n1266697</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t know what will happen with us if they kick the families out from the houses,” Yacoub Abu Arafa who is facing eviction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity stockpicker reveals Bill Hwang behind funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/ark-invest-ceo-wood-says-bill-hwang-provided-seed-capital-for-first-4-etfs--cnbc-2499924</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ark Invest CEO Wood says Bill Hwang provided seed capital for first 4 ETFs - CNBC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45,000 volunteer to kill 12 bison in national park...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210507-more-than-45-000-people-volunteer-to-kill-12-bison-in-us-national-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 45,000 people volunteer to kill 12 bison in US national park</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Video Shows Endangered Right Whales 'Hugging' In Cape Cod Bay...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/07/right-whales-hugging-video-cape-cod-bay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New drone footage shows an incredible encounter between endangered whales in Cape Cod Bay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY ending temperature checks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/walt-disney-world-universal-studios-end-temperature-checks-guests-n1266683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As temperature checks end, coronavirus safety measures such as face coverings and social distancing requirements will remain intact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHINGTONIAN staffers protest CEO's 'public threat' to return to in-person work...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/07/media/washingtonian-remote-work-culture/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staffers at the Washingtonian, a monthly DC-based magazine, are protesting Friday in response to their CEO's opposition of remote work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent clashes break out at Temple Mount... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/riots-break-out-at-temple-mount-667550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Police officers closed off Damascus Gate in the Old City in an attempt to regain control of the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians, Israel police clash at Al-Aqsa Mosque; 53 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-west-bank-shootings-d5c6b1ed602844be69318bd1d1a334cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Palestinian worshippers clashed with Israeli police on Friday evening at Al-Aqsa Mosque in Jerusalem’s Old City as weeks-long tensions between Israel and the Palestinians over Jerusalem soared again...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World turns to China for vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/china/covid-the-world-turns-to-china-for-vaccines-after-india-us-stumble/articleshow/82451380.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China News: China’s reliability as a vaccine supplier is increasing its geopolitical clout at a time when the US and the EU have been slow confronting the global</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America burned out on news...</title>
      <link>https://interpreter.substack.com/p/america-is-burned-out-on-the-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;interpreter.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s okay. You can take a break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California reports first yearly population decline in history...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/society/california-reports-first-yearly-population-decline-in-states-history/10594297/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials announced Friday that California's population dipped 0.46% to just under 39.5 million people from January 2020 to January 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Headache' left behind on White House lawn...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/07/politics/white-house-construction-trump-biden/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The project that's currently tearing up the White House's South Lawn initially landed on Donald Trump's desk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why demand for armed drones is surging around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/07/turkey-and-china-disrupt-the-multibillion-dollar-armed-drone-market-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies in China, Turkey and Russia are increasingly producing armed drones, remotely piloted aircraft that can use guided weapons on and off the battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC still storing victims in refrigerated trucks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-68c9762a4420094d300f9cbada0186f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York City is still using refrigerated trucks to store bodies of coronavirus victims, more than a year after they were first set up as temporary morgues as deaths surged at at the height of the pandemic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA loses more than 182,000 residents; First yearly drop...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/californias-population-fell-182000-2020-yearly-drop-nations-77558321</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's population fell by more than 182,000 in 2020, the first yearly drop for the nation's most populous state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIPADVISOR removes insensitive review of Auschwitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/tripadvisor-removes-insensitive-review-auschwitz-museum-n1266685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The author of the review said they went to Auschwitz to “test the chamber” and called the site “fun for the family."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The music festival refusing to bow to Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210507-the-music-festival-refusing-to-bow-to-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music festival refusing to bow to Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORWEGIAN Cruises threaten to skip Florida ports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-eb9db87299caeb813bb7aa4c0194c780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norwegian Cruise Lines is threatening to steer clear of Florida after the governor signed an order banning businesses from requiring that customers show proof of vaccination against COVID-19. The company says the order by Gov...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiring bust as unemployment rate RISES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-5dc338627748f7c75ba7e9a040a894d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — America’s employers added just 266,000 jobs last month, sharply lower than in March and a sign that some businesses are struggling to find enough workers as the economic recovery rapidly strengthens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S:  STOCKS SET MORE RECORDS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-financial-markets-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-78ed5d6167e083061655f79a72b91297</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Stocks are rallying to records on Wall Street Friday despite a stunningly disappointing report on the nation's job market, as investors see it helping to keep interest rates low. The S&amp;amp;P 500 rose 0...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flower Shortage For Mother's Day?</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/05/05/mothers-day-flowers-may-be-hard-to-come-by-this-year-due-to-global-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World-renowned floral artist Deborah de la Flor and her team are poetry in motion arranging textures and colors, filling orders non-stop for Mother's Day, but like so many industries COVID has been a thorn in their side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight For Women To Be Topless In MD's Most Popular Beach Town Returns To Court...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/05/06/fight-for-women-to-be-topless-in-ocean-city-back-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight for women to go topless in Maryland's most popular beach town is back in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Elon' would rule over Mars  -- predicted 70 years ago!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/14881853/predict-man-elon-colonise-mars-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk’s plot to colonise other worlds may have been predicted by a German scientist 70 years ago. Writing in his 1952 science fiction novel “Project Mars”, engineer Wernher vo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  True U.S. Death Toll More Than 900,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/true-u-s-death-toll-from-covid-is-more-than-900000-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Covid-19 death toll has reportedly been undercounted by 300,000 deaths, according to a study conducted by the University of Washington's Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation (IHME).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiring bust as unemployment rate RISES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/07/jobs-report-april-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hiring was a huge letdown in April, with nonfarm payrolls increasing by a much less than expected 266,000 and the unemployment rate rose to 6.1%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRIST ON THE CROSS:  Dems cool to latest bid for gov...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/552209-democrats-cool-on-crists-latest-bid-for-florida-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Rep. Charlie Crist’s (D) nascent campaign for Florida governor is receiving a tepid reception from some Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bedlam At Presser For Floyd Mayweather, Logan Paul Boxing Match; Fists Fly...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/05/06/floyd-mayweather-logan-paul-exhibition-press-conference-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boxing Hall of Famer Floyd Mayweather will face off in the ring against YouTuber Logan Paul for a June 6 exhibition boxing match in Miami, but the fight started early on Thursday during a news conference when Paul’s brother, Jake stole Mayweather’s hat and the fists starting flying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Movie theater manager sold cocaine hidden in popcorn bag...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/coke-and-popcorn-507619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 6--The manager of a Minnesota movie theater sold cocaine hidden in a bag of popcorn to a police informant, according to court records. Jamie Lynn Hiniker, 39, was named yesterday in a criminal co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Songwriting Survive Streaming? ABBA's Bjorn Ulvaeus Is Worried...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/07/will-songwriting-survive-streaming-abbas-bjorn-ulvaeus-is-worried/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Abba, Bjorn Ulvaeus tasted the highest reaches of musical fame, selling millions of albums that defined earworm 1970s pop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Engineer Says Musk Overstated Autopilot Reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/companies/news/tesla-engineer-says-musk-overstates-reality-of-tesla-s-autopilot-11620395420272.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Tesla Inc.’s engineers told California authorities that Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk overstated the capability of Autopilot, the company’s driver-assistance system, early this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOT WARNS YOU IF YOUR TWEET IS 'MEAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/twitter-mean-tweets-prompt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter will now encourage you to pause and reconsider when you post something unkind in reply to someone else.The company has been testing a function that identifies potentially harmful, offensive and inconsiderate replies and then prompts users to potentially reconsider their Tweet before sending....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Adds 48,000 Employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/government-grew-48000-employees-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal, state and local governments in the United States increased their employment by a combined 48,000 workers in April, according to the numbers released today by the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S:  STOCKS SET MORE RECORDS!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/06/stock-futures-open-slightly-higher-ahead-of-key-april-jobs-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls increased by just 266,000 in April, far less than the 1 million total economists were expecting, according to Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-DeSantis staffers form support group...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/552308-former-desantis-staffers-form-support-group</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of former staffers for Florida Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melinda Gates Warned Bill About Sex Offender...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/melinda-gates-warned-bill-jeffrey-005850998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos via GettyMelinda Gates met with convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein alongside her husband Bill in New York City and soon after said she was furious at the relationship between the two men, according to people familiar with the situation.The previously unreported meeting occurred at Epstein’s Upper East Side Mansion in September 2013, on the same day the couple accepted the Lasker Bloomberg Public Service Award at the Pierre Hotel and were photographed alongside then-mayor Mike Bloomberg.The meeting would prove a turning point for Gates’ relationship with Epstein, the people familiar with the matter say, as Melinda told friends after the encounter how uncomfortable she was in the company of the wealthy sex offender and how she wanted nothing to do with him.Gates’ friendship with Epstein—who for years was accused of molesting scores of underage girls—still haunts Melinda, according to friends of the couple who spoke to The Daily Beast this week in light of the pair’s divorce announcement, which had been weeks in the making.Jeffrey Epstein Accuser Names Powerful Men in Alleged Sex RingThe Daily Beast has learned that financial and public relations specialists had been feverishly working on details of the pair’s split for weeks before the couple announced their divorce on Monday.“After a great deal of thought and a lot of work on our relationship, we have made the decision to end our marriage,” the two said in a brief statement posted on Twitter. “We have raised three incredible children and built a foundation that works all over the world to enable all people to lead healthy, productive lives.”A representative for Bill and Melinda Gates did not respond to requests for comment for this story.The ties between Gates and Epstein ran much deeper than the tech mogul first admitted. As The New York Times reported, starting in 2011, Gates met with Epstein on numerous occasions. This was three years after Epstein pleaded guilty to soliciting an underage girl in Florida; by then, accusations that Epstein exploited girls and young women were widely reported in the press.As The Times reported, two people close to Gates acted as intermediaries between the two: Boris Nikolic, a biotech investor and former adviser to Gates who was mysteriously named a backup executor in Epstein’s last will and testament; and Melanie Walker, who worked at the Gates foundation and served as a science advisor to Epstein. A person close to Walker told The Daily Beast she did not attend nor help set up any meetings between Gates and Epstein. Nikolic did not return multiple requests for comment.Soon after Epstein’s arrest in July 2019, Gates became one of many prominent people to face scrutiny over ties to the sex-trafficker.The New York Times revealed Gates had met with Epstein at a 2011 get-together at Epstein’s Manhattan townhouse that included the financier’s ex-girlfriend Eva Andersson-Dubin and her daughter. (Virginia Giuffre, a survivor of Epstein’s sex ring, has accused Dubin’s hedge-funder husband, Glenn, of abuse—a charge he strenuously denies).Indeed, the Times reported Gates visited Epstein multiple times from 2011 to 2013, and that Epstein had tried pitching a new charitable fund to JPMorgan honchos and to the Gates foundation. In 2013, Gates also took a ride on Epstein’s private jet (christened by tabloids as the Lolita Express), from Teterboro Airport in New Jersey to Palm Beach, Florida, according to flight records reviewed by the Times. CNBC also reported that Gates rendezvoused with Epstein in New York in 2013.When Gates first met Epstein, he was still Microsoft’s chairman and the second richest person in the world with a net worth of $56 billion.“I met him. I didn’t have any business relationship or friendship with him,” Gates said in September 2019, as media coverage into his connections with Epstein were heating up. “I didn’t go to New Mexico or Florida or Palm Beach or any of that. There were people around him who were saying, ‘Hey, if you want to raise money for global health and get more philanthropy, he knows a lot of rich people.’“Every meeting where I was with him were meetings with men. I was never at any parties or anything like that. He never donated any money to anything that I know about.”One associate in the technology world who’s attended the same events as Epstein, including a TED conference in Monterey, California, was surprised Gates had considered cultivating philanthropic ties with the late peadophile.“I can’t make the claim that so many are claiming,” the person told The Daily Beast on the condition of anonymity, referring to people in Epstein’s orbit who’ve said they had no suspicions of Epstein’s abuse. “If you ask Bill Gates, he’ll say, ‘Oh I had absolutely no idea he wasn’t up to anything of the highest moral character.’ But I seriously doubted Epstein’s moral character.”“The people around him,” the person added, referring to Epstein, “had a varying spectrum of what they knew and what they didn’t know and how they rationalized it.”This person wasn’t surprised that Melinda Gates was put off by Epstein, saying “a lot of people were uncomfortable with Epstein, completely independent of his” sexual misconduct. “He just was an obnoxious guy. He almost made a point of having bad manners, not paying attention at dinner… I could see how anybody, even without suspicions, would not want to be around him.”Still, Epstein had a “superhuman” ability as a social climber, the one-time colleague of the financier said, adding that the photos displayed in Epstein’s mansion of former President Bill Clinton and the Pope were “really obnoxious, especially if you’re somebody like Melinda and hanging around with heads of state anyway. Then to have someone do this endless name-dropping…“When he got up from the table at dinner, he wouldn’t just get up, he’d tell you he had a call with a president of some country.”Epstein also reportedly had a habit of bragging that he was an unofficial adviser to Bill Gates—a claim the Microsoft founder’s representatives denied. One Times report indicates Epstein claimed to be a tax consultant for the tech magnate.After his initial meeting with the financier, the billionaire philanthropist told Gates Foundation staff in an email: “His lifestyle is very different and kind of intriguing although it would not work for me.” Asked about this message, Gates’ spokeswoman said he “was referring only to the unique decor” at Epstein's Manhattan mansion and “Epstein’s habit of spontaneously bringing acquaintances in to meet Mr. Gates.”The rapport between Gates and Epstein seems to have fizzled in the fall of 2014, sometime after Gates donated $2 million to MIT’s Media Lab. The lab’s former director Joi Ito, in an internal email unearthed by the New Yorker, claimed Epstein facilitated that donation. As the Times investigation noted: “Mr. Epstein complained to an acquaintance at the end of 2014 that Mr. Gates had stopped talking to him, according to a person familiar with the discussion.”Some special guests at @thrive's leadership meeting: board member @DavidAgus &amp; Dr Melanie Walker who's working w/@BillGates on global health pic.twitter.com/SaqQ4HQSrt— Arianna Huffington (@ariannahuff) March 7, 2017 Gates wasn’t Epstein’s only link to Microsoft. Walker, a neurosurgeon who worked for the Gates’ foundation from late 2005 to 2013, had known Epstein since 1992. She told the Times that she’d just graduated from college and Epstein had offered to land her a modeling job at Victoria’s Secret because he was an adviser to Les Wexner, the founder of the lingerie chain’s parent company, L Brands.Walker once stayed in an Epstein-owned apartment in Manhattan while traveling to New York, and in 1998, she became the financier's science adviser. Within a few years, she moved to Seattle to be with her now husband, then-Microsoft executive Steven Sinofsky, and was hired by the Bill &amp; Melinda Gates Foundation. There she met Nikolic, the Times report adds, and introduced him to Epstein.For his part, Nikolic told Bloomberg News he was “shocked” to be named as a “successor executor” in Epstein’s will, a position he quickly turned down. “I was not consulted in these matters and I have no intent to fulfill these duties, whatsoever,” he said in a statement released by his spokeswoman in August 2019.Nikolic is a graduate of Harvard Medical School, where at least one faculty member received funding that was facilitated by Epstein. According to Bloomberg, Nikolic “waxed enthusiastic about Epstein’s financial advice in discussions with private bankers” in 2014, ahead of a public offering for a genome editing firm Nikolic had funded.When Jeffrey Epstein needed a backup person to handle his estate, he chose Boris Nikolic, an ex-science adviser to Bill Gates https://t.co/ke2X08uwrL— Bloomberg (@business) August 20, 2019 Little is known about Nikolic and Epstein’s relationship, though Bloomberg reported the biotech venture capitalist insisted they had no financial ties.Meanwhile, Linda Stone, an ex-Microsoft VP, appears to have longer-standing ties to Epstein and vouched for him at MIT. “Ito was introduced to Epstein in February 2013 by Linda Stone, a former member of the Media Lab’s Advisory Council, at a TED Conference in Long Beach, California,” said one 2020 MIT report into Epstein’s largesse reviewed by The Daily Beast.“He has a tainted past, but Linda assures me that he’s awesome,” Ito said in an email to three MIT staffers, according to the document. But, in June 2013, when a lab assistant raised questions about Epstein’s checkered past, Ito asked Stone for help in avoiding a potential backlash over Epstein’s donations to the MIT Media Lab. In an email cited in the MIT report, Stone advised Ito that Epstein had “given a tremendous amount of money to Harvard” and “other scientists” and it would be “good to show that list.”“Focus on his funding of Harvard, scientists, over many years,” added Stone, whose tenure at Microsoft lasted from 1993 to 2002. She then mentioned Epstein “aggressively funds science &amp; tech &amp; interesting people.”The report notes that Stone apparently believed Epstein when he “insisted to her that he was ‘wrongfully convicted,’ pointing both to his light sentence and his assertion that he had been cleared by a lie detector test as evidence that he was truly innocent of the charges.”Epstein’s address book contained multiple phone numbers for Stone and listed Kelly Bovino—a former model who sources tell The Daily Beast was once part of Epstein’s inner circle—as Stone’s “emergency contact.” As The Daily Beast reported, Giuffre has publicly accused Bovino of aiding Epstein’s trafficking scheme.The tech insider who spoke to The Daily Beast noted Stone thrived on connecting people but that she “has a lot of friends who are infinitely richer than Epstein.” They added: “I can’t see anything Linda got out of it.”Here’s a curious photograph. Jeffrey Epstein talks to Nathan Myhrvold, formerly Microsoft’s chief technology officer, at the 2000 https://t.co/oEYOr4QjJI John Brockman billionaires’ dinner. pic.twitter.com/2DMKGe8s6Z— Xeni Jardin is fully vaccinated (@xeni) October 12, 2019 Epstein’s rolodex also had a variety of phone numbers for Nathan Myhrvold, Microsoft’s former chief technology officer. In July 2019, Vanity Fair reported the men were longtime friends, and that Epstein allegedly visited Myhrvold’s investment firm, Intellectual Ventures, with “young girls” who were possibly “Russian models” in tow.In 2003, Vanity Fair named Myhrvold as one of the many businessmen to dine with Epstein at his Manhattan townhouse, and the 2019 article cites a source who claimed Myhrvold openly discussed visiting Epstein’s homes in Florida and New York.A flight records database shows Myhrvold traveled on Epstein’s plane, in December 1996 and January 1997. Other passengers included Harvard law professor Alan Dershowitz and “GM,” believed to be Epstein’s alleged accomplice Ghislaine Maxwell.When Giuffre sued Dershowitz for defamation in April 2019, her complaint alleged the famed lawyer attempted to throw Myhrvold under the bus. The document refers to Giuffre by her maiden name, Roberts. “In May 2015 Dershowitz requested confidential settlement negotiations with Ms. Roberts’ lawyers in which Dershowitz sought to convince Ms. Roberts lawyer that Ms. Roberts was mistaken, and that the person to whom Epstein had lent Ms. Roberts was Nathan Myhrvold, not Dershowitz.”The lawsuit added that Giuffre “was, and is, clear that it was Dershowitz, not Myhrvold, with whom she had sex.”Myhrvold’s spokesperson told Vanity Fair: “Nathan has no knowledge of or any involvement in the various crimes that Mr. Epstein is accused of committing.”“He was never a client of his money management business, and he’s never done business with him of any sort,” the spokesperson added. “Back in the day Epstein was a regular at TED conferences and he was a large donor to basic scientific research, so while Nathan knew him and has socialized with him, that’s exactly where their association ends.”Myhrvold did, however, take a trip to Russia with tech journalist and conference host Esther Dyson sometime in the 1990s, and spent time with Epstein there.When reached by The Daily Beast, Dyson said that Epstein joined her and Myhrvold for a couple of days when their itineraries intersected in Sarov. The Microsoft executive had planned the meetup with the financier, she said.One photo Dyson posted on social media of herself and Epstein is timestamped 1998. Another image of Myhrvold includes the caption: “at Microsoft Russia in Moscow, April 98. This was the beginning of a three-week trip during which Nathan and a variety of hangers-on (including a bodyguard) explored the state of post-Soviet science.”Years later Dyson saw Epstein at Edge dinners and other events but says she didn’t have much interaction with him.“I wasn’t his category so to speak,” Dyson told The Daily Beast. “He liked rich people and scientists and there were a lot of them at [Edge] dinners.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Half Americans Think They're Better Than Everyone They Know...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/half-americans-think-better-person-than-everyone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 3 in 4 admit to judging other people’s behavior. Another 61 percent also worry other people are actively judging them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN unveils crypto trading team...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/07/goldman-sachs-unveils-new-cryptocurrency-trading-team-in-employee-memo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs formally kicked off the cryptocurrency trading era on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is FOX Peter Doocy Just Asking Questions - Or Trolling White House?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/05/07/peter-doocy-fox-news-profile-biden-white-house-485248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's is a born-and-raised scion of Fox. Now he’s sparring with the president’s team on national TV, and the game is kind of working for both sides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans could 'erase' unhappy memories with ground-breaking neurotechnology...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/humans-could-erase-unhappy-memories-24059390</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The memory-editing technique, called decoded neurofeedback, or DecNef, was created for the treatment of PTSD, but some critics say it could potentially be used to implant false memories</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon church sued over restrictions. Now, outbreak there has sickened 74...</title>
      <link>https://kval.com/news/local/74-get-covid-19-at-church-that-sued-last-year-in-effort-overturn-oregon-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kval.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) - Oregon health officials say at least 74 people linked to a church in Salem have contracted COVID-19. The Oregon Health Authority started investigating the outbreak at the People's Church on April 6, The Statesman Journal reported. The state did not release information about the outbreak until Wednesday. The church's website and Facebook page indicates in-person services and events continue to be held there including Mother's Day services scheduled for Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio's deadly police shootout prompts claims of abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-top-news-brazil-rio-de-janeiro-crime-health-5b59728164b4b133517c385b38f55865</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — A bloody, hourslong gunbattle in a Rio de Janeiro slum echoed into Friday, with authorities saying the police mission successfully eliminated two dozen criminals, while residents and activists claimed human rights abuses...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copper jumps to record...</title>
      <link>https://www.theedgemarkets.com/article/copper-jumps-record-growth-bets-supercharge-commodities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theedgemarkets.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(May 7): Copper soared to an all-time high as optimism about a global rebound from the pandemic spurs a surge across commodities markets.The metal — an economic bellwether — is front and centre in a rally that’s driven raw materials from lumber to iron ore to multi-year highs or records. Stimulus measures and vaccine rollouts are fueling prospects for a resurgence in demand that’s set to strain supply, while copper’s crucial role in the green-energy transition is set to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bar owner charged with selling fake vax cards in one of first cases of its kind...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Bar-owner-charged-with-selling-fake-coronavirus-16159225.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Old Corner Saloon fashions itself as a small-town institution. Sitting on a historic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Capitol rioter had 'Foxitis,' his attorney says: He 'started believing what was fed to him'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/accused-capitol-rioter-had-foxitis-his-attorney-says-he-started-believing-what-was-being-fed-to-him/ar-BB1gsEBj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At at a hearing Thursday, Anthony Antonio’s attorney said he spent six months watching Fox News, which contributed to his decision to participate in the insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEC Dems blast decision to drop probe into hush-money payment to Stormy Daniels...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Democrats-on-FEC-blast-decision-to-drop-probe-16159195.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Election Commission on Thursday dropped its inquiry to determine whether...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Americans hesitate to shed masks despite eased outdoor rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210507085304-dpx57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-MASKS (TV, PIX):'You feel naked': Some Americans hesitate to shed masks despite eased outdoor rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Enough Chlorine, Propane...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/05/nationwide-shortage-of-chlorine-and-propane-tank-impacting-pools-right-before-summer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nationwide shortage of pool products is making chlorine tablets and propane tanks hard to come by and increasing prices right as the summer months approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Warns of Peril for Asset Prices as Investors Gorge on Risk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-says-asset-prices-may-201252345.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A rising appetite for risk across a variety of asset markets is stretching valuations and creating vulnerabilities in the U.S. financial system, the Federal Reserve said in its semi-annual financial stability report.“Vulnerabilities associated with elevated risk appetite are rising,” Fed Governor Lael Brainard, the head of the Board’s financial stability committee, said in a statement accompanying the report released Thursday. “The combination of stretched valuations with very high levels of corporate indebtedness bear watching because of the potential to amplify the effects of a re-pricing event.”In this environment, prices may be vulnerable to “significant declines” should risk appetite fall, the Fed report noted.Brainard and the report mentioned losses at banks stemming from dealings with Archegos Capital Management, and the governor called for “more granular, higher-frequency disclosures.”“The Archegos event illustrates the limited visibility into hedge-fund exposures and serves as a reminder that available measures of hedge-fund leverage may not be capturing important risks,” she said.The Managed Funds Association, which represents hedge funds, took issue with Brainard’s remarks.“It is unfortunate policy makers incorrectly conflate hedge funds with unregulated entities like individuals and family offices,” Association President Bryan Corbett said in a statement. “Hedge funds are well regulated” by the Securities and Exchange Commission.Near-zero interest rates and massive bond purchases, with the Fed buying $40 billion in mortgage-backed securities and $80 billion in Treasuries every month, have fueled a search for returns and helped buoy asset prices including those of risky investments such as speculative stocks, cryptocurrencies and high-yield debt. The Standard and Poor’s 500 stock index has risen 12% this year.“The real story here is the tension -- if not the glaring contradiction -- of the Fed’s pursuit of quantitative easing, the aim of which is to lower long-term rates and encourage reach for yield, and their concern that people are indeed reaching for yield,” said George Selgin, a senior fellow at the Cato Institute in Washington, referring to the bond buying. “The Fed could certainly taper its QE activities to counter this risk-taking as the recovery continues.”Spacs, Meme Stocks“Indicators pointing to elevated risk appetite in equity markets in early 2021 include the episodes of high trading volumes and price volatility for so-called meme stocks -- stocks that increased in trading volume after going viral on social media,” the report said. “Elevated equity issuance through SPACs also suggests a higher-than-typical appetite for risk among equity investors.”Low rates are also impacting the real economy. Home prices are up 12% year over year amid high demand for property and scarce supply, while a boom in home remodeling has helped push lumber futures to record highs. The Bloomberg Commodity Index, which tracks everything from grains to natural gas and nickel, is up 19%.The report said house-price increases have had a positive effect for borrowers by boosting equity. Still, it noted that borrowers in forbearance programs, who are likely to be employed in industries hard hit by the pandemic, could be vulnerable when they exit. “Even so, a large fraction of borrowers have already exited forbearance -- in general, these borrowers have loans that are either current or paid off,” the report said.The report also noted that low interest rates have reduced default expectations, and underwriting standards have weakened. “The share of newly issued loans to large corporations with high leverage -- defined as those with ratios of debt to earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization greater than 6 -- has exceeded the historical highs reached in recent years,” it said.Hedge Fund LeverageThe report said that “available data suggest” that hedge funds are highly leveraged, and said there is a need for greater transparency on opaque risk exposures, echoing Brainard’s call for more transparency.“Some hedge funds with substantial short positions sustained losses during the meme stock episode in January 2021, when intense social media activity contributed to fluctuations in the prices of some specific stocks,” the report said, probably a reference to the short squeeze in shares of GameStop Corp., which soared to more than $300 a share from around $20 a share in a matter of days.Jon Caplis, chief executive officer at hedge fund consultant PivotalPath, said after the report’s release that one disclosure in particular could mitigate the risk of a future Archegos-like situation happening again.“Before you try and rewrite all the regulatory statutes, you can make one small change that would be effective,” he said. “If you merely treat total-return swaps in the same way hedge funds are already disclosing equity holdings, you would drastically mitigate an Archegos-like fallout from happening again.”(Updates with hedge fund reaction in sixth and seventh paragraphs.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
