<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Beto throws shade at McConaughey...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/politics/article/Beto-O-Rourke-Texas-governor-run-McConaughey-16485628.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Texas congressman pondered McConaughey's ambiguous politics while remaining...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran and Venezuela strike oil deal amid US sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/573931-iran-and-venezuela-strike-oil-deal-amid-us-sanctions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran and Venezuela have struck an oil deal amid U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-elections-germany-angela-merkel-european-union-0203ca4281803d2d9af5e1df421a7f26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's closely fought election on Sunday will set the direction of the European Union's most populous country after 16 years under Angela Merkel, whose party is scrambling to avoid defeat by its center-left rivals after a rollercoaster campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The great sperm heist: 'They were playing with people's lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/sep/25/the-great-sperm-heist-they-were-playing-with-peoples-lives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul was in his 80s when someone called to say she was his daughter, conceived in a fertility clinic with his sperm. The only problem? He’d never donated any</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychedelic awakening led Navy SEAL on mission to save monarch butterflies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/environment/monarch-butterflies-are-wiped-combat-veterans-are-trying-rcna2200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guardian Grange aims to help veterans cope with trauma and transitioning back to civilian life. The group's first projects is to help build a butterfly preserve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Hawke 'BLACK PHONE' Next Horror Smash?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/ethan-hawke-the-black-phone-blumhouse-1235049261/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally, something scarier than the COVID-19 delta variant has come out of CinemaCon 2021. Universal Pictures unveiled a packed trailer for its upcoming Blumhouse horror thriller “The Black P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in booster guidance leads to confusion, chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/changes-in-booster-shot-guidance-leads-to-confusion-chaos-for-doctors-and-the-vaccinated/ar-AAOOsq9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confusion over boosters, which has been brewing for months, heightened over the past week as government regulators and advisers met to hash out the pros and cons of doling out third doses - and came up with different recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When FBI seizes messages from Big Tech, you may not know for years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/when-the-fbi-seizes-your-messages-from-big-tech-you-may-not-know-it-for-years/ar-AAONVgy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft, Google, Facebook and other tech firms are pressing lawmakers to enact new rules to stop prosecutors from secretly snooping on private messages, photos, search history and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junkies shoot up in broad daylight in Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/25/nyc-drug-users-shoot-up-in-broad-daylight-in-midtown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The block bordered by 35th and 36th streets, and Seventh and Eighth Avenues, is “littered with used needles, broken glass crack pipes, trash, urine, and feces.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police departments clamoring for de-escalation training...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/death-of-george-floyd-police-new-york-new-york-city-maine-a85463f8955fcf4be53e7b66287c1a87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACO, Maine (AP) — Angry over being fired, a former employee slashed the tires of his boss’ vehicle and still held the knife when police officers arrived. Three officers positioned themselves at a safe distance as the man yelled and ranted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazis still using. And making money...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-technology-sports-business-43cc5e3bc9fbdd6d2d2f425c117e4f0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — It’s the premier martial arts group in Europe for right-wing extremists. German authorities have twice banned their signature tournament. But Kampf der Nibelungen, or Battle of the Nibelungs, still thrives on Facebook, where organizers maintain multiple pages, as well as on Instagram and YouTube, which they use to spread their ideology, draw in recruits and make money through ticket sales and branded merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pill to Treat Covid 'Months Away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/daily-pill-treat-covid-could-be-just-months-away-scientists-n1279938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three promising antivirals that could prevent symptoms and limit transmission of Covid-19 are in clinical trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Germany's battle to succeed Merkel, final campaign scrambles with race up for grabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-germany-e2-80-99s-battle-to-succeed-merkel-final-campaign-scrambles-with-race-up-for-grabs/ar-AAOO3HS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even after Sunday's voting, difficult coalition talks are likely ahead to form a government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Spanish volcano eruption intensifies and suspends flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/la-palma-volcano-eruption-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eruptions on the Cumbre Vieja volcano on the Canary Island of La Palma intensifies, as flights are suspended and more evacuations are made while hot lava spews from the volcano and toxic ash blankets the surrounding area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI investigating alleged assault on Fort Bliss soldier at refugee camp...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/573901-fbi-investigating-alleged-assault-on-female-service-member-at-afghan-refugee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is investigating an alleged assault on a female service member at an Afghan refugee camp in New Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: How Thiel became most feared man in Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/25/how-peter-thiel-became-the-most-feared-man-in-silicon-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Facebook’s first president, Sean Parker, first brought Thiel into the fold as an investor in 2004, he warned Zuckerberg against the financier’s “dirty tricks.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reparations for Black Residents Gaining Steam...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/25/reparations-for-black-residents-are-becoming-a-local-issue-as-well-as-a-national-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Detroit took everything from Keith E. Williams and his family. He now wants it back. Right before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among Those Who Marched Into Capitol on Jan. 6: FBI Informant...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/25/among-those-who-marched-into-the-capitol-on-jan-6-an-f-b-i-informant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As scores of Proud Boys made their way, chanting and shouting, toward the Capitol on Jan. 6, one member of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Hospitals Face Mass Firings as Workers Spurn Vax...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/new-york-hospitals-face-possible-mass-firings-as-workers-spurn-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Buffalo, the Erie County Medical Center plans to suspend elective in-patient surgeries and not take intensive-care patients from other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitness Teachers, Plumbers Highest-Paying Jobs With No Experience Necessary...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/no-experience-highest-paying-jobs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although jobs that don't require a college education have a reputation of being low-paying, the study finds several which buck that trend significantly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces 'substantial' legal risk in Georgia case, think tank report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/politics/2021/09/24/trump-faces-substantial-legal-risk-georgia-case-think-tank-report-says/5851857001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report, written by seven legal analysts, concludes that Trump’s post-election conduct leaves him at “substantial risk of possible state charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Britain, Rising Prices and Shortages Evoke 1970s-Style Jitters...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/in-britain-rising-prices-and-shortages-evoke-1970s-style-jitters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Long lines at gas stations, rising fuel prices, empty shelves in supermarkets, and worries about runaway inflation. Britons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Afghans arrive near small Virginia town...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Thousands-of-Afghans-arrived-near-a-small-16486872.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLACKSTONE, Va. - Mayor Billy Coleburn finished his burger, pulled out his cellphone and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surveillance Apparatus That Surrounded Britney...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/the-surveillance-apparatus-that-surrounded-britney-spears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears’s father and the security firm he hired to protect her ran an intense surveillance apparatus that monitored her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Looking Anew at Carbon Tax...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/24/sinemas-income-tax-stance-has-democrats-looking-anew-at-a-carbon-tax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Opposition from a single moderate Democrat to corporate and income tax rate increases has revived efforts in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah's Ark hunters claims found boat using 3D scans...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3725022/noahs-ark-buried-turkish-mountains-experts-3d-scans-prove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GIANT shape claimed to match the Biblical description of Noah’s Ark has been found by researchers using 3D scans. Biblical archaeologists used ground penetrating radar to study the boat-lik…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cavers Reach Bottom of Ancient 'Well of Hell' For First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbn39/cavers-reached-the-bottom-of-an-ancient-well-of-hell-for-the-first-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Well of Barhout in Yemen is millions of years old, nobody knows how it formed, and now cavers have reached the floor for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Legal Gambling Rise Will Ruin Sports...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/mlb/sports-gambling-is-a-disaster-waiting-to-happen/ar-AAOLRrk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Betting on Tom Brady’s next completion may sound like harmless fun. But it’s not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden WILL Release Trump Documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/24/politics/biden-trump-white-house-executive-privilege/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has determined he will not assert executive privilege to shield Trump-era records from being seen by a congressional committee investigating the January 6 insurrection attempt, the White House said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey says he's 'more of folk singin', philosopher, poet-statesman' than politician...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/matthew-mcconaughey-says-he-s-more-of-a-folk-singin-philosopher-poet-statesman-than-a-politician-as-he-continues-to-flirt-with-run-for-texas-governor/ar-AAOMSPO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The McConaissance never stopped," McConaughey said, adding he's "measuring" a run for Texas governor, and that "politics needs redefinition."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian C-17 weave between skyscrapers in 'insane' video...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/news/c-17-flyover-brisbane-australia-riverfire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Royal Australian Air Force C-17 Globemaster III cargo jet flew low between skyscrapers in Brisbane, Australia on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael K. Williams overdosed on cocaine, heroin, fentanyl accidentally...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/local/michael-k-williams-death-ruled-accidental-overdose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wire” and “Boardwalk Empire” star Michael K. Williams died of an accidental overdose of fentanyl, cocaine and heroin, the New York City Office of Chief Medical Examiner said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART customer 'stabbed in HEAD with machete'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3726781/man-stabbed-in-head-with-machete/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN was reportedly stabbed in the head with a machete during a fight at a Walmart. Police responded to a chaotic scene inside a Walmart located on Harrison Avenue in Kearny, New Jersey,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boss may be watching long after pandemic ends...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/keystroke-tracking-screenshots-and-facial-recognition-the-boss-may-be-watching-long-after-the-pandemic-ends/ar-AAOM9bF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies are increasingly turning to surveillance software tools as they consider permanent remote work policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet America's Most Censored Person...</title>
      <link>https://taibbi.substack.com/p/meet-josiah-zayner-americas-most</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taibbi.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientist Josiah Zayner is brilliant, daring, and may have incurred the wrath of more internet platforms than any person alive. Is America's most interesting person also its most censored?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
