<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CHIEFS assistant coach investigated for crash after 'drank and took Adderall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/sportsnews/article-9230969/Kansas-City-Chiefs-coach-Britt-Reid-involved-multi-car-crash-ahead-Super-Bowl-LV.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britt Reid, 35, is in hospital with undisclosed injuries and could be there for days, according to reports from ESPN, after the incident which has left a young child with life-threatening injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robert Maxwell rose from poverty -- and corrupted daughter Ghislaine...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/how-robert-maxwell-rose-from-poverty-and-corrupted-daughter-ghislaine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Within 72 hours of her birth, Ghislaine Maxwell’s life was twisted by tragedy. Baby Ghislaine was the ninth child born to Robert Maxwell, the self-made millionaire publisher, and his wife Betty. Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NISSAN 'office pod' imagines new kind of remote working...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/nissan-concept-office-pod/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inspired by the new realities of the Covid-19 era, the concept camper features a retractable office for remote workers and digital nomads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD: Migrants Force Biden to Confront Border Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/06/migrant-families-force-biden-to-confront-new-border-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — President Biden’s first immigration crisis has already begun as thousands of families have surged toward the southwestern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race is on...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/learn-on-mars-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;February is a big month for Mars exploration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Deficit, Met Considers Selling Art to Pay Bills...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/05/facing-deficit-met-considers-selling-art-to-help-pay-the-bills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a potential shortfall of $150 million because of the pandemic, the Metropolitan Museum of Art has begun conversations with auction houses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald's Senate Trial to Be Held With Signs of Siege All Around...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-senate-trial-to-be-held-with-signs-of-siege-all-around/ar-BB1drCOo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s Senate trial will be enveloped by a thick security cordon of razor-wire-topped fencing, National Guard troops and armed police officers protecting lawmakers -- a stark reminder of the violent assault on the Capitol that touched off his unprecedented second impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Thinking we are unique is arrogant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210206-harvard-astronomer-argues-that-alien-vessel-paid-us-a-visit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard astronomer argues that alien vessel paid us a visit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutated virus may reinfect people already stricken once...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/mutated-virus-may-reinfect-people-already-stricken-once-with-covid-19-sparking-debate-and-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trial of an experimental coronavirus vaccine detected the most sobering signal yet that people who have recovered from infections are not completely protected against a variant that originated in South Africa and is spreading rapidly, preliminary data presented this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED PLANET: China probe sends back first image of Mars; Landing nears...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210206-china-s-space-probe-sends-back-first-image-of-mars-ahead-of-this-year-s-landing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Tianwen-1 probe has sent back its first image of Mars, the national space agency said, as the mission prepares to touch down on the Red Planet later this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX DUMPS DOBBS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fox-news-cancels-lou-dobbs-231003769.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lou Dobbs remains under contract at Fox News but won't be back on the air after he hosted his last show Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  NYT Star Reporter Fired for 'Racial Slurs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ny-times-star-reporter-fired-after-daily-beast-expose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple students who attended a Times-sponsored trip with Don McNeil in 2019 alleged that he used racist slurs throughout the journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says no intel briefs for 'erratic' Donald...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/joe-biden-says-donald-trump-should-get-intelligence-briefings-1234688771/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden says that Donald Trump should not receive intelligence briefings even though they typically have been given to previous former presidents. In his first sit-down interview with a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  NO FED CHARGES FOR TRUMP OVER STORMY HUSH MONEY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-campaign-case-dead-a03b35429340d997593f049885331035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The federal probe of hush money paid to cover up former President Donald Trump's alleged extramarital affairs hasn’t been restarted, even though he no longer has the legal shield...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX DUMPS DOBBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2021-02-05/fox-news-cancels-lou-dobbs-tonight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lou Dobbs remains under contract at Fox News but won't be back on the air after he hosted his last show Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG:  'We should be teleporting, not transporting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9229465/Mark-Zuckerberg-says-teleporting-not-transporting-believes-AR-VR-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg appeared in the audio-only social app Clubhouse to talk about VR and AR. He said the technology will help us 'teleport' to physical places - such as the office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Sized Security Despite Smallest Crowd; 70 Agencies Flanking Stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/super-bowl-2021-security-tampa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventy federal, state and local agencies will flank Raymond James Stadium for the Super Bowl's most sparsely attended game ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Guru Resigns After Resurfaced Sex Harassment Accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/ny-times-caliphate-producer-andy-mills-resigns-after-resurfaced-sexual-harassment-accusations/ar-BB1dr0Qb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andy Mills, the New York Times audio producer who helped lead the now-discredited "Caliphate" podcast and has been accused of sexual harassment, has resigned. In a note posted to his personal website on Friday, Mills said he made "mistakes" in the past that he now looks back on with "extraordinary regret and embarrassment." Though he said he "strived to continue to grow and be a better co-worker and person" when at the Times, the accusations...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica's marijuana shortage branded 'cultural embarrassment'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/jamaicas-marijuana-shortage-branded-a-cultural-embarrassment-12209752</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricanes, drought and the COVID-19 pandemic have all taken their toll on farmers and their crops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Brain-altering bioweapons' to DNA surveillance: The next threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/worse-than-covid-next-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most distressing topics researchers list is the immediate concern of DNA's use in government surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Business Sought Stake In PARLER...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/trump-parler-ownership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents seen by BuzzFeed News show that Parler offered Trump 40% of the company if he posted exclusively to the platform. The deal was never finalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NYTIMES Star Reporter Fired for 'Slur'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-times-star-reporter-fired-214228379.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DON EMMERTThe New York Times on Friday announced the ouster of science and health reporter Donald McNeil Jr., who The Daily Beast reported had allegedly used racist language while on a 2019 trip with students to Peru.McNeil, formerly the paper of record’s top reporter on COVID-19, leaves amid fallout from an incident that occurred during a Times-sponsored educational trip to Peru when he used the “n-word” and made other racist comments, according to complaints first reported by The Daily Beast. At least six students or their parents claimed McNeil had made racist and sexist remarks throughout the trip.“I should not have done that,” McNeil confessed in a Friday email shared with Times staff. “Originally, I thought the context in which I used this ugly word could be defended.”The science reporter further described the “n-word” incident as having occurred during a dinner discussion about the use of racial slurs, in which one student on the trip asked whether a classmate should have been suspended for using racist rhetoric in a video. “To understand what was in the video, I asked if she had called someone else the slur or whether she was rapping or quoting a book title. In asking the question, I used the slur itself,” McNeil wrote. He apologized for “extraordinarily bad judgment” to both the staff of the Times, singling out those he worked closely with, and to the students on the trip. “I am sorry. I let you all down.”McNeil’s departure comes just days after Times staffers wrote a letter to the paper’s top brass expressing outrage over the allegations that McNeil had used racial slurs; and over the response from Times leadership which the signees suggested was wholly insufficient.Baquet had previously said McNeil should be “given another chance” because his comments were not “hateful or malicious” in intent, but in a message to staff on Friday, the top editor wrote: “We do not tolerate racist language regardless of intent.”McNeil’s behavior on the trip had been hotly debated between Times staffers, including some who took part in a meeting with executive editor Dean Baquet and assistant managing editor Carolyn Ryan last Friday. At that meeting, Pulitzer Prize winner Nikole Hannah-Jones said she planned on calling the parents and students on the trip to determine what McNeil had said and in what context, according to people familiar with the situation.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson suspected in massive fire at Texas courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-arson-courts-texas-896fbf8e5052512e62ad02fb94a24845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MASON, Texas (AP) — A suspect has been arrested been taken into custody following a massive fire that destroyed all but the rock outer walls of an 111-year-old Texas courthouse, an official...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica faces marijuana shortage...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/jamaica-faces-marijuana-shortage-farmers-struggle-75710269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamaica is running low on ganja</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 5,077 deaths...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/05/us-records-record-5077-covid-deaths-after-audit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US recorded its deadliest day of the pandemic Thursday — tallying 5,077 COVID-19 deaths and exceeding the previous pandemic peak set in January by more than 600, according to Johns Hopkins Univ…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dems, Republicans competing to throw cash at you...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/blog/meet-press-blog-latest-news-analysis-data-driving-political-discussion-n988541/ncrd1256872#blogHeader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden wants to send parents up to $300 a month per child. Sen. Mitt Romney wants to boost it to $350. They're both part of a broader trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of no-ad advertising...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/the-hottest-super-bowl-ad-trend-not-running-an-ad/ar-BB1dq0sG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a time and place for mourning an anthropomorphized legume, but the midst of a pandemic is not it. This is the short way of telling you that there will be no second attempt to kill off Mr. Peanut this year, after the advertising logo initially died in a pregame Super Bowl ad in 2020. Planters originally intended for Mr. Peanut's funeral to air during last year's Super Bowl — as the dramatic precursor to his Lazarus moment, when he was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas announce 6 new NETFLIX projects...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-9229287/Obamas-production-company-Netflix-announces-new-shows-movies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Higher Ground Productions, which President Barack Obama and Michelle Obama formed in partnership with Netflix, announced a new lineup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Americans Shouldn't Be Treated Like ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/05/americans-shouldnt-be-treated-like-isis-insurgents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adopting "counterinsurgency" tactics for use against wide swaths of Americans can only make the situation worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal divided over massive King of Hammers off-road event...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-news/article/Joshua-Tree-King-Hammers-Yucca-Valley-SoCal-15924814.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s good old-fashioned American freedom out here.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All New Orleans bars closed for Mardi Gras...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/politics/article_2abead06-67c3-11eb-adce-5b477745ca7b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bars will be closed, people will have to pass through checkpoints to get to major streets like Bourbon and Frenchmen streets and a heavy police presence will patrol New Orleans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First U.S. Funeral Home That Turns Bodies Into Compost Now Open...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93wmd5/the-first-us-funeral-home-that-turns-bodies-into-compost-is-now-open</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recompose, located outside of Seattle, has turned its first customers into soil after years of development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia to become first southern state to abolish death penalty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/05/virginia-first-southern-state-abolish-death-penalty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State house’s vote makes abolition assured, a historically important step since capital punishment emerged from the south as a legal alternative to lynching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intruder gained unauthorized access, entered jet at Andrews... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/02/05/intruder-gained-unauthorized-access-entered-c-40-jet-at-joint-base-andrews-home-of-air-force-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was arrested after gaining unauthorized access to Joint Base Andrews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going big, fast and alone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/senate-ok-fast-track-coronavirus-aid-c497b8cda93486d9f0a09abb88235291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden laid out the case Friday for moving fast and without Republicans, if necessary, to pass $1.9 trillion in coronavirus relief, armed with new signs of economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military grapples with widespread skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/survey-finds-military-families-less-trusting-of-the-coronavirus-vaccine-than-general-population-1.661092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of military families found just 33 percent would receive an approved coronavirus vaccine should it become available at no cost. A Gallup survey of the general U.S. population found 58 percent of respondents were willing to receive the vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops deploy for vaccine campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210205-us-covid-cases-down-61-since-peak-troops-deploy-for-vaccine-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Covid cases down 61% since peak, troops deploy for vaccine campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Plummer Dead at 91...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/christopher-plummer-dies-91-sound-of-music-all-the-money-in-the-world-star-1234688379/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Plummer, who starred in The Sound of Music, won an Oscar for Beginners and was nominated for All the Money in the World and The Last Station, died peacefully today at his home in Connec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says next stimulus check with be for $1,400...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2276071/joe-biden-act-fact-stimulus-checks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENT Joe Biden vowed “to act fact” to get $1,400 stimulus checks to Americans after the new $1.9trillion Covid budget plan has passed. During a press briefing on Friday, Biden told…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients asphyxiate as Latin America battles oxygen crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210205-patients-asphyxiate-as-latin-america-battles-oxygen-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients asphyxiate as Latin America battles oxygen crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER HUMAN?</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/05/tom-brady-legacy-beyond-the-scope-of-understanding-super-bowl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That Tom Brady is playing in his 10th Super Bowl at the age of 43 is a testament to the quarterback's indomitable drive to just keep winning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only fools bet against Brady. Or against Mahomes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-football-coronavirus-pandemic-081ffc7ce4ccaf5f93fc418073559ff0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the dilemma prognosticators face for Sunday's Super Bowl: Only fools bet against Tom Brady. Or against Patrick Mahomes. So here we are, with an on-time NFL championship game...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filmmakers use secret interviews and archival material...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/woody-allen-scandal-mia-farrow-dylan-hbo-kirby-dick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Woody Allen scandal will again be brought into the spotlight, this time in a new, four-part docuseries, "Allen v. Farrow," coming Feb. 21</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of no-ad advertising...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/the-hottest-super-bowl-ad-trend-not-running-an-ad/ar-BB1dq0sG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen Scandal to Get HBO Docuseries Treatment in 'ALLEN V. FARROW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/secret-explosive-woody-allen-doc-series-from-kirby-dick-amy-ziering-coming-to-hbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen v. Farrow goes behind decades of sensational headlines to reveal the private story of one of Hollywood’s most notorious and public scandals: the accusation of sexual abuse against Woody Allen involving Dylan, his then 7-year-old daughter with Mia Farrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed robber steals chicken from restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/angry-maskless-customer-armed-with-gun-robs-roscoes-chicken-waffles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pasadena police are looking for an armed robber who hit the Roscoe’s Chicken and Waffles on Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AI Can Detect Emotion With Radio Waves...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2021/02/new-ai-can-detect-emotion-radio-waves/171863/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are national security and privacy implications to an experimental UK neural network that deciphers how people respond to emotional stimuli.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payrolls barely grow to start 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/05/jobs-report-january-2021.html'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodell gives 'greatest' tribute to Brady 5 years after suspending...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/02/05/sports/roger-goodell-gives-tribute-tom-brady-five-years-after-suspending-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Brady has done since his suspension is qualify for four of the next five Super Bowls, including this weekend’s game between the Buccaneers and Chiefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAM IT THROUGH: KAMALA HARRIS BREAKS FIRST SENATE TIE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/senate-budget-resolution-advances-43b5f08b-bc93-470d-827e-0a1818b026cd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris served as the tie-breaking vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Gets Sued Over Its Social Media Surveillance Tactics...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dhs-sued-over-its-social-media-surveillance-tactics-1846092273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security is being slammed with a new lawsuit after spending just over a year failing to respond to repeated attempts at investigating its long-term data hoovering practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Threatening, 'Menacing' People Who Paid Their Taxes: 'They're Freaked Out'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/02/04/irs-threatens-coloradans-who-already-paid-taxes-theyre-frightened-and-they-dont-understand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accountants along the Front Range are telling CBS4 that dozens of clients who paid their 2019 taxes are nonetheless getting menacing letters from the IRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why global travel unlikely to resume 'till 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/coronavirus-in-israel-vaccination-doesnt-equal-liberation-657898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH AFFAIRS: Vaccination doesn’t equal liberation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago's Deep Feb Freeze Could Become Longest Cold Stretch on Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcchicago.com/weather/chicagos-deep-february-freeze-could-become-longest-such-cold-stretch-on-record/2429315/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cold spell hitting the Chicago area this weekend isn’t going to let up anytime soon, and could become the longest stretch of such February temperatures the city has ever seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Wagers Fire Up Rally in Gambling Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.fa-mag.com/news/record-super-bowl-wagers-fire-up-rally-in-sports-gambling-stocks-60216.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fa-mag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super Bowl will be the first time users in states like Colorado, Illinois, Michigan and Virginia can lawfully bet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Race war evident long before Capitol siege...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-us-news-race-and-ethnicity-conspiracy-theories-philanthropy-f8f793b94b0dd7e8ec62957dcbeb53d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A war rages on in America, and it didn’t begin with Donald Trump or the assault on the Capitol. It started with slavery and never ended, through lynchings and voter suppression, the snarling...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
