<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Owes millions in taxes?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1260064/youtuber-jake-paul-owed-two-million-federal-taxes-before-fbi-raid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOUTUBER Jake Paul was hit with a federal tax lien for over $2 million before the FBI raided his Los Angeles home and seized guns from the residence, The Sun can exclusively reveal.  On Wednes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Digital Revenue Exceeds Print for 1st Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/new-york-times-tops-q2-estimates-as-digital-revenue-exceeds-print-revenue-for-the-first-time-2020-08-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times Co. undefined posted better-than-expected earnings for the second quarter on Wednesday, and said digital revenue exceeded print revenue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Member of controversial church sues online critics who claimed he helped spread virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/coronavirus/article244610242.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: USA has world's worst outbreak..</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/fauci-says-cant-deny-us-has-worst-covid-19-outbreak-2020-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fauci's comments on Wednesday stood in stark contrast to President Trump's recent rhetoric on the US outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of public data hampers covid fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/lack-of-public-data-hampers-covid-19-fight/article_5488f802-ae46-52d7-9abc-a6742663a4ab.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Ali Mokdad, an epidemiologist at the University of Washington, has been trying to make sense of this summer's COVID-19 surge. He says he can theorize only in a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAND PAUL: Republicans should apologize to Obama for complaining about spending!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rand-paul-republicans-apologize-obama-spending-3e352d95-360b-4645-9678-de06e7ba212b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They might lose this election because they are acting like Democrats now."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION ORACLE SEES BIDEN WIN...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/510754-professor-with-history-of-correctly-predicting-elections-forecasts-that</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American University professor Allan Lichtman, who has a record of accurately predicting presidential races, said he expects former Vice President Joe Biden, the presumptive Democratic nominee, to defeat President Trump in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women break silence, tell stories of rape, groping by Ron Jeremy over decades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/years-silence-ron-jeremys-arrest-120046906.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the days since Ron Jeremy was charged with sexual assault, half a dozen women have contacted The Times to detail allegations of rape and groping against the adult film star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn video interrupts court hearing for accused TWITTER hacker...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/porn-video-interrupts-us-court-hearing-accused-twitter-222829377.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A court hearing held via Zoom for a US teenager accused of masterminding a stunning hack of Twitter was interrupted Wednesday with rap music and porn, a newspaper reported. Investigators view the youth -- AFP has chosen not to release his name because he is a minor -- as the brains behind the mid-July</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE DANGER:  Trump's Bank Subpoenaed by NY Prosecutors in Criminal Inquiry... </title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/05/trumps-bank-was-subpoenaed-by-n-y-prosecutors-in-criminal-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York prosecutors who are seeking President Trump’s tax records have also subpoenaed his longtime lender, a sign that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won't go to Milwaukee for acceptance speech...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7970759fa14fdb8c9b1e7a6ad65b5f9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden will not travel to Milwaukee to accept the Democratic presidential nomination because of concerns over the coronavirus, party officials said Wednesday, signaling a move to a convention...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY SWIRLS</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/mystery-swirls-around-what-caused-ammonium-nitrate-to-explode-in-beirut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unconfirmed picture appears to show workers welding door of warehouse filled with chemical; report says authorities warned of dangers for years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Winter Will Be Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2020/08/winter-us-coronavirus-pandemic-dangerous-indoors/614965/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When socializing outside gets harder in much of the U.S., daily life will get more dismal, and the virus might spread even further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided ketamine trip therapy clinic opening in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/05/licensed-guided-ketamine-trip-clinic-opening-in-nyc-this-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mind-expanding injection may be just what the doctor ordered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Income Predicts How Well You Can Socially Distance...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/your-income-predicts-how-well-you-can-socially-distance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's rich used to move around more than the poor. When Covid landed, that flipped: The wealthy now work remotely, while essential workers toil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheap, Easy Deepfakes Getting Closer to Real Thing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/cheap-easy-deepfakes-closer-real-thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using open-source software and less than $100, a researcher was able to create plausible images and audio of actor Tom Hanks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans push for more money for airlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/gop-senators-support-more-money-for-airlines-to-pay-workers/572017322/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow the StarTribune for the news, photos and videos from the Twin Cities and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Must Better Police 'Hate', State AGs Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/20-state-attorneys-general-facebook-tackle-hate-speech-disinformation-2020-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is facing mounting political and regulatory pressure over its failures to police its social network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model's video gives rare glimpse inside Chinese internment...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-53650246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven months ago Merdan Ghappar disappeared in Xinjiang. Then his family started getting messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus testing in USA dropping...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aebdc0978de958f20ab3f398cdf6f769</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. testing for the coronavirus is dropping even as infections remain high and the death toll rises by more than 1,000 a day, a worrisome trend that officials attribute largely to Americans...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why scientists worry about 'Warp Speed' vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/science/article/Why-scientists-worry-about-a-Warp-Speed-15458316.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the race for a COVID-19 vaccine heads into the stretch run, scientists are tempering their enthusiasm with caution.  The goal of Operation Warp Speed, the U.S. vaccine initiative, is 300 million doses of a safe, effective vaccine by January, and if realized, it would be one of the greatest scientific achievements of all time. On Tuesday, Goldman Sachs predicted the Food and Drug Administration would approve at least one vaccine before the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women break silence, tell stories of rape, groping by Ron Jeremy over decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-08-05/ron-jeremy-arrest-uncovers-rape-groping-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the days since Ron Jeremy was charged with sexual assault, half a dozen women have contacted The Times to detail allegations of rape and groping against the adult film star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former clients of acting 'Homeland' chief got millions in DHS contracts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/05/former-clients-of-acting-homeland-security-chief-chad-wolf-get-millions-in-dhs-contracts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wolf, who became the acting chief of the department late last year, was a lobbyist for over a decade at Wexler &amp; Walker before he took leadership roles with DHS under President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign seeks early September presidential debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-campaign-debate-september-0c85776c-0cb1-4741-8210-2adf46c9c6b8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The aim is to force Joe Biden to the debate stage before the first early voting takes place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$108M in cash seized from air travelers in Atlanta...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/business/millions-in-currency-seized-at-airports-often-due-to-reporting-violation/QNZ4RDKSSNDMDC2VRYM3H5CIGI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection has seized millions of dollars in currency from travelers, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors alarmed by loss of hair...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/freaking-covid-19-survivors-hair-153850699.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a quarter of patients recovering from COVID-19 report hair loss in the aftermath of the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim new toll: 1 death every 80 seconds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/one-death-every-80-seconds-grim-new-toll-covid-19-n1235890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It will go away like things go away," President Trump claimed. Joe Biden says Trump is living in a world of delusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interior secretary confirms feds monitoring protesters' socials...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/interior-secretary-calls-confederate-statue-protesters-baddoers-confirms-feds-are-monitoring-their-social-media-feeds-160351551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his condemnation of protesters, David Bernhardt was wading into the culture wars with a zeal that does not ordinarily attach to the role of interior secretary. And since Bernhardt happens to be in charge of public lands, he can effectively campaign for Trump while claiming to do agency work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  80% of Black Americans Want Same or More Cops in Neighborhoods...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/four-in-five-black-americans-want-same-or-more-cop-presence-in-neighborhood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 80 percent of black Americans want the police to spend as much or more time in their neighborhoods as they currently do, new polling from Gallup conducted last month finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Begs the Rich to Come Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8595717/Cuomo-begs-wealthy-New-Yorkers-come-save-city-Ill-buy-drink.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of New York City residents fled Manhattan and Brooklyn earlier this year when the city was the COVID-19 epicenter of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Receives Mysterious Package Of Face Masks From China...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/08/04/pennsylvania-man-receives-package-of-face-masks-from-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First, there were reports of unsolicited seeds from China. Now, it's face masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral sex milestone: Lab-grown, replanted corals spawn in Florida Keys...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coral-sex-milestone-lab-grown-165735733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not long after the August full moon, Florida’s reefs are the scene of an annual show of sexual reproduction called the coral spawn, with coral colonies releasing masses of tiny white, pink and orange spheres into the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Raids CA Home Of YOUTUBE Star Jake Paul...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/08/05/fbi-raids-calabasas-home-of-youtube-star-jake-paul/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No arrests were planned, the FBI said. The search warrant has been sealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama says she is managing 'low-grade depression'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/quarantine-racial-strife-trump-michelle-obama-feeling-down-163512867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former First Lady Michelle Obama said she is suffering from &amp;quot;low-grade depression&amp;quot; from coronavirus quarantine, racial strife in the United States and the &amp;quot;hypocrisy&amp;quot; of the Trump administration. Obama made the remarks in the latest episode of &amp;quot;The Michelle Obama Podcast&amp;quot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another watchdog at US State Department abruptly gone... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/another-watchdog-us-state-department-abruptly-gone-154639696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internal watchdog looking into accusations against Secretary of State Mike Pompeo abruptly quit Wednesday, just months after his predecessor was fired. The State Department&amp;#39;s acting inspector general, Stephen Akard, is a longtime aide to Vice President Mike Pence and his installation in May</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury ramps up auctions as borrowing surges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4c09bd62585932f560c35f4995ccb42a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Treasury Department will ramp up the size of the bonds and other securities it auctions across-the-board in the face of the unprecedented borrowing needs of the the U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encourages mail voting in Florida but sues in Nevada?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/19ade6dafb5b6f82f324e4be9b12a7a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In an abrupt reversal, President Donald Trump is encouraging voters in the critical swing state of Florida to vote by mail after months of criticizing the practice — and while...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City streets drain of life in Australia's toughest lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1587622775452a3036c1141998984033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia (AP) — Melbourne’s usually vibrant downtown streets were draining of signs of life on Wednesday on the eve of Australia’s toughest-ever pandemic restrictions coming into...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fort Hood investigating death of a fourth soldier as body pulled from lake...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1258269/fort-hood-death-fourth-soldier-lake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT Hood has started an investigation into the death of a fourth soldier after the body of a 24-year-old was pulled from a lake. Francisco Gilberto Hernandezvargas, from Woodside, New York, was re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Surging Covid 'Will Go Away Like Things Go Away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-says-surging-virus-e2-80-98will-go-away-like-things-go-away-e2-80-99/ar-BB17BcbL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Bailout Cash Won't Stop Wave of Credit Card Defaults...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/more-bailout-cash-won-t-stop-wave-of-credit-card-defaults/ar-BB17zMRe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protest leader Bush ousts 20-year Rep. Clay in Missouri...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/cori-bush-democrat-missouri-primary-william-lacy-clay-a9654931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violators face $10,000 fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-to-set-up-quarantine-checkpoints-at-city-borders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City is going to set up checkpoints into the city to check out of state travelers to make sure they are following quarantine rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIDESPREAD DESTRUCTION</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200805135902-1g5wx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON-SECURITY/BLAST (UPDATE 6, GRAPHIC, TV, PIX):UPDATE 6-Beirut reels from huge blast, as death toll climbs to at least 113</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS moves forward with 'LOVE ISLAND' quarantine edition...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/tv/love-island-las-vegas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for nasal swabs, PPE and hook-ups as reality TV singles navigate Love Island amid the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY AFTER IN BEIRUT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7a104960789d9b25e89a889fbbc125e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Residents of Beirut —stunned, sleepless and stoic — emerged Wednesday from the aftermath of a catastrophic explosion searching for missing relatives, bandaging their wounds and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORT OFFICIALS UNDER HOUSE ARREST</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2020-08-05/lebanon-to-place-beirut-port-officials-under-house-arrest-sources</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bass faces rush of attacks as VP selection enters uncertain final stretch...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/politics-government/election/article244726782.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe to Black Journalist: 'Are You Junkie?'</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/biden-to-black-journalist-are-you-a-junkie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsurprisingly, many are cringing that Biden is, unprompted, asking an African-American journalist if he’s “a junkie” .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB game delayed by unauthorized drone hovering over field...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/mlb/an-mlb-game-was-delayed-by-an-unauthorized-drone-hovering-over-the-field/ar-BB17BeGG?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For unemployed, rising grocery prices stretch budgets even more...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/personalfinance/for-the-unemployed-rising-grocery-prices-stretch-budgets-even-more/ar-BB17z6H8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC sets up quarantine checkpoints as it toughens travel restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/05/new-york-city-sets-up-quarantine-checkpoints-as-it-toughens-state-travel-restrictions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDBERG: Maybe we're not as 'free' as we think...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/civil-rights/510402-afraid-to-speak-your-mind-maybe-were-not-as-free-as-we-think</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just because we still have free-speech rights doesn’t mean we feel free to say what’s on our minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy Oprah labeled 'fraud' for calling out 'white privilege'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/05/oprah-criticized-for-calling-out-white-privilege-since-shes-rich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Why is Oprah, maybe the richest black woman in the world, trying to shame white people?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In U-turn, Finland to recommend remote working after COVID-19 surge...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200805132559-qftks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FINLAND:In U-turn, Finland to recommend remote working after COVID-19 surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Barrels Past $2,000...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-barrels-past-2-000-005419682.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Gold advanced to a fresh record beyond $2,000 an ounce as investors assessed increased geopolitical risks and the prospect for further stimulus to combat fallout from the coronavirus pandemic.Bullion is up almost 35% this year, with its haven status enhanced by sliding U.S. real yields</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tlaib Holds Off Primary Challenge in Victory for Progressives...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/05/rashida-tlaib-holds-off-primary-challenge-in-a-victory-for-progressives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Rashida Tlaib, Democrat of Michigan, beat back a formidable primary challenge Tuesday from a repeat rival, widening her 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are People So Deathly Afraid of Criticizing Beyonce?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/why-are-people-so-deathly-afraid-of-criticizing-beyonce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s been a startling lack of mischievous, dissenting voices when it comes to Beyoncé’s visual album ‘Black Is King.’ Cassie da Costa finds that troubling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welder sparked?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1252803/beirut-explosion-huge-blast-lebanon-capital-hiroshima/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE massive explosion which killed at least 100 people and left 4,000 injured in Lebanon’s capital Beirut is feared to have been started by a reckless welder. Shocking images show flattened b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Chip Will Allow Users to Take Charge of Moods and Emotions...</title>
      <link>https://www.techtimes.com/articles/251574/20200804/elon-musk-neuralink-update-mood-control.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It can soon help you balance your hormone levels, here's how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hamill, Quintessential New York Journalist, Dies at 85...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-writer-pete-hamill-dead-at-85-20200805-4wowyopsrnazznqbbj5ze25ibi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary Hamill worked for three city tabloids, serving as editor for both the Daily News and the New York Post during a newspaper career that covered the last 40 years of the 20th century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCONN Becomes First Major College To Cancel Football Season...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/college-football/story/_/id/29600577/uconn-becomes-1st-fbs-team-cancel-football-season-due-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UConn announced Wednesday that it is suspending its football program for the 2020 season because of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says Surging Covid 'Will Go Away Like Things Go Away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-says-surging-virus-will-go-away-like-things-go-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Says Surging Virus â€˜Will Go Away Like Things Go Awayâ€™</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Do you really need to party?' WHO asks youth...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200805120022-t4ort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO (PIX):'Do you really need to party?' WHO asks world's youth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLLAR 'CRASH RISK'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/business/497072-us-dollar-crash-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US dollar could be a ‘CRASH RISK’ amid rising economic &amp; political uncertainty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle East Closer To Major War?</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/did-the-mushroom-cloud-explosion-in-beirut-just-push-the-middle-east-closer-to-a-major-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 just keeps getting weirder.  On Tuesday, an absolutely massive explosion caused a red mushroom cloud to rise high over the city of Beirut, Lebanon.  It is being called "Beirut's Hiroshima", and the blast was heard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300,000 homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.time24.news/2020/08/300000-homeless-people-damage-spread-to-half-of-the-city.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.time24.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIDESPREAD DESTRUCTION</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8595015/Inside-Beiruts-ground-zero-Astonishing-images-reveal-scale-devastation-Lebanese-capital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescuers worked throughout the night scouring ground zero for survivors after the cataclysmic blast in Beirut, Lebanon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Search Monopoly Complicates Mental Health Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/google-s-search-monopoly-complicates-a-mental-health-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Googleâ€™s Search Monopoly Complicates a Mental Health Crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State could elect first trans lawmaker...</title>
      <link>https://washingtonsources.org/politics/kansas-could-elect-its-first-openly-transgender-lawmaker-this-fall/24285/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonsources.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths pile up on Texas border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c5da90cb311e320d9ece7310b4fe257e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO GRANDE CITY, Texas (AP) — When labor pains signaled that Clarissa Muñoz was at last going to be a mom, she jumped in a car and headed two hours down the Texas border into one of the nation's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protest leader Bush ousts 20-year Rep. Clay in Missouri...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/36ae43993c0fe43e67bcdd9539675997</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cori Bush, a onetime homeless woman who led protests following a white police officer's fatal shooting of a Black 18-year-old in Ferguson, ousted longtime Rep. William Lacy Clay Tuesday in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says 'Mars looking real' after SPACEX launches Starship craft...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-mars-spacex-launch-starship-a9654466.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden announces largest ad buy ever by presidential candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/joe-biden-ads-2020-campaign-announces-largest-political-ad-buy-ever-by-presidential-candidate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Signaling the states they see as most competitive, the Biden campaign said their ads will 15 states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Bailout Cash Won't Stop Wave of Credit Card Defaults...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/more-bailout-cash-may-just-delay-wave-of-credit-card-defaults</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Bailout Cash Wonâ€™t Stop Wave of Credit Card Defaults</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Search Monopoly Complicates Mental Health Crisis...</title>
      <link> https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/google-s-search-monopoly-complicates-a-mental-health-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLOSIONS ROCK BEIRUT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4475998de078a93bbe91b7ac9d43ada2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Residents of Beirut awoke to a scene of utter devastation on Wednesday, a day after a massive explosion at the port sent shock waves across the Lebanese capital, killing at least 100...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY +++:  STREAMER CHARGING $30 MORE TO VIEW 'MULAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/08/04/disney-plus-plus-plus-studio-will-charge-30-bucks-extra-over-subscription-fee-to-stream-long-delayed-mulan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney– look, they’re suffering. The theme parks are losing money, no one’s going to movie theaters, Mickey and Minnie can’t even get stimulus checks. So on September 24th t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  Entrepreneur spent PPP loans on Lamborghini, Rolex, real estate and strip clubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8593503/Entrepreneur-arrested-fraudulently-obtaining-PPP-loans-1-6million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lee Price III, 29, is accused of scamming the US government's Payment Protection Program out of more than $1.6 million. He allegedly spent relief loans that were for small businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chasm grows between Trump and govt experts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ee505d5a774598babc6b4b925d7bfa6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the early days of the coronavirus crisis, President Donald Trump was flanked in the White House briefing room by a team of public health experts in a seeming portrait of unity...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KOBACH DOWN IN KANSAS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6646c990bce8bd3d93e2722015de87f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPEKA, Kan. (AP) — Kansas Republicans on Tuesday nominated Rep. Roger Marshall for the Senate instead of polarizing conservative Kris Kobach, heeding the party establishment’s advice for keeping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa teen pleads not guilty as documents reveal how feds cracked his TWITTER hack case...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/crime/2020/08/04/tampa-teen-accused-of-profiting-from-twitter-hacks-pleads-not-guilty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graham Ivan Clark, 17, remains in jail on $725,000 bail. His attorneys will argue Wednesday for a lower amount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President changes tone, backs mail-in voting in Florida!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-backs-off-mail-voting-attacks-in-florida-as-democrats-build-huge-advantage/ar-BB17zbvr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksn.com/news/your-local-election-hq/2020-primary-election-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mobile app users please click here for results U.S. Races | Kansas State Races | Kansas County Races U.S. Races U.S. Races | Kansas State Races | Kansas County Races Kansas State Races U.S. Races |…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yale student's lawsuit claims online courses were inferior...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/coronavirus/hc-news-coronavirus-student-sues-yale-20200804-eyr4lbjs2nhz7lapjgvrtnyyea-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Yale University student from Ohio has sued the Ivy League School claiming breach of contract and unjust enrichment after all courses went online. Jonathan Michel claims the online college experience was inferior to in-person and wants a refund of tuition for the time classes were online. His lawyers are seeking class action status to represent other students affected by Yale's decision to go online because of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base starting to erode in California...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trumps-starting-erode-poll-shows-120003990.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Central Valley and other conservative parts of California, small but significant numbers of Republican voters have turned against Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  Was bomb of some kind... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-us-generals-tell-him-beirut-blast-231802329.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Tuesday that US generals had told him that the powerful explosions which rocked Beirut appeared to have been caused by a &amp;quot;bomb of some kind.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;It looks like a terrible attack,&amp;quot; Trump told reporters at the White House. Prime Minister Hassan Diab said 2,750</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  LA Deputies accused of being in secret societies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deputies-accused-being-secret-societies-230851807.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County has paid out roughly $55 million in settlements since 1990 in civil cases involving allegations that sheriff&amp;#39;s deputies belonged to a secret society, records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countries tighten measures as global virus death toll nears 700,000...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australian-city-begins-curfew-global-virus-cases-top-073131503.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France and the Netherlands are gearing up for stricter mask-wearing rules to fight the coronavirus as the global death toll from the pandemic neared 700,000. In the Netherlands, the same mask-wearing measure will be applied in Rotterdam and the famous red-light district of Amsterdam from Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic scenes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/apocalyptic-scenes-blasts-ravage-beirut-233353329.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An entire port engulfed in fire, ships ablaze at sea and crumbling buildings: the site of the massive blast in Beirut&amp;#39;s harbour area resembled a post-nuclear landscape. A woman in her twenties stood screaming at security forces, asking about the fate of her brother, a port employee. &amp;quot;His name</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like an animal': NASA astronauts describe noisy, jolting descent on Dragon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/animal-nasa-astronauts-describe-noisy-jolting-descent-232523066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX&amp;#39;s crewed capsule isn&amp;#39;t called Dragon for nothing. The two NASA astronauts brought back to Earth on Sunday said they felt they were inside the belly of a beast as it careened into the atmosphere at 17,500 mph. &amp;quot;It came alive,&amp;quot; said mission commander Bob Behnkhen at a virtual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIDESPREAD DESTRUCTION</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200804221345-3reit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON-SECURITY/BLAST (UPDATE 9, GRAPHIC, TV, PIX):UPDATE 9-Massive blast rips through Beirut, killing 78 and injuring thousands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Aid Kanye West Bid to Get on 2020 Ballot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/04/republicans-aid-kanye-wests-bid-to-get-on-the-2020-ballot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Danny Hakim and Maggie Haberman At least three people who have been active in Republican politics are linked to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS REPORTER GOES WHERE NO ONE HAS GONE BEFORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/04/media/axios-trump-jonathan-swan-interview/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was enraging to watch Axios reporter Jonathan Swan's interview with President Trump — and not only because the President displayed naiveté when repeatedly confronted with the facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans consider South Lawn of White House for Trump's convention speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Republicans-consider-South-Lawn-of-the-White-15459083.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Republican National Convention planners are considering the White House South Lawn as the site of President Donald Trump's nationally televised nomination acceptance speech later this month, according to a Republican familiar with the discussions.  The decision to stage the most high-profile political event of Trump's reelection campaign at the national seat of presidential power would be just the latest break by Trump in presidential norms, which have historically drawn clear lines between official business of the president and campaign events.  People involved in the planning said that no final decision had been made on the location of the Republican convention's celebratory events. Trump abandoned plans to hold the full convention in Charlotte, and later Jacksonville, Fla., over concerns that large crowds could spread the novel coronavirus.  The South Lawn, which can be subject to intense heat and afternoon thunderstorms in late August, is one of several sites under consideration for the week of festivities, including the Trump International Hotel in the District of Columbia, which the president leases from the federal government, officials said. Any costs incurred by the government to host the events would be repaid, said the Republican, who, like others, spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal deliberations.  Several hundred Republican delegates plan to gather for a pared-down session of official meetings on Aug. 24 in Charlotte, N.C., to nominate Trump. That will be followed by three more days of speeches and programming from undetermined sites, culminating in Trump's acceptance speech on Aug. 27.  In a press briefing last month, Trump dodged a question about holding the acceptance speech in the White House.  "We haven't set that yet," Trump said. "We'll probably announce that over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 MILLION WITHOUT POWER AFTER TROPICAL STORM RIPS EAST COAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/northeast-takes-a-pummeling-as-isaias-storms-up-i-95-corridor/789039</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
