<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS POLL: 49%  WANT TRUMP REMOVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/nbc-wsj-poll-49-percent-now-back-trump-s-impeachment-n1075296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the president's support among Republicans remains strong one year out from Election Day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DON JR:  'BULLSHIT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-booed-at-second-sporting-event-in-less-than-a-week-this-time-at-ufc-championship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump went to New York City tonight to watch a mixed martial arts championship, and was greeted by boos according to videos and reporters at the event. Trump was also apparently not s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple earthquakes rattle Kansas, Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/state/kansas/article236963833.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL: 49% WANT TRUMP REMOVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-poll-49-percent-favor-impeaching-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of voters want President Trump impeached and removed from office, according to a new Fox News Poll. In addition, 6-in-10 believe the president did ask foreign leaders to investigate political opponents -- and two-thirds say that action is inappropriate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE FLOCK PRAISES CHRIST</title>
      <link>https://www.disrn.com/2019/11/03/over-1000-commit-lives-to-christ-at-kanye-wests-sunday-service/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL: Biden in dead heat  -- with Hillary?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/shock-poll-hillary-only-1-point-behind-biden-in-hypothetical-match-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Hillary Clinton entered the presidential race today, she would essentially be vying to be the frontrunner. Despite some 20 candidates competing for the nomination, a weak media-appointed leading candidate is providing an opportunity for the 2016 loser to rethink getting into the race. A new poll from Harvard Harris finds Clinton nipping at the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Schiff Takes His Case to a Bigger Ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/adam-schiff-a-trump-punching-bag-takes-his-case-to-a-bigger-ring/ar-AAJLmZe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tops Trump by 12 points in head-to-head matchup...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-poll-biden-leads-nomination-race-tops-trump-by-12-points-in-matchup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic primary voters increasingly feel the need to nominate a candidate who can beat President Trump in 2020, and more think Joe Biden can do that than any of the other top Democratic hopefuls.  In addition, while most Democratic primary voters are satisfied with their field, over a quarter wish they had other options, according to a new Fox News Poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 person, 1 vote? Maybe not. NYC mulls ranked choice voting...</title>
      <link>https://federalnewsnetwork.com/government-news/2019/11/1-person-1-vote-maybe-not-nyc-mulls-ranked-choice-voting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;federalnewsnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A measure on New York City’s ballot this week will give voters in some future elections the chance to rank their choices 1 through 5 rather than picking just one candidate…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death knell or $1M idea? Campaign tries to turn gaffes into gold...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/03/trump-campaign-2020-branding-064443</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Defends:  'You can cut through any wall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/02/trump-smugglers-sawing-border-wall-064446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Health Now an Issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-warren-sanders-stay-on-top-health-is-now-an-issue-for-sanders-poll/ar-AAJL5OX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test could detect breast cancer 5 years early...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/blood-test-could-detect-breast-cancer-five-years-before-clinical-signs-11852901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The test, which identifies the body's immune response to proteins produced by cancer cells, could be available in four years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Year Out: Divided nation lurches toward 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8149c3ca0e7461bb3cc3bd303063eff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — One year from Sunday, voters will decide whether to grant President Donald Trump a second term in office, an election that will be a referendum on Trump's vision for America's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interest growing. So is anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eada3111efdf4880b492cac1ef376abe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A year out from the 2020 general election, there already is significant interest in the presidential campaign. But a poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigate Milwaukee acid attack as hate crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/local/2019/11/02/milwaukee-battery-acid-attack-man-burned-police-looking-suspect/4140669002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milwaukee police are searching for a suspect they believe threw acid on the man after an altercation Friday night near S. 13th St. and W. Cleveland Ave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans fury at birth coach who said only women can have babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7643251/Charity-hounds-birth-coach-post-saying-women-children.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doula UK found that Lynsey McCarthy-Calvert's Facebook post, said that only women have kids, breached their equality and diversity guidelines after trans rights activists prompted an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concussion rate for teen female soccer players rivals football...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional/concussion-rate-for-teen-female-soccer-players-rivals-football-study/iTmHIe0vmbSonev1LLNsNO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concussion rates in U.S. high school soccer are much higher for females than males, according to a UNC study published in Pediatrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian capital Delhi gasps under choking smog...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/indian-capital-delhi-gasps-under-choking-smog-073555612--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India&amp;#39;s capital New Delhi was enveloped in heavy, toxic smog Sunday -- the worst levels in recent years -- with flights diverted or delayed as politicians blamed each other for failing to tackle the crisis. Every winter, the megacity of 20 million people is blanketed by a poisonous smog of car fumes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal drones ground water-dropping helicopters in CA fire battle...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/11/02/illegal-drones-interrupt-water-dropping-helicopters-during-critical-moment-in-maria-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As flames rapidly spread along a hillside in Santa Paula early Friday morning, firefighters were faced with a perilous dilemma: ground night-flying helicopters working to contain the growing fire or risk an aerial collision with a thrill-seeking drone. A Ventura County Fire Department helicopter pilot radioed in at 3:19 a.m. that a drone had been spotted flying above the flames, apparently trying to take a photograph or video of the scene below. Air operations were immediately stopped for at least 45 minutes until the sky was clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot police storm Hong Kong malls to nip more protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/74137204c9d04da7b72bac4f53665a4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Riot police stormed several malls in Hong Kong on Sunday in a move to thwart more pro-democracy protests, as the city's leader heads to Beijing for talks on deepening economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronan Farrow calls for 'revisiting' Bill Clinton allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/3/ronan-farrow-bill-clinton-credibly-accused-rape-ju/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Author and journalist Ronan Farrow said that former President Bill Clinton was “credibly accused of rape” by Juanita Broaddrick, an allegation “overdue for revisiting.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheap, powerful 'meth 2.0' ravages communities...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/11/02/meth-use-surges-stronger-cheaper-drugs-imported-mexico/4124765002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Meth 2.0” is stronger, cheaper and more plentiful than the old home-cooked variety. But most federal funding is focused on fighting opioid addiction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Charles Caught Up in $136 Million Fake Art Hoax...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7643225/Prince-Charles-hit-major-counterfeit-art-scandal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Tetro, who was once sentenced to six months in prison for art forgery, says he painted the 17 pictures on display at Dunfries House which were loaned by bankrupt businessman James Stunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, SKorea to Suspend Joint Air Drill Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-south-korea-to-suspend-joint-air-drill-again-yonhap-says/ar-AAJL9NJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILLIE BROWN:  Impeachment a winner for Dems? Don't bet on it...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/williesworld/article/Impeachment-a-winner-for-Democrats-Don-t-bet-14803559.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anything, the House’s impeachment inquiry vote solidified President Trump’s hold on power. There were zero GOP defections, meaning we have zero drama heading into the public phase of impeachment. Everyone is pretty much still in the same lanes they’ve been in since the Russian collusion investigation, the obstruction of justice investigation and every other investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Downtown Hong Kong becomes battleground as night falls...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7641999/Hong-Kong-police-fire-tears-gas-thousands-masked-anti-government-protesters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protests happened in Victoria Park, a traditional venue for demonstrations and vigils. Police action was a fast response to a rally billed as an 'emergency call' for autonomy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There's Nothing People Can't Breach'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/border-wall-smugglers-are-sawing-through-the-border-wall-but-officials-say-its-not-an-issue-2019-11-02/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customs and Border Protection told CBS News "it's happening but not to the point where it's an issue"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP GETS BOOS AT MSG FIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/468703-trump-gets-heavy-rain-of-boos-upon-entering-msg-prior-to-ufc-244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump was welcomed into Madison Square Garden Saturday night with heavy booing from the crowd.The president is at the arena to watch the main fight of UFC 244.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lonely battle of the last Republican lawmaker from Northern Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/The-lonely-battle-of-the-last-Republican-lawmaker-14802784.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Hugo, the last Republican legislator in the Virginia suburbs closest to Washington, calls himself "Delegate Pothole." He tweets about neighborhood detours, car break-ins and lane closings. "Be sure to find an alternative route!" he wrote ahead of repair work at one intersection.  Ask him what impact President Donald Trump's unpopularity in Virginia is having on next week's pivotal state election, and Hugo says, "I focus on the local issues." Ask whether Democrats are succeeding in nationalizing the last election before the 2020 presidential contest, and Hugo says, "I focus on the local issues."  Six questions, six times Hugo repeats the mantra, all the while hurrying out of a candidates forum to avoid a clot of reporters. On the way to the parking lot, a man from Centreville approaches and thanks Hugo for helping to get his local bike trail paved. The delegate stops, appreciates the voter, and announces to any and all, "See, it's all about local politics."  But on the suburban streets of House District 40 that wind through Fairfax and Prince William counties - one of the last pockets of Northern Virginia to transition from largely white, affluent and conservative to a Democratic-leaning mix of immigrants and tech and government workers - Hugo's recipe for winning a ninth term in Richmond may be short on some ingredients.  The man making Republicans' last stand in once-dependably red suburbia is nobody's idea of a General Custer or even a Susan Collins, the last Republican member of Congress from all of New England. In an affluent district of big homes on generous lots, Hugo, an Army veteran who works as a lobbyist for the defense and technology sectors, is trying to persuade voters that he is neither a hard-right partisan warrior nor a relic of the vanishing species once known as liberal Republican.  Rather, in an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sprint to Feb. 3 caucuses... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-the-Democratic-presidential-field-shrinks-14804984.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa - The Democratic presidential field narrowed and the intensity of its survivors heightened this weekend, with one once-major candidate dropping out and a dozen others frantically trying to avoid that fate in a state that has taken on a striking importance in the 2020 race.  As they have nationally, four candidates have emerged in Iowa from the sprawling pool - the largest and most diverse in history - as the leaders in statewide polling: former vice president Joe Biden, Sens. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., and Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., and South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg.  Their challengers received a blunt reminder Friday of the stakes three months before the state's caucuses, when the first votes of the 2020 nomination will be cast, as former Rep. Beto O'Rourke of Texas abruptly left the race. That came days after another trailing contestant, Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., was forced to publicly acknowledge layoffs and consolidations because of her dwindling campaign fundraising.  A series of events in Iowa this weekend marked the beginning of the unofficial sprint to the Feb. 3 caucuses and summoned questions about which candidates would survive until then. All were operating on the hope that Iowa would provide them the sort of political magic that propelled Barack Obama to an upset victory in the 2008 caucuses.  For the trailing candidates, a fundraising dinner for the state party in Des Moines on Friday night was an opportunity to try to break into the top tier - or even just get a little buzz on social media. The evening often felt more like a high school field day competition, but with a blown-up budget, than a sober part of the nomination process.  By the end of the marathon speechmaking, however, it was not clear whether any of the candidates significantly benefited from the exercise or if...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Whimpering' Terrorist Only Trump Seems to Have Heard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-whimpering-terrorist-only-trump-seems-to-have-heard/ar-AAJIrLi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  65% believe country headed in wrong direction...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/daily-presidential-tracking-poll/ar-AADKLI1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West, with debt piling up, thanks God for $68 million tax refund...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/kanye-west-with-his-debt-piling-up-thanks-god-for-his-68-million-tax-return-2019-10-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West has been making headlines lately for his Sunday Service, an invitation-only event that started earlier this year in which the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But he struggles for black support...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-10-31/pete-buttigieg-struggles-to-convince-black-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buttigieg is struggling to connect with African American voters, who for the most part remain loyal to Joe Biden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga to Star in Gucci Grandson Murder Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/lady-gaga-ridley-scott-team-up-movie-gucci-grandson-murder-1251708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her Oscar win for 'A Star is Born,' the pop star has lined up her next movie project, playing the wife of a murdered Gucci heir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities, tribes try a new environmental approach: Give nature rights...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-11-cities-tribes-environmental-approach-nature.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When members of the White Earth band of Ojibwe in Minnesota take out their canoes to harvest wild rice, they're gathering a source of nourishment and following a tradition that has connected them to the land for generations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER NOTES:  Trump pushed for stolen emails...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/02/politics/mueller-investigation-notes-trump-stolen-emails/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump and other top 2016 Trump campaign officials repeatedly privately discussed how the campaign could get access to stolen Democratic emails WikiLeaks had in 2016, according to newly released interview notes from Robert Mueller's special counsel investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB bans 'party houses' after shooting kills 5...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47f1797489eb4ab3928cd56aacfbfcec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORINDA, Calif. (AP) — Airbnb's CEO said the company was taking actions against unauthorized parties in the wake of a deadly shooting at a Halloween party held at an Airbnb rental home in...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
