<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mass evacuation as Japan braces for typhoon...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-54046150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200,000 people are ordered to shelter from the second storm to hit the region in a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISHES DIRT ON DONALD... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8702221/Trump-said-Obama-got-Harvard-Law-f-ing-affirmative-action-Cohen-says-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen's memoir, Disloyal, hits bookshelves Tuesday - despite his still serving out a federal prison sentence for tax evasion, lying to Congress and campaign finance violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considered suicide as way to 'escape the unrelenting insanity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/05/politics/michael-cohen-book-trump-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Donald Trump ever sought the Oval Office, he was preoccupied by its occupant President Barack Obama, publicly questioning his birthplace and privately describing him as "a Manchurian candidate" who obtained his Ivy League degrees only by way of affirmative action, according to a new book by Trump's former attorney, Michael Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California grid operator warns of rotating power outages in record heat wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200906022155-95z56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WEATHER/POWER:California grid operator warns of rotating power outages in record heat wave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France now Europe's hotspot with highest ever daily cases figure...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1426073/france-europe-covid-hotspot-icu-two-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE has become Europe’s new coronavirus hotspot as it recorded its highest ever number of daily cases The country’s count hit a new high with nearly 9,000 yesterday – almost do…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS MAGA:  Multiple boats sink during Trump Boat Parade on Lake Travis...</title>
      <link>https://cbsaustin.com/news/local/multiple-boats-in-distress-sinking-at-trump-boat-parade-on-lake-travis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbsaustin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parade for President Donald Trump gets dicey when multiple boats sink on Lake Travis. According to first responders, nobody was injured. At around 2:50 p. m. the TCSO confirmed via tweet that they had responded to multiple calls made about boats being in distress at the parade. They also confirmed that several of those boats sank on the lake. As of Saturday night, the Travis County Sheriff&amp;lsquo;s office said they were still sorting out just how many boats went under.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spends hours in box filled with ice cubes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6839bc681e86b773f26ba1c17fb43d58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELK, Austria (AP) — An Austrian man beat his own record for the longest full body contact with ice cubes on Saturday. Josef Koeberl managed to stay 2 hours, 30 minutes and 57 seconds inside...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan raises rhetoric in Greece standoff in Mediterranean...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/61226ebfea4cb7ddcf9c23b5fbd94b84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Saturday warned Greece to enter talks over disputed eastern Mediterranean territorial claims or face the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen memoir casts him as star witness against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2b171cabf1801526a76d4534e808a99d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Michael Cohen's tell-all memoir makes the case that President Donald Trump is “guilty of the same crimes” that landed his former fixer in federal prison, offering a blow-by-blow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK blocks end-of-life broadcasts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/16880246e8bbdc5ceb98ed57b87a88ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LE PECQ, France (AP) — Facebook on Saturday blocked live broadcasts from a chronically ill bed-ridden man who appealed to French President Emmanuel Macron for a medically-assisted death and who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran blasts 'heartless and evil' US for killing thousands with coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/iran-brands-heartless-evil-thousands-22634200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani has hit out at the USA over sanctions that have been in place since 2018. The political leader has argument the global health crisis should have seen sanctions reduced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for placing 1171 calls to 911...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/egg-roll-call-915027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 4--A Tennessee man called 911 more than 1100 times over the past six weeks, a prolific misuse of the emergency dispatch system that included the suspect asking a police operator “if they wa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple boats in distress, sinking at Trump Boat Parade on Lake Travis... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://cbsaustin.com/news/local/multiple-boats-in-distress-sinking-at-trump-boat-parade-on-lake-travis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbsaustin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple 911 calls have been made regarding boats being in distress, some sinking at the &amp;lsquo;Trump Boat Parade&amp;rsquo; scheduled for Saturday afternoon on Lake Travis, according to the Travis County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office. TCSO confirmed with CBS Austin that multiple boats have been sinking and are in distress. The sheriff's office says calls have been made about boats along the entire route of the parade, some of the locations include: Paradise Cove, Emerald Point and West Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Reporters Defend Colleague After Trump Calls for Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2020/09/05/fox-news-journalists-defend-colleague-targeted-by-president-trump/#263dcfdf2a84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My sources are not anonymous to me and I doubt they are anonymous to the president.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNAL CONFUSION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/05/media/the-atlantic-trump-military-fox-news/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Fox News has worked to undermine and discredit the work of other news organizations that have reported damning details about President Trump and his administration. But on Friday, something unusual happened: The network turned a skeptical eye toward reporting from its own correspondent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirby, LaBeouf Grieve Over Loss of Newborn in 'PIECES OF A WOMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/pieces-of-a-woman-film-review-venice-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: He has yet to find magic potion to get ahead in race...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-has-yet-to-find-magic-potion-to-get-ahead-15545477.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential election is now eight weeks away, and the structure of the contest is little changed from where it has been for some time. President Donald Trump is struggling and at times floundering. The question is whether he has the skills to turn around his candidacy in hopes of replicating his 2016 surprise victory.  At the traditional Labor Day kickoff to the fall campaign, the race remains former vice president Joe Biden's to lose - which of course could still happen. Trump has tried many things over the past months in an effort to avoid becoming a one-term president. So far, nothing has proved to be the magic potion the president seems to believe is out there.  Trump has claimed Biden is mentally challenged. He has gone after Biden's son Hunter as corrupt. The president has accused Biden of being a radical leftist, a socialist. He says the former vice president is weak. He says his challenger is soft on China. He has said Biden supports violent protesters and doesn't support the police. Oh, he's also said Biden's 1994 crime bill was too tough on crime (and by implication, therefore, on the side of the police).  He is now preaching law and order, seizing on months of nightly protests in Portland, Ore., which often have turned violent, along with the protests and violence that followed the police shooting of Jacob Blake in Kenosha, Wis. He claims the nation's cities are ablaze and that a Biden presidency would destroy the suburbs. The rhetoric aimed at suburban voters is grounded in racism.  It is premature to say the law and order message isn't working, though there's been minimal movement in the polls since the conventions ended. What is left in the Trump tool kit if this message fails to do what Trump hopes it will do?  Trump's mistakes, record and history plague his candidacy. He paints his record in glorious...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer culture skewered in film at Venice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d7ab5511afd1787133056db3ff6a36b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE (AP) — Coronavirus lockdowns have kept most U.S. filmmakers and actors away from the Venice Film Festival, but Gia Coppola and Maya Hawke have brought a bit of today’s America to the Lido...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unions threaten work stoppages amid calls for racial justice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/02da00cb921ec61a69d8a30c9ff56244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ahead of Labor Day, unions representing millions across several working-class sectors are threatening to authorize work stoppages in support of the Black Lives Matter movement amid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Reporters Defend Colleague After Trump Calls for Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/fox-news-reporters-leap-to-defend-jennifer-griffin-from-trumps-demand-she-be-fired-for-reporting-he-trashed-vets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News reporters leapt to the defense of their colleague Jennifer Griffin after President Donald Trump demanded her firing after she confirmed the key elements of a raft of stories in which Trump denigrated military veterans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DERBY DAY SHOWDOWN: Militia gather at Churchill Downs ahead of protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8701095/Armed-Trump-supporters-gather-near-Churchill-Downs-ahead-Kentucky-Derby-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavily armed pro-Trump activists and far-right militia members have gathered near Churchill Downs in Louisville vowing to protect the city ahead of a day of Black Lives Matter protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting in person Nov. 3? Expect drive-thrus, sports arenas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8f347fec097280234fdef8589def9a44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Voting will look a little different this November. States are turning to stadiums, drive-thrus and possibly even movie theaters as safe options for in-person polling places...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Already Itching to Sue Frats Over Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/college-students-are-already-itching-to-sue-frats-over-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fraternities and sororities are undoubtedly engaging in risky behavior during the pandemic. But can they be sued for it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Braces For EMP Attack?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/dhs-braces-potential-emp-attack-presidential-election-nears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Orthodox Jews clash with secular Israeli officials over measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Ultra-Orthodox-Jews-clash-with-secular-Israeli-15545201.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - Israel's rapidly escalating coronavirus crisis is aggravating a religious divide in the Jewish state, with ultra-Orthodox leaders accusing mostly secular health officials of discrimination and fostering anti-Semitism by focusing on outbreaks in highly observant communities.  As the government struggles to contain the outbreak, ultra-Orthodox Jewish rabbis, cabinet ministers and parliament members have resisted attempts to curtail activities in ultra-Orthodox areas, including many that have emerged as covid-19 hot spots.  Facing particular ire has been Ronni Gamzu, the pugnacious former hospital administrator appointed last month as the government's "corona czar." Gamzu has clashed with religious leaders over his efforts to impose targeted lockdowns on neighborhoods with high infection rates, block a yearly pilgrimage to the grave of a revered Hasidic rabbi in Ukraine and compel virus testing for thousands of foreign students who have recently arrived to attend religious schools, or yeshivas.  Gamzu said last week that 80% of the most recent coronavirus cases occurred in ultra-Orthodox neighborhoods. The government expects to enact targeted restrictions Monday in 10 hot spot communities, many of them ultra-Orthodox.  The tensions have riven Israel's coronavirus cabinet, the government body that sets policy. On Friday, one day after Israel recorded 3,141 new cases - the largest single day per capita increase in any country since the pandemic began - cabinet discussions grew heated over proposed lockdowns during the Jewish holidays of Rosh Hashanah and Yom Kippur later this month.  "You want a lockdown during the High Holidays because you don't want people praying," Housing Minister Yaakov Litzman said to Gamzu, according to Israeli media reports. "We will not let this happen."  Gamzu says that his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overfed and underexercised, dogs putting on pandemic pounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Overfed-and-underexercised-some-dogs-are-putting-15545194.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When shutdowns to stem the spread of the novel coronavirus began last spring, Massachusetts retiree Lisa Allen took her state's stay-at-home guidance seriously. She holed up in her high-rise Boston condo with her 6-year-old Pomeranian, Desi.  She reduced walks from three to two a day - the better to avoid the elevator and lobby. She bought pee pads for Desi and gave him a treat when he used them.  By late June, Desi was having trouble breathing. A routine visit to the veterinarian revealed that the tiny dog had gained a pound.  "If I only gained a pound, I'd be very happy," Allen said. "But when you're 5 pounds, that's 20% of your weight. It was putting strain on him."  The problem, the vet said, was one familiar to millions of Americans and a growing number of their pet dogs: a routine upended by covid-19. In many cases, housebound humans are giving their dogs more attention and walks, boosting fitness for pets and people alike. But in others, veterinarians and professional dog walkers say, the changes have led to overfed and either underexercised or overwalked dogs - and to new joint problems and obesity.  Banfield Pet Hospital, which has more than 1,000 locations across the United States, surveyed pet owners at the end of May about how they were faring during the pandemic. Many reported pudgier pets.  "It's too soon to tell if the covid crisis has resulted in weight gain for the average pet," said Andrea Sanchez, a Banfield veterinarian and senior manager of operations support. But of 1,000 respondents, she said, "33% said they thought their pet had gained weight - and it was especially dog owners."  Tomika Bruen, who owns a dog-walking company in the Los Angeles area, said that when her clients began calling her back recently to take their dogs out, she detected not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside El Salvador's hell hole jails; Packed into overcrowded cells...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8700681/Gangsters-Guatemala-make-crew-signs-handcuffs-shaken-prison-guards.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities visited three Salvadorean prisons, some of them maximum security, to check on the inmates and to carry out searches amid the COVID-19 novel coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOKHARI: Everything You Post Online Will Be Scanned by 'Hate Speech Algorithms'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2020/09/05/bokhari-everything-you-post-online-will-be-scanned-by-hate-speech-algorithms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breitbart News technology reporter Allum Bokhari appeared on the Liz Callaway show on TALK 94.5 FM WTKN last week, to discuss revelations in his upcoming book, #DELETED: Big Tech's Battle to Erase The Trump Movement and Steal The Election, which features interviews with insiders from Google, Facebook, and other companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Notion That US Debt Can Ever Be Paid Back is Ridiculous', Analyst Says...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/analysis/202009051080375191-the-notion-that-us-debt-can-ever-be-paid-back-is-ridiculous-analyst-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In June, US Department of the Treasury data revealed that America's national debt had exceeded $26 trillion for the first time in the nation's history, as the country...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rochester rocked by another night of protests, counter-protests...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/05/rochester-rocked-by-another-night-of-daniel-prude-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violence erupted on the third night of protests in Rochester against the death of Daniel Prude, with anti-police demonstrators terrorizing diners inside a restaurant and setting off what looked lik…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rush to rent 'winter houses' ahead of second wave...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/04/new-yorkers-scramble-to-rent-posh-winter-houses-ahead-of-second-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months before a possible second wave of the coronavirus, deep-pocketed locals are already looking for an escape route.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese pianist Lang Lang says Bach the remedy for troubled times...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chinese-pianist-lang-lang-says-023017080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In times of crisis star Chinese pianist Lang Lang believes music is the best medicine, especially Bach, who he says penned the perfect soundtrack for these pandemic-troubled times more than 250 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENGINEERS TEST JETLINER WHERE YOU RIDE IN WINGS...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/test-jetliner-ride-wings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the first flight test for a model Flying-V, which has its seats and cargo inside its wings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Number of Catholic Schools Shutting Down Forever...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/05/a-growing-number-of-catholic-schools-are-shutting-down-forever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In more than four decades of coaching girls’ basketball at Lebanon Catholic High School in southeastern Pennsylvania, Patti Hower had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's loneliest elephant' okayed to quit zoo for new life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f09d3de7b5aad108678ec2e5f0d6bc55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISLAMABAD (AP) — An elephant who has become a cause celebre for animal rights activists around the world will be allowed to leave his Pakistani zoo and transferred to better conditions, the animal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Hold Secret Edge If Too Close to Call...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-hold-secret-edge-if-election-is-too-close-to-call/ar-BB18JOdH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
