<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>OLIGARCHS ON THE RUN:  Abramovich's plane lands in Moscow, hours after he was spotted at Israel's airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/abramovichs-plane-lands-in-moscow-hours-after-he-was-spotted-at-israeli-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oligarch apparently touched down in Turkey before heading to Russia, after a day in Israel; UK welcomes Israel's announcement it won't allow oligarchs to bypass sanctions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Proud Boys leader  to remain behind bars as he faces Jan. 6 charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/miami-judge-orders-proud-boys-leader-tarrio-to-remain-behind-bars-as-he-faces-jan-6-charges/ar-AAV680j?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Rachel Wood Says Marilyn Manson Used a Nazi Whip to Torture Her and Made Her Drink His Blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/evan-rachel-wood-says-marilyn-manson-used-a-nazi-whip-to-torture-her-and-made-her-drink-his-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evan Rachel Wood has shared more horrifying allegations about her relationship with Marilyn Manson in the second part of HBO documentary Phoenix Rising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St Gets Reprieve From Fed Crackdown as Raskin Bows Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/wall-street-gets-reprieve-from-fed-crackdown-as-raskin-bows-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street Gets Reprieve From Fed Crackdown as Raskin Bows Out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU LEADERS COME TO KYIV</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-forces-press-kyiv-talks-162918340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of eastern European leaders met Ukraine's president in his besieged capital Tuesday, in a defiant act of solidarity as Russian forces pressed in and air strikes claimed yet more lives in the city under curfew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark mulls cigarette sale ban for next generations...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2022-03-denmark-mulls-cigarette-sale.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark unveiled plans on Tuesday to ensure that future generations are tobacco-free, and is considering banning the sale of cigarettes and other nicotine products to anyone born after 2010.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First trial of a sitting member of Congress in 21 years begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/mar/15/jeff-fortenberry-trial-begins-wednesday-first-of-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little-known Republican congressman from Nebraska will begin a high-profile trial Wednesday in California over accusations by federal prosecutors that he lied about illegal campaign contributions from a Nigerian billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Very meticulous in his planning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-gunman-caught-targeted-homeless-men-nyc-washington-dc-20220315-bviym7pczna4jd252sxe3x4up4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Early this AM, law enforcement arrested the suspect in Washington, DC,” the Metropolitan Police Department said in a tweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe getting hit by ANOTHER resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/europe-is-getting-hit-by-covid-resurgence-after-rushed-exit/ar-AAV4alQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Turned it down three or four times, I wanted no part of it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/nicolas-cage-interview-unbearable-weight-of-massive-talent-1235104433/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar winner candidly discusses his struggle to play himself in his new comedy 'The Unbearable Weight of Massive Talent,' his "mutual departure" with Hollywood, why he's become a meme favorite, and whether he'd be down for 'Face/Off 2.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Tax Files: Nine Months and Still No Answers from the IRS...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/stolen-tax-files-nine-months-and-still-no-answers-from-the-irs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine months ago it was revealed that the private tax files of “thousands” of Americans – covering a period of 15 years — had been stolen and given to a progressive news organization. The IRS and the Biden administration immediately vowed to investigate and prosecute. Yet here we are nine months later with no answers […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Spiraling Toward $150 Billion Default Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russia-spiraling-toward-150-billion-040120029.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia’s economy is fraying, its currency has collapsed, and its debt is junk. Next up is a potential default that could cost investors billions and shut the country out of most funding markets.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: China Seeks to Avoid Russia Sanctions SideswipeElon Musk Challenges Vladimir Putin to ‘Single Combat’ for UkrainePutin’s State Media News Is Interrupted: ‘They’re Lying to You’Panic Selling Grips Chinese Stocks in Biggest Plunge Since 2008U.S. Sewer D</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 FOX NEWS JOURNALISTS KILLED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-afghanistan-kyiv-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-d9eaf6c6ae19140c061e7d4b54f74bfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A veteran videographer and a 24-year-old Ukrainian journalist working for Fox News were both killed when their vehicle came under fire outside of Kyiv, the network said on Tuesday. Pierre Zakrzewski, 55, and Oleksandra “Sasha” Kuvshynova were traveling Monday with Fox News reporter Benjamin Hall, who remains hospitalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZELENSKY CENTER STAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-business-nato-congress-348b29a5b19e87cb277a8b353b93f7ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy will address the U.S. Congress on Wednesday, the actor-turned-turned-wartime leader's latest video stop as he employs the West's great legislative bodies as a global stage to orchestrate support against Russia’s crushing invasion .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER seeking OK for 4th dose...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pfizer-seeks-approval-for-fourth-covid19-booster-0f4477f4dcc5d10f36974b66eac86d6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Drugmaker Pfizer is expected to request authorization this week for an additional COVID-19 booster dose for seniors, according to a person familiar with the matter. It would add a fourth dose to the regimen — currently a primary series of two shots, followed months later by a booster dose — in an effort to provide maximum protection to the over-65 population that has been hit hardest by the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY LGBT employees plan walkout over Florida bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/disney-lgbtq-employees-plan-walkout-over-florida-bill/ar-AAV6jDc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz In Talks to Return To TV...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/dr-oz-in-talks-return-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The television doctor is running for Senate in Pennsylvania — but his numbers aren't promising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Forces Have Plans for Insurgency...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dg43z/ukraine-russia-insurgency-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Ukraine has a long history of national resistance against occupation,” a special forces soldier told VICE World News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students steer school bus to safety after driver collapses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-maine-education-b64058734fcee75156ab772397a9ea77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPSHAM, Maine (AP) — A group of Maine middle and high school students grabbed the wheel of their school bus Monday morning when their driver suffered a fatal medical condition, steering the vehicle to safety while another classmate attempted to administer first aid to the stricken driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BUZZFEED Accused of Illegally Shortchanging Employees in IPO...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/buzzfeed-accused-illegally-shortchanging-employees-192910655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The complainants are seeking compensation of at least $4.6 million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders visit capital to show support...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/leaders-eu-states-head-kyiv-attacks-intensify-83451392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime ministers of Poland, Czech Republic and Slovenia have arrived by train to Kyiv in a show of support for Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India explores opening alternate payment channels...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/politics/policy/russia-india-explore-opening-alternative-payment-channels-amid-sanctions-11647371750761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both sides are discussing accepting RuPay and MIR Cards within national payment infrastructures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate approves making Daylight Saving Time permanent...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/598314-senate-unanimously-approves-making-daylight-saving-time-permanent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate on Tuesday approved a proposal to make daylight saving time permanent, which if passed in the House and signed by President Biden, would mean Americans would never again have to set their clocks back an hour and lose an hour of afternoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostages as forces occupy hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60757133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors and patients are prevented from leaving Mariupol's main hospital, the deputy mayor says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA first lab-grown mosquitoes may take flight...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2022-03-california-lab-grown-mosquitoes-flightstirring-controversy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A biotech firm is seeking permission to release genetically modified mosquitoes into the open air of California for the first time later this year, aiming to reduce the expanding populations of invasive mosquitoes and prevent deadly disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ELVIS' to Play Cannes...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/elvis-presley-movie-cannes-film-festival-premiere-baz-luhrmann-tom-hanks-austin-butler-1234979064/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Warner Bros has firmed a splashy Cannes premiere for Elvis, the Baz Luhrmann-directed epic story about the relationship between Elvis Presley and his manager Colonel Tom Parker that shoo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cargo ship stuck in Chesapeake Bay; 'Logistical challenge'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/cargo-ship-stuck-marylands-chesapeake-bay-presenting-coast/story?id=83455048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The loaded 1,095-foot cargo ship remained stuck Tuesday morning in Maryland's Chesapeake Bay, according to the Coast Guard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Cold, Die Old: Lower Body Temperature Linked To Longer Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/lower-body-temperature-longer-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that body temperature can have a bigger impact on your lifespan than your metabolism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron F-bomb rant as LAKERS get blown out again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/15/lebron-james-goes-on-f-bomb-rant-in-lakers-loss-to-raptors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lakers’ struggles seem to have finally cracked LeBron James.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/11 plotters in talks over deal to avoid death penalty trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/15/september-11-khalid-sheikh-mohammed-prosecutors-plea-deal-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Times reports talks under way for plea agreement that could bring an end to one of biggest criminal cases in US history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Apps of Quiet Dissent...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-apps-of-quiet-dissent/ar-AAV5evs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine invasion shuffling alliances in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://denvergazette.com/ap/international/explainer-how-russia-s-war-in-ukraine-is-shuffling-us-alliances-in-latin-america/article_f09839a2-4046-5971-8341-3720ad3364d4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denvergazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia’s invasion of Ukraine has reverberated across the globe, including in the Western Hemisphere, where both Washington and Moscow see the crisis as an opportunity to shift regional alliances in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to travel to Brussels...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/15/biden-will-travel-to-brussels-this-month-for-nato-summit-about-russias-attack-on-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to disarm far-right extremists, restricts gun access...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-europe-berlin-gun-politics-music-festivals-5d4e13c2ab476dc4b904381ee28608eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's top security officials announced a 10-point plan Tuesday to combat far-right extremism in the country that includes disarming about 1,500 suspected extremists and tightening background checks for those wanting to acquire guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless serial killer suspect arrested in DC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/15/suspect-in-deadly-shooting-spree-of-dc-nyc-homeless-people-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspect in the serial killing and shooting of homeless people in the Big Apple and Washington, DC, was arrested early Tuesday in the capital, police announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's Responsible if TELSA on Autopilot Kills Someone?</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2022/03/whos-responsible-if-tesla-autopilot-kills-someone/363111/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Courts will decide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Cage getting best reviews of career  -- for playing himself!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/nicolas-cage-unbearable-weight-perfect-rotten-tomatoes-reviews-1235111572/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After its premiere at the South by Southwest festival, Cage's new comedy has received a massive critics' score (so far).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISCOVERY CEO'S Pay Soars to $246 MILLION Ahead of  Merger...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/discovery-ceo-david-zaslav-pay-2021-1235101727/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company disclosed latest annual compensation details for its top executives, with the calculation for Zaslav getting a huge boost from stock options he received as part of a contract extension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman accused of torturing, holding online date hostage for $100K...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-woman-accused-of-holding-online-date-hostage-for-100k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 22-year-old New York City woman faces attempted murder charges over claims she duped a Tinder date into coming to her apartment where he was allegedly tortured and held for a $100,000 ransom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model who called Putin psychopath found dead in suitcase...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-model-found-dead-suitcase-26468230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Model Gretta Vedler, 23, went missing after savagely criticising Russian President Vladimir Putin online last year - her ex-boyfriend has now confessed to the murder</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian MP wanted to fire nuclear missile at USA to 'send a message'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-threaten-america-nuclear-strike-26471984</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Duma member Yevgeny Alexeyevich Fyodorov has claimed America would not retaliate if Russia fired a ballistic missile at them, with casualties of roughly 10,000 predicted by the politician</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney warns of 'extraordinary challenge' to preserve American democracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mitt-romney-american-democracy-extraordinary-challenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His stark message came at a fundraiser for Congresswoman Liz Cheney Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Calls for her 'Protection'...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/macron-says-to-raise-with-putin-protection-for-journalist-who-protested-on-tv-01647351907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron on Tuesday said he would discuss with Russian counterpart Vladimir Putin offering protection for a Russian journalist facing a long prison sentence after she brandished on live TV a slogan protesting the invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin calls anti-war protest on state TV 'hooliganism'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kremlin-anti-war-protest-state-095350362.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (Reuters) -The Kremlin on Tuesday dismissed as "hooliganism" an act of dissent by a woman who interrupted a live news bulletin on Russia's state television to denounce the war in Ukraine. The protester held up a sign behind a studio presenter reading the news on Channel One on Monday night and shouted slogans condemning Russia's Feb. 24 invasion of Ukraine. "As far as this woman is concerned, this is hooliganism," said Kremlin spokesperson Dmitry Peskov, who went on to laud the state channel as a pillar of objective and timely news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation surge, war cloud Fed's rate trajectory...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inflation-surge-war-cloud-feds-101101152.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New economic projections from the Federal Reserve this week will show how far and how fast policymakers see interest rates rising this year, in a first test of the impact of the Ukraine war and surging inflation on the coming shift in U.S. monetary policy. The Fed's policy-setting committee is expected to raise borrowing costs by a quarter of a percentage point at the end of its two-day meeting on Wednesday, a session that will set the tone for the central bank's reaction to a war-driven energy shock that is colliding with an end-of-pandemic economic reopening and strong consumer demand. The latest quarterly economic projections, due to be issued along with a policy statement at 2 p.m. EDT (1800 GMT) on Wednesday, will show what officials anticipate in terms of key indicators, including GDP growth, inflation and unemployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX NEWS CAMERAMAN KILLED</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/breaking-fox-news-cameraman-dies-in-attack-that-wounded-benjamin-hall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News cameraman was killed outside of Kyiv on Monday, the network announced on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL PLUNGES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/15/oil-drops-again-now-more-than-25percent-below-recent-high.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices came under pressure as a number of factors weighed on the market, including the Russia-Ukraine war and a potential slowdown in demand from China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders visit capital to show support...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-eu-country-leaders-train-091223044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime ministers of the Czech Republic, Poland and Slovenia were travelling to Kyiv by train on Tuesday to show support for the country on behalf of the EU, the first foreign leaders to visit the Ukrainian capital since Russia invaded last month. Kyiv has been under Russian attacks: two powerful explosions rocked the capital before dawn on Tuesday. Polish Prime Minister Mateusz Morawiecki said on Facebook the trip took place on the 20th day of Russian President Vladimir Putin's Putin's "criminal aggression against Ukraine".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearing political violence in '24, judges sentence Jan. 6 defendants to probation through next election...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/dc-md-va/2022/03/15/jan-6-sentences-probation-2024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. judges increasingly warn that as Donald Trump’s “false narrative” of a stolen election persists, so does the damage to democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin calls anti-war protest on state TV 'hooliganism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/kremlin-anti-war-protest-state-tv-was-hooliganism-2022-03-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin on Tuesday dismissed as "hooliganism" an act of dissent by a woman who interrupted a live news bulletin on Russia's state television to denounce the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow rallies militias ahead of urban assaults...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220315-russia-rallies-militias-ahead-of-ukraine-urban-assaults</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian call for fighters from Syria and Chechnya to join its war in Ukraine is motivated by plans to take major cities with urban warfare tactics which will require overwhelmingly superior attacki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Close the sky', residents beg after new strikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220315-close-the-sky-kyiv-residents-beg-after-new-strikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside her glass-strewn Kyiv apartment, Alla Ragulina cries as she surveys the wreckage of a life shattered by a surge in Russian strikes on the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian teacher suspended for refusing to call students by pronouns. Now suing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-christian-teacher-was-suspended-for-refusing-to-call-students-by-the-pronouns-they-use-now-she-is-suing/ar-AAV5772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOP GUN: MAVERICK' to Screen at Cannes...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2022/03/top-gun-maverick-cannes-1234708027/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film will premiere at Cannes before its wide release on May 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless serial killer arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10614513/Police-arrest-man-attacks-homeless-men-left-two-dead-three-injured-DC-NYC.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the early hours of Tuesday morning, Washington DC's police department confirmed officers had arrested the suspect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once-starving lions roar back to life in Sudan sanctuary...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220315-once-starving-lions-roar-back-to-life-in-sudan-sanctuary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kandaka the lioness was once sick and emaciated in a rundown zoo in Sudan's capital, but thanks to wildlife enthusiasts she now thrives in a reserve watching her cubs grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Needs Ice? Roller-Skating Comes to Rockefeller Center...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/15/who-needs-ice-roller-skating-comes-to-rockefeller-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The winter ice-skating season may be drawing to a close at Rockefeller Center, but this year the party will continue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poodles pop in popularity, but Labs still No. 1 dog breed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-sports-trending-news-dogs-arts-and-entertainment-fa33e1765dcd15e64afcb003870c1571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Labrador retrievers are still tugging hardest on U.S. dog lovers' heartstrings, but poodles just strutted back into the American Kennel Club's top five most popular dog breeds for the first time in nearly a quarter-century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation surge, war cloud Fed's interest rate trajectory...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-fed-projections/inflation-surge-war-cloud-feds-interest-rate-trajectory-idUSKCN2LC10S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New economic projections from the Federal Reserve this week will show how far and how fast policymakers see interest rates rising this year, in a first test of the impact of the Ukraine war and surging inflation on the coming shift in U.S. monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dancing  Good For Masculinity...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dancing-good-for-masculinity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interviewees said dancing was a good way of expressing themselves physically and made them more positive about their bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Hit Woman in the Head 125 Times Because She Was Asian, Officials Say...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/14/man-hit-woman-in-the-head-125-times-because-she-was-asian-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 67-year-old woman, wearing a white face mask and dark hooded jacket and pushing a shopping cart, enters an apartment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog sniffs out cancer, saves owner's life ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4894316/dog-sniffed-out-cancerous-lump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MUM’S life was saved by her “unusually affectionate” dog — when it sniffed out a cancerous lump in her breast. Tanya Hibberd thought husky Sapphire was being more cuddly than normal because she h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Chance, one of CNN's star correspondents, gets a break...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/Matthew-Chance-one-of-CNN-s-star-Ukraine-17001999.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many TV viewers, the war in Ukraine became real when Matthew Chance donned his flak...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child becoming refugee every second in Ukraine war...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/ukraine-russia-war-one-child-becoming-a-refugee-every-second-in-ukraine-says-un-2824172</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 1.4 million children have now fled Ukraine since the Russian invasion began on February 24, meaning nearly one child a second has become a refugee, the UN said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German WWII ghosts loom large...</title>
      <link>https://www.deccanherald.com/international/world-news-politics/german-wwii-ghosts-loom-large-in-ukraine-crisis-1091513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deccanherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The war weighs heavy on Ilse Thiele's mind these days as she sits in the floral print armchair in her Berlin living room, the television constantly tuned to the news from Ukraine. "Of course all the memories come flooding back," the 85-year-old retired manager of an East German post office says, as she watches the streams of exhausted refugees meeting armies of volunteers just minutes away at Berlin's main train station. "I feel so sorry for all those people, especially the children."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service report details incel threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/incel-threat-secret-service-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since 2014, attacks inspired by the "incel movement" and spanning the U.S. and Canada have left dozens dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curfew For 'Difficult And Dangerous' 35 Hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/kyiv-to-impose-36-hour-curfew-from-late-tuesday-mayor-01647336907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kyiv will impose a 35-hour curfew from Tuesday night amid a "difficult and dangerous moment" after several Russian strikes, Mayor Vitali Klitschko said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass brawls, attacks as soccer violence spreads in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/mass-brawls-attacks-football-violence-195225628.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A string of outbreaks of violence, several deadly, suggest that fan unrest in Latin American football is spiralling out of control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reports record daily cases...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/china-reports-record-5280-daily-covid-cases/articleshow/90212909.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record figure was driven by a surge in nationwide Omicron outbreaks, with over 3,000 domestic transmissions in the northeastern province of Jilin, according to NHC data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY: Judge permanently blocks release of photos, records related to Bob Saget's death...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/judge-permanently-blocks-release-photos-220300963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Local authorities will be permanently blocked from releasing photos and videos taken of comedian Bob Saget’s body and his personal effects under a ruling issued by a judge Monday. At a virtual hearing for the lawsuit filed by Saget’s family, Circuit Judge Vincent Chiu agreed on a permanent injunction stopping the Orange County Sheriff’s Office and District 9 medical examiner’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIANS COULD BUCKLE IN 10 DAYS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4895753/russians-buckle-ten-days-ukraine-resistance-putin-forces-mariupol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin could only have ten days to win the war in Ukraine before his forces buckle, defence experts have claimed. The Russian tyrant expected a quick victory when he ordered the invasion on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU country leaders visit capital to show support...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/three-eu-country-leaders-take-train-kyiv-show-support-ukraine-2022-03-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime ministers of the Czech Republic, Poland and Slovenia were travelling to Kyiv by train on Tuesday to show support for the country on behalf of the EU, the first foreign leaders to visit the Ukrainian capital since Russia invaded last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Weighs Biden Trip to Europe as War Rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/white-house-weighs-biden-trip-to-europe-as-ukraine-war-rages/ar-AAV29BW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persian Gulf monarchies hedging bets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-ukraine-conflict-has-persian-gulf-monarchies-hedging-their-bets/ar-AAV1TbD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The antiwar protester who crashed Russian TV broadcast can't be found, lawyers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-antiwar-protester-who-crashed-a-russian-tv-broadcast-can-t-be-found-her-lawyers-say/ar-AAV4ebR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How defenders have kept forces from capturing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-kyiv-e2-80-99s-outgunned-defenders-have-kept-russian-forces-from-capturing-the-capital/ar-AAV3zA2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fentanyl in everything': New hospitalizations days after Spring Breakers overdosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/theres-fentanyl-in-everything-4-new-hospitalizations-linked-to-fentanyl-just-days-after-spring-breakers-overdosed/ar-AAV3hr6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sewer data warns of new bump in COVID cases after lull...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/u-s-sewer-data-warns-of-a-new-bump-in-covid-cases-after-lull/ar-AAV39E2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jussie Smollett lawyers argue for release pending appeal...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jussie-smollett-lawyers-argue-actor-173200409.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Jussie Smollett’s attorneys want a state appellate court to release the actor from jail while his appeal is pending, according to recent court filings arguing that Smollett’s time in custody could put his mental and physical health at risk. Smollett’s family, meanwhile, is echoing the actor’s extraordinary statement after sentencing, saying he is strong and has no desire to hurt ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shelling of Kyiv intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-kyiv-business-moscow-d357f90e5a332e10abd8e2b7c7be67c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russia’s relentless bombardment of Ukraine edged closer to central Kyiv on Tuesday, with a series of strikes hitting a residential neighborhood as the leaders of three European Union countries planned a bold visit to Ukraine’s embattled capital in a show of support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict disrupts key supply chains -- and lives...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-technology-business-europe-texas-2d6a87d8b0af4b4b4872a1b8fd0f276d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It can be hard to measure the ways that Russia’s war in Ukraine has disrupted the global supply of parts and raw materials needed to complete a variety of products – from cars to computer chips. But cutting off one of those supply links brought a “depressing feeling” to Andrey Bibik, head of the Interpipe steel plant in Dnipro, Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May lead to rethinking of defense of Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-biden-business-nato-5f084c3bde893b44dd087ec69de8c02c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin's war in Ukraine and his push to upend the broader security order in Europe may lead to a historic shift in American thinking about defense of the continent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How plausible is military aid?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-jake-sullivan-china-moscow-europe-0f7645e7e81fc736f9e82ba33eac380a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The U.S. says Russia has asked China to provide military assistance for its war in Ukraine, and that China has responded affirmatively. Both Moscow and Beijing have denied the allegation, with a Chinese spokesperson dismissing it as “disinformation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns China not to assist Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-works-to-keep-china-on-board-in-ukraine-conflict/ar-AAV3C30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kyiv outgunned defenders have kept Russian forces from capturing capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-kyiv-e2-80-99s-outgunned-defenders-have-kept-russian-forces-from-capturing-the-capital/ar-AAV3zA2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Raises Alarm as Covid Infections Surge to Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/covid-digest-germanys-situation-critical-lauterbach-says/a-61094888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The German health minister has called on the federal states to reevaluate the coronavirus rules before restrictions are lifted. In other news, a Chinese city locks down as COVID cases rise. Follow DW for more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
