<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Navy robot sub to kill without human control...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2236638-us-navy-robot-submarine-would-be-able-to-kill-without-human-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A secret US Navy project known only as CLAWS will equip armed robot submarines with sensors and algorithms enabling them to destroy targets without explicit human control</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Considering Emergency Shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/anxiety-aging-congress-spreads-along-coronavirus-n1152851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There's a lot of concern that members could bring it home," a senior Democratic leadership aide says as offices discuss recessing Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There is 'tipping point' before it kills...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/coronavirus-nears-fatal-tipping-point-when-lungs-are-inflamed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in seven patients develops difficulty breathing and other severe complications, while 6 percent become critical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire Yield Curve Inside 1% Sounds Alarm...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/treasury-yields-plunge-record-lows-004348502.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The entire yield curve for U.S. bonds fell below 1% for the first time in history after an all-out price war between the world’s biggest oil exporters triggered an unprecedented global bond rally.U.S. Treasury yields plunged, with the rate on 30-year bonds diving as much as 59 basis points</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does worrying increase risk of getting sick?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/coronavirus-worrying-increase-risk-sick/story?id=69478552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the number of people infected by coronavirus – also known as COVID-19 – continues to grow, so does the number of individuals concerned about the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Close call threatens to upend Trump's routine...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Close-call-at-CPAC-threatens-to-upend-Trump-s-15115615.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A growing sense of concern and uncertainty about the reach of the novel coronavirus has begun to take hold in the White House, after an attendee at a recent political conference where President Donald Trump spoke tested positive for covid-19, the disease caused by the virus.  Trump was photographed shaking hands with Matt Schlapp, the chairman of the American Conservative Union who confirmed that he had been in direct contact with the infected man during the Conservative Political Action Conference last month.  The handshake at CPAC put Trump just two degrees of separation away from the virus that he has sought to minimize as it has rocked financial markets and tested his leadership skills. While the White House has maintained that Trump was never in direct contact with the infected person and is not suffering from any symptoms, the potential close call at a political event underscores how the outbreak threatens to upend the president's routine as he campaigns for reelection.  There is growing tension among Trump administration officials, who now see the rapidly spreading outbreak as an event that could consume the president's fourth year in office, even as Trump remains reluctant to see much cause for concern, according to White House officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe the internal mood.  "I'm not concerned at all," Trump said Saturday when asked about the potential threat posed to the White House by the coronavirus.  He also pledged to keep holding "tremendous" political rallies, even as top public health officials within his government have called for millions of Americans to avoid large crowds and major events to reduce the risk of being infected.  White House officials have said they expect the outbreak to spread significantly throughout the country in the coming days,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE agents storm New York City restaurant and douse detainee with pepper spray...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-ice-detain-pepper-spray-20200308-7soq22x5tbas7iizdynq763f3i-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agents barged into La Cabana, a Spanish eatery on Flatbush Ave. near Beverly Road in Prospect Park South on March 1 and nabbed Maria De Los Angel Sanz Pimentel, a Dominican immigrant without a work visa, according to ICE and officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As coronavirus spreads, warnings become more urgent for elderly and frail...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-08/coronavirus-elderly-frail-people-at-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older people, especially those with health problems, are being told to avoid large gatherings and trips: 'Don't get on a cruise ship.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to Draft Teens and Army to Fight Spread... </title>
      <link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/world/2020/03/08/israel-to-draft-teens-and-army-to-fight-spread-of-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freemalaysiatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli PM Benjamin Netanyahu believes 'the pandemic is not afflicting children or young people'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival biker gangs gunfight in Cleveland; 18 shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/crime/2020/03/18-shot-1-killed-following-fight-between-multiple-motorcycle-clubs-on-clevelands-east-side.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eighteen people were shot – including one fatally – late Saturday after a large fight broke out among several motorcycle clubs on the city’s East Side, Cleveland police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump escalates fight against press with libel lawsuits...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/486273-trump-escalates-fight-against-press-with-libel-lawsuits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump campaign’s libel lawsuits against The New York Times and The Washington Post marked a dramatic escalation in the president's long fight with the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sparks panic on plane by deliberately coughing on crew!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/507275/cabin-crew-tackle-woman-who-sparked-coronavirus-panic-by-coughing-on-staff-deliberately-to-get-them-to-let-her-off-jet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING footage shows cabin crew tackling an airline passenger who deliberately coughed on staff, it is claimed. The dramatic unverified video was allegedly filmed on board a Thai Airways flight i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops in hazmat suits enforce lockdown in Spain...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/507166/coronavirus-patients-in-spain-forced-to-stay-in-their-homes-by-terror-cops-in-hazmat-suits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TERROR cops in hazmat suits are forcing coronavirus-infected residents in a Spanish town to stay at home and self-isolate. Around 30 people infected with the bug in the town of Haro – in the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-year Treasury below 0.5%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/09/10-year-treasury-yield-plunges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL PLUNGE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/08/oil-plummets-30percent-as-opec-deal-failure-sparks-price-war-fears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices dropped in early trading as the breakdown in OPEC talks stoked oversupply fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz self-quarantines after contact at CPAC...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ted-cruz-coronavirus-self-quarantine-0c85ef4e-8022-43c9-9196-ab2d43db3aba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm not experiencing any symptoms, and I feel fine and healthy," he tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RALLIES ON PAUSE?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-refuses-halt-rallies-coronavirus-surges-032735605.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump signaled Saturday that he has no intention of halting campaign rallies despite surging coronavirus infections, as a case was confirmed for the first time within miles of the White House. The president struck a defiant tone as he spoke to reporters about the outbreak at his Mar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport screeners, health workers plagued by fear and anger...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200308001731-hjzm5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WORKERS (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-U.S. airport screeners, health workers plagued by fear and anger as coronavirus spreads</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires 3 unidentified projectiles toward East Sea...</title>
      <link>https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20200309000451325?section=national/defense</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.yna.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(ATTN: RECASTS headline, lead; ADDS more info, JCS comment in paras 2, 3) SEOUL, March 9...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 hopefuls keep up campaigns for now...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d1368e1e4853e2ad7431c04b1a82d967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAND RAPIDS, Mich. (AP) — As the coronavirus hits more states, Democratic presidential candidate Bernie Sanders said Sunday his campaign is gauging when it may become necessary to cancel the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety grips companies across world as virus spreads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b0b49661addb3b99efaca70c4ba1d189</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Since breaking out of China, the coronavirus has breached the walls of the Vatican. It's struck the Iranian holy city of Qom and contaminated a nursing home in Seattle. And...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 30 Minute Daily Walk Dramatically Cuts Risk Of Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/seniors-who-walk-for-30-minutes-daily-cut-risk-of-death-from-any-cause/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two new studies agree that staying active is perhaps the best way for older adults to live longer is to walk every day well into their golden years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most daunting virus' in half century...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/03/07/harvard-forum-experts-warn-most-daunting-virus-in-50-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran epidemiologist, a homeland security authority, and a global health reporter agree: SARS-CoV-2 is "the most daunting virus" in half a century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Administration, Debate Raged Over What to Tell Public...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inside-trump-administration-debate-raged-over-what-to-tell-public/ar-BB10SKCK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  'Perfectly coordinated and fine tuned plan'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-defends-coronavirus-response-as-he-attacks-fake-news-again-we-have-a-perfectly-coordinated-and-fine-tuned-plan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump defended the U.S.' response to coronavirus this morning and once again attacked the "fake news."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blagojevich praises President's 'testicular virility'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/03/07/exclusive-rod-blagojevich-explains-why-he-is-a-trumpocrat-democrats-have-abandoned-american-workers-black-voters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blagojevich ripped into his former political party, the Democrats, and laid out why he considers himself now a “Trumpocrat.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Bans Non-Essential Public Gatherings At City Facilities...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/07/san-francisco-bans-non-essential-public-gatherings-at-city-facilities-for-2-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City and County of San Francisco has banned "non-essential group events" at any city-owned facilities for the next two weeks because of concerns about the spread of coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robbers wearing surgical masks rob NY casino...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/08/two-armed-gunmen-hold-up-aqueduct-racetrack-for-a-lot-of-money-saturday-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two guys cleaned up big at Aqueduct Saturday night — robbing the Queens racetrack at gunpoint and making off with as much as a quarter-million dollars. The brazen bandits, who were being soug…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's intel power play spooks the spooks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/08/john-ratcliffe-trump-intel-power-play-123452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CIA never welcomed its overlords in the Office of the Director of National Intelligence. But now, the agency confronts its worst nightmare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak spreads to 32 states and DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/08/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of deaths from coronavirus in the US rose to 19 as several states joined the rapidly growing list of states with confirmed cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  'Perfectly coordinated and fine tuned plan'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1236634209516752896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We have a perfectly coordinated and fine tuned plan at the White House for our attack on CoronaVirus. We moved VERY early to close borders to certain areas, which was a Godsend. V.P. is doing a great job. The Fake News Media is doing everything possible to make us look bad. Sad!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala bet campaign on attacking him. Now she supports...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/486480-kamala-harris-endorses-biden-presidential-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders, Biden up attacks as head-to-head race takes shape...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb997d0999faecc2f6ba19a5de43aa3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEARBORN, Mich. (AP) — The Democratic presidential primary is down to two major candidates, and it shows. Former Vice President Joe Biden and Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders are spending their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot in head drives self to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/man-shot-in-head-drives-self-to-stroger-hospital-police/5994863/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 28-year-old man who was shot in the head drove himself to the hospital Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Deaths That Exposed Horse Racing's Brutal Underbelly...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-mysterious-deaths-that-exposed-horse-racings-brutal-underbelly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The horses keep dying at California’s Santa Anita racetrack—and racing insiders know the real reason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army suspends travel to and from SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/coronavirus-us-army-south-korea-suspends-travel-soldiers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Army on Sunday suspended travel for all soldiers and their families to and from South Korea over COVID-19 concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malfunction causes red wine to flow from faucets in Italian town...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/italy-lambrusco-wine-from-faucet-castelvetro-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident provided a moment of levity to the town that's in the midst of the coronavirus crisis -- which has hit northern Italy the hardest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official: White House didn't want to tell seniors not to fly...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/921ad7f1f08d7634bf681ba785faf269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The White House overruled health officials who wanted to recommend that elderly and physically fragile Americans be advised not to fly on commercial airlines because of the new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB limits spring autographs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/87c707ecd6f88fa763e2f4368aa0ecca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. (AP) — A baseball fan's treasure trove sat on a table outside the San Francisco Giants clubhouse Saturday morning — hundreds of baseball cards signed by the franchise's biggest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Saudi Starts All-Out Oil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/commodities/saudi-arabia-starts-all-out-oil-war-destroys-opec-flooding-market-slashing-oil-prices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/8/washington-dc-coronavirus-case-confirmed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man in his 50s tested positive for coronavirus - the first presumptively confirmed case in the nation’s capital, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon Church discloses $38 billion stock portfolio...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/religion/2020/03/07/lds-church-discloses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, the LDS Church’s biggest investment fund has disclosed its Wall Street holdings, revealing $37.8 billion in stocks and mutual funds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE socialist slams wealthy but lived in luxury...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/07/youtube-socialist-carlos-maza-slams-the-wealthy-but-lives-in-luxury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlos Maza doesn’t like rich people. The social media socialist with more than 150,000 followers on Twitter and YouTube combined regularly uses his platforms to rail against the wealthy and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal purge over 'coup plot'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-arabia-royal-purge-over-coup-plot-210020989.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi authorities have detained three princes including King Salman's brother and nephew for allegedly plotting a coup, three sources told AFP Saturday, signalling the de facto ruler's tightening grip on power. The detentions, which cast aside the last vestiges of potential opposition to Crown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL CHAOS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f3be69cc2cf55f74a35118c557ad8461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italy announced a sweeping quarantine early Sunday for its northern regions, igniting travel chaos as it restricted the movements of a quarter of its people in a bid to halt the new...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
