<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PARTY OVER  FOR UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6755687/england-croatia-world-cup-2018-fans-celebrations-uk-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENGLAND fans have been left heartbroken after Croatia won 2-1 in extra time of the World Cup semi-final tonight. The hopes of a nation were dashed as it became clear England’s years of hurt w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROATIA MAKES WORLD CUP FINAL!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/croatia-stuns-england-in-extra-time-to-advance-to-world-cup-final-1531341455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mario Mandzukic’s 109th-minute shot into the left corner of the net sealed a 2-1 comeback win for Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama out of hiding; Enters 2018 campaign...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/11/obama-campaign-congress-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of hiding?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE TV Outage in Middle of Game...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/digital/news/youtube-tv-outage-world-cup-england-croatia-1202870724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube TV, Google’s internet-delivered subscription TV service, was hit with nationwide outages — right in the middle of the 2018 World Cup semifinal match between England and Croatia.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When GOOGLE was young: Sex, drugs and rock n' roll...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/11/when-google-was-young-oral-history-from-new-book-has-sex-street-view-and-how-it-all-began/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All this was back when the “don’t be evil” mantra wasn’t quite as complicated for Google as it is nowadays — and way before the “Me Too” movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Claims Autism, Arthritis Treatable By Pot...</title>
      <link>http://detroit.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/michigan-medical-marijuana-autism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan has added several medical conditions to the state's list of ailments which qualify for a medical marijuana prescription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPA JOHN'S shares skid after report founder used N-word...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/11/papa-johns-shares-crater-after-report-that-founder-used-a-n-word.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Papa John's skidded on Wednesday after a report surfaced alleging that founder John Schnatter has used the N-word during a conference call in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump protest in Brussels expected THOUSANDS, got DOZENS...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/anti-trump-protest-at-nato-draws-only-a-couple-dozen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs Urge City Citizens To Report 'Illegal Aliens' To ICE...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/signs-report-illegal-aliens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some residents in Omaha have been pulling the homemade flyers down, calling them hateful and offensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Blitzer's airtime trimmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/brianna-keilar-will-anchor-cnns-1-p-m-timeslot-beginning-this-fall/369804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wolf Blitzer will continue to anchor The Situation Room weekdays from 5 - 7 p.m. ET.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST: Inside Mueller's New Army...</title>
      <link>'https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/11/papa-johns-shares-crater-after-report-that-founder-used-a-n-word.html&gt;PAPA JOHN'S shares skid after report founder used N-word...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL player attacked by employee at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nfl-player-pacman-jones-attacked-employee-airport-162700741--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Police say former Cincinnati Bengals cornerback Adam "Pacman" Jones was attacked during a run-in with a facility-service employee at the airport in Atlanta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tells NATO leaders to increase defense spending to 4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-tells-nato-leaders-military-spending-4-percent-155939755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump told NATO leaders on Wednesday they should increase their defense spending to 4 percent of their country's economic output, double the group's current goal of two percent. NATO allies shrugged off the demand as part and parcel of Trump's brash push for allies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals attack Brett Kavanaugh for 'frat boy' name...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/11/liberals-attack-brett-kavanaugh-for-frat-boy-name.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest line of attack from liberals against Brett Kavanaugh, President Trump’s nominee for the Supreme Court, is knocking the judge for his “frat boy”-sounding first name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Tom Petty Song Drops...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/music/news/tom-petty-an-american-treasure-boxed-set-track-list-revealed-new-song-drops-1202870299/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As announced on SiriusXM yesterday, on September 28, Reprise Records will release “An American Treasure” — a career-spanning Tom Petty box set containing dozens of previously unreleased recordings,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK WORLD CUP MANIA RAMPS UP AGAIN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6751746/england-world-cup-2018-party-kicks-off-russia-moscow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENGLAND’s World Cup party kicked-off in style as thousands of fans gathered in bars around Moscow’s iconic Red Square today before the big game – and the Wags joined in too. Jamie Vardy’s wif…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA screeners win immunity from flier abuse claims...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/tsa-screeners-win-immunity-flier-abuse-claims-u-150740124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - Fliers may have a tough time recovering damages for invasive screenings at U.S. airport security checkpoints, after a federal appeals court on Wednesday said screeners are immune from claims under a federal law governing assaults, false arrests and other abuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey detains Muslim televangelist on fraud charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkey-detains-muslim-televangelist-fraud-charges-135215166.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish police on Wednesday detained on fraud charges a televangelist notorious for propagating conservative views while surrounded by scantily-clad women he refers to as his "kittens". Adnan Oktar, a bizarre and controversial figure who also denies evolution, was detained alongside dozens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO CRACKING</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-slams-captive-germany-nato-summit-081237901.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump traded barbs with German Chancellor Angela Merkel at a tense NATO summit Wednesday after he accused Berlin of being "captive" to Russia and demanded it immediately step up defence spending. The two-day meet in Brussels is shaping up as the alliance's most difficult</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK WORLD CUP MANIA RAMPS UP AGAIN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5941087/England-fans-say-nervous-slightly-sick-ahead-crunch-Croatia-match.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country will come to a complete standstill tonight as 30million people tune in to watch Harry Kane’s heroes take on Croatia in the World Cup semi-final.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breed Becomes First Black Female Mayor of San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/London-Breed-stepping-in-as-mayor-of-an-unsettled-13064524.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elected by the slimmest margin in modern history, London Breed takes the helm of a city Wednesday where, despite a booming economy and rocketing job growth, the majority of voters feel San Francisco is on the wrong track. And where, despite hundreds of millions of dollars spent on various programs to house the homeless, clean up the city’s streets and clear up the clogged traffic, only 2 out of 10 voters feel City Hall is doing a good job managing its resources. “You would think with 2.5 percent unemployment and an $11 billion budget, the public would be more upbeat,” said Chamber of Commerce Vice President Jim Lazarus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems hold overall turnout edge in competitive House races...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/10/democrats-hold-overall-turnout-edge-in-competitive-house-races</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Hold Overall Turnout Edge in Competitive House Races</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University flies blackened American flag for art display...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Kansas is flying a blackened American flag on campus that is intended as a commentary on “the current political climate.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Over 'Straight Pride Month'...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/10/dixon-vice-mayor-spam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since publishing an article calling for a Straight Pride American Month, Ted Hickman addressed the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania to meet with British vets and school children...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5942717/Melania-meet-British-vets-school-children-exclusive-details-London-visit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First Lady Melania Trump will visit British school children and veterans when she is in London later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Box Office Heats Up, But Some Studios Left in Cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/summer-box-office-heats-up-but-some-studios-left-cold-1126179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's now a year-round business," says a Warner Bros. exec as the studio sits out blockbuster season, leaving Disney and Universal to sweep up more than 60 percent of domestic revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing pony washed away in flood -- found alive on house roof!</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/07/10/missing-pony-washed-away-flood-found-alive-house-roof-7701298/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But nobody knows how she got there...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel military says fired Patriot missile at drone from Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-israel/israel-military-says-fired-patriot-missile-at-drone-from-syria-idUSKBN1K11RX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel launched a Patriot interceptor missile on Wednesday at a drone spotted approaching from Syria, the second such incident in as many months, the Israeli military said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: DC, Detroit, NYC Top 'Worst-Run' Cities...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2018/07/10/survey-washington-worst-run-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal finance website WalletHub has released their rankings for the worst big cities in the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOVES OFF AT NATO SUMMIT</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/11/trump-brings-grievances-to-nato-summit-worrying-u-s-allies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Brings Grievances to NATO Summit, Worrying U.S. Allies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mutant human-like sea creature' sparks panic after found alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/715672/Mutant-sea-creature-looks-like-human-discovered-China-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitney Houston's mom expresses 'shock' over abuse claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/whitney-houstons-mom-expresses-shock-over-abuse-claims-120323275.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Whitney Houston's mother says allegations that her superstar daughter and her son were molested by her niece are "unfathomable."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Woman Found Dead In Trash Compactor At Manhattan Apt Building...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/union-square-woman-found-dead-trash-compactor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say a 48-year-old woman was found in the trash compactor chute around 5 p.m. Tuesday at 1 Irving Place near Union Square.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEC OIL OUTPUT JUMPS; SAUDIS OPEN TAPS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/11/opecs-oil-output-jumps-in-june-as-saudi-arabia-opens-the-taps.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia hiked its oil output in June to the highest level since the end of 2016, boosting OPEC's production for the month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST: Inside Mueller's New Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-muellers-new-army</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the special counsel zeroes in on Russia’s online arsonists, he’s brought in a new crew of cyberspy fighters—and a straight-up street crime prosecutor, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sale of guillotine divides France; 'Few dents on blade'...</title>
      <link>https://www.expatica.com/fr/news/country-news/France-auction-history-crime-guillotine_1973648.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.expatica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 150-year-old guillotine with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England World Cup excitement hits fever pitch...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/england-world-cup-excitement-hits-160416351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation has reached a state of feverish excitement as England prepares for its first World Cup semi-final since the penalty shootout heartbreak of Italia 90. England erupted in collective euphoria on Saturday as almost 20 million gathered around TV sets to witness their comfortable 2-0 victory over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan flag emoji crashes iPhones to appease China...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-flag-emoji-crashes-iphones-090941643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has fixed a glitch that caused iPhones registered in China to crash when they received a message with an emoji showing the Taiwanese flag.  Devices have reportedly been crashing since the icon was blocked in 2017, an apparent attempt at censorship because the Chinese government refuses to acknowledge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check-in with smile: MARRIOTT, ALIBABA trial facial recognition at hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-alibaba-marriott-intnl-facial-recogni/check-in-with-a-smile-marriott-alibaba-trial-facial-recognition-at-china-hotels-idUSKBN1K11B0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese guests at Marriott International, the world's largest hotel chain, may soon be able to check in with a quick scan of their facial features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STD 'stealth' bug which makes infertile spreading rapidly...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/715625/sti-sexually-transmitted-disease-mycoplasma-genitalium-chlamydia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Protection says NYC mayor crossed border illegally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f65ed6b3027046dd8e7068b76d56e778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio and his security detail violated both Mexican and U.S. immigration laws by crossing the border on foot during a visit near El</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying Trains?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/2018/07/11/flying-trains-france-s-akka-technologies-makes-pitch-to-boeing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Link &amp; Fly” is Akka Technologies’s new flagship aircraft design, with wings that come off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Military Drone Documents Found for Sale on Dark Web...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stolen-u-s-military-drone-documents-found-for-sale-on-dark-web-researchers-say-1531301401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unidentified hacker tried to sell purported U.S. military documents containing information about combat drones, a cybersecurity research firm said, after they were allegedly stolen from an Air Force officer’s computer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF CORTEZ: New Dem star to rattle DC establishment...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/396412-new-dem-star-to-rattle-dc-establishment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingmar Bergman, portrayer of inner demons, 100 years on...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ingmar-bergman-portrayer-inner-demons-100-years-050255450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The essence of our education was based on the principles of sin, confession, punishment, redemption and forgiveness," Bergman wrote in his autobiography "The Magic Lantern". Throughout his career, with his debut film "Crisis" to final "Saraband", the gifted director</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: WARNER BROS. plans $100 million cable car to Hollywood sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/warner-bros-plans-100-mn-cable-car-hollywood-232514277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros. has announced plans for a $100 million cable car to take tourists from its studio lot to the iconic Hollywood sign, an area increasingly choked by tourist traffic. The six-minute ride would extend more than a mile (1.6 kilometers) from Warner's base in Burbank up Mount Lee to a visitor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurse poisoned ailing patients so they would die during someone else's watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/10/nurse-japan-poisoned-least-20-ailing-patients-avoid-work/773071002/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nurse in Japan told police that she sped up the deaths at least 20 patients to avoid having to tell families that their loved ones died while she was working, local media reported. Ayumi Kuboki, 31, was arrested Saturday for the death of Sozo Nishikawa, 88, who was poisoned in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON:  Joaquin Phoenix to star as JOKER... </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/bistro/people/2018/07/10/joaquin-phoenix-star-joker-origin-story/773628002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans weren't happy about the overexposed Joker when a new film was announced at Comic-Con last year. But Joaquin Phoenix is now officially set to star in the DC Comics origin movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel on Watch as Once-Quiet Border Rumbles With Sounds of War...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/10/israel-on-watch-as-once-quiet-border-rumbles-with-sounds-of-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel on Watch as Once-Quiet Border Rumbles With Sounds of War</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumers flooded with dubious claims about marijuana's health benefits...</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/consumers-flooded-with-dubious-claims-about-marijuana-s-health-benefits/article_9cef1240-ae24-52f1-a069-f77b8a417246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spend a few minutes surfing Twitter and you’re likely to encounter a startling claim that comes without proof:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH OF THE BORDER: Jared to meet AMLO...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-son-law-kushner-meet-mexico-president-elect-194514600.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Leftist President-elect Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador is enjoying a bit of a honeymoon with U.S. President Donald Trump, and he was effusive Tuesday in praising the U.S. leader's restraint in not bringing up his proposed border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020: Hillary To Speak At Conference With Bernie, Elizabeth...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/10/hillary-clinton-bernie-2020-teachers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is she up to?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying taxi startups got Pentagon funding...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jul/10/flying-cars-taxis-pentagon-us-military-funds-joby-kitty-hawk </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Self-flying vehicle firms got $2m last year, as military envisions taxis as more Blade Runner than Back to the Future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'witness protection' for whistle-blowers exposing tech industry... </title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/21/new-witness-protection-scheme-whistle-blowers-exposing-technology/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whistleblowers are being offered a &amp;ldquo;witness protection scheme&amp;rdquo; to expose &amp;ldquo;wrongdoing&amp;rdquo; in the technology industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Set to Become World's Top Oil Producer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/07/10/u-s-set-to-become-world-s-top-oil-producer-government-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Is Set to Become World's Top Oil Producer, Government Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROAD SIGNS DETECT PHONES BEING USED IN VEHICLES...</title>
      <link>http://home.bt.com/tech-gadgets/tech-news/new-road-signs-can-detect-mobile-phones-are-being-used-in-vehicles-11364282956723 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;home.bt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology detects when a phone is in use within the vehicle and triggers a flash warning sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hype builds...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/jul/10/sacha-baron-cohen-who-is-america-trump-tv-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shot in secrecy, the satirist’s new show Who Is America? sees him take aim at Trump and the US political elite. It looks set to be something truly special</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media elites rub shoulders at bougy Sun Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/wine-wimbledon-personal-touch-courting-corporate-mergers-n890366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gifts, gab and a little bit of liquid encouragement are all part of the corporate romance that can lead to mega-deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS SHOCK: SACHA BARON COHEN MOCKS DISABLED VETS?</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/sarah-palin-sacha-baron-cohen-duped-interview-who-is-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin says she was unwittingly interviewed by comedian Sacha Baron Cohen for his upcoming Showtime series, Who Is America?, after he "duped" her into believing he was a disabled U.S. veteran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEDY PRANK SHOW SPIRALS OUT OF CONTROL...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/07/10/new-sacha-baron-cohen-series-right-wing-hit-job-source-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source familiar with the project – who saw some of the series in its early, rough-cut stage during a private screening at Sony Studios in Los Angeles on the 22nd of March – told Fox News that, at least then, it was nothing more than a Hollywood hit job on Trump supporters and the Republican party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PALIN DEMANDS NETWORK DONATE PROCEEDS...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/10/sarah-palin-sacha-baron-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Palin: "My daughter thinks you’re a piece of ****, Sacha."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCALATE: $200B MORE TARIFFS READIED ON CHINA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/10/trump-china-trade-tariffs-708707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The percentage of imports from China facing new U.S. duties is now about 50 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zsa Zsa Dead Just Weeks After 'World's Ugliest' Win...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/07/10/minnesota-dog-dies-just-weeks-after-winning-worlds-ugliest-dog-title/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zsa Zsa, the floppy-tongued bulldog from Minnesota who won the World’s Ugliest Dog contest just last month, has reportedly died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: HUAWEI 'Front Company' Infiltrated Silicon Summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/10/huawei-in-santa-clara-infiltrated-summit-at-facebook-sent-trade-secrets-to-china-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two employees from Huawei’s subsidiary in Santa Clara deceived their way into a meeting at Facebook attended by Huawei competitors, suit claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerable Dems Dodge Questions: 'Lost Voice', 'On Phone'..</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/senate/396410-dems-grasp-for-way-to-stop-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats went on the attack Tuesday against President Trump’s new pick for the Supreme Court, but acknowledged they are unlikely to win the war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rangers capture mammoth crocodile after decade-long hunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/science/rangers-capture-mammoth-crocodile-after-decadelong-hunt/news-story/0340de36849cee5787f34c5391385976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CROCS in the Northern Territory aren’t rare — but they are at this size.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YORK: Special Counsel Tenuous Link Between Trump, Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-mueller-reveals-tenuous-link-between-manafort-charges-and-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's often been observed that special counsel Robert Mueller, assigned to investigate alleged Trump-Russia collusion in the 2016 presidential campaign, has yet to charge anyone with a crime involving Trump-Russia collusion in the 2016 presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming battles 'racist, sexist' charges of Cowboy slogan...</title>
      <link>https://trib.com/news/local/education/faculty-criticize-use-of-cowboy-in-uw-slogan-as-sexist/article_f312ad4f-0bec-5054-9358-a61ca7ab73c5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faculty groups are criticizing a new University of Wyoming marketing campaign built around the image of a cowboy, saying its proposed slogan is sexist and promotes a white, heterosexual stereotype.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh Woos Senators as Battle Kicks Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/kavanaugh-nomination-kicks-off-parallel-fights-in-divided-senate-1531225802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Brett Kavanaugh launched his courtship Tuesday of the senators who will determine whether he ascends to the Supreme Court, the first salvo of the summer’s fiercest political battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Buys Print Ads To Counter 'Fake News' On WHATSAPP...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1324828/its-so-hard-to-fight-fake-news-on-whatsapp-that-in-india-facebook-is-buying-newspaper-ads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When messages are encrypted, battling misinformation is even harder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mueller Team, FBI served up Manafort reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/10/how-muellers-team-and-the-fbi-served-up-paul-manaf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI and Justice Department officials gave Associated Press reporters a green light on information they gathered which ended up in a negative story on former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada to become first state to use fetanyl in execution...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jul/10/nevada-fentanyl-execution-opioid-crisis-drug-death-row</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Questions raised about whether the state’s department of corrections broke the law to obtain the drug, which is at the heart of the US opioid epidemic</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
