<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DOUBLE AGENT: Brit arrested for 'spying for Putin' in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15837275/brit-embassy-worker-arrested-spy-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRIT working at the UK Embassy in Berlin has been arrested on suspicion of passing secrets to Russia. Scotland Yard said the 57-year old was arrested as part of a joint investigation between its …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The judge upending CA gun laws: 'Blessed' jurist or 'stone-cold ideologue'?</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/the-judge-upending-california-s-gun-laws-blessed-jurist-or-stone-cold-ideologue/article_685667a2-ba22-5abc-a3d3-73dc4ed22018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For nearly two decades, U.S. District Judge Roger T. Benitez was a low-profile jurist handling routine immigration and drug cases in San Diego federal court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continued problems after massive beach sewage spill now hitting water supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/continued-problems-after-massive-beach-sewage-spill-now-hitting-water-supply-amid-drought/article_b97f70db-0a55-5a4d-9590-1aa700429224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES – Problems at a Los Angeles sewage treatment plant that caused a massive sewage spill into Santa Monica Bay last month have severely reduced the region's water recycling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal shelter puts lonely pets on TINDER...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210811134103-sgfll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY-PETS (TV, PIX):A purrfect match! Animal shelter puts lonely pets on Tinder</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Most Prefer To Get Revenge On Others Immediately...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/revenge-serve-hot-and-fast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;58 percent of participants preferred to take immediate revenge, even if it meant dealing a lesser blow to an enemy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of white people in USA declines first time in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9881353/Minorities-drive-population-growth-number-white-people-declines-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data, set to be released on August 12, will reveal just how much the ethnic and racial make up of the nation has shifted over the past decade, with Hispanic and Asian populations on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Cuomo Hemorrhages Female Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/chris-andrew-cuomo-cnn-female-viewers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week's ratings took a tumble compared to this time last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOFUNDME topped $200K after woman said she and kids faced eviction. Then real mom came forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/a-gofundme-topped-200k-after-a-woman-said-she-and-her-kids-faced-eviction-then-their-real-mom-came-forward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dasha Kelly's online fundraiser caught the attention of many sympathetic people and media such as CNN. Money was flying in until the truth came out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German nurse injected patients with saline instead of vaccines, sparking fury...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-german-nurse-injected-patients-with-saline-instead-of-coronavirus-vaccines-sparking-fury/ar-AANbUwf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 9,000 people who may have been given bogus shots in the spring will be offered new vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sickos can plant porn on iPhone...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3452390/iphone-airdrop-apple-block-strangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PERVS can put pornography on your iPhone by exploiting one of the gadget’s best features. We reveal how to stop people taking advantage of this handy trick. Read all the latest Phones &amp; G…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China brutal death row with mobile injection vans, firing squads...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3452791/china-death-row-canadian-diplomat-sentenced-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CANADIAN man is set to join hundreds of shackled inmates on China’s degrading death row as they await agonising lethal injections or firing squads. Robert Schellenberg, believed to be 38, from Ab…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Abbott lacks predecessor star power. Yet nobody even close to him in gov race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/08/11/gov-greg-abbott-texas-502135</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Governor Greg Abbott lacks his predecessors’ star power. He’s constantly dodging attacks from the right. His state is facing another Covid surge. Yet nobody is even close to him in the governor’s race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy, 13, duct taped to seat after 'trying to kick out window' on flight...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/08/10/caught-on-camera-teenage-passenger-restrained-on-flight-from-maui-to-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American Airlines flight from Maui to Los Angeles was diverted to Honolulu after a 13-year-old boy became disruptive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elder outspoken conservative radio rhetoric under scrutiny in recall election...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/story/2021-08-10/larry-elder-views-newsom-recall-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Elder leapfrogs the others vying to replace Newsom, with provocative stances from firing teachers to downplaying the dangers of secondhand smoke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA new challenge to reaching moon: $1 billion spacesuit program...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/nasa-has-a-new-challenge-to-reaching-the-moon-by-2024-its-241-billion-spacesuit-program/ar-AANbzgC </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer prices rise 5.4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/11/cpi-report-july-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists surveyed by Dow Jones expected the Labor Department to report the consumer-price index rose 5.3% in July from a year earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA Awards Secret $10 Billion Contract to AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/it-modernization/2021/08/nsa-awards-secret-10-billion-contract-amazon/184390/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the NSA’s most prized intelligence data may be moving to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANCHIN: IRRESPONSIBLE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210811114919-j026v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/INFRASTRUCTURE-MANCHIN (URGENT):U.S. Democratic Senator Manchin objects to $3.5 trln spending bill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDI Skysphere two cars in one...</title>
      <link>https://electrek.co/2021/08/10/audis-new-skysphere-concept-is-two-cars-in-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;electrek.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Audi's new Skysphere concept may never make it to production, but it has some incredibly cool ideas we hope to see more of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heaven can wait, maybe, but not phone call for pope...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-europe-religion-4ecf10f1cd7a4a2ba93bf0f5210a97ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Maybe heaven can wait, but a phone call for the pope could not. In a decidedly unusual break from protocol, Pope Francis took a cellphone from an aide while standing at center stage in a Vatican auditorium for his weekly Wednesday audience with the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hochul to become NY's first female governor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-health-coronavirus-pandemic-cf6794c4cf5a82d6be7739009b8fe8fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — Kathy Hochul, a western New York Democrat unfamiliar to many people in the state even after six years as its lieutenant governor, was set to begin reintroducing herself to the public Wednesday as she prepared to take the reins of power after Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercise Vigorously for 4 Seconds. Repeat. Muscles May Thank You...</title>
      <link>https://lightlynews.com/2021/08/11/health/exercise-vigorously-for-four-seconds-repeat-your-muscles-may-thank-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lightlynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise Vigorously for four Seconds. Repeat. Your Muscles May Thank You. - LIGHTLYNEWS.COM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Women Muscle In on World of Vintage Cars...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/11/more-women-muscle-in-on-the-world-of-vintage-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caroline Cassini, now 29, may have startled some neighbors in West Orange, N.J., when she announced that, rather than applying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest Warrants Issued for TX Dems Who Fled Over Voting-Rights Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/08/10/texas-house-arrest-warrants-democrats-quorum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Supreme Court earlier Tuesday ruled that Democrats who refuse to show up could be detained by law enforcement and brought back to the state Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii to reimpose rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hawaii-reimpose-covid-19-restrictions-delta-variant-surges-2021-08-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii will re-impose COVID-19 restrictions limiting social gatherings to avert straining the state's healthcare, Governor David Ige said on Tuesday, as the rapid spread of the Delta variant of the coronavirus pushed cases and hospitalizations in the United States to a six-month high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In blistering drought, California farmers rip up precious almond trees...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-08-blistering-drought-california-farmers-rip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crushed by a devastating drought and new water restrictions, Daniel Hartwig had no choice but to pull thousands of precious, fragrant almond trees from his California farm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban now controls two-thirds of Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-taliban-e2c0e7b46c03cebb4fdddca309e005e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban seized three more provincial capitals in Afghanistan and a local army headquarters in a blitz across the country’s northeast, officials said Wednesday, with the insurgents now controlling some two-thirds of the nation as the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LQzmCrZ6BUw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US DEBT NEARS $29 TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.usdebtclock.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usdebtclock.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  FOX IN TALKS TO BUY TMZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/warnermedia-in-talks-to-sell-tmz-to-fox/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T continues to pare down media assets ahead of WarnerMedia-Discovery merger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW WORLD ORDER:   Kissinger &amp;  Schmidt Plan Treatise on Artificial Intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/08/10/henry-kissinger-eric-schmidts-big-treatise-on-artificial-intelligence-panned-in-early-important-book-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who knew? Henry Kissinger, age 97, has written a new book. One of his two co-authors is former Google chief Eric Schmidt. Little, Brown has “The Age of A.I.: And our Human Future” set f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean Up After Fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ny-e2-80-99s-first-female-governor-must-clean-up-after-cuomo-fallout/ar-AAN9UUW?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Kathy Hochul becomes New York’s governor in two weeks, cleaning up after Andrew Cuomo will be only one of her newfound problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STILL FACES IMPEACHMENT?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cuomo-may-still-face-n-y-impeachment-to-keep-him-from-running/ar-AANabNj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Governor Andrew Cuomo, who resigned Tuesday in the aftermath of multiple sexual-harassment allegations, may still face impeachment if only to keep him from running for office again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TODD:  CAN MAKE COMEBACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chuck-todd-suggests-andrew-cuomo-can-make-political-comeback-mere-minutes-after-his-resignation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chuck Todd reacted to Andrew Cuomo's resignation by assessing that the New York governor's decision to step down is a matter of pure political calculus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST 3 GOVS LEFT OFFICE AMID SCANDAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/new-yorks-last-three-governors-democrats-leave-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo will be replaced by Lt. Gov. Kathy Hochul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Cuomo pardon himself?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/andrew-cuomo-pardon-himself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo on Tuesday announced his resignation effective in two weeks, following a damning sexual harassment investigation by the state attorney general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEPSI releasing alcoholic Mountain Dew...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/pepsico-and-boston-beer-co-to-create-alcoholic-mountain-dew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alcoholic Mountain Dew is set to hit shelves in early 2022 in a collaboration with PepsiCo and Boston Beer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire house burns as firefighters battle Dixie Inferno...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/dixie-fire-destroys-fire-station-while-volunteer-crews-battle-blaze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indian Valley Fire Rescue Department was destroyed by the Dixie Fire while the volunteer firefighters were trying to save homes in the Greenville area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE ANDREW FACING MORE ACCUSATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9881139/Prince-Andrew-seen-Balmoral-supported-ex-wife-Fergie-day-sued-New-York.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York's convoy made a quick entrance to his mother's Scottish Highlands estate just after 6pm, a day he was sued in New York for allegedly sexually abusing Epstein victim Virginia Roberts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO STEPS ASIDE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/10/politics/andrew-cuomo-resigns/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo said that he will resign, relinquishing under extraordinary pressure his decade-long grip on power and heading off a potential impeachment by New York's Democratic-led legislature a week after the release of a report by the state attorney general that found he had sexually harassed 11 women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  EU weighs restrictions on American tourists, while U.S. says avoid Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/So-much-for-post-pandemic-travel-E-U-weighs-16377759.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS - The summer started on a hopeful note. Coronavirus cases were falling, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban eye full control of northern Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.arabnews.com/node/1908666/world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arabnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm warnings issued for Caribbean islands; Florida on Alert...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/florida-put-on-alert-for-developing-tropical-system/996922</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just over a month after Elsa struck the Sunshine State, AccuWeather forecasters are saying a strengthening system will approach the state with potential impacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIACOMCBS waiting for other suitors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/10/viacomcbs-waiting-for-other-suitors-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shari Redstone is hitting pause on any potential partnership talks between her media company ViacomCBS and NBC owner Comcast in hopes of lining up more suitors, The Post has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empire State Dynasty Sputters Out...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/10/andrew-cuomo-resigns-as-governor-of-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo resigned amid a barrage of sexual harassment allegations a year after he was hailed for his leadership during the darkest days of COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House escalates battle with DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-house-escalates-battle-with-republican-governors-over-masking-in-schools-224251633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration said Tuesday that school districts across the nation should follow federal masking guidelines, even if that means resisting Republican governors who have enacted measures prohibiting districts from establishing mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin blames 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tragic-day-alec-baldwin-blames-180500756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor tweeted his views following the governor’s resignation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hochul to become NY's first female governor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/factbox-cuomos-replacement-kathy-hochul-161638547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hochul, a former Democratic congresswoman who has served as lieutenant governor since 2015, will take over from Cuomo until his third four-year term in office ends in December 2022. -- Cuomo asked Hochul, a rising star in the Democratic Party, to join the gubernatorial ticket in 2014 after the then-lieutenant governor, Robert Duffy, announced he would not seek another term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell joins Dems to pass Biden infrastructure...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/mcconnell-joins-democrats-voting-pass-12-trillion-infrastructure-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bill moves to the Democratic-led House for consideration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only  Quarter of Office Crowd Now Working From Home...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/only-quarter-office-crowd-now-154801009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In July, roughly 25% of managers and professional workers teleworked at some point because of the pandemic, the lowest since the government started tracking the data in May 2020. It’s a clear sign that the age-old work compact is mostly intact, and that the office model is far from defunct.The July number is down from 41% in January and 57% in May of last year, according to data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, which tallies the number of employed who teleworked or worked at h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Driver bites off man's nipple in road rage...</title>
      <link>https://cwbchicago.com/2021/08/man-bit-off-motorists-nipple-during-road-rage-clash-on-lake-shore-drive-prosecutors-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cwbchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago man battered an off-duty CPD officer and bit the nipple off the cop's buddy during a road rage incident Sunday night on Lake Shore Drive, prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>69-30 vote in Senate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/senate-infrastructure-bill-politics-joe-biden-a431f8c9f3f113b661cb3526512fc4e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With a robust vote after weeks of fits and starts, the Senate approved a $1 trillion infrastructure plan for states coast to coast on Tuesday,  as a rare coalition of Democrats and Republicans joined together to overcome skeptics and deliver a cornerstone of President Joe Biden’s agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAINTAINS INNOCENCE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-resigns-17161f546bb83c32a337036ecf8d2a34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Gov. Andrew Cuomo announced his resignation Tuesday over a barrage of sexual harassment allegations in a fall from grace a year after he was widely hailed nationally for his detailed daily briefings and leadership during some of the darkest days of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did archaeologists find the Trojan Horse?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/did-archaeologists-just-find-the-trojan-horse-676349</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish archaeologists excavating the site of the city of Troy on the hills of Hisarlik have discovered a large wooden structure that they believe are the remains of the famous Trojan Horse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro flexes muscles with military parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210810-brazil-s-bolsonaro-flexes-muscles-with-military-parade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's Bolsonaro flexes muscles with military parade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech-savvy teens falling prey to online scams faster than grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/10/tech-savvy-teens-falling-prey-to-online-scams-faster-than-their-grandparents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of individuals under age 21 reporting that they've been victims of cyber-fraud has surged 156% over the last three years, a study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We rented CA vacation home and got spied on by surveillance camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/California-vacation-rental-surveillance-camera-law-16346246.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you pull up to your vacation rental, you might be greeted by a surveillance camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Mask Mandate May Be in Effect Through Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/dc-mask-mandate-may-be-in-effect-through-thanksgiving-if-vaccinations-dont-increase/2767657/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;D.C. health officials hope the indoor mask mandate can be dropped by Thanksgiving — but that may not be possible if the numbers don’t improve.  As D.C. enters its second week of a new mask mandate and the delta variant spreads, the number of people getting tested at pop-up testing sites has jumped. The number of new cases is rising…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod man catches Great White Shark...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2021/08/09/watch-cape-cod-man-catches-great-white-shark/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Pieciak caught a shark while fishing at Nauset Beach in Orleans on Sunday, according to a video he posted on instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBIN COMES OUT AS BISEXUAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/08/10/robin-comes-out-bisexual-dc-comics-batman-urban-legends-series/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robin comes out as bisexual in DC Comics series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting Machine Tampering Coming From Inside The MAGA House...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/voting-machine-tampering-is-coming-from-inside-the-maga-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The truth is, these are not very bright guys, and things got out of hand.” – Hal Holbrook After months of being promised by the former President and his stooges that Dominion Voting Systems had RIGGED the election, we finally have our first credible investigation into voting machine tampering. The lede in Monday’s Grand Junction […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going door-to-door dragging out girls as young as 12 to make them sex slaves'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3448281/taliban-grabbing-girls-sex-slaves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Taliban are “going to door to door” to round up young girls to be “sex slaves” to fighters in the terror group, reports claim. An inside source suggests that Taliban leaders are att…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$611 Million Stolen in Massive Hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/611-million-cryptocurrencies-stolen-massive-hack-1617999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We will take legal actions and we urge the hackers to return the assets," Poly Network tweeted in a thread. The hack has been labeled the largest DeFi hack in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China weighs whether to abandon Covid zero-tolerance approach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/china-weighs-whether-abandon-covid-zero-tolerance-approach-n1276333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Even if you can lock down all the regions in China, people might still die, and more might die due to hunger," a Yale University health economist says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst governor during pandemic? Lot of candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/melinda-henneberger-the-worst-governor-during-this-pandemic-there-are-a-lot-of-candidates/ar-AAN8Y28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of the 18 months since Americans began dying of COVID-19, some of my friends in Missouri, Texas and Florida have been arguing about which of us has the worst wartime governor in the country. Missouri’s Mike Parson got off to a fast start, doing nothing at first, and as little as possible ever since: By April 1, 2020, according to a state compilation of every action taken by every ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon scraps requirement for high school students to read, write...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9879959/Oregon-scraps-requirement-high-school-students-prove-proficiency-math-reading-writing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Oregon has suspended its requirement that high school students demonstrate a proficiency in math, writing and reading in order to receive a diploma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Banana republic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/10/bolsonaro-banana-republic-military-parade-condemned-by-critics-brazil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanks roll through streets of Brasília as congress prepares to vote on plans to change Brazil’s voting system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student proves TWITTER algorithm bias toward lighter, slimmer, younger faces...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/aug/10/twitters-image-cropping-algorithm-prefers-younger-slimmer-faces-with-lighter-skin-analysis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company pays $3,500 to Bogdan Kulynych who demonstrated flaw in image cropping software</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks battle to protect town from ferocious blaze...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/huge-force-struggling-contain-greek-105045534.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteers and firefighters are workinground-the-clock, often without masks or helmets, in a desperate bid to stop a violent blaze from reaching a key town on Greece's Evia island, one of hundreds of fires that have raged through the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamblers lifting casino market to its best year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-39f5928cee71d63ba06549e75b5a70fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — Gamblers anxious to hit the slot machines and table games in person after a year of coronavirus restrictions are lifting the U.S. casino industry to its best year ever. But the great unknown is whether a new, more contagious variant of COVID-19 will slow an industry that is now winning money at a record pace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-caribbean-brazil-74267e007a4c09417d905b5447d16782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASILIA, Brazil (AP) — Brazil's military staged an unusual convoy of troops and armored vehicles through the capital on Tuesday — an event announced only a day before and that coincided with a scheduled vote in Congress on one of President Jair Bolsonaro's key proposals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decline of traditional TV happening fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tokyo-olympics-ratings-spiral-spelling-trouble-for-traditional-tv-7a50241a-6c96-4bec-94f7-b81367c86922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a big long-term problem for NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor responds after officers turn backs on her following cop killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wbbm780/news/local/chicago-cops-turn-backs-on-lightfoot-after-officer-killed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Lori Lightfoot has responded to reports that a group of Chicago police officers turned their backs on her after the murder of a female cop over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire-backed mining firm to seek electric vehicle metals in Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/billionaire-backed-mining-firm-seek-electric-vehicle-metals-greenland-2021-08-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mineral exploration company KoBold Metals, backed by billionaires including Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates, has signed an agreement with London-listed Bluejay Mining (JAY.L) to search in Greenland for critical materials used in electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penélope Cruz Movie Poster Featuring Lactating Nipple Censored on INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/penelope-cruz-movie-poster-featuring-lactating-nipple-censored-instagram-1617842</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A striking poster for "Madres Paralelas" (Parallel Mothers) was recently unveiled, ahead of it opening the Venice Film Festival in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC investigating 2 deaths, 2 illnesses from rare bacterial disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/melioidosis-us-cases-cdc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The source of the infections remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene for vax tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/10/tech/twitter-marjorie-taylor-greene/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has suspended Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene's account for one week following another violation of the platform's rules, the company said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eviction moratorium forces small landlords to consider selling...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/with-tenants-who-won-e2-80-99t-pay-or-leave-small-landlords-face-struggles-of-their-own/ar-AAN9niL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many corporate apartment chains catering to white-collar workers are raising rents and booking enormous profits while some small landlords are giving up and deciding to sell as the eviction moratorium stretches on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another city falls...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldsun.com.au/news/breaking-news/thousands-flee-as-taliban-noose-tightens-around-afghan-north/news-story/54b01324939add545b6ce02d3292b3a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldsun.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban seized another Afghan provincial capital Tuesday -- the seventh in less than a week -- as tens of thousands of people fled their homes in the north for the relative safety of Kabul and other centres.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810140426-j6vax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/ (PIX, TV):Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
