<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bibi Fighting for Political Life... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/israels-election-is-seen-as-a-referendum-on-netanyahu-in-a-country-he-helped-transform-11554638418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s quest for a fifth term has become a referendum on his leadership after two decades in public life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality bites O'Rourke after high-flying kickoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/08/beto-orourke-2020-campaign-1260182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texan is campaigning strong, but he's no longer in the stratosphere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: TECH GIANT TAX DODGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/google-avoided-paying-15bn-tax-14250344</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Internet giant are accused of paying 24 times less corporation tax than they should have done — a major hit to public services</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I bonded with Ted Bundy to make him confess to murders of 30 women'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/real-life-stories/i-bonded-ted-bundy-make-14223691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Michaud, 71, spent months locked in a room intensely interviewing the notorious serial killer in 1976 to get to the harrowing truth of all those murders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLION VIEWERS FOR 'GAME OF THRONES'?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6895775/Game-Thrones-set-one-billion-viewers-worldwide-final-series-airs-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Game Of Thrones returns next week and the smash hit is expected to draw in more than one billion viewers across 170 countries. It comes after venues in Northern Ireland were guarded tightly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangles West Bank Annexation...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/netanyahu-gambles-on-west-bank-annexation-vow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu Gambles on West Bank Annexation Vow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App About Xi Impossible to Ignore -- Even if Try...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/07/world/asia/china-xi-jinping-study-the-great-nation-app.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Chinese are using the app as part of President Xi’s efforts to strengthen ideological control in the digital age. Critics say it fuels a personality cult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran trash pickers make living from billionaire garbage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-Trickle-Down-Economics-of-Trash-Picking-13747019.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three blocks from Mark Zuckerberg's $10 million Tudor home in San Francisco, Jake Orta lives in a small, single-window studio apartment filled with trash.  There's a child's pink bicycle helmet that Orta dug out from the garbage bin across the street from Zuckerberg's house. And a vacuum cleaner, a hair dryer, a coffee machine - all in working condition - and a pile of clothes that he carried home in a Whole Foods paper bag retrieved from Zuckerberg's bin.  A military veteran who fell into homelessness and now lives in government-subsidized housing, Orta is a full-time trash picker, part of an underground economy in San Francisco of people who work the sidewalks in front of multimillion-dollar homes, rummaging for things they can sell.  Trash picking is a profession more often associated with shantytowns and favelas than a city at the doorstep of Silicon Valley. The Global Alliance of Waste Pickers, a nonprofit research and advocacy organization, counts more than 400 trash picking organizations across the globe, almost all of them in Latin America, Africa and southern Asia.  But trash scavengers exist in many U.S. cities and, like the rampant homelessness in San Francisco, are a signpost of the extremes of U.S. capitalism. A snapshot from 2019: One of the world's richest men and a trash picker, living a few minutes' walk from each other.  Orta, 56, sees himself as more of a treasure hunter.  "It just amazes me what people throw away," he said one night, as he found a pair of gently used designer jeans, a new black cotton jacket, gray Nike running sneakers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrutiny and suspicion as Mueller report undergoes redaction...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/scrutiny-and-suspicion-as-mueller-report-undergoes-redaction/ar-BBVHqAa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers have to wear location-tracking bracelets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/4/6/18298562/these-chinese-sanitation-workers-have-to-wear-location-tracking-bracelets-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public pressure barely made a dent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHART: Who owns everything in Big Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.recode.net/2018/1/23/16905844/media-landscape-verizon-amazon-comcast-disney-fox-relationships-chart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.recode.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It probably won’t look like this for long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: 24 shot in 30 hours. Violence back as cold breaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-citywide-shootings-20190407-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three children under age 13 were among 24 people shot — three of them fatally — in a span of about 30 hours from early Saturday to Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Testimony: Assassination Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/455825-assange-assasination-risk-ecuador-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuador will be violating its own constitution if it expels Julian Assange from its London embassy while fully aware of a possible “assassination” plot against him, WikiLeaks suggested, releasing the journalist’s court testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Paper Editor: Media Parroted 'SOUTHERN POVERTY' Releases...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/opinion/2019/04/opinion-southern-poverty-law-center-should-be-investigated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s something strange afoot at one of the nation’s richest civil and human rights charities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio Meets With 7 Voters In Pahrump...</title>
      <link>https://www.ny1.com/nyc/all-boroughs/politics/2019/04/07/de-blasio-visits-nevada-as-decision-to-run-for-president-inches-closer-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ny1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here&amp;#39;s how Nevadans reacted to his message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Space Station teeming with corrosive bacteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/international-space-station-bacteria-fungi-disease-iss-a8858846.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infested with microbes, could carry 'infectious diseases'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1111178/NASA-news-International-Space-Station-bacteria-disease-Mars-Moon-Sun-Space-earth-JPL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE INTERNATIONAL Space Station (ISS) is packed full of bacteria and fungi that could potentially be harmful to astronauts, a new study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: E-cigarette explosion rips away chunk of vaper's face...</title>
      <link>https://www.commercialappeal.com/story/news/2019/04/07/e-cigarette-explodes-memphis-mans-face-lawsuit-says/3232880002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.commercialappeal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The explosion of the vaping device ripped away a chunk of David Bishop's face, burned him, and broke some of his teeth, a lawsuit alleges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Naked woman breaks into daycare, tries to fire employee...</title>
      <link>https://wtkr.com/2019/04/05/naked-woman-found-in-daycare-claims-she-is-owners-wife-tries-to-fire-employees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtkr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 23-year-old woman is behind bars after breaking into a Stafford daycare and being found completely naked by an employee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady arrested in Dubai 'for calling ex-husband wife horse' on social... </title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/04/07/british-mum-arrested-dubai-calling-ex-husbands-wife-horse-facebook-9129707/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laleh Sharavesh, 55, was arrested along with her daughter, 14, for old Facebook comments she made in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  FOXNEWS.COM OVER CNN; DRUDGE TOPS GOOGLE NEWS, NYTIMES; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impossible challenge of tracking visa overstays...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/immigration/story/2019-04-06/the-impossible-challenge-of-tracking-visa-overstays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visa overstays account for an estimated 44 percent of the unauthorized immigrant population in U.S., study shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCMANUS: Stop thinking of  Sanders as gadfly and start thinking of him as front-runner...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/doyle-mcmanus-stop-thinking-of-bernie-sanders-as-a-gadfly/article_36b7f59f-8061-55f5-a3fd-bd8cb4de6326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In case you missed it, Bernie Sanders is now, for all practical purposes, the front-runner in the race for the Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro three-month approval rating a record low for Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brazil-bolsonaro-faces-record-low-154738487.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- An opinion poll shows Jair Bolsonaro is facing the lowest approval rate for a first-term Brazilian president through 100 days among all elected predecessors since the country’s return to democracy in the late 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOMELAND' SEC OUT AFTER BORDER BOTCH</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kirstjen-nielsen-resigning-dhs-secretary-expected-to-offer-resignation-today-live-updates-2019-04-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customs and Border Protection Commissioner Kevin McAleenan will serve as acting DHS secretary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY: Dems will 'never' see president's tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/94d053425cdd485f86fb4d65eb464911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats will "never" see President Donald Trump's tax returns, said White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney on Sunday, as a new front opened in the confrontation between the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran threatens USA over potential Revolutionary Guard terror designation...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/7/iran-threatens-retaliation-over-potential-revoluti/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in Tehran over the weekend vowed retaliation if the Trump administration moves ahead with a plan to label Iran’s Revolutionary Guard a terrorist organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandinavian Banks' Clean Reputations Threatened by Dirty Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/why-scandinavian-banks-clean-reputations-are-threatened-by-dirty-money/ar-BBVG8oJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY: Dems will 'never' see president's tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/437729-mulvaney-democrats-will-never-see-trumps-tax-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney said Sunday that Democrats will "never" see President Trump's tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man fears feds will kill event...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/burningman/article/Burning-Man-begs-festival-goers-to-help-stop-BLM-13746797.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burning Man organizers are pleading with festival-goers to write to the Bureau of Land Management (BLM) and urge them to reconsider a number of new requirements for the festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE: LET FELONS IN PRISON VOTE</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2019/04/06/bernie-sanders-says-states-should-felon-voting-rights-election-2020-iowa-caucus/3388679002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator was asked whether the imprisoned should have the right to vote. Only his home state and Maine allow felons to vote from behind bars. "I think that is absolutely the direction we should go," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65 get pizza shop logo tattooed for free food...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/2019/04/06/blaze-pizza-restaurant-des-moines-iowa-ia-offers-free-pizza-logo-tattoo-flame-twisted-ink/3387288002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $40 flame tattoo comes with 24 free pizzas and the $65 Blaze name logo comes with 48 free pizzas as part of the promotion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats know they need white male voters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/79fefc13c5a54b089da12c7007e98ac8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPPER ST. CLAIR TOWNSHIP, Pa. (AP) — When he moved to Pennsylvania about five years ago, it was a coin toss which party Brian Heitman would register with. No longer. Since Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop shows up intoxicated to breathalyzer training...</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/region/detroit/detroit-police-officer-shows-up-intoxicated-to-msp-breathalyzer-training</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Detroit Police officer is at the center of an internal investigation after he showed up under the influence of alcohol to training in Lansing, Detroit Police Chief James Craig told reporters Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In extreme wildfire era, firefighting aircraft 'increasingly ineffective'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-aircraft-increasingly-ineffective-against-california-wildfires-20190407-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is poised to spend $273 million on new firefighting aircraft, but the tools won't help fight the most devastating kinds of blazes California has seen of late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Surreal' Pyongyang marathon in spotlight as tensions ease...</title>
      <link>https://whtc.com/news/articles/2019/apr/07/athletics-surreal-pyongyang-marathon-in-spotlight-as-tensions-ease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whtc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Karolos Grohmann (Reuters) - North Korea's Pyongyang marathon may be among the most complicated to enter but an easing of tensions on the Korean peninsula has made it a stage to highlight the power of sport amid growing interest for the race. Athletes can only register through one operator, Koryo Tours, for a chance to run through the capital...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE legend attacked by audience member during Hall of Fame speech...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wwes-bret-hart-attacked-man-york-city-hall/story?id=62228075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 26-year-old man was arrested on Saturday for punching Bret "The Hitman" Hart during a Hall of Fame speech at the Barclay Center in Brooklyn, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative takeover of Supreme Court stalled by Roberts-Kavanaugh bromance...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/04/07/supreme-court-bromance-john-roberts-brett-kavanaugh-tie-up-court/3342377002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative takeover of the Supreme Court under Donald Trump is stalled by a bromance between Chief Justice John Roberts and Brett Kavanaugh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhino poacher trampled to death by elephants then eaten by lions...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8807049/rhino-poacher-dead-elephants-lions-kruger-national-park-south-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POACHER hunting rhinos in the Kruger National Park met a gruesome end after being trampled to death by an elephant and then eaten by a pride of hungry lions. Four other poachers who fled the game…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest female python ever captured...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/this-is-the-biggest-female-python-ever-captured-in-the-everglades-big-cypress-researchers-say/ar-BBVGEnb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker dies setting up Coachella Festival...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/worker-dies-fall-setting-coachella-festival-62225759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get breaking national and world news, broadcast video coverage, and exclusive interviews. Find the top news online at ABC news.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
