<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brazilians Grow Angry as Inequality Hits Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/brazilians-grow-unhappy-and-angry-as-inequality-hits-record/ar-AAL4SX3 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NKorea Kim looks much thinner, causing health speculation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-lifestyle-effd61316feab540d6eb1922935ba1e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — The health of North Korean leader Kim Jong Un has long been a source of morbid fascination in rival South Korea, which sits in the shadow of Kim's 1.2-million-strong army and his growing arsenal of nuclear-armed missiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poultry Prices Highest Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.farmprogress.com/poultry/poultry-prices-soar-record-amid-us-chicken-sandwich-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.farmprogress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With multiple fast-food restaurants launching fried-chicken sandwiches, poultry prices jumped to an all-time high in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company ignored warnings launches might not be safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9692065/SpaceX-ignored-warnings-SN8-blastoff-December-not-safe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SN8 successfully launched on December 9 from SpaceX's Boca Chica, Texas testing facility, but ended up crash-landing in a ball of flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can $110 Million Helmet Unlock Secrets of Mind?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-06-16/braintree-founder-s-helmet-size-hospital-aims-to-mine-mind-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bryan Johnson, who made a fortune in online payment processing, has spent a lot of it building hardware meant to radically expand science’s understanding of the brain’s aging and effects on the body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC grapples with growing presence of homeless in midtown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210616084957-tdu3x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK-HOMELESS/ (TV, PIX):New York grapples with growing presence of homeless in midtown Manhattan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Lode of $100 Billion Stirs Worry Over Hidden Danger...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-lode-100-billion-stirs-060000168.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Follow @crypto Twitter for the latest news.Regulators are worried about hidden risks to investors and even the financial system stemming from a fast-growing corner of the crypto market meant to be immune from volatility.Their focus is on so-called stablecoins, a form of cryptocurrency that has a fixed price, typically one dollar, and is backed by real-money reserves.At the end of May, the total market capitalization of stablecoins, which include ones offered by crypto firms Tether</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR GAMES HAWAII: USA scrambles strike group to face off with Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3091412/us-fighter-jets-russian-war-games-biden-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US scrambled F-22 fighter jets and a carrier strike group to face off with Russian war games near Hawaii ahead of a showdown meeting between Vladimir Putin and Joe Biden, it was revealed on Tue…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titanic clash pits Desantis against potent cruise industry as it prepares to restart...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/tourism-cruises/article252054773.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The return of operations for one of South Florida’s most iconic industries has turned into a battle of the heavyweights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Exercise Adds Up to Big Health Care Savings...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/16/lifelong-exercise-adds-up-to-big-health-care-savings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Becoming more physically active today might help us avoid thousands of dollars in health care costs later, according to a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Exec Could Face Charges This Summer...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/15/trump-executive-could-face-charges-as-soon-as-this-summer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney’s office appears to have entered the final stages of a criminal tax investigation into Donald J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN GENEVA</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-europe-summits-government-and-politics-23e73d69f1a7ca338850736a9cf032f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — U.S. President Joe Biden and Russia's Vladimir Putin sit down Wednesday for their highly anticipated summit in the Swiss city of Geneva, a moment of high-stakes diplomacy at a time when both leaders agree that relations between their countries are at an all-time low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives Cheer Jon Stewart For Backing Wuhan Lab Leak Theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/conservatives-takes-a-victory-lap-after-jon-stewart-backs-lab-leak-theory-on-the-late-shows-return-online-leftists-seem-big-mad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservatives were quite pleased with Jon Stewart's advancement of the coronavirus lab leak theory in The Late Show's first post-pandemic episode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fifth of asymptomatic patients develop long Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210615-a-fifth-of-asymptomatic-covid-patients-develop-long-covid-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fifth of asymptomatic Covid patients develop long Covid: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods seen for first time since crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9689455/Tiger-Woods-seen-hobbling-crutches-four-months-horror-car-crash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In photographs exclusively obtained by DailyMail.com, the golfing legend, 45, was spotted arriving at a Los Angeles airport via private jet on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Plagued By Fires Started By Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/14/rash-of-homeless-encampment-fires-continues-across-southland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents and business owners are growing frustrated and worried about the rash of homeless encampment fires that have been seen across the Southland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed Cameras Churn Out Hundreds Of Thousands Of Tickets After Rule Change...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/06/15/chicagos-speed-cameras-churn-out-hundreds-of-thousands-of-tickets-after-rule-change-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid In USA by Christmas '19...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/more-evidence-covid-in-us-by-christmas-2019-11346afc5e18eee81ebcf35d9e6caee2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A new analysis of blood samples from 24,000 Americans taken early last year is the latest and largest study to suggest that the new coronavirus popped up in the U.S. in December 2019 — weeks before cases were first recognized by health officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden Art to Hit Market -- Up to $500,000 Per Piece!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2021/06/14/hunter-biden-art-is-for-sale-for-up-to-500000-per-piece/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His art dealer plans to mount a solo show in New York this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein to be extradited to CA to face sex charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/harvey-weinstein-be-extradited-california-face-sexual-assault-charges-judge-n1270933</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former movie mogul and convicted rapist, currently serving time in a New York prison, faces 11 sexual assault counts in California involving five women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Says Systems Restored After 1,400 Flights Disrupted...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/southwest-says-systems-restored-after-1400-flights-disrupted/ar-AAL4H1T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines Co. said systems have been restored after the second disruption in a matter of hours forced the company to cancel or delay more than 1,400 flights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN GENEVA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-swaggers-toward-summit-with-biden-as-an-old-hand-at-dueling-with-the-west/ar-AAL41Hg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an NBC television interview ahead of the Geneva meeting, the Russian president was dismissive and nonchalant about issues of U.S. concern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE China censoring LGBT apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/china/china-app-store-lgbtq-censorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The App Store enables government censorship of LGBTQ+ apps in 152 countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parachuting protester crash lands European soccer game...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/06/15/france-vs-germany-greenpeace-protestor-nearly-crashes-into-fans-during-euro-2020-match-14778134/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protestor's parachute collided with the stadium's spider camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP will no longer name suspects in minor crime stories...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/558566-ap-will-no-longer-name-suspects-in-minor-crime-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press said Tuesday that it will no longer name suspects in minor crime stories that only cover an arrest with no follow-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond California, record year for recalls...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/558574-beyond-california-a-record-year-for-recalls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters across the country are moving to recall their elected officials at an unprecedented pace, driven in part by a backlash against restrictions imposed during the coronavirus pandemic and in part by anger at officials who have run afoul of culture war issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran faces worst drug epidemic ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/fentanyl-San-Francisco-overdose-drug-epidemic-16237333.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We talked to the head of emergency medicine at Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composer Condemned Arson. Now No One Will Hire Him...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/06/15/daniel-elder-cancel-culture-choral-composer-antifa-blm-gia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I chose to be that guy who didn't issue the apology," says Daniel Elder. "Things went from there and it wasn't good."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Lift Most Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-momentous-day-new-york-lifts-most-virus-restrictions/ar-AAL4vNN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurants will no longer be forced to space tables six feet apart or use physical partitions; movie theaters will be allowed to pack their auditoriums without spacing seats apart; and entering commercial buildings won’t require a temperature check. With 70 percent of adults in New York having received at least one dose of a coronavirus vaccine, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo said on Tuesday that effective immediately the state was ready to “return to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIGHTFOOT UNHINGED...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mayor-lori-lightfoot-says-email-ripping-aide-over-lack-of-office-time-that-drew-comparisons-to-a-scene-in-the-shining-was-born-out-of-frustration/ar-AAL2nfV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Lori Lightfoot on Monday said a much-circulated email in which she berated an aide was “born out of frustration” and she’s now in “a better place” with her team. In late January, Lightfoot sent her then-scheduler an email complaining that she doesn’t get enough of what she called “office time.” That’s typically a less structured part of the day when the mayor can think, write or make ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crayfish take more risks while on antidepressants...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210615-crayfish-take-more-risks-while-on-antidepressants-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crayfish take more risks while on antidepressants, study shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filth and feces growing problem on NYC subways...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/filth-and-feces-report-finds-increase-in-dirty-subway-cars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As people return to the subway system they are finding more trash and filth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA,</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/15/us/california-reopening-15th/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California lifted most of its Covid-19 restrictions Tuesday as part of a grand reopening in which the state will end capacity limits, physical distancing and -- at least for those vaccinated -- mask requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust pioneer confirmed as FTC commissioner...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/15/22527709/lina-khan-ftc-commissioner-competition-facebook-amazon-google-apple</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move follows a slate of tech competition bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lin-Manuel Miranda Apologizes For Lack Of Afro-Latinx Actors In 'HEIGHTS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/15/1006606967/lin-manuel-miranda-apologizes-for-lack-of-afro-latinx-actors-in-in-the-heights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a Twitter message, the co-creator of In The Heights wrote: "In trying to paint a mosaic of this community, we fell short. I'm truly sorry."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-lawmaker insisted sister-in-law murdered in trailer. Now she's been killed at same site...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ex-lawmaker-insisted-her-sister-in-law-was-16248525.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grassy property surrounding a charred trailer had grown wild over the past six months...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua spirals deeper into repression...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/nicaragua-spirals-deeper-into-repression-as-ortega-jails-rivals-and-former-allies/ar-AAL4jLs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicaragua's President Daniel Ortega stepped up attacks on his political opponents over the weekend by arresting five leading critics, including three former allies who fought alongside him during the Sandinista revolution, as he continues to suppress the opposition ahead of presidential elections in November. Defying U.S. demands for the immediate release of four presidential candidates ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashier slaughtered in supermarket for telling man to wear mask...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/14/woman-killed-in-supermarket-for-telling-man-to-wear-a-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was shot dead after telling a man to put on a mask at a Big Bear supermarket in DeKalb, Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>onald Pressed Official to Wield DOJ to Back Election Claims...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/15/trump-pressed-official-to-wield-justice-dept-to-back-election-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — An hour before President Donald J. Trump announced in December that William P. Barr would step down as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>899 people got expired vaccine at Times Square site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nyc-state-wire-ny-state-wire-health-coronavirus-pandemic-sports-3af5dc68742fa13bfed9804ef54e3553</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Nearly 900 people received expired COVID-19 vaccine doses at a vaccination site in Times Square this month, health officials said Tuesday. The 899 people who received doses of the Pfizer vaccine at the former NFL Experience building in Times Square between June 5 and June 10 should schedule another Pfizer shot as soon as possible, the New York City Health Department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Waters turns down 'huge money' for FACEBOOK ad: 'No f--kin' way'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/15/pink-floyds-roger-waters-turns-down-big-bucks-for-facebook-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The co-founding member of Pink Floyd turned “little p–k” Mark Zuckerberg down flat — with a cantankerously foulmouthed touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic stars could be 'deported and stripped of their medals' if they break Japan quarantine rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3087404/team-gb-deportation-japan-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEAM GB athletes have been threatened with strict SIX-day hotel quarantine spells when they arrive in Tokyo for next month’s Olympics. And all athletes taking part in the Games have been warned the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL BLAST:  Death Valley to come within 10 degrees of all-time world record high temp!  Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/record-smashing-heat-wave-poised-to-send-temps-even-higher/963033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of record highs have been set already this week, and the heat is only forecast to intensify. One city could break a record for consecutive days above 115 F, while Death Valley may come fairly close to its world record high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgruntled fire hydrant factory worker shoots co-workers, kills self...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9688459/Police-Alabama-fire-hydrant-plant-worker-kills-2-wounds-2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worker at a fire hydrant plant in Alabama pulled out a gun and began firing early Tuesday, killing two people and wounding two more, before going on the run and shooting himself dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: American workers among most stressed in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/15/gallup-us-workers-are-among-the-most-stressed-in-the-world.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gallup's latest State of the Global Workplace report captures how employees are feeling about work and life in the last year of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacKenzie Scott Donates Another $2.7 Billion, Blasts Wealth Gap...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-philanthropy-business-8e06be7452b8c70f0d9802a6c10ca6a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MacKenzie Scott, the billionaire philanthropist known for her impromptu multi-billion dollar donations to charities and racial equity issues, announced Tuesday that she has given $2.7 billion to 286 organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed at DISNEY WORLD: More tourists caught with concealed guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/armed-at-disney-world-more-tourists-caught-with-concealed-guns-during/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Planning to go to a firing range later, Mustafa Alameen, an Iraqi immigrant, said he forgot he had 100 rounds of ammunition and a handgun in an otherwise empty stroller when he arrived at Disney Springs this year. The 21-year-old stepped through the security detector and when an alar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Fatigue? Number of Services Per User Falls for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/streaming-services-number-user-fatigue-1234967952/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average number of video streaming services utilized per U.S. user has fallen for the first time, according to technology research firm Omdia. In a Tuesday report, it said the figure declined fr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Sends 28 Planes Near Taiwan in Largest Exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/china-sends-28-warplanes-near-taiwan-in-years-largest-exercise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is China's largest sortie to Taipei as the island seeks to strengthen ties with the US.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech issues hit three airlines, grounding flights...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/558438-tech-issues-hit-three-us-airlines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three U.S. airlines were hit with technical issues on Monday that caused flight delays and hampered ticket purchases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Mike Lindell Can't Stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/06/15/mike-lindell-mypillow-trump-election-conspiracy-494302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MyPillow tycoon has lost business pumping up Trump conspiracy theories, and probably lost his chance at a political future. But he believes he’s on a divine mission to overturn the election—and he’s not alone.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
