<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pilot for AMERICAN arrested at Louisville airport for 2015 triple homicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdrb.com/news/pilot-for-american-airlines-arrested-at-louisville-airport-for-triple/article_a0e33820-73c4-11e9-9dd5-5fd5311b436d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdrb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian Richard Martin was arrested early Saturday morning at the airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign policy setbacks raising questions; 'We're courting danger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/05/11/trump-foreign-policy-foiled-amid-new-crises-iran-north-korea-venezuela/1158106001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has suffered a series of stunning foreign policy setbacks this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's status of the wall?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/05/10/trump-wants-border-wall-what-status-its-construction/1145825001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's signature campaign promise was the construction of a wall on the southern border. Is the wall being built?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/05/11/severe-weather-houston-faces-more-flooding-la-state-emergency/1174543001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a one day break from heavy rain, water-logged Houston braced for another round from a lingering storm system that hasÂ prompted the governor of Louisiana to declare a state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside HUAWEI where staff forced to sleep under desk on 'endless' shifts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9051537/huawei-campus-pictures-factory-china-5g-spy-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE fascinating pictures show the grim reality of life inside Huawei’s £1.2bn research and development centre – where exhausted employees sleep at their desks and endure endless gruel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant, proud Cuba gay rights activists take to streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/12/cubas-gay-rights-activists-take-to-the-streets-defiant-and-proud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gay pride parade in Cuba’s capital goes ahead despite official march being banned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of rage: Are we really living in angrier times?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/may/11/all-fired-up-are-we-really-living-angrier-times</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a world in which populists whip up anger that spreads on social media, it’s easy to conclude we have never been more furious</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Sex Lives of Nuns...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-secret-sex-lives-of-nuns </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The question of sex in the sanctuary is not always one of victimization for women. What is certain is that it is complicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LORD OF AMAZON WANTS MOON'S WATER</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/05/jeff-bezos-moon-nasa/589150/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon CEO unveiled a sleek-looking lunar lander—and he hopes the White House takes notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: How Much Coffee Too Much? 6 Cups In Day Bad For Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drinking-six-cups-coffee-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's no shortage of research showing how drinking coffee is good for health, but is there a point where consuming too much can be harmful?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden entry provides jolt to Bernie candidacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Biden-s-entry-into-the-Democratic-race-provides-a-13838004.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's been no more consistent performer in the field of Democratic presidential candidates than Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt. From the day he first announced his candidacy in the spring of 2015 straight on through to today, as he makes his second run for the White House, his message has remained constant, his style has varied not at all. Bernie is Bernie.  The policy ideas he put forward in the 2016 race, during his surprisingly strong challenge to Hillary Clinton, have become more broadly accepted within the Democratic Party. He has defined and expanded the party's progressive wing and given voice to liberals who found Barack Obama's presidency disappointing for its timidity in areas of policy. He has made the words "democratic socialism" part of the political lexicon.  Sanders has redefined presidential fundraising, demonstrating in 2016 that the traditional approach of relying on wealthy individuals to write checks for the maximum allowed under the law and building a big team of bundlers who would raise hundreds of thousands of campaign dollars through their personal networks wasn't the only way. Sanders showed that small but regular contributions from hundreds of thousands of people can fuel and sustain an underdog candidacy.  The senator from Vermont's first-quarter performance - financially, politically and rhetorically - helped establish him as a power in the contest for the nomination. As the Democratic field took shape in those earlier months, he became the biggest name and impressed some of the skeptics who discounted him.  But Sanders is no longer the biggest name in the field. That title now goes to former Vice President Joe Biden, who became a candidate just two weeks ago. His entry into the 2020 fray and the initial impact of his candidacy have pointed to questions about the trajectory of Sanders' candidacy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI interrogates...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-reporter-declined-to-reveal-his-source-Then-13838421.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bryan Carmody, a freelance reporter in San Francisco, awoke Friday to the sounds of someone trying to break into his house.  About 10 officers from the San Francisco Police Department were bashing the front gate of his Outer-Richmond home with a sledgehammer, he said. It was just after 8 o'clock in the morning.  Carmody called out and said he would let them into the house. The officers showed him a search warrant, and proceeded to go through his home - from "top to bottom" he says - with their guns drawn.  "They treated me like I was some kind of drug dealer," he said in an interview with The Washington Post.  Carmody was being raided in connection with a criminal investigation.  Two weeks before, police investigators showed up at his home to ask him, politely he says, to identify the source who provided him with a confidential police report about the February death of the city's public defender, Jeff Adachi. Carmody, who said he worked with three local television news stations on the story, declined.  He wasn't about to give up his source on Friday either, despite the escalation - not to the police, or two FBI agents in suits who questioned him about the case, he said.  "I'm smart enough not to talk to federal agents, ever," Carmody said. "I just kept saying, 'lawyer, lawyer, lawyer.' "  So he stayed handcuffed for the next six hours, he says - a certificate of release he distributed from the police department says he was in custody from 8:22 a.m. until 1:55 p.m. - as investigators searched his home, and then his office, where they found the report in a safe. A search warrant filed in the case notes that it was issued as police investigated "stolen or embezzled property."  "There's only two people on this planet who know who leaked this report - me and the guy who leaked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran police raid journalist to find leaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfexaminer.com/the-city/san-francisco-police-raid-home-of-journalist-to-find-leak-in-adachi-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Guards chief says USA started 'psychological war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran/iran-guards-chief-says-americans-have-started-psychological-war-idUSKCN1SI056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has started a psychological war in the region, the commander o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida takes shape as Joe firewall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/11/joe-biden-florida-1317604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president is crushing the Democratic field in the nation’s third-largest state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Heartbeat' Abortion Bans Advancing in South, Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/national-international/Heartbeat-Abortion-Bans-South-Midwest-509800251.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a new Mississippi law survives a court challenge, it will be nearly impossible for most pregnant women to get an abortion there. Or, potentially, in neighboring Louisiana. Or Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police using facial recognition daily -- raising privacy concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/how-facial-recognition-became-routine-policing-tool-america-n1004251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology is proliferating amid concerns that it is prone to errors and allows the government to expand surveillance without much oversight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peggy Lipton Dead At 72...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/peggy-lipton-co-star-of-the-60s-hit-the-mod-squad-dies-at-72/ar-AABeIY0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake meat: Don't go bacon my heart, say butchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.malaymail.com/news/eat-drink/2019/05/12/fake-meat-dont-go-bacon-my-heart-say-butchers/1752091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.malaymail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT, May 12 — Slicing through juicy cuts of pork belly alongside rarer delicacies of ox brain and sheep intestine, young butchers at a Frankfurt trade hall cast a suspicious eye towards the so-called fake meat products on display.&amp;nbsp; Puzzlingly, for the butchers, the fake meat seems to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detention cells so overcrowded US using aircraft to move migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Border-detention-cells-in-Texas-are-so-13837856.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overcrowding at Border Patrol stations in South Texas has become so acute in recent days that U.S. authorities have taken the rare step of using aircraft to relocate migrants to other areas of the border simply to begin processing them, according to three Homeland Security officials.  The first flight left McAllen, Texas, on Friday, transferring detainees to Border Patrol facilities in Del Rio, Texas. There are daily flights scheduled for the next several days, with two planned for Tuesday, according to officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe the operations.  The flights are conducted by U.S. Customs and Immigration Enforcement, but the detainees remain in the custody of Border Patrol, officials said. Though ICE routinely uses aircraft to move detainees among its detention facilities, it is very unusual for Border Patrol to fly recent arrivals from one part of the border to another to perform routine booking procedures.  Homeland Security officials requested the aircraft because Border Patrol urgently needs to move single adults out of the lower Rio Grande Valley of South Texas. The agency is scrambling to make room for the large volume of families and children who have come across the border in dramatically higher numbers in the past several days, officials said.  One official said the U.S. government has resorted to using aircraft because all available buses were already in use and authorities needed every available transportation option.  "This is the worst I have ever seen it, by far," said one veteran Border Patrol agent in South Texas who was not authorized to speak to reporters.  The number of people taken into custody along the Mexico border has exceeded 5,500 each day for several days in a row, and Border Patrol currently has more than 17,500 people in holding cells and tent sites set up in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Agents Contracting Illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/border-patrol-rep-record-number-of-agents-contracting-illness-from-illegals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I believe this is probably the record, you know, Border Patrol-wide, since ever, of agents calling in sick'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The extraordinary battle over an aging Hollywood titan's care...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/the-extraordinary-battle-over-an-aging-hollywood-titan-s-care/article_19247d1d-3656-53ef-9f83-0844b31c3e49.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Last May, Eric Semel, the eldest child and only son of former Warner Bros. chief Terry Semel, filed a petition in Los Angeles County Superior Court to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia demands NASA answer for 'alcohol stench' on Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/778046/russia-nasa-iss-international-space-station-alcohol-smell-dragon-capsule-explosion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 hit in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/777832/Measles-outbreak-hits-100-000-people-in-Europe-WHO-confirms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Spending Sets Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/2573708000000-federal-spending-sets-all-time-record-through-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Win McNamee)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Flirting With Debt Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/11/politics/congress-debt-ceiling/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US government is hurtling toward a potential financial crisis, and no one in Washington seems to know how to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superstar rapper Drake, who rails against climate change, buys massive private jet...</title>
      <link>https://www.climatedepot.com/2019/05/10/superstar-rapper-drake-who-rails-against-climate-change-buys-massive-private-jet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORDS SMASHED: WETTEST YEAR IN USA HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Genuinely-scary-Torrential-rain-in-Houston-13834973.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clusters of violent and slow-moving thunderstorms converged on the Houston area Thursday night, unleashing torrential rain and enormous hail. The deluge wrought havoc on the city, spurring floods reminiscent of Hurricane Harvey in some areas.  And the heavy rain threat is not over.  Houston is under a flash flood watch through Saturday night given the potential for at least one to three additional inches of rain on top of the two to five inches which fell Thursday night and two to three inches Tuesday.  "Soils remain saturated from recent rainfall and many bayous, creeks and rivers remain high so any additional rainfall should run off quickly and cause flooding," the National Weather Service office serving Houston wrote.  Houston is in a slight risk zone for excessive rainfall both Friday and Saturday.  Additional rainfall is not predicted to be as intense as Thursday night's deluge, but the Weather Service urged residents to "stay put" if extreme rainfall returns: "Do not attempt to travel," it warned. "Underpasses and low-water crossings will be life-threatening. If caught in a sinking vehicle, get OUT. Bayous will likely exceed banks and structure flooding could be possible."  By all accounts, Thursday night's storms in Houston, which have left the region susceptible to more flooding, were wild. "This is probably the most hellacious rain I've ever heard in my life," tweeted Matt Lanza, meteorologist for the Houston weather website SpaceCityWeather.com.  The storms left "at least three bayous flowing over the top of their banks, nearly 90,000 residents without power and dozens reportedly trapped for a time in floodwater on Interstate 10," The Washington Post's Timothy Bella reported.  As much as five inches of rain reportedly fell in one hour in east Houston's Greens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Will Measles Break Out Next? Chicago, L.A. or Miami, Scientists Predict...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-met-cook-county-worst-measles-outbreak-risk-20190509-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers who in 2015 correctly predicted where the Zika outbreak would strike now are placing their scientifically backed bets on the next measles outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In NC swamp, researcher finds tree older than Christianity...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article230191724.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hear world's largest single-room speaker system...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/london-royal-albert-hall-this-is-what-the-worlds-largest-single-room-speaker-system-sounds-like/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Albert Hall now sounds as beautiful as it looks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Trumpville' Site Chosen on Israel-Held Golan to Honor President...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-12/-trumpville-site-chosen-on-israel-held-golan-to-honor-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Crash Fight Will Set Price on Victims' Minutes of Terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-11/boeing-crash-fight-will-set-price-on-victims-minutes-of-terror </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unprecedented' pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-48242997</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Hassan Rouhani calls for political unity at home in the face of international sanctions "war".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-impeach? Talk shifts toward defiance of Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/55869d792c66493e97c5c96ea87dc8ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi has introduced a new concept into the debate over President Donald Trump's actions: "self-impeaching." As Trump all but goads Democrats into...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto plans 'reintroduction' as 2020 buzz fizzles...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1e32cf3855734117b0aa1a1d55867b6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWTON, Iowa (AP) — Beto O'Rourke barreled into the 2020 presidential race with breakneck energy and a fly-by-the-seat-of-his-pants campaign style that saw him leap atop tables to address overflow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Trump takes over Fourth of July celebration, changing location, inserting self into program...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2019/05/11/president-trump-takes-over-fourth-of-july-celebration-changing-its-location-and-inserting-himself-into-the-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s starring role has the potential to turn what has long been a nonpartisan celebration of the nation’s founding into another version of a Trump campaign rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaner New York waterways cause surge in beached whales...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/11/cleaner-new-york-waterways-are-causing-surge-in-beached-whales/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cleaner waterways in New York City have attracted more sea life, including seals, dolphins, whales, and sharks in bigger numbers than seen in a century. But there are also more mammals washing asho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average American hasn't made new friend in 5 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/09/why-the-average-american-hasnt-made-a-new-friend-in-5-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-five percent of adults say they find it difficult to make new friends, according to new research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assault ship, missiles to Mideast...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-sends-assault-ship-missiles-mideast-amid-iran-220835740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon announced Friday that it is deploying an amphibious assault ship and a Patriot missile battery to the Middle East to bolster an aircraft carrier force sent to counter alleged threats from Iran. The USS Arlington, which transports marines, amphibious vehicles, conventional landing craft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standoff intensifies as Dems subpoena Trump tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/standoff-intensifies-democrats-subpoena-trump-tax-returns-214443035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US House Democrats issued subpoenas Friday against top government officials demanding President Donald Trump's tax returns, the latest twist in the sharpening battle between the White House and opponents in Congress. House Ways and Means Committee chairman Richard Neal said he subpoenaed Treasury</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete to Trump Over Nickname: 'What, Me Worry?'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mayor-pete-president-trump-over-164238311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump loves to dole out nicknames to his political rivals -- and they almost always carry an edge of cruelty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro clamps down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/guaido-deputy-being-held-military-prison-165946513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido on Saturday urged his supporters to reject fear and maintain nationwide protests against President Nicolas Maduro, who has been ratcheting up pressure on the lawmaker since a failed military uprising. Some 1,500 to 2,000 people filled a square in an opposition-friendly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Loomer Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Names Its Price...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-names-trade-deal-price-060802514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I think that China felt they were beaten so badly in the recent negotiation that they may as well wait around for the next election,” Trump said Saturday in a pair of early-evening tweets. Trump’s comments came a day after talks between the two economic superpowers ended without a resolution, the U.S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climber's Camera Captures 60-Foot Free-Fall Off Rock Face; Miraculously Lives...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/05/10/kyle-walker-flatiron-fall-scrambler/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who fell while climbing the Flatirons in Boulder is hoping video of the incident will serve as a warning to others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk faces trial for 'pedo' insult of diver...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb8b1cbc1fb1407e951a667fbe03b297</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Tesla CEO Elon Musk will have to go to trial to defend himself for mocking a British diver as a pedophile in a verbal sparring match that unfolded last summer after the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space-tourism enters home stretch toward commercial flight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8224cbee677b40bca8ab7d712a9df1fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) — Billionaire Richard Branson is moving Virgin Galactic's winged passenger rocket and more than 100 employees from California to a remote commercial launch and landing facility...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread rationing in face of crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/42b62f24be9b4e0d9f764f1a3fa9647a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — The Cuban government announced Friday that it is launching widespread rationing of chicken, eggs, rice, beans, soap and other basic products in the face of a grave economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>