<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fire at secret Iran missile base...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/fire-in-iran-occurred-at-secret-irgc-missile-base-report-680760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday, Tel Aviv-based ImageSat International - ISI, a commercial servicer for satellite images - estimated that the facility was not just any military compound - it was a secret missile base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage mayor backs use of yellow stars by mask opponents...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/anchorage/2021/09/29/tensions-run-high-over-proposed-mask-ordinance-at-second-night-of-anchorage-assembly-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public testimony stretched until midnight and the Assembly did not vote on the ordinance. Another meeting is scheduled for Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMITH &amp; WESSON Moving From MA To TN Over Proposed Gun Laws...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/30/smith-and-wesson-massachusetts-tennessee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smith &amp; Wesson, one of the oldest gun manufacturers in the country, announced Thursday it is moving operations from Springfield to Tennessee due to gun laws in Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Combat Meth, California To Pay Drug Users To Stop Using...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/09/30/1040412804/to-combat-meth-california-will-try-a-bold-treatment-pay-drug-users-to-stop-using</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fatal drug overdoses, including from meth, have soared. California is preparing to roll out a controversial but proven treatment that involves paying stimulant users small sums of money not to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shakira says wild boars attacked her, stole purse in park...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/shakira-says-wild-boars-attacked-her-stole-her-purse-barcelona-n1280477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Look at how two wild boar which attacked me in the park have left my bag," Shakira told her more than 70 million Instagram followers as she held up her torn bag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Tom Brady Sounds Extremely Sick -- Doesn't Know Why...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/30/tom-brady-sounds-extremely-sick-hoarse-voice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady spoke to the media Thursday, though he didn't sound at all like Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who survived 1918 flu succumbs to corona...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Woman-who-survived-Spanish-flu-world-war-16498363.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She lived a life of adventure that spanned two continents. She fell in love with a World...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN 'toxic' workplace, workers claim in essay...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/30/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-essay-claims-toxic-workplace.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos' space company Blue Origin is described as a "toxic" workplace in an essay by 21 current and former employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COSBY: R. Kelly Was 'Screwed,' 'Railroaded' In Trial!</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/celebrities/news/2021/09/29/bill-cosby-r-kelly-verdict-comments-railroaded.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Wyatt spoke out on behalf of his 84-year old client.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Becomes Social Experiment For Behavioral Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-lockdown-social-experiment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study finds women tend to make significantly longer phone calls and follow government measures more closely than men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Stagehands Set to Begin Strike Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98about-power-not-reason-e2-80-99-as-locals-build-support-iatse-votes-on-strike-authorization-next-week/ar-AAOKniV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voting begins October 1 on a strike authorization vote that could lead to a production shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orban Foe Who'd Break the Law to Raze His Regime Leads Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/orban-foe-who-d-break-the-law-to-raze-his-regime-leads-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orban Foe Who’d Break the Law to Raze His Regime Leads Primaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How tech journalism turned against technology...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/tech-media-has-turned-anti-tech/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook want you to join them on the Metaverse. The Metaverse is the company’s Next Big Thing, and where they see the internet going: an online world of total wraparound experience, a lot more like the Lawnmower Man version than what we have now. They released a statement this week earmarking some $50 million towards [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIEW TO A CHILL:  WILL AUDIENCES FLOCK TO BOND?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rave-james-bond-reviews-raise-110742055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Rave reviews for the long-delayed James Bond movie “No Time to Die” could finally entice people away from Netflix and into theaters. Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionHSBC Bets Big on China as Pressure Mounts in LondonHow Los Angeles Became the City of DingbatsTiming can dictate the success or failure of a b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S sues to block AMAZON billboard off flagship store...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/macys-files-suit-to-keep-amazon-billboard-off-flagship-store</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looks like Amazon may be trying to encroach on Macy's territory in the heart of Midtown Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous FACEBOOK Whistleblower Speaks Out on '60 MINUTES'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/facebook-whistleblower-60-minutes-2021-09-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former employee, who recently filed anonymous federal complaints against Facebook, reveals her identity on 60 Minutes, Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Someone Betting Oil Will Soar to Record $200 a Barrel...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/commodities/energy/oil-gas/someone-is-betting-that-oil-will-soar-to-a-record-200-a-barrel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SORKIN: Rudin Got What He Deserves...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/09/aaron-sorkin-on-scott-rudin-scott-got-what-he-deserves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exclusive interview with Sorkin as his smash adaptation of 'To Kill a Mockingbird' reopens on Broadway, without its disgraced producer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Academic Success Often Leads To 'Vicious Cycle' Of Perfectionism, Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/school-success-perfectionism-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some students can't help but feel like they're fighting a never-ending scholarly battle just to prove they're "good enough."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem agenda hangs in balance...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-e2-80-99-agenda-hangs-in-balance-as-pelosi-biden-scramble-for-support-on-infrastructure-vote/ar-AAP0flj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expected House vote increasingly appears doomed: Liberal-leaning Democrats over the past day have reinforced their opposition to the measure, as they wage a broader, still-intensifying war with moderates over the fuller size and scope of Biden’s economic agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Price-Distorting' iBuyers Like ZILLOW Hurt Homeowners, Rivals Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3aq389/price-distorting-ibuyers-like-zillow-hurt-us-homeowners-rivals-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The model ultimately comes at a “cost to the consumer,” one said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth and Moon Growing Apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/09/moon-moving-away-earth/620254/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And we can’t stop that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.1 quake couldn't kill this Mojave Desert town. But water war just might...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/7-1-earthquake-couldnt-kill-120058578.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small desert town of Trona imports its water from 30 miles away. A 2014 law aimed at preserving California's groundwater has set off a complicated battle that has some residents fearing the worst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foes united vs FACEBOOK over INSTAGRAM effect on teens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-technology-health-congress-25bf24d23a3ac6f08f833b8066a34000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Political adversaries in Congress are united in outrage against Facebook for privately compiling information that its Instagram photo-sharing service appears to grievously harm some teens, especially girls, while publicly downplaying the popular platform’s negative impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Officials Beg for Protection Against Threats From 'Angry Mobs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/school-officials-beg-biden-and-fbi-for-protection-against-threats-from-angry-mobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National School Boards Association has likened recent threats against school staffers across the U.S. to “domestic terrorism and hate crimes.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Lethal kids games drive viral fame of NETFLIX series 'SQUID GAME'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/lethal-kids-games-drive-viral-fame-netflix-series-squid-games-2021-09-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hit Netflix series "Squid Game" from South Korea has gone viral across the world and online by morphing childhood games popular before the digital era such as "Red Light, Green Light" into deadly survival challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONES share previously unreleased track 'TROUBLES A' COMIN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/music/the-rolling-stones-share-previously-unreleased-track-troubles-a-comin-3058970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rolling Stones have shared a previously unreleased track – watch the video for 'Troubles A' Comin' below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man opens emergency door, jumps onto wing of plane in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/miami-483f6805eee6f38310873c65f432b794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A passenger on an American Airlines flight that landed at Miami International Airport opened an emergency door and walked onto the wing as the plane reached the terminal, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see peril in tight Virginia gov race...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Democrats-see-peril-in-tight-Virginia-governor-16497791.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden's slumping approval ratings and gridlock on Capitol Hill...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'YOLO' generation of investors ready for anything, even crash...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/yolo-generation-investors-ready-anything-020615714.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street has been a booming place over the past year and a half even as the wider US economy has suffered -- a trend that an entire generation of young investors has both noticed, and cashed in on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazi war crimes suspect, 96, caught after fleeing trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210930124352-xd6ar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-NAZI/TRIAL (UPDATE 4, TV, PIX):UPDATE 4-Nazi war crimes suspect, 96, caught after fleeing trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Someone Betting Oil Will Soar to Record $200 a Barrel...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/someone-is-betting-that-oil-will-soar-to-a-record-200-a-barrel-1.1659692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could the energy crunch get so bad that oil prices hit $200 a barrel? One options trader thinks so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Warns Having Flu Simultaneously Could Be 'Catastrophic'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/09/29/covid-flu-simultaneously/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Adrian Burrowes has seen hundreds of COVID-19 patients, but he is especially worried about what will happen this flu season, even more so than last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who survived Spanish flu, world war succumbs to COVID...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-europe-health-pandemics-connecticut-34a70ec8c61abe37abac05d985a8c76f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She lived a life of adventure that spanned two continents. She fell in love with a World War II fighter pilot, barely escaped Europe ahead of Benito Mussolini’s fascists, ground steel for the U.S. war effort and advocated for her disabled daughter in a far less enlightened time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Hospital ICU Reaches 150% Capacity...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/montana-hospital-icu-reaches-150-capacity-amid-surge-of-covid-19-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past week, Montana averaged about 108 COVID-19 patients in hospital ICUs — breaking the record seen during the winter of 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway's 'ALADDIN' shuts after one performance due to breakthrough cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/broadways-aladdin-shuts-after-only-one-performance-since-re-opening-night-due-to-breakthrough-covid-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was no word on when one of the Great White Way's most anticipated shows would re-open — again, and concern spread about other shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military units track guns using tech that could aid foes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/rfid-military-weapons-guns-62c88008478f4ac403047c21f3184677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Determined to keep track of their guns, some U.S. military units have turned to a technology that could let enemies detect troops on the battlefield, The Associated Press has found. The rollout on Army and Air Force bases continues even though the Department of Defense itself describes putting the technology in firearms as a “significant” security risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema in spotlight as obstacle to agenda...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210930095908-i0w61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/CONGRESS-SINEMA (PIX):Democrat Sinema in spotlight as obstacle to Biden economic agenda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German 96-year-old Nazi war crimes suspect flees ahead of trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210930091906-bctra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-NAZI/TRIAL (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-German 96-year-old Nazi war crimes suspect flees ahead of trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii's Kilauea volcano erupts, lava fountains form in park...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-hawaii-kilauea-volcanoes-hawaii-volcanoes-national-park-21deaf9cafc50adf7b6fadccfd18b6f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — One of the most active volcanos on Earth is erupting on Hawaii's Big Island. Officials with the U.S. Geological Survey confirmed Wednesday that an eruption has begun in Kilauea volcano's Halemaumau crater at the volcano's summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Faces Revolt from Ex-Supporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/kyrsten-sinema-faces-a-growing-revolt-from-her-former-supporters/ar-AAOY5Fi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX — Jade Duran once spent her weekends knocking on doors to campaign for Senator Kyrsten Sinema, the stubbornly centrist Democrat whose vote could seal the fate of a vast Democratic effort to remake America’s social safety net. But no more. When Ms. Sinema famously gave a thumbs down to a $15 minimum wage and refused to eliminate the filibuster to pass new voting rights laws this year, Ms. Duran, a Democrat and biomedical engineer from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 75 percent of Venezuelans now living in extreme poverty...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/574603-more-than-75-percent-of-venezuelans-now-living-in-extreme-poverty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 75 percent of Venezuelans are now living in extreme poverty, according to a new study published on Wednesday, Reuters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress poised to avert shutdown, but brawl looms on debt...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/574607-congress-poised-to-avert-shutdown-but-brawl-looms-on-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress is moving to avert a government shutdown before Friday, leaving Democrats with a tough choice on how to raise the debt ceiling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala poll numbers rise as Biden's fall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/574604-harriss-poll-numbers-rise-as-bidens-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris has rebounded in recent weeks, regaining her footing with approval ratings that now stand higher than President Biden’s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ecuador declares prison emergency after 116 killed in riot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/latin-america-prisons-guillermo-lasso-ecuador-drug-cartels-b79572a799d4d9b6b5549504de1dfa2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — Ecuador's president has declared a state of emergency in the prison system following a battle among gang members in a coastal lockup that killed at least 116 people and injured 80 in what authorities say was the worst prison bloodbath ever in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarkozy convicted by French court in campaign financing case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-france-elections-trials-campaigns-aa6fc25ed310108a29b77bc5175a6de6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French ex-President Nicolas Sarkozy, who was convicted Thursday and sentenced to a year of house arrest for illegal campaign financing of his unsuccessful 2012 reelection bid, will appeal the ruling, his lawyer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of restaurants say conditions worse than 3 months ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/29/majority-of-restaurants-say-business-is-worse-than-3-months-ago-survey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The restaurant industry trade group is asking lawmakers to replenish the Restaurant Revitalization Fund amid continued fallout from Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE's upcoming search redesign to push more traffic  -- to GOOGLE properties...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/29/google-wants-search-results-to-be-endless-stream-of-visual-ideas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is redesigning search, and users can expect to see more of a focus on e-commerce and more YouTube videos,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney warns unvaccinated face total social isolation INDEFINITELY when lockdown ends...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210928025122-5mqe6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Sydney's unvaccinated warned of social isolation when COVID-19 lockdown ends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney's 13-Year Conservatorship Set To End In November; Dad Booted By Judge...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/britney-spears-father-suspended-from-conservatorship-judge-hearing-court-1234846613/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with more hearing details: The harsh and much criticized conservatorship that has dominated Britney Spears’ life for more than a decade isn’t over, but the onetime Princess of P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Alleges Animal Cruelty at 'Humane' Slaughterhouse...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/09/29/animal-cruelty-chickens-foster-farms-humane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists arrested while protesting Foster Farms are being held in county jail on $50,000 bonds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-Editing Experiment Let Patients See Color Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/09/29/1040879179/vision-loss-crispr-treatment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a first, doctors injected the gene-editing tool CRISPR directly into cells in patients' eyes. The experiment helped these vision-impaired patients see shapes and colors again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Covid may cause 'restless anal syndrome'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/covid-may-cause-restless-anal-syndrome-report-680582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patient in Japan seems to have developed the condition due to COVID-19, according to initial findings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top General: USA 'lost' 20-year war...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210929-us-lost-the-20-year-war-in-afghanistan-top-us-general</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US 'lost' the 20-year war in Afghanistan: top US general</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacon prices reach record levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcra.com/article/bacon-prices-have-reached-record-levels-heres-why-they-might-not-go-down-anytime-soon/37791555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price of one of your favorite breakfast items is on the rise. Here's how long it could last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New, 'first-class' high-rise will house homeless on LA skid row...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/new-high-rise-to-house-homeless-people-on-l-a-s-skid-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Construction kicked off Tuesday on a 19-story homeless housing project designed to reshape a corner of skid row in the image of more well-to-do environs. The 278-unit Weingart Tower will replace a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Bush strategist to run as Dem for Texas lieutenant governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/politics/article/Matthew-Dowd-former-George-W-Bush-strategist-16495798.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew Dowd called Patrick 'cruel and craven' while announcing his candidacy for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming for K-12 Students...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/29/vaccine-mandates-coming-for-k-12-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Diego becomes latest school district to require teen jabs. But is it good policy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video apparently shows shootout that left KGB officer, IT worker dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/29/video-apparently-shows-murder-of-kgb-officer-it-worker-in-belarus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video apparently captured a shootout between Belarusian security forces and a man reported to be an IT worker with a US company, amid a crackdown on pro-democracy protestors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katie Couric's new book sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10037351/Katie-Courics-new-book-sparks-outrage-rips-ex-boyfriends-former-NBC-CBS-colleagues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com has read the manuscript for Katie Couric's book ' Going There' , which is out in late October and will be accompanied by an 11-city book tour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 High School Refs Barricaded Inside Locker Room After Altercation With Coach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/general/news/seven-ohio-high-school-football-referees-claim-they-were-barricaded-inside-of-locker-room-after-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Grove City High School assistant coach 'charged' the referees in a 'very threatening manner' on the field before the officials moved to the locker room</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal gathering sends Australian region into lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/coronavirus/australia/australia-covid-news-live-lockdowns-case-numbers-and-vaccinations/news-story/ba54d427d65e0df8cd2ef80842f5a54f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Wednesday’s coverage of Australia’s Covid-19 situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply chain workers warn of 'system collapse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/29/business/supply-chain-workers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seafarers, truck drivers and airline workers have endured quarantines, travel restrictions and complex Covid-19 vaccination and testing requirements to keep stretched supply chains moving during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mice experiencing defeat get depressed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/mental-health/574535-mice-vicariously-experiencing-defeat-get-depressed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a study focused on the pathophysiology of depression, researchers look at how the brains of mice change when experiencing ‘second-hand’ psychological stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Happiness Prevents Dementia?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/happiness-young-adulthood-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study reveals a 73-percent higher chance of cognitive impairment among those with more depressive symptoms during young adulthood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA considers wide-ranging requirement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-los-angeles-public-health-fe955da901bddcb53a82307566986161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles City Council will vote Wednesday on a proposed ordinance to require people to have proof of full vaccination against COVID-19 to enter a wide range of businesses and venues.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
