<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT DELAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/10169227/brexit-news-boris-johnson-saturday-vote-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson will write to the EU to ask for another Brexit delay TONIGHT after Tory rebel Sir Oliver Letwin trashed his chance to make history today. In a day of high-drama in the House of Common…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubting death: How our brains shield us from mortal truth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/oct/19/doubting-death-how-our-brains-shield-us-from-mortal-truth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brain seems to categorise death as something that only befalls other people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT TODAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/19/uk-lawmakers-back-a-change-to-brexit-vote-which-delays-full-approval-and-forces-deadline-extension.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House of Commons sat for a historic Saturday session and lawmakers were due to have a "meaningful vote" on Johnson's new deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIOTS STUN CHILE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chile-president-declares-state-emergency-violent-protests-070230347.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Chile's capital awoke Saturday to a ravaged city as burned-out buses, bikes and garbage littered the streets after a day of violent protests that prompted the government to declare a state of emergency and call out soldiers to maintain order for the first time in decades. The stunning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191019133903-wrh6q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 8-Johnson defiant after British parliament votes to force Brexit delay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unveils biggest ancient coffin find in century...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-archaeology-luxor-idUSKBN1WY0C5 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt on Saturday unveiled the details of 30 ancient wooden coffins with mummies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Water System Collapsing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/19/world/americas/venezuela-water.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To understand how far it has deteriorated, The New York Times ran tests and found dangerous levels of bacteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican House member 'thinking' about impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/54ebdce60d6c4075a3a9e8c7447fc1d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump gave an atta-boy to Republican Rep. Francis Rooney last year on the congressman's home turf in swing state Florida. "I love it when he defends me,"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confronted by impeachment, Trump adds to chaos...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49fd63d02be24f5daad0bba353edc738</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The impeachment investigation into President Donald Trump has thrust Washington into a political crisis. And Trump keeps adding to the chaos. In the four weeks since House...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump outstripping Obama on pace of executive orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/25ca8d3b39024f9e828df7ebeb718274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It wasn't too long ago that Donald Trump derided presidential executive orders as "power grabs" and a "basic disaster." He's switched sides in a big way: In each year of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest for new vote...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191019125601-6t3wf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/PROTEST (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nestor Approaches Florida Gulf Coast with Surge, Wind, Rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/news/storms/hurricane/news/2019-10-18-tropical-storm-nestor-forecast-gulf-of-mexico-southeast-mid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrest in Chile... </title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20191019-chile-president-declares-state-of-emergency-after-riots-over-metro-fare-hikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chile's president declared a state of emergency in Santiago Friday night and gave the military responsibility for security after a day of violent protests over an increase in the price of metro tickets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNIFE EDGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-50104789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson urges MPs to back his agreement with the EU, amid moves by MPs to delay approval of the deal until Brexit laws are passed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Ebola vaccine gets green light...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10168543/first-ebola-vaccine-go-ahead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s first Ebola vaccine was recommended for approval by European regulators yesterday. The move was hailed by the World Health Organisation as a “triumph for public health” that would save …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KOVACH: History will not be on FACEBOOK's side, no matter what Zuckerberg says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/18/mark-zuckerberg-georgetown-speech-history-isnt-on-facebooks-side.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg's address at Georgetown University was rooted in the principles of free speech, but ignored the role Facebook plays as a publisher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension mounts in Canada as election nears...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vote-splitting-fears-raised-final-days-canada-election-063242929.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just three days left before Canada votes in a hotly contested election, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and Conservative rival Andrew Scheer on Friday ratcheted up the mudslinging, as both seek to avoid ending up with a minority government. Policy announcements gave way to calls to vote strategically</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems aim to block...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-democrats-aim-block-trump-resort-hosting-g7-232501910.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furious that US President Donald Trump announced he will host the next G7 summit at his own golf resort in Florida, congressional Democrats introduced legislation Friday to block his plan. Lawmakers said the "Trump's Heist Undermines the G-7 (THUG) Act" would cut off all federal funding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence escalates in Barcelona after half a million separatists protest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/general-strike-catalonia-freedom-marchers-head-barcelona-101725960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violent clashes escalated in Barcelona late Friday, as radical Catalan separatists hurled rocks and fireworks at police, who responded with teargas and rubber bullets, turning the city centre into a chaotic battleground. The deterioration came on the fifth consecutive day of protests in the Catalan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrest in Chile... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191019000159-ple8z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILE-PROTESTS/METRO (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Chile shuts down capital city metro as violent protests spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nestor Hurtles Toward Florida's Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/PTC-16-Hurtles-Toward-Floridas-Gulf-Coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nestor is headed toward landfall on Florida's Gulf Coast early Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radar...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/weather/radar/interactive/l/Gainesville+FL?canonicalCityId=60abec507069aebac1e447d90076e4b6b558e78de143c7ab0a0dec3d482870fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interactive weather map allows you to pan and zoom to get unmatched weather details in your local neighbourhood or half a world away from The Weather Channel and Weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perry won't comply with subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/466532-perry-wont-comply-with-subpoena-in-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outgoing Energy Sec. Rick Perry will not comply with a House subpoena to turn over documents tied to his involvement with Ukraine, the Department of Energy (DOE) wrote in a letter to Democratic lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden struggles to reverse fall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/466515-biden-struggles-to-reverse-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s presidential campaign is hitting major bumps at a critical moment in the 2020 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump baffles with claim to have taken control of Mideast oil...</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Energy-General/Trump-Claims-To-Have-Taken-Control-Of-Middle-East-Oil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump claimed to have taken control of the oil in the Middle East, a statement that likely refers to the Deir Ezzor fields in Syria which have remained under special forces control despite the U.S. withdrawal from the area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Boris Pull Off the Impossible? </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boris-johnson-pull-off-impossible-171636349.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Boris Johnson has managed to strike a new Brexit deal with the European Union. But does he have the numbers to get it past Parliament?Well short of a majority, he needs to persuade 61 Members of Parliament to back his deal. He looks more than half-way there, based on public comments made</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers Slam APPLE for Censorship of Apps at China's Behest...</title>
      <link>https://au.lifestyle.yahoo.com/2019-10-18-us-lawmakers-criticize-apple-over-chinese-app-censorship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.lifestyle.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new letter co-penned by a bipartisan group of members of Congress, federal lawmakers say they have "strong concern" related to Apple's recent actions in China. The letter, which is addressed to CEO Tim Cook, zeroes in on Apple's decision earlier this month to remove HKMap, an app</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE BEGINS DRONE DELIVERIES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9fd494757cd499980211f8a34793eb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Google affiliate started using drones Friday to deliver customers' Walgreens and FedEx purchases in a test being run in a Virginia town. Wing, which is owned by Google parent Alphabet,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Flares in Syria Despite Hours-Old Cease-Fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8f709724b8b5465fab01e56f6c56d064</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump punched back Friday at criticism that his Syria withdrawal is damaging U.S. credibility, betraying Kurdish allies and opening the door for a possible...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL's rising star joins growing list of sidelined QBs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cbb9eeff93d432fa4e1ef7e8f149687</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — With Patrick Mahomes sidelined, fans across the NFL may be longing for the days when the backup quarterback's job was to carry a clipboard and not the hopes and dreams of an entire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifting explanations for withholding aid draw Republican alarm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0a81feef4dd74bf0a746c9245136b229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The shifting White House explanation for President Donald Trump's decision to withhold military aid from Ukraine drew alarm Friday from Republicans as the impeachment inquiry...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND WITH BERNIE:  ALL-STAR RALLY...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/10/bernie-sanders-returns-with-a-rally-with-aoc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator and presidential candidate has made his return to the trail, buoyed by an endorsement for Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez. What happens next?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Tech Coming to School Near You...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/gadget-lab-podcast-427/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WIRED Editor in Chief Nicholas Thompson joins us for a special edition of this week’s podcast, to discuss Facebook, Google, and facial recognition technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  'SOUTH PARK' Nears $500 Million Streaming Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/south-park-streaming-rights-may-fetch-up-500m-bidding-war-1248757</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Comedy Central staple currently streams on Hulu, and is said to be among half a dozen companies bidding for the rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate-Concerned 2020 Dems Spend Big on Private Jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/10/18/climate-concerned-2020-democrats-spending-hundreds-of-thousands-on-private-air-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several 2020 Democrats have spent tens of thousands on private air travel, calling their concerns over climate change into question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diplomat accused of political retribution steps down...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab6bf25d4925489f88dd7389e539088f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A senior State Department official accused of carrying out political retribution against career diplomats deemed insufficiently supportive of President Donald Trump has announced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMANDS SUBSTANTIAL DAMAGES FROM BIAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trump-campaign-to-sue-cnn-over-pro-impeachment-bias-demands-substantial-payment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outraged by secretly taped anti-Trump comments attributed to CNN President Jeff Zucker and others at the cable network, President Trump’s campaign is vowing to sue the company for “a substantial payment of damages.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'QUEEN OF WARMONGERS'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/tulsi-gabbard-fires-back-at-queen-of-warmongers-hillary-clinton-for-suggesting-shes-a-russian-asset/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard fired back this afternoon at Hillary Clinton over comments she made suggesting the Hawaii congresswoman and 2020 candidate is being groomed by the Russians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  President bound, abused in Times Square ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/18/donald-trump-bound-abused-appears-in-dhvanis-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump — held against his will and abused — is the focus of a new ad campaign by the athletic apparel company Dhvani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem. Congresswoman Accused of 'Throuple' With Female Staffer...</title>
      <link>https://www.redstate.com/jenvanlaar/2019/10/18/ca-rep.-katie-hill-allegedly-involved-female-staffer-2-yr-throuple-relationship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.redstate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What in the world is going on here?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo lashes out...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/18/mike-pompeo-trump-impeachment-inquiry-050845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, Texas is a  battleground: Million$ more flow in...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/10/18/yes-texas-is-a-battleground-millions-more-dollars-flow-into-us-house-races-than-in-2018-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – Texas’ road to battleground relevancy is paved with campaign cash. More than $39.6 million flowed into U.S. House races in the Lone Star State...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS tests passengers, pilots' brains on world's longest flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/18/qantas-studies-jet-lag-on-new-york-sydney-nonstop-worlds-longest-flight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qantas will test how pilots and passengers withstand a 20-hour nonstop from New York to Sydney, monitoring brain activity and melatonin levels during the flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  'SOUTH PARK' Nears $500 Million Streaming Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-10-18/-south-park-nears-500-million-deal-for-u-s-streaming-rights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38 people cited for violations in Clinton email probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14b14afc5d8647858489a2cf5385c28d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The State Department has completed its internal investigation into former Secretary of State Hillary Rodham Clinton's use of private email and found violations by 38 people, some...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses who use insulin, other drugs to kill patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/10/18/clarksburg-west-virginia-veterans-affairs-deaths-medical-murders/3936045002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A string of suspicious deaths at the Clarksburg VA hospital in West Virginia could prove to be an "investigative nightmare." Here's why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICK-FIL-A's first UK location will close after pressure from LGBTQ rights group...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/18/chick-fil-as-first-uk-location-will-close-after-pressure-from-lgbtq-rights-group.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British shopping center leasing Chick-fil-A's first U.K. location has already said it will not extend the restaurant's six-month lease, BBC reported Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frictions raise doubts about nukes at Turk base...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/182a2170a1d24ac6b4f0c7242d8ff514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Frayed U.S. relations with Turkey over its incursion in Syria raise a sensitive question rarely discussed in public: Should the United States remove the nuclear bombs it has long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal messages suggest BOEING may have misled FAA on 737 MAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-airplane-boeing-exclusive/exclusive-boeing-2016-internal-messages-suggest-employees-may-have-misled-faa-on-737-max-sources-idUSKBN1WX25G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Co turned over instant messages from 2016 between two employees that sugg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most U.S. Dairy Cows Are Descended From Just 2 Bulls...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2019/10/17/770696476/most-u-s-dairy-cows-are-descended-from-just-2-bulls-thats-not-good</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drive to make more milk has had an unsavory side effect: Cows have become more genetically similar and less fertile. Scientists are trying to recover valuable genetic variation that was lost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANKEES fans mock ASTROS pitcher for depression, anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/18/yankees-fan-mock-zack-greinke-for-social-anxiety-disorder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reputation of Yankees fans this postseason only got worse Thursday night. One fan reportedly was ejected from the Stadium before Game 4 of the ALCS after taunting Astros starter Zack Greinke ov…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pause' in fighting in jeopardy...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/pause-fighting-syria-turkish-kurdish-forces-appears-jeopardy/story?id=66367747</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eyewitnesses report that fighting has not stopped in Syria between Turkish and Kurdish forces, despite an agreement between Turkey and the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 men, many in the military, attacked or sexually assaulted in NC city...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article236398558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana could become the first state without abortion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/louisiana-abortion-case-supreme-court-state-could-become-first-without-abortion-access-next-year-2019-10-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana could become the first state not to have legal abortion access since the procedure was legalized in 1973</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University bans 'acts of intolerance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=13877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can they do that?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
