<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Female senator wears handgun to podium to present bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/virginia/government-politics/general-assembly/sen-chase-wears-handgun-to-podium-to-present-bills-in/article_c047eb24-0136-5ee0-b848-63489e824dde.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not just her bills that are sparking attention. State Sen. Amanda Chase, R-Chesterfield, generated buzz on Tuesday by presenting them while wearing her .38-caliber revolver in a custom-made holster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Openly strapped after colleague mobbed by activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/on-senate-floor-with-gun-on-hip-republican-amanda-chase-says-she-will-deter-violence-1978870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in Virginia, where gun culture runs deep and some state lawmakers wear concealed weapons as routinely as dress socks, this scene raised eyebrows: State Sen. Amanda Chase standing on the floor of the ornate chamber with a .38 special openly strapped to her hip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Pelley Deletes Posts Saying Egypt Wants To Arrest Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/cbs-news-correspondent-scott-pelley-deletes-social-media-posts-egypt-n959876</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Pelley’s post was in error and has been taken down,” said a spokesman for CBS News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA TURNING AGAINST 'BABBLING' BETO...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/opinion/article/Preseason-is-over-for-Beto-O-Rourke-13542085.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O'Rourke, welcome to the National Football League. As a potential top-tier presidential candidate, O'Rourke has arrived at a much tougher level of competition, and he had better raise his game quickly. To continue the metaphor, he is like a No. 1 draft pick, and everyone is looking to see whether he's worth it. The nation's best and toughest reporters have his number and want nothing more than to take his measure and knock him down. Now that he is under a whole new burden of proof, he is going to have a more thoughtful positions on national issues than the one O'Rourke gave The Washington Post's Jenna Johnson, published in an article on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Sales From 'BIRD BOX' Boom Disappoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-17/netflix-growth-falls-short-as-programming-fails-to-hook-viewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest 1% own 50% of stocks held by American households...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/the-richest-1-own-50-of-stocks-held-by-american-households-150758595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stock ownership has gotten extremely concentrated in the U.S. with the top 1% owning half of equities held by American households.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife burns husband alive after he 'refuses to give phone password'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/wife-burns-husband-alive-after-13871070</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - GRAPHIC IMAGES: Ilham Cahyani has been arrested after the married could got into an argument over his mobile phone pasword</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Blasts Beto: Excellent adventure drips with white male privilege...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/17/politics/beto-orourke-funk-drive-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine this: A 46-year-old former congresswoman and mother of three, who just lost a Senate bid to one of the most despised incumbents, sets off on a road trip adventure to clear her head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acting AG's wife rips reporter over article 'viciousness'...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2019/01/marci-whitaker-email-matthew-whitaker-attorney-general.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marci Whitaker, wife of the acting attorney general, says the Mueller investigation is “wrapping up.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Obama Lawyer Made False Statements to DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/17/obama-lawyer-ukraine-justice-department/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DID TRUMP BRIBE DRUDGE POLL?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/poll-rigging-for-trump-and-creating-womenforcohen-one-it-firms-work-order-11547722801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early 2015, the owner of a small tech company showed up at Trump Tower to collect $50,000 for helping Michael Cohen try to rig online polls in Donald Trump’s favor before the presidential campaign. He says he never got what he was owed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scheme was carried out 'at direction and for sole benefit' of the president...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cohen-hired-it-firm-to-rig-online-polls-for-trump-says-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-fixer confirms WSJ bombshell report: Scheme with Liberty University’s IT director was carried out ‘at the direction and for the sole benefit’ of the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen and bag of cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/01/17/the-quintessential-trump-campaign-story-a-bag-of-cash-michael-cohen-and-a-rigged-online-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have, on Thursday, a story that perhaps serves as the best encapsulation to date of how the early days of Donald Trump’s campaign for the presidency worked, a summary that, itself, seems to expl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLETTE accused of 'pink tax' sexism after toxic masculinity ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gillette-ad-commercial-pink-tax-controversy-toxic-masculinity-metoo-a8731821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Playoff Belichick: Dead Headsets, Paranoia, 'Chasing Ghosts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/01/16/facing-bill-belichick-nfl-playoffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In late January 2004, while studying film in his Houston hotel room, Jake Delhomme received a call from Peyton Manning. The New England Patriots had just beaten Manning’s Colts in the AFC Cha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal govt sued for records on social media surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/425906-aclu-sues-federal-agencies-for-social-media-surveillance-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) on Thursday sued seven federal agencies, seeking to obtain records on how the government surveils people on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron LAKERS move crippling NBA TV ratings...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/17/lebron-james-lakers-move-is-crippling-the-nbas-tv-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James went west, and the NBA ratings have gone south. More than halfway through the regular season, NBA ratings have fallen. The real plummet has been on Turner, which started with a LeBron-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to publicly testify Feb. 7...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/17/cohen-tech-rig-drudge-report-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'At the direction' of Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem's Wailing Wall covered in rare SNOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8218861/jerusalems-iconic-wailing-wall-and-dome-of-the-rock-covered-in-snow-as-6c-temperatures-bring-middle-eastern-city-to-a-standstill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM has been hit by a rare snow fall that has led to schools being closed and put Israel’s only ski resort out of action. Pictures show the city’s iconic monuments including the Wailing…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathalyzed... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6604071/Duke-Edinburgh-involved-road-crash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Philip is 'conscious but very shocked and shaken' after flipping his Land Rover near the Sandringham Estate. The Queen is by the Duke's side following the collision on the A149 in Norfolk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia detains model claiming Trump secrets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/model-claiming-trump-secrets-deported-thailand-101351022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Thursday detained a Belarusian model who claimed she had evidence of Russian efforts to help Donald Trump win office, witnesses told AFP. Anastasia Vashukevich, known by her pen-name Nastya Rybka, was held for questioning at a Moscow airport on Thursday evening after she was deported from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo Mistress Flips on Him in Court -- While Wife Looks On...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/el-chapos-mistress-flipped-on-him-in-court-while-his-wife-looked-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO-CORTEZ: Set To Party With Hollywood At Sundance...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-sundance-2019-appearance-boomerang-bet-series-macro-1202536625/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Lena Waite- and Halle Berry-executive produced Boomerang recharge doesn’t debut until February, but Sundance Film Festival attendees are going to get a world premiere preview of the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Weighs Lifting China Tariffs to Hasten Trade Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-weighs-lifting-china-tariffs-to-hasten-trade-deal-calm-markets-11547754006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials are debating ratcheting back tariffs on Chinese imports as a way to calm markets and give Beijing an incentive to make deeper concessions in a trade battle that has rattled global economies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroids smacking Earth twice as often as before...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e49b55b8c20d4465b5f80522e61df8f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Giant rocks from space are falling from the sky more than they used to, but don't worry. For the past 290 million years, large asteroids have been crashing into Earth more than twice as often as they did in the previous 700 million years, according to a new study in Thursday's journal Science .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flips RANGE ROVER; 'Shocked and shaken'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8221056/prince-philip-car-crash-near-queens-sandringham-estate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Philip, 97, was left “conscious but shocked and very, very shaken” today after his Land Rover flipped in a dramatic car crash near the Sandringham estate. The fiercely independen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 700 million emails, passwords found on 'hacking' forum...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jan/17/breached-data-largest-collection-ever-seen-email-password-hacking </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Store of 770m email addresses and passwords discovered after being put on hacking site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>97-year-old reportedly not injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/754151/breaking-prince-philip-car-crash-royal-news-duke-of-edinburgh-pictures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept. Says 'Found' Money For Diplomats To Return To Work...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/state-department-diplomats-return-work-found-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Brings Emotional Support ALLIGATOR To Assisted-Living Facility...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/01/17/emotional-support-alligator-makes-new-friends-at-assisted-living-facility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet Wally, a four-and-a-half foot long emotional support alligator with razor-sharp teeth who likes to make new friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to develop space-based missile defense...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33e12cf640a6408bb11aa3defa864966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Declaring that space is the new warfighting domain, President Donald Trump on Thursday vowed the U.S. will develop an unrivaled missile defense system to protect against advanced hypersonic and cruise missile threats from competitors and adversaries. Trump said in a Pentagon speech that the U.S. will do what it takes "to ensure that we can detect and destroy any missile launched against the United States anywhere, any time, any place."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa Hitler mug found in home of Miami man cops say targeted Jews...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article224640350.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trove of Nazi memorabilia was found inside the home of Walter Stolper, who is accused of trying to kill Jews by burning down a Miami Beach condo. Prosecutors at a Feb. 7 hearing will try to keep him behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON sets conference on robotics, AI...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190117-amazon-sets-conference-robotics-artificial-intelligence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon sets conference on robotics, artificial intelligence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5-Term Republican Congressman Suddenly Resigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyitem.com/news/tom-marino-resigning-from-congress/article_90c9a66a-1a7b-11e9-b258-bb164d4c1d8e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyitem.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Marino, who just began his fifth term in the U.S. Congress, has announced his resignation effective Jan. 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist who exposed soccer corruption shot dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/27cc00bdbaf24445a13283e3c459d0db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACCRA, Ghana (AP) — An investigative journalist in Ghana who helped expose a high-ranking official at world soccer body FIFA as corrupt was shot dead by gunmen on a motorbike as he drove home alone at night, police said Thursday. His employers said he was assassinated. Ahmed Hussein-Suale was killed late Wednesday, shot twice in the chest and once in the neck at close range while driving in the suburb of Accra where he lived. He died immediately, according to police. Tiger Eye PI, the investigative journalism house Hussein-Suale worked for, said it had the hallmarks of a professional hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who built Billionaire's Row battles to sell world's tallest condo...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-man-behind-billionaires-row-battles-to-sell-the-worlds-tallest-condo-11547739897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extell’s Gary Barnett remade Manhattan’s skyline and spurred a supertall-tower boom with One57. In a faltering real-estate market, he’s hoping to sell the ultra-rich on Central Park Tower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Has 50-Pound Tumor Removed...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-01-17/50-pound-tumor-removed-from-woman-who-thought-shed-gained-weight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venom From Vampire Bats May Revolutionize Treatments For Hypertension, Heart Failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/vanom-vampire-bats-hypertension-heart-failure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It turns out Dracula may have some good in him after all. Australian scientists say the venom from vampire bats may pave the road to new treatments for a slew of medical conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detective Maligned By NETFLIX Builds Safe Room After Death Threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/inside-a-making-a-murderer-lawsuit-hidden-dangers-true-crime-tv-1176395</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Netflix hit helped launch the current boom in sleuthing docuseries. Now the detective at its center is suing for defamation — and other real-life subjects are claiming emotional distress and worse as "a cottage industry of conspiracy theorists" is turning lives "upside down."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top UK hedge fund tycoon warns: 'Revolution' if Brexit fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.fnlondon.com/articles/crispin-odey-if-brexit-is-not-delivered-we-risk-revolution-20190117</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fnlondon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-profile hedge fund manager donated generously to the Vote Leave campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON investors pressure Bezos to stop selling facial recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/amazon-shareholders-submit-resolution-on-halting-rekognition-sales-2019-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil liberties organizations, academics, and Amazon employees have all protested against facial recognition software Rekognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE THAN HALF OF BORDER UNCOVERED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/immigration-southern-border-the-wall-trump-mexico-fcfef592-03d4-4cee-9260-e4fb2929d56d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's already fencing, but it covers less than half of the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS, MEDIA LAUNCH WHISPER CAMPAIGN ON LINDSEY GRAHAM...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-dems-media-launch-whisper-campaign-lindsey-graham-gay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freshman lawmakers are suggesting the White House is blackmailing the senator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake Rattles Mudslide-Ravaged Malibu On 25th Anniversary Of Northridge...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/17/malibu-micro-earthquake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The magnitude-2.8 earthquake was reported at 12:35 a.m. at a depth of just over one mile, with an epicenter just a few miles inland from Point Dume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown Buys Illegals More Time; 42,000 Immigration Cases Canceled Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/01/16/immigration-government-shutdown-chicago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 1,200 immigration cases in Illinois have been canceled since the government shutdown. More than 42,000 cases have been canceled around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER 'representatives' training Dems on how to use social platform more effectively...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/twitter-representatives-training-dems-on-how-to-use-social-platform-more-effectively/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter is colluding with Democrats in Congress to ensure they’re using the social media platform as effectively as possible. Yesterday, USA Today reported Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, who has the largest following in the U.S. House would be taking the lead. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez dances outside her office, solicits Instant Pot recipes and gets into fights on Twitter. Soon …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Americans Drink Less Alcohol, Booze Makers Look Beyond Barrel...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/americans-are-drinking-less-alcohol-11547733600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are increasingly laying off the booze, prompting the world’s biggest brewers and liquor companies to push beyond their traditional fare and roll out teas, energy drinks and nonalcoholic spirits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood from young now on sale for old?</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/01/17/blood-from-the-young-now-on-sale-for-the-old-in-san-francisco-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company’s plasma infusions called ‘dangerous’ by UC Berkeley researchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Models Can't Keep Up With Migrating Magnetic North Pole...</title>
      <link>https://www.gizmodo.com.au/2019/01/models-cant-keep-up-with-migrating-magnetic-north-pole-and-the-us-government-shutdown-just-made-it-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gizmodo.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapid and erratic movements of Earth’s north magnetic pole have prompted an early update to a model that assists with navigation. The scheduled fix was supposed to happen on January 15, but the US government shutdown has forced an unwelcome delay....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newborn found dead in AMAZON distribution center...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/newborn-found-dead-in-amazon-distribution-center-in-phoenix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phoenix police say body was found in women's restroom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves to Fight CBS Decision to Withhold $120 Million Severance...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/leslie-moonves-to-fight-cbs-decision-to-withhold-120-million-severance-11547737633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leslie Moonves, the former chairman and CEO of CBS who resigned amid accusations of sexual harassment last September, is challenging the company’s decision last month to deny him his severance package of $120 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US plans new space sensors for missile defense against 'rogue states'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jan/17/us-plans-new-space-sensors-for-missile-defence-against-rogue-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump likely to present Pentagon findings about changing threat as justification for his planned ‘space force’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early morning quake strikes Bay Area for second day in row...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/napa-northern-california-earthquake/article/oakland-bay-area-earthquake-strength-location-13540953.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second morning in a row, East Bay residents were jolted out of bed by an earthquake.  Thursday morning's quake was mercifully a little later, at 6:11 a.m. The USGS gave it a preliminary magnitude of 3.5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen Fingers Trump in Payment to Rig Polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/michael-cohen-fingers-trump-in-payment-to-rig-polls-during-2016-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Florida Mansion Sales Surge as Tax Exiles Seek Savings...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/south-florida-luxury-properties-gain-as-tax-exiles-seek-savings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Florida Luxury Properties Gain as Tax Exiles Seek Savings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation Z may be most liberal demographic yet...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/425818-generation-z-may-be-most-liberal-demographic-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A generation of post-Millennials is poised to enter the electorate as perhaps the most liberal age cohort ever, fueled by unprecedented diversity and expansive views of the role of government. On issues ranging from th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecosystems On Collision Course With Extinction; Insect Populations Plummet...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/earths-ecosystems-are-on-a-collision-course-with-extinction-insect-populations-have-declined-by-up-to-98-percent-in-some-areas-of-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive global environmental collapse is already well underway</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Ambidextrous' robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6602105/Ambidextrous-robot-speed-online-order-processing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineers from the University of California, Berkeley, designed a new machine-learning algorithm that can teach robots to grasp and carry items.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook: Govt should let people track and delete data 'on demand'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/17/apple-ceo-tim-cook-ftc-should-let-people-track-delete-data-on-demand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Chief Executive Tim Cook said the U.S. Federal Trade Commission should form what he called a "data-broker clearinghouse."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: IT'S TIME...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/425786-the-atlantic-calls-for-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new issue of The Atlantic features a striking call for President Trump’s impeachment on its cover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foodborne illnesses on rise...</title>
      <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/investigations/2019/01/17/food-recalls-increasing-romaine-lettuce-beef-pirg-usda-fda-ecoli-salmonella/2595775002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a year of E. coli outbreaks in romaine lettuce, a new report finds food recalls have increased over the last five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
610,577 citizens: World's biggest experiment with guaranteed income...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Tiny-Indian-state-proposes-world-s-biggest-13540638.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI - High in the Himalayas, Sikkim is one of the tiniest states in India. But it is about to embark on an experiment of global interest. Sikkim's ruling party has announced an ambitious plan to implement a universal basic income for every one of its 610,577 citizens. If successful, the scheme would represent the largest trial run anywhere in the world of a concept that supporters like Facebook's Mark Zuckerberg say could provide a safety net, help alleviate poverty and address the challenge of job automation. Detractors, meanwhile, say it would reduce the incentive to work and would come at a huge expense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flushable wipes' pile up in sewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/counties/fayette-county/article224555325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Flushable” wipe clogs are occurring more frequently in Lexington’s larger pump stations that move waste through the city’s sewers, according to city workers. The obstructions have to be removed by hand in some cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests, and a punch thrown, as Louis C.K. performs at comedy club...</title>
      <link>https://datebook.sfchronicle.com/comedy/san-jose-improv-defends-louis-c-k-booking-despite-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;datebook.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Jose police stand by in patrol vehicles as people protest the appearance of comedian Louis CK at San Jose Improv on Wednesday, Jan. 16, 2019,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious naked holy men a huge draw at religious festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-religion-kumbh/mysterious-naked-holy-men-a-huge-draw-at-indias-kumbh-mela-idUSKCN1PB0HU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ash-smeared and dreadlocked Naga sadhus or Hindu ascetics, naked except for rosa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARAMOUNT Was Hollywood's 'Mountain.' Now It's Molehill...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/17/business/media/paramount-pictures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After decades of nearly slapstick mismanagement — spinning off TV and missing the internet — the studio behind “The Godfather” is fighting for its life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New taxes. Medicare, free tuition for all. She's just getting started...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-s-big-ideas-for-taxes-and-medicare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez Is the Darling of the Left, Nightmare of the Right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not your 'grandfather's' campaign: 2020 Dems look to stand out in crowded race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/425738-not-your-grandfathers-campaign-2020-dems-look-to-stand-out-in-crowded-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic candidates for 2020 are looking for new ways to get attention when they join the presidential race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natives battle Zuckerberg's Hawaii estate: 'Colonial possession'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jan/17/mark-zuckerberg-hawaii-estate-kauai-land-rights-dispute</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook CEO’s involvement in a family dispute over four small parcels of land worries many on an island where longtime residents have lost land to wealthy newcomers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO BLINKS FIRST?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1d99883921d846d1823e20b1dddf3e83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Of all the issues at stake as President Donald Trump and Democrats wrangle over his prized border wall, the latest snag is whether bargaining over the proposal should come before or after shuttered government agencies reopen. It sounds like one of those perplexing snits that frustrates Americans and prompts them to blame both parties for Washington's dysfunction. But it's actually a consequential dispute about who'll have leverage, now and later, as the partial shutdown enters its 27th day Thursday, setting a dubious record for duration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theresa May, Britain's Lady of Perpetual Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/jan/16/mays-government-survives-no-confidence-vote-after-brexit-defeat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime minister invites party leaders to discuss alternative deal but sticks to red lines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Redefines Who Is Essential to Get Parts of Govt Moving Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/16/us/politics/white-house-essential-shutdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is opening the government piece by piece, forcing thousands of workers to report to the job without pay in sectors that could benefit the president’s base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi moves to belittle and undercut Trump in shutdown fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/%E2%80%98she-wields-the-knife%E2%80%99-pelosi-moves-to-belittle-and-undercut-trump-in-shutdown-fight/ar-BBSlOIc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to announce second summit with NKorean leader?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/senior-kim-jong-un-aide-to-meet-trump-later-this-week-sources-say/ar-BBSm6u3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIULIANI: I Never Said There Was No Collusion With Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/giuliani-doesnt-deny-trump-campaign-may-have-colluded-with-russia-2019-01-16?mod=newsviewer_click</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani, the president’s personal attorney, said he doesn’t deny that the Trump campaign may have colluded with Russians in the 2016 election — only that Donald Trump himself did not..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpaid TSA Screeners Citing Financial Hardship for Missing Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-16/unpaid-tsa-screeners-citing-financial-hardship-for-missing-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican truckers fight highway robbery with armored semis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexican-truckers-fight-highway-robbery-armored-semis-030657633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speeding cars pull alongside a semi-truck, box it in and force it to a halt. It seems like something out of Hollywood, but it is happening on a daily basis on Mexico's highways. Jorge Coronel is one of those trying to stop these highway robberies, which have more than doubled in Mexico since</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel dishwasher awarded $21 million after boss made her work on Sundays...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/business/fl-bz-miami-dishwasher-jury-award-20190116-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jury has awarded a Miami hotel dishwasher $21.5 million, concluding that her employer failed to honor her religious beliefs by repeatedly scheduling her on Sundays and ultimately firing her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JIHAD' PLOT AGAINST DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-cumming-man-threatened-attack-white-house-authorities-say/REYZfPSsBFUeiJTIPkYaWN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities on Wednesday arrested a man from Forsyth County in metro Atlanta man on allegations he was plotting to attack the White House but instead got entangled with the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Jewish publication THE FORWARD ending 121-year print run...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/16/storied-jewish-publication-the-forward-ending-121-year-print-run/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Forward is stopping — its print editions. The storied Jewish-American publication is suspending its print operations and plans to lay off about 40 percent of its editorial staff — including Edi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human diet causing 'catastrophic' damage to planet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/human-diet-causing-catastrophic-damage-planet-study-005106550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The way humanity produces and eats food must radically change to avoid millions of deaths and "catastrophic" damage to the planet, according to a landmark study published Thursday. The key to both goals is a dramatic shift in the global diet -- roughly half as much sugar and red meat, and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Babies wanted: Nordic countries crying for kids...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/babies-wanted-nordic-countries-crying-kids-033117429.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oslo (AFP) - "Norway needs more children! I don't think I need to tell anyone how this is done," Norway's prime minister said cheekily, but she was raising a real concern. Too few babies are being born in the Nordic region. The Nordic countries were long a bastion of strong fertility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS claims suicide attack in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/deee082fbdf44064a5ec834ba112c53a </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A suicide bombing claimed by the Islamic State killed at least 16 people, including two U.S. service members and two American civilians, in northern Syria on Wednesday, just a month after President Donald Trump declared that IS had been defeated and he was pulling out U.S. forces. The attack in the strategic northeastern town of Manbij highlighted the threat posed by the Islamic State group despite Trump's claims. It could also complicate what had already become a messy withdrawal plan, with the president's senior advisers disagreeing with the decision and then offering an evolving timetable for the removal of the approximately 2,000 U.S. troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waiting for final Mueller report? It may be short on detail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b224c81d1e464fd19241069a2eb6058b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Robert Mueller's Russia probe has to end with a report. But anyone looking for a grand narrative on President Donald Trump, Russian election interference and all the juicy details uncovered over the last 20 months could end up disappointed. Attorney General nominee William Barr, who will oversee the investigation after an almost certain Senate confirmation, says he wants to release as much information as he can about the probe into possible coordination between Trump associates and Russia's efforts to sway the 2016 election. But during his confirmation hearing Tuesday, he also made clear that he will ultimately decide what the public sees — and that any report will be in his words, not Mueller's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI sting...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/beta-story-container/US/fbi-arrests-georgia-man-allegedly-plotting-attack-white/story?id=60429215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China brushes off outrage over death sentence, Canada fires back...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190117031158-lroy1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-CANADA/ (UPDATE 2, TV):UPDATE 2-China brushes off outrage over death sentence, Canada fires back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New job of vice president's wife sparks LGBT furor...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190116215702-t4mxg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-LGBT/PENCE:New job of US vice president's wife sparks LGBT+ furor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global economy 'headed for recession'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190116130324-fza8m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-ECONOMY/KEMP (COLUMN):COLUMN-Global economy is headed for recession: Kemp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown could threaten SUPER BOWL...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/politics/the-jolt-johnny-isakson-worries-shutdown-could-threaten-super-bowl/zXDUcSey3VHAk9wFtIcc8O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publicly, Republican lawmakers from Georgia are holding the line on the partial federal government s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first robot hotel fires half of 'annoying' non-human workforce...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/01/16/worlds-first-robot-hotel-fires-half-annoying-non-human-workforce-8352150/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It turns out the rise of the robots isn't something people working in the tourist industry have to worry about quite yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>86-year-old loses 120-lbs by walking in living room...</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/2019/01/15/missouri-86-year-old-loses-120-pounds-by-walking-in-her-living-room-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS -- No gym, no problem! An 86-year-old St. Louis woman says she lost 120 pounds just by walking back and forth from her living room to kitchen every day in her one-bedroom apartment. "Even as a kid in Mississippi, I was always the fattest kid in the class. I got teased a lot," Jessica Slaughter told KSDK. "I didn't know how to stop eating. Fried chicken. Bacon and eggs. Desserts, like cakes and pies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mass casualties' via IEDs, anti-tank rocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/forsyth-county-man-charged-with-plot-to-attack-white-house-fbi-says/905525963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new information we're learning about the suspect, LIVE on the Channel 2 Action News Nightbeat at 11 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS THWART DC TERROR THREAT</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/georgia/articles/2019-01-16/fbi-georgia-man-arrested-in-plot-to-attack-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO, NO, NO!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/16/has-trump-met-his-match-pelosi-1106624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi’s move to derail Trump’s State of the Union address underscores her aggressive challenge to the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-ft Great White spotted in Hawaii eating whale...</title>
      <link>https://www.khon2.com/news/local-news/great-white-shark-spotted-off-the-south-shore-eating-a-dead-whale/1704846429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khon2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's something you don't see very often. A great white shark in Hawaii waters.  The large white shark-- who researchers named "Deep Blue" --was spotted miles off of the south shore over the past two days.   She was feeding on a dead sperm whale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVERS IN DISBELIEF SNAP PICS...</title>
      <link>https://ftw.usatoday.com/2019/01/deep-blue-perhaps-the-largest-known-great-white-shark-spotted-off-hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ftw.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strikingly massive great white shark, one of the largest ever documented, was spotted by divers in Hawaii on Sunday as the apex predator feasted on a sperm whale carcass. The sighting of “Deep Bl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Susan Rice, Obama officials to answer questions in Clinton email case...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/16/susan-rice-clinton-email-lawsuit/2592081002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Judge Royce Lamberth said the case of Clinton's email server involved "one of the gravest modern offenses to government transparency."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Elementary students 'put into effect plot to murder' child...</title>
      <link>https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2019/01/16/details-reveal-roberts-elementary-students-planned-murder-plot-tallahassee-leon-county-schools/2585737002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tallahassee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the students brought a bag to school with a wrench, baseball batting gloves, adjustable clamp pliers, and a multitool with a blade on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN SACHS Tactic in Huge Fraud Case: Smear Ex-Partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/16/business/goldman-malaysia-1mdb-leissner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investment bank is campaigning to convince authorities that a former partner, Tim Leissner, was a master con man — and that is how the bank became ensnared in a vast fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First artificial meteor shower set to fly...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90293194/the-worlds-first-artificial-meteor-shower-is-set-to-fly-over-japan-tonight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astro Live Experiences is going to put on a show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS waiving penalty for some in first filing season under tax law...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/425747-irs-waiving-penalty-for-some-in-first-filing-season-under-trumps-tax-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRS on Wednesday announced that it will waive a penalty for some taxpayers who didn't have enough money withheld from their paychecks last year, in an effort to aid people as they adjust to the tax-code changes made by President Trump's t</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
