<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trust in media hits bottom; 60% say sources pay for stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trust-in-media-hits-bottom-60-say-sources-pay-for-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidence in the media has hit rock bottom, with many news consumers believing that reporters file their reports before knowing the facts and 60 percent are under the impression that sources pay for stories, according to a depressing new survey of American journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her Dad Died a Decade Ago. She's 3...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/02/posthumous-reproduction-israel-sperm-donors-ivf/583588/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is preserving a Jewish bloodline worth creating a child who will never know her father?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie shakeup: Top staff leaves campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/bernie-sanders-staff-shakeup-top-strategists-leave-his-presidential-campaign-n976221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief strategist of the Vermont independent's 2016 campaign and two other aides cited creative differences as they parted ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US press booted from hotel after NKorean officials 'flipped out'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/26/us-press-booted-from-vietnam-hotel-after-north-korean-officials-flipped-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House press corps was kicked out of its filing center in Hanoi, site of the two-day summit between President Trump and Kim Jong Un, when the North Korean leader’s security detail re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup maestro dupes town through network of lies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/897c540ddfb647e6971bd77d6b12e305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPELIKA, Ala. (AP) — Looking back, there are so many reasons Kyle Sandler was able to separate so many people from so much of their money. Sandler rolled into this old railroad crossroads at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust in media hits bottom; 60% say sources pay for stories...</title>
      <link>ttps://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trust-in-media-hits-bottom-60-say-sources-pay-for-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother, daughter charged in deaths of five relatives...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/pennsylvania/murder-bucks-county-morrisville-pa-suicide-plan-homicide-probable-cause-affidavit-20190226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two survivors charged in the case apparently also intended to die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC plan calls for congestion pricing, weed tax to fix crumbling transit system...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Cuomo-De-Blasio-Announce-10-Point-Proposal-for-MTA-Overhaul-New-York-City-506381411.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio and Gov. Cuomo announced Tuesday a proposal to transform the MTA and create funding streams for the agency, which includes the joint endorsement of congestion pricing — marking the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIEWING GUIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/projects/la-na-pol-michael-cohen-testimony-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen spent more than a decade as Donald Trump's lawyer, fixer and attack dog. Now he's been cooperating with prosecutors and is testifying publicly before Congress for the first time Wednesday. Here is everything you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Buenos Aires rabbi brutally beaten in home attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.jta.org/2019/02/26/global/chief-rabbi-of-buenos-aires-beaten-and-seriously-injured-in-home-invasion-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jta.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The assailants shouted that they knew he was the community rabbi, tied up his wife, and stole money and belongings from his apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New fitness test presents challenges for Military...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/new-fitness-test-presents-challenges-for-army-guard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army National Guard is looking for nearly 5,000 fitness instructors and buying roughly $40 million in workout equipment in the next seven months to help its soldiers meet new physical fitness standards being set by the military service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS CALLS WITNESS CONVICTED OF LYING TO CONGRESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/michael-cohen-testifies-behind-closed-doors-on-capitol-hill-in-first-of-three-hearings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago voters to pick from largest field of mayoral candidates in city's 181-year history...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/politics/ct-met-chicago-mayors-race-election-day-20190225-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago voters will head to the polls Tuesday to pick from a record 14 contenders to become the city’s next mayor, an exercise that almost certainly will narrow the field down to two finalists rather than decide an outright winner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Justice Kavanaugh Flunks His First Test as an Originalist...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2019/02/25/brett-kavanaugh-flunks-his-first-test-as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike Thomas and Gorsuch, Kavanaugh stayed mum on originalism in a major constitutional case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delays release of tax returns...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/sanders-stammers-when-asked-about-when-hell-release-his-very-boring-tax-returns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders will release his “very boring tax returns” sometime soon, in the future, just not right now. The socialist senator from Vermont owns several homes and has inked lucrative book deals in recent years, despite his heated rhetoric about evil rich Americans who allegedly don’t pay their fair share. Sanders recently joined a crowded …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW Robin Roberts Thinks There Was 'Lot of Red Flags' in Smollett Case?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2019/02/25/oh-now-robin-roberts-thinks-there-was-lot-red-flags-smollett-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Morning America co-host Robin Roberts, the woman who refused to say the word “alleged” when interviewing Jussie Smollett, has suddenly discovered that there were “a lot of red flags” in the hate crimes case, now widely dismissed as a hoax. Roberts got a do-over as she interviewed Chicago’s superintendent of police, Eddie Johnson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAT FEST ON HILL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/michael-cohen-will-give-congress-evidence-trump-criminal-conduct-source-n976046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A knowledgeable source told NBC News Trump's ex-attorney will detail what he will describe as the president's lies, racism and cheating as a private businessman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Backup Disk' Of Human Knowledge Sent To Moon For Safe Keeping...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90311572/lunar-library-30-million-pages-of-backup-human-culture-head-to-moon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arch Mission Foundation’s Lunar Library is headed to the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Warming: Los Angeles Has Coldest February in 60 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2019/02/25/global-warming-los-angeles-has-coldest-february-in-60-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles is officially experiencing the coldest February in nearly 60 years, according to the National Weather Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PODESTA PREDICTS:  ROGERS STONE GOING TO PRISON...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/hillary-clintons-campaign-chairman-victim-2016-campaign-hack/story?id=61235732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Podesta still believes Roger Stone played a role in releasing his hacked emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs Experience Profound Personality Changes As Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-personality-changes-owners-personalities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's probably no surprise to their owners, but dogs, much like people, have distinct personalities (canine-alities?) that shift and change over time, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to Provide Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/michael-cohen-reportedly-plans-to-provide-evidence-of-trumps-criminal-activity-to-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka challenges Ocasio-Cortez; Americans don't want 'guaranteed minimum'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ivanka-trump-challenges-ocasio-cortez-platform-says-americans-dont-want-guaranteed-minimum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump, President Trump’s daughter and a White House senior adviser, lauded her father’s economy and said the majority of Americans ideologically believe differently than Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, in an interview with Fox News host Steve Hilton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funeral firm to sue pastor for 'resurrection stunt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-47370398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say a South African pastor's outlandish video has caused them reputational damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USGS: California's Next 'Big One' Could Be VOLCANIC Eruption...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/02/25/californias-big-one-volcanic-eruption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's next 'big one' may not be an earthquake. According to a new study from the U.S. Geological Survey, a future volcanic eruption is not only inevitable, hundreds of thousands of people are in harm's way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Car Tech Rat Driver Out to Cops...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/02/25/autonomous-snitch-car-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company behind the technology says it will keep people safe, but is it an invasion of privacy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Secret Sting Ops to Expose Celeb Psychics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/26/magazine/psychics-skeptics-facebook.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are some celebrity mediums fooling their audience members by reading social media pages in advance? A group of online vigilantes is out to prove it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Socialism talk will sink Dems; Left-wing overreach backfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ny-oped-socialism-talk-will-sink-democrats-20190225-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don’t quite know what a handbasket is, but the Democratic Party is heading in one to electoral hell with its talk of socialism and reparations. Given a Republican incumbent who has never exceeded 50% in Gallup’s approval ratings poll and who won the presidency thanks to a dysfunctional electoral</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of Watergate...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-michael-cohen-trump-oversight-hearing-20190226-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, who once vowed to "take a bullet" for President Trump, will testify Wednesday in a House hearing that could be as consequential as John Dean's appearance before a congressional committee during Watergate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROTTEN TOMATOES tweaks audience ratings system to thwart trolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.denofgeek.com/uk/movies/rotten-tomatoes/63655/rotten-tomatoes-captain-marvel-site-changes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denofgeek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World has become more peaceful, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6743223/The-world-peaceful-fewer-people-dying-armed-conflicts-scientists-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts from Norway's Peace Research Institute Oslo examined statistics from 'all possible' wars, the countries involved, and how many people were killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets live chip implant at tech fair...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenews.com.pk/latest/437210-man-gets-live-under-skin-chip-implant-at-mobile-fair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenews.com.pk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man gets live chip implant at mobile fair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson banned from FACEBOOK, INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/feb/26/tommy-robinson-banned-from-facebook-and-instagram</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right founder of English Defence League repeatedly breached hate speech rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'APOLLO 11' review: Eye-opening documentary five-star triumph...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/feb/25/apollo-11-review-eye-opening-documentary-is-a-five-star-triumph</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exceptional, vibrant restoration of never-before-seen footage results in one of the most astounding films about space ever made</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-cohen/trumps-ex-fixer-cohen-to-offer-new-russia-details-to-u-s-congress-source-idUSKCN1QF12R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's former personal attorney Michael Cohen plans to te...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May surrenders to Remainers: Promises vote on delaying Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6746049/PM-holds-crisis-Cabinet-sign-two-month-Brexit-delay.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May is gathering her senior team as tensions hit new heights, with negotiations deadlocked in Brussels and just weeks to go until the UK is due to crash out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMTRAK train with 183 passengers stranded in Oregon for more than 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/26/us/oregon-train-passengers-stranded-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Amtrak train headed for Los Angeles with nearly 200 people on board came to a standstill Sunday evening after hitting a tree that had fallen onto the tracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using 1 germ to fight another when antibiotics fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b4c7e8aace4d45bca6d4b2f6b2ee0ac0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW HAVEN, Conn. (AP) — Bacteria lodged deep in Ella Balasa's lungs were impervious to most antibiotics. At 26, gasping for breath, she sought out a dramatic experiment — deliberately inhaling a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border rebuke looms for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/431526-border-rebuke-looms-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) isn’t going to use political capital to fight a Democratic-sponsored resolution disapproving of President Trump’s emergency declaration for the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOOSE TIGHTENS ON MADURO...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/venezuelas-guaido-meets-foreign-allies-anti-maduro-strategy-085421973.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Vice President Mike Pence and Venezuela opposition leader Juan Guaido agreed on a strategy to tighten the noose around President Nicolas Maduro following a meeting with regional allies in Colombia on Monday. Pence announced more sanctions against Venezuela and $56 million in aid for neighboring countries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Vatican cleric Cardinal Pell convicted of child sex crimes...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/top-vatican-cleric-cardinal-pell-convicted-child-sex-001713104.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian Cardinal George Pell, who helped elect popes and ran the Vatican's finances, has been found guilty of sexually assaulting two choirboys, a court said Tuesday, becoming the most senior Catholic cleric ever convicted of child sex crimes. An Australian court found Pell guilty by a trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospice Documenting Patients' Mysterious Dream Experiences...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/02/25/hospice-buffalo-death-dreams-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Death is one of the mysteries of life. But the dreams of patients at Hospice Buffalo in New York State are revealing something incredible about the process of dying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One in four teen suicides involves internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2019/02/25/internet-played-role-quarter-teenage-suicides-official-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internet played a role in a quarter of teenage suicides, an official inquiry has revealed - as its author accused social media firms of having shown &amp;ldquo;little concern&amp;rdquo; to stop self-harm online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Kraft charged with soliciting prostitution on day of AFC title game...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/news/20190225/robert-kraft-sao-files-charges-report-details-visit-to-jupiter-spa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New England Patriots owner Robert Kraft is among 25 men arrested following a sting at a Jupiter day spa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY SURROUNDS ZARIF 'RESIGNATION'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Mystery-surrounds-Mohammad-Javad-Zarifs-resignation-581810 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the report there are other diplomats who will resign if Zarif indeed leaves the foreign ministry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia claims USA preparing to invade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/762009/venezuela-invasion-us-military-troops-russia-claims-maduro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Weighs Fate of 40-Foot Cross Built as War Memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/supreme-court-weighs-fate-of-40-foot-cross-built-as-war-memorial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Weighs Fate of 40-Foot Cross Built as War Memorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCALATION: India strikes inside Pakistan after deadly Kashmir attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e64d72f76c4f475493e4d41501ebab06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PESHAWAR, Pakistan (AP) — Pakistan says India launched an airstrike on its territory early Tuesday that caused no casualties, while India said it targeted a terrorist training camp in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES HANOI</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/872da8b73d8f4b35a41f6a904b9e55f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HANOI, Vietnam (AP) — North Korean leader Kim Jong Un spent the eve of his summit with Donald Trump traveling around Hanoi in his armored limousine Tuesday, his squad of encircling bodyguards in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: Cohen to Testify That Trump Engaged in Criminal Conduct While in Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cohen-to-testify-that-trump-engaged-in-criminal-conduct-while-in-office-11551175201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, Donald Trump’s former lawyer, will for the first time publicly accuse the president of criminal conduct while in office related to a hush-money payment to a porn star, a person familiar with his planned testimony before Congress said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVISION Ramos briefly detained after Maduro shown 'garbage eating' video...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-univision/venezuela-to-deport-univision-team-after-maduro-shown-garbage-eating-video-idUSKCN1QF05F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. television network Univision said on Monday Venezuela was deporting a news ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacked and powerless, Venezuela soldiers choose desertion...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5047b6d203bb473ea3ca704ad630b898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUCUTA, Colombia (AP) — The simple house on a street ridden with potholes in this town on Colombia's restive border with Venezuela has become a refuge for the newly homeless — 40 Venezuelan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen hearings designed to keep public in dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-cohen-hearings-designed-to-keep-public-in-dark-about-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump lawyer and fixer Michael Cohen is scheduled to appear before three congressional committees this week before he heads to jail to serve a sentence for tax evasion and lying to Congress. On Tuesday, Cohen will testify before the Senate Intelligence Committee. On Wednesday, he will go…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Virginia, AMAZON faces some New York-style pushback...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/virginia-amazon-faces-some-new-york-style-pushback-n975836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “For Us, Not Amazon” coalition is calling for transparency from Amazon and politicians over their plans for the East Coast headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The skier who made 'impossible' descent of deadly K2...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/adventure/2019/02/national-geographic-2019-adventurers-of-the-year/andrzej-bargiel-ski-mountaineer-k2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many have died attempting to ski the world's second tallest mountain. See how National Geographic Adventurer of the Year Andrzej Bargiel made history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POMPEO: 'Just front man for corrupt religious mafia'...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/middle-east-news/iran/iranian-foreign-minister-zarif-announces-resignation-in-instagram-post-1.6965180</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET TRIAL: Powerful Cardinal Guilty of Child Sex Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-02-26/george-pell-trial-why-cardinal-court-case-held-in-secret/10233118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cardinal George Pell was found guilty of child sex offences last year, in a courtroom full of journalists. So why is the verdict only being made public now?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blows Past $10M Raised, 39% From NEW Donors...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/431519-nearly-40-percent-of-sanders-2020-donors-used-email-address-never</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 40 percent of donors to Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blows Past $10M Raised, 39% From NEW Donors...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/25/us/politics/bernie-sanders-10-million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Sanders started the race with the largest donor network in the 2020 field. That list has grown substantially since then, as more than a third of his donations came from new email addresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MAN BEHIND MUELLER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/its-muellers-investigation-but-right-behind-him-is-andrew-goldstein/ar-BBU4y4N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Faces Contempt Claim for Tweeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-25/elon-musk-faces-u-s-contempt-claim-for-violating-sec-accord-jskytn6n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangers of Mandatory DNA Database...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2019/02/dangers-mandatory-dna-database/155028/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A controversy in Arizona is a portent of future public-policy fights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Devices with 'Moral AI' Could Call Police on Owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/02/25/report-home-assistants-with-moral-ai-could-call-police-on-owners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Mail reported that home assistants could soon report their owners to the police for breaking the law based on a "Moral A.I." system, if the ideas of academics in Europe are implemented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They built this. It's theirs': Reporter blames social for jailing...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/world/asia/philippine-journalist-facebook-is-partly-responsible-for-her-jailing-20190226-p5107j.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Man Behind Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/25/us/politics/andrew-goldstein-mueller-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel has a reputation as the all-knowing investigator, but Andrew D. Goldstein, a former Time magazine reporter, has a day-to-day role in one of the central lines of investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead humpback in Brazil jungle puzzles researchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/dead-humpback-whale-in-brazils-amazon-jungle-puzzles-researchers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biologists were baffled to discover the body of a huge humpback whale in the midst of shrubbery in Brazil's Amazon jungle over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosenstein says govt transparency isn't always advisable...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5dede9c0dedb477fb3dd817784bfd603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The man who long oversaw special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation said Monday that it is not always appropriate for the government to be transparent about its work as he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens If...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-trump-russia-scenarios/what-happens-if-mueller-finds-trump-fingerprints-in-russia-conspiracy-idUKKCN1QE2H0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller is preparing to submit to U.S. Attorney General W...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady gives Bob Kraft hug in show of support...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/25/robert-kraft-flies-home-with-tom-brady-after-prostitution-bust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper, the award for the tenderest on-camera moment goes to . . . Robert Kraft and Tom Brady! The allegedly hooker-loving New England Patriots owner and his star quart…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weiner ditches politics for weed business...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6735613/Anthony-Weiner-ditches-politics-marijuana-business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Weiner, 54, met with a potential business partner to discuss getting involved in the marijuana business. The two had a breakfast meeting in downtown New York City on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President announces recovery of American hostage in Yemen...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/02/25/politics/donald-trump-daniel-burch-yemen-hostage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump announced Monday that the United States has recovered Danny Burch, an American citizen who was being held hostage in Yemen for the last year and a half.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>900 people died in measles outbreak. Could it happen in USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/02/25/measles-outbreak-900-dead-madagascar-could-happen-u-s/2977595002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As public health officials monitor a measles outbreak in Washington state, WHO says a separate measles epidemic inÂ Madagascar has killed hundreds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strep outbreak prompts antibiotics FOR ALL at basic training...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2019/02/25/strep-outbreak-prompts-antibiotics-for-all-at-fort-benning-basic-training/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six soldiers have been treated so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DON JR: Feds using 'Stalinist' tactics against family...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0912533d1cc439185273d84ac5ad4b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's eldest son says federal authorities are using "Stalinist" tactics as they investigate the president's inaugural committee and family...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities: Kraft visited parlor for sex on day of AFC game...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75dec6f5f50a40d4a38731a3812db940</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Authorities say New England Patriots owner Robert Kraft visited a Florida massage parlor for sex acts on the morning of the AFC Championship Game, which he attended in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico president sells predecessors' bulletproof cars...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/mexico-president-sells-bulletproof-cars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador says his administration has auctioned off most of the bulletproof and luxury vehicles used by past presidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former campaign staffer alleges in suit that Trump 'kissed' without consent...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/former-campaign-staffer-alleges-in-lawsuit-that-trump-kissed-her-without-her-consent-the-white-house-denies-the-charge/2019/02/25/fe1869a4-3498-11e9-946a-115a5932c45b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In interviews and in the lawsuit, Alva Johnson said Trump grabbed her hand and leaned in to kiss her on the lips as he exited an RV outside the rally in Tampa on Aug. 24, 2016. Johnson said she turned her head and the unwanted kiss landed on the side of her mouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weed killer in wine and beer?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/02/25/new-pirg-study-says-weed-killer-in-your-wine-beer/2943880002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. PIRG tested five wines and 15 beers, including organic ones, and found traces of the controversial herbicideÂ glyphosate in 19 of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rami Malek treated by medics after  tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/popculture/rami-malek-treated-medics-after-fall-oscars-t149353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the "Bohemian Rhapsody" actor, a triumphant night took an awkward turn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Critics Fume...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/green-book-critics-best-picture-oscar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times and Los Angeles Times critics were very displeased with "Green Book" winning Best Picture at the Oscars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos wants to put TRILLION humans in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8503517/amazon-jeff-bezos-space-blue-origin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON chief Jeff Bezos dreams of creating a new space race of humans across our solar system – with a population of one trillion. The billionaire tech mogul revealed the lofty goal during a speech…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU draws up plans to delay until 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8500453/brexit-delayed-until-2021-backstop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU chiefs are drawing up a plan to delay Brexit until 2021 to do away with a need for any Irish backstop. Under the latest thinking in Brussels, Britain’s 21 month transition period after exit day …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect cancer in 10 mins?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/feb/24/the-10-minute-test-for-cancer-pioneering-methods-blood-test-detection-tumours-lung-breast-colorectal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pioneering methods are being developed to find traces of tumours quickly in small blood samples</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE: Time to complete revolution we started!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2019/feb/25/its-time-to-complete-the-revolution-we-started </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, our campaign began the political revolution. Now, it is time to defeat Donald Trump, complete that revolution and implement the vision we fought for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake on a plane goes 9,300 miles in woman's shoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2019/feb/25/snake-plane-australia-scotland-shoe </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holidaymaker shocked to see stowaway python in her slip-ons on return from Queensland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley on Alert as Dems Eye Top Antitrust Mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lina-khan-a-top-anti-trust-thinker-joins-democratic-staff-in-the-house-putting-silicon-valley-on-alert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Khan, who wrote a semi-viral article about Amazon, is in discussions to join the staff of the congressional panel overseeing antitrust issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Putin's warning, Russian TV lists nuclear targets in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-nuclear-russia/after-putins-warning-russian-tv-lists-nuclear-targets-in-u-s-idUSKCN1QE1DM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian state television has listed U.S. military facilities that Moscow would t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syria's Assad meets Khamenei in first Iran visit since war began...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-assad/syrias-assad-meets-khamenei-in-first-iran-visit-since-war-began-idUSKCN1QE24G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syrian President Bashar al Assad made his first public visit to his closest regi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Clinton staffers slam Sanders over private jet flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/25/bernie-sanders-hillary-clinton-private-jet-flights-1182793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator’s 2016 travel as a Clinton surrogate became “a running joke in the office.“</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of live FISH rain from sky during mega storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/hundreds-live-fish-rain-sky-14050294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Malta enjoyed a free pick of seafood as they battled gale-force winds and high waves during storm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing woes throughout nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/governors-grapple-with-housing-woes-felt-throughout-nation-2019-02-25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Vermont to California, governors and housing associations agree Americans in rural and urban areas are facing a housing affordability crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GREEN BOOK' OVERCOMES BACKLASH, NABS BEST PICTURE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/2019-oscars-green-book-wins-best-picture-1189784</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Farrelly's film nabbed three wins on Sunday night, including the top honor at the 91st Academy Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bye-bye Beverley: Credits roll for Paris's last porn cinema...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190225-bye-bye-beverley-credits-roll-pariss-last-porn-cinema</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bye-bye Beverley: Credits roll for Paris's last porn cinema</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Muslim official arrested after holy site unrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190224-israel-arrests-top-muslim-official-after-holy-site-unrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel arrests top Muslim official after holy site unrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot 'GOD': AI deity to preach in temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1091915/Japan-robot-God-robot-buddhist-Kyoto-temple-Kannon-Bodhisattva</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A JAPANESE robot has been created to preach the teachings of Buddha in colloquial language at the Kodaiji Temple in the ancient city of Kyoto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO-CORTEZ: People Shouldn't Reproduce Due To 'Climate Change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/43880/ocasio-cortez-people-maybe-shouldnt-reproduce-due-ryan-saavedra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic socialist Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-NY) suggested on Sunday night that people should consider not having children due to climate change because there is a "scientific consensus" that life will be hard for kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Biblical' locust plague set to hit Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/761648/locusts-Egypt-biblical-UN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden plague: Disease X predicted to kill millions of HEALTHY people...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/761387/disease-x-to-kill-healthy-people-spanish-flu-world-health-organisation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists fear end to Mankind...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/760048/civilisation-collapse-when-end-of-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRISPR Infuses First Human in Landmark Gene-Editing Study...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/crispr-infuses-first-human-in-landmark-gene-editing-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crispr Therapeutics AG says it has treated the first human by gene editing technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired-Up Iowans Want Winner but Disagree on Who Can Beat Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/fired-up-iowans-want-a-winner-but-disagree-on-who-can-beat-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fired-Up Iowans Want a Winner but Disagree on Who Can Beat Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Green New Deal Costs $93,000,000,000,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-25/group-sees-ocasio-cortez-s-green-new-deal-costing-93-trillion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour to back new Brexit referendum...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-47363307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeremy Corbyn says the party is prepared to support a new public vote as MPs seek to delay the UK's exit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid image shows touchdown marks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-47359152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new image from Japan's Hayabusa-2 spacecraft reveals a dark splodge where it touched down on the surface of an asteroid last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expectations low as Trump looks for win in NKorea summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f8f44f79449b4b06bd1cb10889896d80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump will head into his second meeting with North Korea's Kim Jong Un having reframed what would make a successful summit, lowering expectations for Pyongyang's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-stakes trial over ROUNDUP cancer claim to begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d46918f31f5f4713b322b623ae5ad3c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A jury in federal court in San Francisco will decide whether Roundup weed killer caused a California man's cancer in a trial starting Monday that plaintiffs' attorneys say...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40-Foot Cross Divides Community; Prompts Supreme Court Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cb5d73cde81c4b83b67aa9814116abb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLADENSBURG, Md. (AP) — Steven C. Lowe says he has always thought that a 40-foot-tall (12-meter-tall) concrete cross that stands on a large, grassy highway median near his home was odd. For...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor People's Campaign to hold bus tours of poverty areas...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7ce398637a4b415e9bdc70cc8ccff7ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — The Poor People's Campaign will hold bus tours of poverty-stricken areas in more than 20 states to call attention to "what the national emergencies really are" in the wake of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive monkeys back at zoo, days after breakout...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/383e4a0ebc51471485466f15b303ad80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A 17-year-old fugitive monkey has been reunited with her daughter at a Berlin zoo after being caught at a railway station in the German capital. Both the capuchin monkey and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor knocks borders, walls during speech in Spanish...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/431364-javier-bardem-knocks-borders-walls-during-oscars-speech-in-spanish</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Javier Bardem appeared to push back on President Trump’s immigration rhetoric at the Academy Awards, telling the audience in Spanish, “There are no borders or walls that can restrain ingenuity and talent.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah's tunnels offer sneak peek at looming major conflict with Israel...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/politics/431370-hezbollahs-tunnels-offer-sneak-peek-at-looming-major-conflict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is vitally important that American policymakers, the media and other public leaders recognize, publicize and highlight Israel’s lawful efforts to address the illicit threats posed by Hezbollah – for the sakes of our ally, U.S. national security and regional stability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHASE Bank Denies Service to Conservatives...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/time-for-action-chase-bank-denies-service-to-conservatives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you think banks should be allowed to discriminate against conservatives for their political views?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACKLASH BREWING:  Outrage As Construction Begins On New STARBUCKS  -- Right Across Street From Popular Philly Coffee Shop...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/02/24/philadelphia-coffee-controversy-starbucks-la-colombe-dilworth-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphians are split over the new Starbucks being built in Dilworth Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stage designed to look like Trump hair?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/24/the-oscars-stage-this-year-strongly-resembles-donald-trumps-hair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you’ve seen it, you can’t unsee it. Social media users are convinced that the Oscars stage was inspired this year by President Trump’s hair. “I can’t be the only …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires for Bloomberg: Warren Buffett Endorses...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/billionaires-for-bloomberg-warren-buffett-says-he-would-support-mike-bloomberg-for-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGET: MADURO</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuelas-guaido-meets-foreign-allies-anti-maduro-strategy-085421096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United States Vice President Mike Pence told Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido that Donald Trump supports him "100 percent" as the pair met regional allies on Monday to thrash out a strategy to remove Nicolas Maduro from power after the failed attempt to ship in humanitarian aid. The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Americans' Perceptions of USA World Image Best Since 2003...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/247064/americans-perceptions-world-image-best-2003.aspx </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-eight percent of Americans say the U.S. rates favorably in the world, up slightly from last year, and the highest figure Gallup has found since 2003.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Food Preservatives May Make You Lazy...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/02/22/texas-researchers-food-preservatives-lazy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The research focuses on inorganic phosphates, which are added to foods like cereals, packaged snacks and sodas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furious Spike Lee Paces Aisle, Turns Back To Stage...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/spike-lee-green-book-storms-out-oscars-blackkklansman-jordan-peele-1202564402/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with details from backstage: While he didn’t take the stage like Kanye West did years ago on the MTV Video Music Awards when Taylor Swift won an award that he felt should have gone to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Ratings Rise With Hostless Show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/2019-oscars-ratings-rise-spike-lee-protest-green-book-abc-1202564523/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 10:53 AM: A bleary eyed Hollywood is already thinking about the 92nd Academy Awards this morning and now the last announcement of last night’s hostless Oscars is upon us. The final numbers …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advocates stand up in court for abused animals...</title>
      <link>https://ctmirror.org/2019/02/24/advocates-stand-up-in-court-for-abused-animals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ctmirror.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Connecticut's first-in-the-nation law permits animal advocates in courtrooms for abuse cases involving dogs and cats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Prosecutor says lack of evidence for rape claim against Luc Besson...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/629becd503324be798ba0cc9b55f6fc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Paris prosecutor's office says an investigation failed to turn up evidence to support a woman's rape allegation against filmmaker Luc Besson and the case has been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA's 'BLACK PANTHER' tweets leave fans confused...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/cias-black-panther-tweets-oscars-leaves-fans-confused/story?id=61289094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency sent out a dozen or so tweets about the fictional tech in the film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>http://www.jewishworldreview.com/0219/shapiro_archives.php3#.XG2A5KJKhhE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jewishworldreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we on road to civilization collapse?</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20190218-are-we-on-the-road-to-civilisation-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studying the demise of historic civilisations can tell us about the risk we face today, says collapse expert Luke Kemp. Worryingly, the signs are worsening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS:  Madonna and Guy Oseary's After-Party...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/longform/oscars-2019-after-party-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga and others attended Madonna and Guy Oseary's annual soirée</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop arrested couple perform sex acts in rear of squad car...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/sex/police-cruiser-tryst-539210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 24--A Florida cop has been disciplined for allowing a couple under arrest to smoke, kiss, cuddle, and engage in sexual activity while they were in the rear of a police cruiser, according to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ice Tsunami' Forces Evacuations Along Lake Erie...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/02/25/lake-erie-ice-tsunami/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High winds continue to cause chaos across the East coast, and residents along Lake Erie are dealing with another problem caused by the winds, an ice tsunami.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican leader knocks racism at home after 'ROMA' wins...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190225153257-x363j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AWARDS-OSCARS/MEXICO-RACISM:Mexican leader knocks racism at home after 'Roma' Oscar wins</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Voters Annoyed As Phones Flooded With Texts Amid Mayoral Campaign...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/02/25/mayoral-campaign-text-messages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just one day until Chicago’s mayoral election, campaigns are working overtime, which might mean overloading your phones with text messages.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
