<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>For Muhammad Ali's grandson, family legacy extends beyond ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/2021/12/10/nico-ali-walsh-muhammad-ali-grandson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nico Ali Walsh looks to remain undefeated in his pro career as he prepares for his final challenge of 2021, a middleweight bout Saturday at Madison Square Garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Maxwell Photo Signal Fresh Legal Danger for Prince Andrew?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/does-ghislaine-and-epstein-photograph-signal-fresh-legal-danger-for-prince-andrew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A just-revealed photograph of Jeffrey Epstein and Ghislaine Maxwell lounging in the queen’s private Balmoral cabin shows just how toxic Andrew’s past is for the royals’ future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is NASA Sending New Telescope Million Miles Away?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/12/james-webb-space-telescope-lagrange-point/620935/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From one very specific point, a space telescope can see for light-years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another variant spreads in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1534321/covid-new-variant-found-france-marseille-hospital-forcalquier-ihu-b16402-omicron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANOTHER variant of coronavirus has been detected by experts working in Marseille, France, as the world continues to battle the deadly virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR studio launches high-tech sex dolls to take user to 'futuristic brothel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/vr-studio-launches-high-tech-25663944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virtual reality porn studio DaDoinkVR has teamed up with Berlin-based sex doll creator Kokeshi Cybrothel to merge the world of high-tech sex dolls with 180 degree stereoscopic virtual reality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Over, Tennis and Golf. Networks, Brands Cashing In on Pickleball...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/move-over-tennis-and-golf-networks-and-brands-are-cashing-in-on-pickleball</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move Over, Tennis and Golf. Networks and Brands Are Cashing In on Pickleball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden set to make 1st late-night TV appearance as president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-jimmy-fallon-2cfef220d15c5dcc07352d07e46c297c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is getting ready for his first late-night TV appearance since taking office. Biden is set to appear Friday on NBC’s “The Tonight Show” with comedian Jimmy Fallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold weather states struggling to hire snowplow drivers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-storms-pennsylvania-e694fe4467db0116dd32fae4806d5dd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA, Mont. (AP) — More U.S. drivers could find themselves stuck on snowy highways or have their travel delayed this winter due to a shortage of snowplow drivers — a reality that could hit home Friday as winter storms start dumping snow from the Intermountain West to the Upper Great Lakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rift Between Senator, Son Shows the Challenge of Taxing Ultrarich...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/10/rift-between-senator-and-son-shows-the-challenge-of-taxing-the-ultrarich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — ADW Capital Partners would appear to be the kind of hedge fund that Democrats on the Senate Finance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In TX, Battle Over What Can Be Taught, and What Books Can Be Read...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/10/in-texas-a-battle-over-what-can-be-taught-and-what-books-can-be-read/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO — In late September, Carrie Damon, a middle school librarian, celebrated “Banned Books Week,” an annual free-speech event,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Innovation: Troll Philanthropy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/10/elon-musks-latest-innovation-troll-philanthropy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The richest people on earth typically devote a share of their vast resources to charity. That is the bargain and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK: I'M THINKING OF QUITTING...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/teslas-musk-says-he-is-thinking-of-quitting-his-jobs-2021-12-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk is "thinking of" leaving his jobs and becoming an influencer, the world's richest man tweeted on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Braces for latest inflation surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/09/investors-brace-for-the-highest-inflation-reading-in-nearly-40-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street expects the the CPI to reflect a 0.7% gain for the month, which would translate into a 6.7% increase from a year ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan probing if lab mouse bite behind infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/asia/taiwan-probing-lab-mouse-bite-worker-covid-19-infection-2371846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI: Taiwan on Friday (Dec 10) said it was investigating whether a mouse bite may have been responsible for a worker at a high-security laboratory testing positive for the coronavirus, the island's first local infection in weeks. Health officials are scrambling to work out how a female employee at Acade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia Man Says YALE Secret Society Made Him Storm Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/militia-member-says-yale-secret-society-made-him-storm-capitol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Militia Member Says Yale Secret Society Made Him Storm Capitol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House points finger at press...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/585187-white-house-points-finger-at-the-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden White House, plagued by low approval ratings that have weakened the president’s clout and raised fears among Democrats over next year’s midterms, is blaming the media for some of its problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hours after community gathered for Christmas tree lighting, it was set on fire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hours-community-members-gathered-christmas-155300558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Beginning in 2019, the Washington Park Chamber of Commerce has hosted a Christmas tree lighting at Garfield Boulevard and Martin Luther King Drive where the community can gather and celebrate the holidays and decorations. And every year, the tree has been destroyed, according to the chamber’s CEO Donna Hampton-Smith. In 2019, someone ran over the display with their car, leaving ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Plane Diverted After Passenger Assaults Air Marshal, Flight Attendant...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/12/09/passenger-detained-during-after-assaulting-an-air-marshal-and-flight-attendant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger on a Delta flight from Washington D.C. to Los Angeles has been detained in Oklahoma City after assaulting an air marshal and a flight attendant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax group targeted head of California Medical Board in 'stalking' incident...</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/news/california-connection/anti-vaccine-group-targets-californias-medical-director/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president of California’s medical board, which issues medical licenses and disciplines doctors, says a group of anti-vaccine activists stalked her at home and followed her to her office — where…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>53 die in horror crash of truck smuggling migrants in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-accidents-smuggling-4a101767083046f872999fe26c788c47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TUXTLA GUTIERREZ, Mexico (AP) — Rescue workers rushing to a highway accident found a horrific scene of death and injury after a freight truck jammed with as many as 200 migrants tipped over and crashed into the base of a steel pedestrian bridge in southern Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demaryius Thomas, former Pro Bowl wide receiver for BRONCOS, dies at 33...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/demaryius-thomas-former-pro-bowl-wide-receiver-for-the-broncos-dies-at-33/ar-AARGkwU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris nightmare before Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-e2-80-99s-nightmare-before-christmas/ar-AARFvKb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man filmed state trooper taking nap in car. Then he was retaliated against...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-man-filmed-a-massachusetts-state-trooper-taking-a-nap-in-his-car-then-he-was-retaliated-against-he-says/ar-AARGm71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG seeks The Don's depo as part of fraud investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/donald-trump-letitia-james-deposition/2021/12/09/01b10140-587f-11ec-a219-9b4ae96da3b7_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The office of Letitia James aims to take the testimony of the former president on Jan. 7 as part of an ongoing probe into whether his company committed fraud in the valuation of its properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES 20 YEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10293113/Jussie-Smollett-jury-reaches-verdict-Actor-returns-court.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jussie Smollett has been convicted of faking a racist and homophobic hate crime, and faces up to 20 years in jail. He was found guilty of five of the six disorderly conduct charges he faced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 cities hit all-time homicide records...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/12-major-us-cities-top-annual-homicide-records/story?id=81466453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 12 major U.S. cities have broken annual homicide records in 2021 -- and there's still three weeks to go in the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jussie Smollett was blindly backed by prominent liberals including Pelosi, Michelle Obama and Shonda Rhimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10289921/How-Jussie-Smolletts-lies-impacted-America.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil rights experts have said Smollett's hoax attack claims are a 'black mark' for the movement and a 'whitewash of justice'. This came after leaders referred to the attack as a 'modern day lynching'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS LOWEST IN HALF CENTURY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/09/us-weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial filings for unemployment insurance totaled 184,000 for the week ended Dec. 4, the lowest going back to Sept. 6, 1969.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUILTY</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/09/jussie-smollett-convicted-of-staging-hate-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jussie Smollett was convicted of staging a hate crime nearly three years after he claimed two Trump-loving bigots beat him up, tied a noose around his neck and doused him in bleach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE HATE HOAX</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/jussie-smollett-guilty-verdict-jury-felony-trial-empire-1234887962/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 5:05 PM: Jussie Smollett has yet to be sentenced for being found guilty today of faking a hate crime attack on himself nearly three years ago, but the Empire actor isn’t over fighting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom stole daughter's identity to start college, date young guys...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/09/mom-48-stole-daughters-identity-to-date-younger-guys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Missouri mama is facing jail time after she admitted to stealing her estranged daughter’s identity in order to secure student loans, enroll in college — and pursue her sexy co-ed fanta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana hospitals see record patient amid surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-indiana-indianapolis-indiana-university-d1b1e610c0001df5a3c39d7329b54a5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — Indiana hospitals are seeing their highest-ever overall patient counts amid a monthlong COVID-19 surge and the state’s largest hospital system announced Thursday it had enlisted National Guard assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNTER BIDEN PAINTING HIS TRUTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/12/hunter-biden-is-painting-his-truth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s son has lived his misfortunes and missteps in the public eye. Now he feels like he’s come out the other side, spending his days listening to philosophy podcasts and mounting exhibits of the art to which he has devoted his new life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court denies effort to block White House records from Jan. 6 investigators...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/09/appeals-court-denies-trump-effort-to-block-white-house-records-from-jan-6-investigators-524046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court gave the former president two weeks to seek an appeal before the order takes effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aliens may have already VISITED Earth, NASA report reveals...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4238103/aliens-may-have-visited-earth-nasa-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALIENS may have already visited Earth, according to a jaw-dropping report by Nasa, which says the organisation is “not closed” to the possibility extraterrestrial life exists. While the report said…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans can't be baptized unless they've 'repented,' diocese says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/transgender-people-can-e2-80-99t-be-baptized-unless-they-e2-80-99ve-e2-80-98repented-e2-80-99-catholic-diocese-says/ar-AARCGes?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans help clear way for Senate vote to raise debt limit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/republicans-help-clear-the-way-for-senate-vote-on-bipartisan-deal-to-avert-debt-ceiling-crisis/ar-AAREMMZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMTRAK cuts service over vaccine rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211209160301-c7uz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-AMTRAK (URGENT):Amtrak to temporarily cut some service over U.S. COVID-19 vaccine rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Despairing Log On, Learn Ways to Die...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/where-despairing-log-learn-ways-124843008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Matthew van Antwerpen, a 17-year-old in suburban Dallas, struggled with remote schooling during the pandemic last year, he grew increasingly despondent. Searching online, he found a website about suicide. “Any enjoyment or progress I make in my life simply comes across as forced,” he wrote on the site after signing up. “I know it is all just a distraction to blow time until the end.” Roberta Barbos, a 22-year-old student at the University of Glasgow, first posted after a breakup, writing that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Employees Say China Makes Final Decisions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/tiktok-insiders-say-beijing-staffers-make-many-product-decisions-even-as-the-company-distances-itself-from-china/ar-AAREwdF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden rejects 'ridiculous' concerns on president's mental fitness...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/585170-jill-biden-rejects-ridiculous-concerns-on-presidents-mental</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jill Biden is dismissing any concerns about President Biden's mental fitness, calling them "ridiculous."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAB LEAK feared to have infected dozens in Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4239264/covid-lab-leak-taiwan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FEMALE lab worker in Taiwan is feared to have infected dozens of people with Covid in a terrifying leak, officials said. The researcher in capital Taipei who tested positive for the coronavirus m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Strongest I've Ever Seen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/cnbcs-jim-cramer-gushes-over-new-numbers-strongest-economy-ive-ever-seen-a-marvel-to-behold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC host Jim Cramer reacted to new jobless claim numbers by gushing that this is “the strongest economy, perhaps, I’ve ever seen.” Cramer delivered his 2022 Investing Club Game Plan Thursday afternoon, during which he grew very excited while discussing the new numbers. Namely, this week’s initial unemployment claims hit a 52-year low of 184,000. […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC to rename Saudi embassy street 'Jamal Khashoggi Way'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211209-washington-to-rename-street-in-front-of-saudi-embassy-jamal-khashoggi-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The street in front of the embassy of Saudi Arabia will be called "Jamal Khashoggi Way," after the Washington city council voted to honor the Saudi journalist murdered by government agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of DISNEY Exit, Iger Delivers Last Weather Forecast...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/bob-iger-weather-forecast-new-book-1235059956/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Appearing on KABC Thursday morning, Iger also confirmed that he is looking into writing another book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawl breaks out in Turkey's parliament...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/585133-brawl-breaks-out-in-turkeys-parliament</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in the Turkish parliament argued and physically fought this week as they debated budgets and policies to address the country's economy struggles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New eye drops could replace reading glasses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/vuity-eye-drops-fda-approved-blurred-vision-presbyopia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vuity, which was approved by the Food and Drug Administration in October, would potentially replace reading glasses for some of the 128 million Americans who have trouble seeing close-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic of the Vaccinated Here...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-pandemic-of-the-vaccinated-is-here/ar-AAREMsi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS employees vote to unionize, first in USA....</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/09/starbucks-employees-at-a-buffalo-cafe-vote-to-unionize-a-first-for-the-coffee-chain-in-the-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks workers in Buffalo, New York voted to unionize at least one cafe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILL LAWYER FORCES 'PAUSE'</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-59601083</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawyer - who has a non-Covid-related illness - is needed for questioning of an upcoming witness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader of Calif. town that's now 'constitutional republic' speaks out...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-politics/article/Oroville-California-constitutional-republic-COVID-16685110.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SFGATE spoke to Thomson about why he felt the need to declare his city a 'constitutional...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footprints show meat-eating dinosaurs were fast and furious...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211209173809-qez45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-DINOSAUR/ (PIX):Footprints in Spain show meat-eating dinosaurs were fast and furious</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSOM: Violent Crime Higher in Texas Than It Is in California....</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/gavin-newsom-says-violent-crime-higher-in-texas-than-it-is-in-california-i-dont-see-that-on-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Gavin Newsom (D-CA) joined the cohosts of The View on Wednesday and was asked about the smash-and-grab robberies plaguing his state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: Economy is 'a juggernaut' now...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/08/cramer-sees-potential-for-roaring-20s-type-boom-as-covid-concerns-ease.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think we could go to a period where we have an economic boom not unlike post-World War I" and after the 1918 pandemic, CNBC's Jim Cramer said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested for breaking sink during sex in restaurant bathroom...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/florida/sink-stink-arrest-723950</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 9--While “being intimate” with a friend inside a restaurant bathroom, a Florida Woman broke a sink off the wall, leading to her arrest for criminal mischief, according to police. Investigator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images show huge build-up of forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/fears-russia-ukraine-war-grow-25653075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images appear to show Russian military forces massing near the Ukrainian border, with a Buk anti-aircraft missile system and army tanks also filmed in the Voronezh region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESTS FOR TEACHERS? Schools screen for progressive politics...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/education/1007869/teachers-shouldnt-have-to-pass-a-political-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES Beats TESLA to Hands-Free Driving on Autobahn...</title>
      <link>https://europe.autonews.com/automakers/mercedes-beats-tesla-hands-free-driving-highways</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;europe.autonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercedes' Drive Pilot system will allow a driver to take their hands off the wheel in slow-moving traffic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC postal workers indicted for stealing 1,000+ credit cards from mail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/postal-workers-allegedly-stole-credit-cards-from-mail-spent-750000-on-luxury-goods/3441547/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four mail carriers are accused of stealing the mail they are supposed to safeguard, with investigators alleging they swiped credit cards and went on a nearly $1 million spending spree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dr. Oz for Senate Will Give Oprah and SONY a Headache...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/politics-news/dr-ozs-political-bid-will-give-sony-and-oprah-a-headache-1235059532/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the host launches a bid for the Senate, his industry backers may get hit with the fallout when reporters dig into his history of questionable claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why UK turned on Boris...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/12/its-time-for-boris-to-go/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He has served his purpose — and taken us all for fools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  Can The Trump Christmas Ornament Save America?</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/merry-politicized-christmas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can the Trump Christmas ornament save America?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  HBO 'SEX AND THE CITY' Revival Falls Flat...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/and-just-like-that-review-sex-the-city-return-sarah-jessica-parker-kim-cattrall-cynthia-nixon-kristin-davis-hbo-max/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We can’t just stay who we were,” says Cynthia Nixon’s Miranda Hobbes in the opening episode of The Sex and the City sequel series And Just Like That… As true as the insight may be, it is also some…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Educators report rise in school threats, fights, misbehavior, and blame COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/educators-report-a-rise-in-school-threats-fights-and-misbehavior-and-blame-covid/ar-AARE2jG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big money, anonymity, slow disclosure: Mystery donor funds McConnell comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/politics-government/article256409021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Basically, One Nation is a political entity masquerading as a nonprofit,” said Robert Maguire, the research director for the Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney, Bennifer, Beatles,  Broadway: Pop culture '21...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travis-scott-britney-spears-r-kelly-alec-baldwin-entertainment-f4fba10a6026be1d4b85ecb482bfe12a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney was freed. Bennifer came back. So did Broadway, yay! And actually, the Beatles! As for Bond — James Bond — he said goodbye, at least the Daniel Craig version. Harry and Meghan spoke to Oprah, and boy, we listened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Hill Staffer Arrested After Showing Up to Work With Gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-allsbrooks-capitol-hill-staffer-arrested-after-showing-up-to-work-with-a-gun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The staffer, identified as Jeffrey Allsbrooks from the House Chief Administrative Office, told authorities he’d forgotten the firearm was in his bag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENES KANTER: Why I Became American...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/12/why-enes-kanter-freedom-speaks/620940/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Turkey’s leader came after me and my family, the United States welcomed me with open arms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Scott Breaks Silence on Astroworld Tragedy in First Interview Since Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/travis-scott-astroworld-interview-1269269/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper reveals he didn’t know that Houston fest was a “mass casualty event” until after police press conferences: “Even at that moment you’re like, ‘Wait, what?’”…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER says fourth shot may be needed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/585065-pfizer-ceo-says-fourth-vaccine-shot-may-eventually-be-needed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla on Wednesday said that a fourth dose of the COVID-19 vaccine may eventually be needed amid concerns about the omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study unlocks secrets to developing regular workout habit...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/study-unlocks-secrets-developing-workout-habit-rcna8075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do I work out more often? A large study unlocks the secrets to developing a workout habit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow says tensions with USA over Ukraine risk repeat of Cuban missile crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/moscow-says-tensions-with-us-over-ukraine-risk-repeat-of-cuban-missile-crisis-688298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead ROOMBAS, stranded packages, delayed exams: How AWS outage wreaked havoc...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/09/how-the-aws-outage-wreaked-havoc-across-the-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's cloud-computing arm was hit with an outage that lasted almost all day Tuesday, knocking offline many web-connected devices and popular sites.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
