<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rat hepatitis infects second human in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/2173951/second-hong-kong-resident-infected-hepatitis-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patient, 70, is a retiree who lived in the Wong Tai Sin district, the same area as man in previous caseExpert says both infections are not linked despite two locations being only 3km apart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Paso 'New Ellis Island'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/11/19/dem-rep-elect-escobar-el-paso-is-the-new-ellis-island/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.-elect Veronica Escobar (D-TX) on Monday's "Morning Joe" on MSNBC discussed immigration, declaring El Paso, TX, as "the new Ellis Island." "El Paso, | Video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correspondents group declares follow-up questions will continue...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/417537-white-house-correspondents-group-promises-reporters-will-continue-to-ask</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president of the White House Correspondents' Association (WHCA) said Monday that the group "fully expect[s]" White House reporters to continue asking follow-up questions at presidential news conferences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS:  IRAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/trump-administration-hawks-putting-us-on-course-for-war-with-iran-report-warns-a8641756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks Hit Hard as Tech Worries Deepen...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-stocks-climb-as-investors-await-brexit-progress-economic-data-1542617934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks lurched lower Monday, deepening a fall rout that has shaken many investors’ confidence in the technology titans that had led the bull market higher for much of the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX flashes  'death cross'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/netflixs-death-cross-is-the-third-for-faang-stocks-and-nasdaq-composite-is-next-2018-11-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix’s stock has fallen far enough and long enough to produce its first “death cross” pattern in nearly three years, becoming the third member of the FAANG technology darlings to suffer that bearish technical fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S Parade could be frigid nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/19/macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-could-be-a-frigid-nightmare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This holiday forecast blows! Thanksgiving paradegoers should bundle up for the coldest temperatures in 20 years — and brace for powerful winds that threaten to ground dazzling giant balloons. It&amp;#8…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTS:  FBI considers 'Proud Boys' extremists with white-nationalist ties... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/19/proud-boys-fbi-classification-extremist-group-white-nationalism-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group is now designated ‘with ties to white nationalism’ according to report produced by Washington law enforcement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM ousting fake followers from accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181119-instagram-ousting-fake-followers-accounts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro's Military Purge Leads to Record Arrests...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/11/19/venezuela-maduro-regimes-continues-military-purge-arrests-reach-record-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politically motivated arrests of military personnel in Venezuela reached an all-time high in 2018, according to a report published Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVING PLANET:  Stunning shots across the globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6405507/The-stunning-winners-panoramic-photography-awards-revealed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both professional and amateur photographers from around the world were invited to enter their best landscape shots for the Epson International Pano Awards 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rain could cause ash flows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/fires-in-california-camp-woolsey-paradise-wildfire-evacuations-death-toll-map-2018-11-19-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impending storm could hinder crews' efforts who are searching for human remains in wake of Camp Fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez pushes for leftist revolt in Democratic Party...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/19/ocasio-cortez-pushes-for-a-leftist-revolt-in-the-democratic-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Rep.-elect Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez backs calls from fellow progressives to mount primary campaigns against moderate Democrats whose politics they believe are to the right of their constit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman opens fire at Chicago hospital, killing 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chicago-police-shots-fired-near-hospital-multiple-victims-215141270.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A gunman opened fire Monday at a Chicago hospital, killing a police officer and two hospital employees in an attack that began with a domestic dispute and exploded into a firefight with law enforcement inside the medical center. The suspect was also dead, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAA warns of record-breaking traffic this Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6407345/AAA-warns-massive-traffic-holiday-season-predicts-WORST-times-hit-road.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Automobile Association predicts that 54.3 million Americans will travel 50 miles or more from their homes this Thanksgiving, the highest number recorded in more than a dozen years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man diagnosed with mysterious polio-like illness...</title>
      <link>https://wkow.com/news/health/2018/11/19/man-diagnosed-with-mysterious-polio-like-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wkow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's the only adult in Wisconsin to have come down with the illness .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Seeks Restraining Order Against Avenatti...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/michael-avenatti-actress-files-domestic-violence-restraining-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Disses Pelosi Critics: 'Mostly Male,' 'Very Few People of Color'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-ocasio-cortez-dems-opposing-pelosi-it-doesnt-reflect-partys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘There’s very few ideological diversity’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustration, chaos as recovery drags on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fddc389df190401a8063fc22819eab7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — It's been 12 days since Christina Taft started the frantic search for her mother Victoria, who refused to evacuate their Paradise home as flames neared, and six days since she gave authorities a cheek swab to identify remains that are likely her mother's. She still hasn't received confirmation that her mother is dead, and says she's been frustrated by what she feels is a lack of communication from Butte County officials. "They said they found remains, they didn't say her remains. They won't confirm it to me the whole time," Taft said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH DRECK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/tech-stocks-like-facebook-and-apple-got-crushed-once-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology stocks were hit hard on Monday, with some of the biggest U.S. companies leading widespread losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imprisoned Cuban Rapper Sews Mouth Shut in Protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/11/19/imprisoned-cuban-dissident-rapper-sews-mouth-shut-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban rapper Maykel Castillo "El Osorbo" sewed his mouth shut in prison after being arrested for organizing an anti-Castro concert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: L.A. sheriff sex crimes investigator arrested -- on suspicion of raping minor in case...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-deputy-svu-rape-20181119-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles County Sheriff's deputy child sex crimes detective has been arrested on suspicion of raping a teenager involved in one of his investigations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO SLAP 'TERROR' LABEL ON VENEZUELA?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/trump-administration-prepares-to-add-venezuela-to-list-of-state-sponsors-of-terrorism/2018/11/19/1ba65b74-ec01-11e8-baac-2a674e91502b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move could limit U.S. assistance and prohibit financial transactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man accused of restaurant bomb threat claims referring to 'bathroom bowel movement'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/crime/2018/11/warrant-man-accused-of-bomb-threat-told-nopd-he-was-referring-to-bowel-movement.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the bomb threat was made at Willie's Chicken Shack on Tuesday (Nov. 13).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Humans Invented 'High-Tech Swiss Army Knife'...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/archaeology/MAGAZINE-early-humans-invented-high-tech-stone-tools-more-than-once-study-suggests-1.6662192</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Gunman Killed Former Fiance In Parking Lot, Continued Into Chicago Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/mercy-hospital-chicago-shooting-2-dead-including-gunman/4720765/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people were shot and two are dead, including the suspected shooter, after a shooting at Mercy Hospital on the city's South Side, Chicago police said. A Chicago police officer is among those shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Khashoggi murder, royals turn against Crown Prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-royals-exclusive/exclusive-after-khashoggi-murder-some-saudi-royals-turn-against-kings-favorite-son-idUSKCN1NO2KP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid international uproar over the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi, some m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's March co-founder calls on leaders to resign: 'Allowed anti-Semitism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jta.org/2018/11/19/top-headlines/womens-march-co-founder-calls-current-organizers-resign-saying-allowed-anti-semitism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jta.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(JTA) — Women’s March co-founder Teresa Shook called on its current organizers to step down Monday, saying they “allowed anti-Semitism.” In a Facebook post, Shook said Bob Bland, Tamika Mallory, Linda Sarsour and Carmen Perez “have steered the Movement away from its true course.” “In opposition to our Unity Principles, they have allowed anti-Semitism, anti-LBGTQIA...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller tells court powers still intact amid DOJ overhaul...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/19/robert-mueller-justice-department-whitaker-1005557</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew Whitaker's appointment as the special counsel's boss 'neither alters the special counsel’s authority to represent the United States nor raises any jurisdictional issue.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheryl saintly image unraveling...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/online/social/sheryl-sandbergs-saintly-image-in-silicon-valley-is-unravelling/news-story/b693c6a44cc114aa3f5eef4ddeffa380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charismatic, personable, strong and highly successful, Sheryl Sandberg has been a shining light for women in business, in particular in the male dominated world of Silicon Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake psychiatrist jailed after practicing for 22 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12162943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zholia Alemi posed as psychiatrist, deception exposed when she tried to fleece a patient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin critic, facing new charge, sounds alarm on Interpol...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6f4706748f584cff9e308862898a9902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian prosecutors announced new criminal charges against U.S.-born Kremlin foe Bill Browder on Monday, days before a Russian police officer could become president of Interpol in a move that some Moscow critics fear might politicize the law enforcement agency. Browder and other opponents of Russian President Vladimir Putin have complained that Russia has tried to use Interpol against them. If a Russian is elected as its new president, it could encourage Moscow to intensify attempts to hunt down its critics abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to begin drawdown of border troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/19/troops-us-mexico-border-come-home-1005510</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the active-duty troops that President Donald Trump ordered sent to the border before the midterm elections should be home by Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches turn to pop music hits instead of hymns to attract young...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/19/arts/music/avicii-mass-church-stockholm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden is one of Europe’s least religious countries. Pastors there are using pop and rock music at Masses to try to attract a younger crowd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise Ships Fueled By Dead Fish...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/terricolby/2018/11/19/hurtigruten-announces-it-will-fuel-cruise-ships-with-dead-fish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norwegian cruise company Hurtigruten announces that by 2021 t will power at least six of its ships with liquified biogas, a renewable fuel produced from dead fish and other organic waste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman Opens Fire On Chicago Hospital Campus... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/11/19/mercy-hospital-gunman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gunman has opened fire on the campus of Mercy Hospital, according to Chicago police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS:  Caravan harboring 500+ criminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/migrant-caravan-may-be-in-tijuana-for-the-long-haul-while-u-s-shuts-down-san-diego-area-crossing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Migrant caravan members who reached a U.S. border crossing near San Diego were met with an icy reception in Tijuana this weekend, and the group is waking up Monday with the realization they could be stuck on that unwelcoming side of the fence for months if they try to enter America the legal way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW RULES FOR REPORTERS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/417487-white-house-drops-bid-to-revoke-acostas-press-pass</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is dropping its effort to strip CNN reporter Jim Acosta of his press credentials, a defeat for President Trump in his campaign against the news media. The reversal comes after the White House notified A</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backs down; DROPS plan to keep Acosta out...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6407333/Trump-administration-backs-DROPS-plan-Jim-Acosta-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House's apparent stand-down came after CNN petitioned a judge for an expedited hearing and scrambled to aseemble a process to retroactively explain why it banned Acosta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>By-Standers Shoot Video Of Officer Being Attacked By Man on PCP...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/11/18/good-samaritan-amongst-crowd-of-phones-saves-dallas-officer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dallas man is being praised for coming to a Dallas police officer’s aid by pinning down a man who was trying to attack the officer.  All while bystanders allegedly were recording video with their phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAANG stocks tumble...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/stock-market-today-nasdaq-tumbles-as-faang-stocks-fall-2018-11-1027739586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO spends boardroom meetings on SNAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/spiegel-spends-board-room-meetings-snapchat-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to The Information, Snap CEO Evan Spiegel spends much of his time during board meetings tied to his phone and messaging people on Snapchat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Parliaments Demand Answers...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/11/19/now-eight-parliaments-are-demanding-zuckerberg-answers-for-facebook-scandals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s founder is facing pressure to accept an invite from eight international parliaments, with lawmakers wanting to question him about negative impacts his social network is having on democratic processes globally. Last week Facebook declined an invitation from five of these parliaments…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5-year runny nose turns out to be brain fluid leaking...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/health/johnston-county-mans-runny-nose-turns-out-to-be-leaking-brain-fluid/4697753/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greg Phillpotts said he had been battling what he thought were allergies during the past five years. Some doctors also diagnosed him with pneumonia and bronchitis. Finally, one doctor recognized it for what it was, leaking brain fluid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -400...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/stock-market-dow-set-for-higher-open-amid-mixed-signals-over-global-trade.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks dropped sharply on Monday as some of the largest technology shares and lingering worries about global trade pressured the broader market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA's Major Drinking Problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/11/19/alcohol-taxes-restrictions-public-health-policy-problem-drinking-blue-laws/1729501002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When officials wanted to reduceÂ deaths from tobacco, they spoke ofÂ cancer risks, pushed for public bans and raised taxes. On alcohol, the way forward is less clear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED Makes 'Asking For Money' Part Of Its Business Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90270049/as-it-considers-mergers-buzzfeed-makes-asking-for-money-part-of-its-revenue-strategy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed is looking into all possible avenues for building a successful media company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD wants to eliminate smell from new cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/money/cars/ford/2018/11/19/ford-new-car-smell-patent/2027822002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customer satisfaction studies show Chinese car consumers really hate the new car smell. Ford has applied for an anti-odor patent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: 4 People Found Shot, Killed 'Execution-Style' In Philly Basement...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/11/19/4-people-found-shot-killed-execution-style-in-west-philadelphia-basement-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victims have not yet been identified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running club sparks terror incident after using white powder to mark route...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/19/running-club-sparks-terror-incident-using-white-powder-mark/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A running club sparked a terror incident after it used white powder to mark out the route of a five-mile circuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nancy Pelosi's Last Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/19/magazine/nancy-pelosi-house-democrats.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As she prepares to lead the House of Representatives again, the most powerful Democrat in Washington will have to navigate between a rampaging president and her colleagues’ plans for fighting back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest peanut allergy study points to life-saving treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/19/largest-peanut-allergy-study-points-live-saving-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peanut allergy sufferers have been given new hope following the results of the largest study of its kind in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper 6ix9ine indicted on racketeering charges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ae2d334712a4f5792420084bc1e39f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The rapper known as Tekashi 6ix9ine was in federal custody Monday awaiting a Manhattan court appearance. The Brooklyn-based rapper, whose legal name is Daniel Hernandez, was among four people arrested on racketeering and firearms charges. An attorney who has previously represented Hernandez did not immediately respond to an email seeking comment Monday. The authorities also arrested three of Hernandez's former associates, Kifano "Shotti" Jordan, Jensel "Ish" Butler and Faheem "Crippy" Walter. It is unclear whether they had defense attorneys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 arrested for looting Cal Fire station during blaze...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article221892190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Concow men were arrested in connection with the burglary of a Butte County fire station during the Camp Fire, Cal Fire said Monday in a news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robber shoots gas station clerk before demanding cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/robber-shoots-gas-station-clerk-before-demanding-cash-witnesses-say/WNv46fD4OI9YdB0OHyHFnK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gas station clerk shot during a robbery early Saturday is hoping newly released surveillance video...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the Western Dissidents...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/11/19/bokhari-rise-of-the-western-dissidents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're used to Russian dissidents, Chinese dissidents, Iranian dissidents, and Saudi Arabian dissidents. But those who rightly believe the west is superior to authoritarian regimes must now contend with a troubling trend — the rise of the western dissident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Bangladeshis Apprehended in 12 Hours at TX Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/19/six-bangladeshis-apprehended-in-12-hours-at-texas-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laredo Sector Border Patrol agents continue to find illegal immigrants from Bangladesh who cross the border from Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App directs robots to hold parking spaces...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mypark-robotic-parking-app-black-friday-e2a616a3-72b6-4b40-a89f-6d115d3c5e31.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You won't have to tip the valet, either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasted for criticizing Navy SEAL in charge of killing bin Laden...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/19/trump-blasted-for-criticizing-navy-seal-in-charge-of-killing-bin-laden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A retired Army general blasted as “disgusting” President Trump’s remarks denigrating a former Navy SEAL who oversaw the 2011 operation to take out Osama bin Laden for not killing the September 11 a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employees point fingers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/inside-facebook-denial-tension-finger-pointing-crisis-foments-n937911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's total arrogance," one Facebook employee said of company leadership's willingness to blame its communications team for recent crises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In smoldering wildfire ruins, life goes on for hardy few...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb048638df544e1989685f92a1374885</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARADISE, Calif. (AP) — Brad Weldon lost his home to fire when he was a kid, so when a deadly wildland blaze came roaring toward his ranch house in the pines where he lives with his 89-year-old blind mother, he wasn't going to let disaster strike twice. Weldon and his mother's caregiver, armed only with a garden hose and buckets, successfully fought the flames for 24 hours. At times, they had to lie down in the dirt to "avoid burning up" as 60 mph (97 kph) winds drove flames through the forest. Having saved his home in Paradise, Weldon's not leaving what he now calls the "hell zone."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US closes busiest Mexico border crossing for several hours...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9515542f7651432dbf072a9098e48230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico (AP) — The United States closed off northbound traffic for several hours at the busiest border crossing with Mexico to install new security barriers on Monday, a day after hundreds of Tijuana residents protested against the presence of thousands of Central American migrants. The U.S. also closed one of two pedestrian crossings at the San Ysidro crossing in a move apparently aimed at preventing any mass rush of migrants across the border. The installation of movable, wire-topped barriers threatens to complicate life for Mexicans using San Ysidro, where about 110,000 people enter the U.S. every day in 40,000 vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Says Chief of Staff 'Will Move On'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/20d3b0c101824425bf3be67c679aaa74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump isn't committing to a previous pledge to keep chief of staff John Kelly for the remainder of his term, part of widespread speculation about staffing changes that could soon sweep through his administration. Trump, in a wide-ranging interview that aired on "Fox News Sunday," praised Kelly's work ethic and much of what he brings to the position but added, "There are certain things that I don't like that he does." "There are a couple of things where it's just not his strength. It's not his fault. It's not his strength," said Trump, who added that Kelly himself might want to depart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge-fund boss who predicted '87 crash says get ready for some 'really scary moments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-boss-who-predicted-87-crash-says-get-ready-for-some-really-scary-moments-2018-11-15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Tudor Jones, a hedge-fund luminary, says he’s stress-testing his portfolio of corporate debt because he expects a tumultuous road ahead for that market segment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homelessness Crisis Looms...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/11/16/homelessness-crisis-looms-camp-fire-evacuees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Friday, hundreds of people displaced by the camp fire were still desperate to figure out a way get a roof over their heads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM GOES BUST!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/facebook-is-on-track-to-post-its-longest-losing-streak-ever.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is facing a mountain of problems. According to some experts, the stock isn't done falling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER:  UNFRIEND HER!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/cramer-facebook-stock-would-go-up-if-coo-sheryl-sandberg-departed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asked on CNBC whether Sandberg leaving would be good or bad for Facebook, Jim Cramer responded by saying the "stock goes up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jacksonville Became America's Trans Murder Capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/we-have-targets-on-our-backs-how-jacksonville-became-americas-transgender-murder-capital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three of the 22 reported killings of trans people in America this year have taken place in Jacksonville, Florida—the victims all black trans women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent accused of wearing referee uniform, swaying football playoff game...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-simeon-nazareth-ihsa-lawsuit-20181119-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A father of a football player of Nazareth Academy is accused of wearing his referee uniform and swaying a Nov. 10th football game against Simeon Career Academy in favor of the suburban Catholic high school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Correspondents' Association Ditches Comedian For Annual Dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.whca.press/2018/11/19/whca-announces-acclaimed-author-ron-chernow-as-featured-speaker-for-2019-dinner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whca.press&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House Correspondents’ Association (WHCA) is pleased to announce that Ron Chernow, one of the most eminent biographers of American presidents and statesmen, will be the featured speaker at its annual dinner on Saturday, April 27, 2019. “I’m delighted that Ron will share his lively, deeply researched perspectives on American politics and history at the 2019 White House Correspondents’ Dinner,” said Olivier Knox, Chief Washington Correspondent for SiriusXM and president of the WHCA. “As we celebrate the importance of a free and independent news media to the health of the republic, I look forward to hearing Ron place this unusual … Continued</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 people aim to smash record for world's largest ORGY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7773652/world-largest-orgy-sex-party-colorado-polyamorous-derrier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POLYAMOROUS events planner has revealed her quest to organise the world’s largest orgy – inviting 1,000 to the marathon sex party. Pearl Derrier, 29, from Denver, Colorado, goes to or…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homebuilder confidence plummets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/homebuilder-confidence-plummets-to-the-lowest-level-in-more-than-two-years-as-demand-stalls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising mortgage rates and continued home price growth are hurting affordability and fast becoming a toxic cocktail for the nation's homebuilders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air pollution shaving years from lives. Where is it claiming most?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/policy/environment/article221668390.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study examines how much longer people could live if particulate pollution — such as soot from cars and trucks — was reduced to levels recommended by the World Health Organization. In Fresno, people could live a year longer, on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars: Christian Bale Leaps Into Lead Actor Race With 'VICE'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/in-contention/oscars-christian-bale-leaps-into-the-lead-actor-race-with-adam-mckays-sobering-vice-1203031566/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;’Tis the season for latter-year revelations. With Adam McKay’s new film “Vice,” a follow-up to his 2015 Oscar winner “The Big Short,” a major one has landed, though it’s hardly a surprise: Christia…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensual goddess fresco discovered in ancient Pompeii bedroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2566d74abc7d4995bbc1dc9c0f5a0b62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Archaeologists have found in an ancient Pompeii bedroom a fresco depicting a sensual scene of a goddess and swan. Pompeii archaeological park director Massimo Osanna told Italian news agency ANSA on Monday that the figure of goddess Leda being impregnated by a swan representing Roman god Jupiter is a fairly common theme in Pompeii home decoration. But he praised this fresco as exceptional since the goddess appears to look at whoever's looking at the fresco. Osanna said "Leda watches the spectator with a sensuality that's absolutely pronounced."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi king urges action against Iran...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181119123649-vxsmr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-KING/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Saudi king urges action against Iran, backs Yemen peace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threaten To Devastate Black Friday Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-18/brutally-cold-temperatures-could-stifle-black-friday-sales</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN Warning: Economy will slow to crawl next year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/goldman-sachs-believes-the-us-economy-will-slow-to-a-crawl-next-year.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman sees economic growth slowing to below 2 percent in the second half of 2019 as the Fed continues to raise rates and the effects of the tax cut wear off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlook for Traditional TV Goes From Bad to Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/outlook-for-traditional-tv-goes-from-bad-to-worse-1542632401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cord-cutters continue to chip away at cable and satellite providers’ dominance of the living room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ousted Trump Aide Nabs Seven-Figure Advance For Tell-All...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/team-of-vipers-ousted-trump-aide-reportedly-nabs-seven-figure-advance-for-tell-all-about-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil price now controlled by just three men...</title>
      <link>https://www.worldoil.com/news/2018/11/18/bloomberg-opinion-the-oil-price-is-now-controlled-by-just-three-men</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.worldoil.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto blows up 2020 Dem primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/19/beto-orourke-2020-democratic-primary-995353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top party donors and operatives are eager to see the Texas congressman jump into the presidential race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 generals can't deploy for medical reasons...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/11/19/one-five-army-generals-were-not-cleared-combat-2016/2029702002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in five Army generals could not deploy in 2016 for medical reasons. Overdue medical and dental exams were the main culprits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Eating Its Oceans...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/42470-earth-is-eating-its-oceans.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three times more water than previously estimated gets dragged into subduction zones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 people aim to smash record for world's largest ORGY...</title>
      <link>/https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7773652/world-largest-orgy-sex-party-colorado-polyamorous-derrier/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University lecturers told DON'T USE CAPS as it frightens students...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1046977/university-lecturers-not-to-use-cap-letters-student-failure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(It might upset the snowflake students)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbulent stock market spooks older workers, retirees...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c96eb2f4b5c54449b13c95e841f89dab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The recent turbulence in the U.S. stock markets is spooking some older workers and retirees, a group that was hit particularly hard during the most recent financial crisis. There's no indication, though, that the recent volatility has brought about large-scale overhauls in retirement planning. "There's a lot of fear that if you have another event like 2008 and you retire the year before or the year after, you're screwed. I'm not taking that risk," says Mark Patterson, a recently retired patent attorney from Nashville, Tennessee. "There's a huge fear of folks my age that they're going to run out of money and they're going to need to rely on the government for help."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red alert after Guatemala volcano erupts again; 3,000 flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181119-red-alert-after-guatemala-volcano-erupts-again-200-flee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French fuel depots targeted as 'yellow vest' protesters persist...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181119-french-fuel-depots-targeted-yellow-vest-protesters-persist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese homoerotic writer gets 10 year jail term...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181119-chinese-homoerotic-writer-gets-10-year-jail-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biting winds to grip Macy's Parade in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/bundle-up-biting-winds-to-grip-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-in-nyc/70006658</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gruesome discovery of tiger farm exposes illegal trade in heart of Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/19/gruesome-discovery-of-czech-tiger-farm-exposes-illegal-trade-in-heart-of-europe </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gruesome haul of fresh pelts and rotting remains marks the end of a five-year probe into an international crime ring, that authorities fear points to a wider problem in Europe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Victims may never be found...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-casualties/some-california-wildfire-victims-may-never-be-found-searcher-idUSKCN1NO16X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Searchers looking for the remains of victims of the wildfire that destroyed the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK CHAOS CONTINUES...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-may-lawmaker-challenge/uk-conservative-lawmaker-says-pm-may-faces-day-of-reckoning-on-monday-idUSKCN1NO0LX?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May faces a day of reckoning on Monday as mutinou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder rate soars in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6405051/Murder-rate-soars-Venezuela-forcing-population-extreme-precautions-amid-shortages.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South American nation registered 26,000 homicides last year, 89 per 100,000 inhabitants and a figure 15 times the global average, according to the Venezuelan Observatory of Violence, an NGO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temps 25 degrees below average...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/weather/weather-blog/coldest-thanksgiving-in-years-when-it-will-feel-like-the-10s-20s/65-615665921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanksgiving Day will be unseasonably cold across the Northeast and Mid-Atlantic -- temperatures in some areas will drop 15° - 25° below average. This is what it means for DC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Goes Mainstream, Drawing Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facial-recognition-goes-mainstream-drawing-concerns-1542623401 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial recognition is increasingly used by law-enforcement agencies and in schools, retail stores and other venues, spurring privacy concerns. In this episode of Moving Upstream, we test out the technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast Coldest Thanksgiving on Record?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2018-11-18-thanksgiving-day-record-cold-northeast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll need to bundle up on Turkey Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE CUTS PRODUCTION ORDERS FOR 3 NEW IPHONE MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-suppliers-suffer-as-it-struggles-to-forecast-iphone-demand-1542618587 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lower-than-expected demand for Apple’s new iPhones and the company’s decision to offer more models have created turmoil along its supply chain and made it harder to predict the number of components and handsets it needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak 11: Empty Seats Abound As Season Enters Final Stretch...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2018/11/18/weal-11-empty-seats-abound-nfl-season-enters-final-stretch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL season is nearly coming to its end, with only six more weeks of regular season play left. Which has caused many fans on social media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As tech booms, Bay Area worker wages drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/11/18/silicon-valley-wages-have-dropped-for-all-except-highest-paying-jobs-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine out of every 10 Silicon Valley jobs pays less now than when Netflix first launched in 1997, despite one of the nation’s strongest economic booms and a historically low unemployment rate …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
