<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Chronic Biden hacking sparks concern as Psaki insists just allergies...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/08/coughing-biden-sparks-concern-as-psaki-says-its-just-allergies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki on Friday assured reporters that President Biden’s ailing cough is the result of allergies and not a more serious medical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA becomes 1st state to make ethnic studies required for high school graduation...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/california-becomes-1st-state-to-make-ethnic-studies-a-required-class-for-high-school-graduation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than five years of intense scrutiny and effort, California on Friday became the first state to make ethnic studies a required class for high school graduation to help students understand…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boy Rabbi Promises Religious Exemptions for Anyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xje9/proud-boy-rabbi-promises-religious-exemptions-for-covid-vaccine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asher Meza went on YouTube to tell his subscribers he’d give out exemptions to both Jews and gentiles alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Area 52's secret military base...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3820666/inside-area-52-secret-military-base-nuclear-bombs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AREA 51, the highly classified US Air Force base which has for years been at the center of a conspiracy among alien fanatics and ufologists, has a lesser-known sister facility that harbors its own …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Criminal Mind Now Suspected in Arson Spree...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/expert-criminal-mind-now-hes-123211677.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LASSEN NATIONAL FOREST, Calif. — He drove out of the Lumberjacks restaurant parking lot on a Tuesday in August, up Main Street, past the fire station and the gun shop. Then, Gary Maynard left the small city of Susanville in the northeastern corner of California and headed up a steep highway into the Sierra Nevada, where, prosecutors say, he set the forest ablaze. Maynard, a criminology professor who specializes in deviancy, now sits in a Sacramento jail awaiting a hearing. The crime expert, inve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men rescued after 29 days lost at sea: 'Nice break'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/08/men-rescued-after-29-days-lost-at-sea-it-was-a-nice-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite losing themselves at sea for nearly a month, two men from the Solomon Islands have returned with a remarkably positive outlook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US delegation to meet Taliban in first high-level talks since pullout...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211008202901-aturu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/USA-MEETING (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-U.S. delegation to meet Taliban in first high-level talks since pullout - officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: 9 Shot, 3 Killed, In Less Than 12 Hours...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/10/07/its-sad-it-really-is-at-least-9-shot-3-killed-in-less-than-12-hours-in-baltimore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least nine people were shot and three were killed in Baltimore in less than 12 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation not going away anytime soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/08/strong-wage-gains-cast-doubt-that-inflation-is-going-away-anytime-soon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;September's wage gains provided more fuel to the argument that the current pace of inflation could run longer than many economists anticipate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY schools to end gifted, talented program...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-new-york-city-race-and-ethnicity-education-d027be86b7d202f1d4ef62e5c3255802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York City will phase out its program for gifted and talented students that critics say favors whites and Asian American students, while enrolling disproportionately few Black and Latino children, in the nation's largest school system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Literally Teaching Course on Fundraising...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/10/08/kyrsten-sinema-fundraising-course-asu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator is educating Arizona State University students on her forte: asking for money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChinaRussia ask UN to check biological warfare strength of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3151668/china-russia-ask-un-check-biological-warfare-capability-us-and</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing’s envoy urges US to agree to a monitoring mechanism, continuing the finger-pointing after the nations traded barbs over the coronavirus’ origins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black people formed one of largest militias. Now leader in crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/black-people-formed-one-largest-090107734.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed Black Americans of the militant group NFAC marched against police brutality in 2020. Now the group's leader is in prosecutors' crosshairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow distraught: 'Heartbreaking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/tim-tebow-distraught-over-urban-meyers-heartbreaking-lap-dance-i-love-his-entire-family-and-im-praying-for-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The list of people who were let down by Urban Meyer’s scandalous lap dance video continues to grow. His family, his team, current players and apparently former players too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  He's Right, Isn't He?</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/dave-chappelle-is-right-isnt-he-b23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian defends reality. Which is currently under siege.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>136 COUNTRIES AGREE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/08/business/ireland-global-tax-deal-oecd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of 136 countries have agreed to a global treaty that would tax large multinationals at a minimum rate of 15% and require companies to pay taxes in the countries where they do business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman jailed for too-close grizzly bear encounter at Yellowstone...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/08/woman-gets-jail-time-for-grizzly-bear-encounter-at-yellowstone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “foolish” Illinois tourist who bucked Yellowstone National Park rules and approached a massive mama grizzly bear to snap a photo will spend four days in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-jab celebs paying for FAKE passports to appear on TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tv/16366629/celebrities-paying-fake-covid-passports-nhs-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RAFT of celebrities have paid for fake Covid passports to get onto TV shows without their required vaccinations. The Sun has the name of five stars who paid £750 each to hoodwink the NHS App syst…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden first president to mark Indigenous Peoples' Day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-lifestyle-holidays-columbus-day-a1ad30d52ad7ff80aa8e7621e2f9a425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden on Friday issued the first-ever presidential proclamation of Indigenous Peoples’ Day, lending the most significant boost yet to efforts to refocus the federal holiday celebrating Christopher Columbus toward an appreciation of Native peoples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House proposes tech 'bill of rights' to limit AI harms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-science-technology-business-biometrics-b9dbf5fee3bf0e407b988b31e21f5300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top science advisers to President Joe Biden are calling for a new “bill of rights" to guard against powerful new artificial intelligence technology. The White House's Office of Science and Technology Policy on Friday launched a fact-finding mission to look at facial recognition and other biometric tools used to identify people or assess their emotional or mental states and character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA sheriff won't enforce mandate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-los-angeles-health-ea88466d28b70560c227f11ee7d44efd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles County sheriff says he will not enforce the county's vaccine mandate in his agency. Sheriff Alex Villanueva, who oversees the largest sheriff's department in the county with roughly 18,000 employees, said Thursday in a Facebook Live event  that he does not plan to carry out the county's mandate, under which Los Angeles County employees had to be fully vaccinated by Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOND GOING WOKE AFTER CRAIG?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/james-bond-next-daniel-craig-woke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Daniel Craig retires as 007, there's no shortage of suggestions on who should take on the British superspy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7% of Israel's serious cases had 3 shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/7-percent-of-israels-serious-covid-cases-had-three-vaccine-shots-681455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were around 460 serious and critical cases on Friday, so 7% is around 32 people, meaning less than 0.000001 of people who have had a third shot are in serious condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  A newspaper tries to make ends meet by asking for donations in honor of its reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-newspaper-tries-to-make-ends-meet-by-asking-for-donations-in-honor-of-its-reporters/ar-AAPh03G?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is that okay? For the Tampa Bay Times, it’s an experiment at a time when local news is desperate to hang on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans growing optimistic about midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article254828122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans fear former President Donald Trump could complicate what is otherwise shaping up as a favorable political environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL TOPS $80...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/08/us-crude-oil-price-tops-80-a-barrel-the-highest-since-2014.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Texas Intermediate crude futures, the U.S. oil benchmark, tops $80 for the first time since November 2014.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF THE GLOBAL TAX</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/08/oecd-reaches-deal-on-corporate-tax-after-ireland-agrees.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Organisation for Economic Cooperation and Development on Friday announced a major breakthrough over corporate tax rates, after years of disagreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Tax Talks Race Against Clock as Holdouts Fall Into Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/global-insider/2021/10/08/global-tax-deal-inches-closer-494638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Meyer's wife after video shock: 'We are all sinners'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/sports/we-are-all-sinners-urban-meyer-s-wife-addresses-video-n1281090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We all make mistakes," Shelley Meyer tweeted after video showed another woman dancing closely to the Jacksonville Jaguars coach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First person charged with trying to steal pandemic aid sentenced to prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/first-person-charged-with-trying-to-steal-pandemic-aid-sentenced-to-prison-after-faking-his-suicide-and-going-on-the-lam-11633662311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Staveley was tracked down by U.S. Marshals after being charged with trying to take $550K in relief money he wasn’t eligible for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots do all the work at NISSAN 'intelligent' plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/robots-do-all-the-work-at-nissans-intelligent-plant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nissan’s “intelligent factory” hardly has any human workers. The robots do the work, including welding and mounting. They do the paint jobs and inspect their own paint jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F**K TWITTER'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/08/dave-chappelle-critics-fk-twitter-comedy-special/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Chappelle doesn&amp;amp;#039;t care what his critics have to say. He said &amp;amp;quot;F**k Twitter&amp;amp;quot; and responded to his critics while at the Hollywood Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCLA doctor escorted from hospital after refusing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article254829122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Christopher Rake said he’s willing to lose his life “for this cause.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local TV Giants Are Coming for CNN's Ad Dollars...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/sinclair-nexstar-scripps-cnn-ad-dollars-1235028101/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nexstar, Scripps and Sinclair, which have extensive reach across the U.S., are readying efforts to peel off enough viewers to become viable alternatives to national sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle braces for mass firing of police as hundreds have yet to show proof of vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/seattle-police-department-braces-for-mass-firing-of-officers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Wednesday, 292 sworn personnel had yet to provide proof of a COVID-19 vaccination. That number is down from 354 on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Whoa!' CNBC Host Stunned Live Reaction to Jobs Report...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/whoa-cnbc-hosts-offer-stunned-live-reaction-to-real-low-jobs-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC anchors expressed astonishment on Friday with September's jobs report, which came less than halfway to meeting projections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NO TIME TO DIE' Rings Up Best Bond Preview Box Office...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/no-time-to-die-weekend-box-office-1234852700/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Artist Releasing/MGM/Eon’s No Time to Die clocked $6.3M from Thursday previews that began at 4 p.m., making it the best Bond domestic preview number ever, 19% ahead of Spectre’s …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey's Big Risk (and Opportunity) If  Runs for Gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/politics-news/matthew-mcconaughey-texas-governor-2-1235027824/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the star vaguely embraces the idea of seeking higher office and leads a hypothetical statewide poll, Texas political insiders weigh in and warn: "People will start to hate him."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC hotel incurred $70 million in losses while president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/08/politics/trump-hotel-dc/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump racked up more than $70 million in losses over a four-year period from his Washington, DC, hotel, while publicly claiming that the hotel was making more than tens of millions of dollars, according to documents released by the House Oversight Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mass Surveillance System Set to Spoil Secret Lovers' Paradise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mass-surveillance-system-set-spoil-090019387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos GettyVENICE—Ah, Venice... The world’s favorite romantic getaway is synonymous with amorous trysts, and not always on the up and up. For centuries, the city—which by no small coincidence is the birthplace of legendary lover Casanova—has been a magnet for romantic affairs by politicians, Hollywood elite, and regular people. Hotels have long offered discreet services, secret entrances and private dining rooms so couples who shouldn’t be se</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING OUTRAGED: ELIMINATE INVADERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-10-07/china-levies-new-threats-at-reports-of-us-commandos-in-taiwan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘See whether the PLA will launch a targeted air strike to eliminate those U.S. invaders!’ the chief of the Chinese Communist Party’s propaganda outlet threatened on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's WALDORF Gets Plush Renovation, Becomes Icon of China's Overreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-10-08/waldorf-astoria-inside-the-renovation-slated-for-condos-hotel-owned-by-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storied hotel was bought by Anbang before its Chairman was jailed. Now it’s undergoing a vast renovation overseen by a state-backed enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrote album for her son...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211008122653-voy8o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSIC-ADELE/VOGUE (TV, PIX):Adele says she wrote upcoming album for her son</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax chiropractors rising force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/anti-virus-chiropractors-rising-force-misinformation-02b347767b45cab1d6d532be03c57529</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — The flashy postcard, covered with images of syringes, beckoned people to attend Vax-Con ’21 to learn “the uncensored truth” about COVID-19 vaccines. Participants traveled from around the country to a Wisconsin Dells resort for a sold-out convention that was, in fact, a sea of misinformation and conspiracy theories about vaccines and the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French cops board train, arrest tourist for 'wearing wrong type of  mask'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3817270/french-cops-eurostar-arrest-brit-wrong-type-of-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARMED French police boarded a London-bound Eurostar after a Brit was accused of wearing “the wrong type of mask”.  The drama saw the unidentified man being arrested and hauled off the train after i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America Running Out Of Everything...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/america-is-choking-under-an-e2-80-98everything-shortage-e2-80-99/ar-AAPeokg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global supply chain is slowing down at the very moment when Americans are demanding that it go into overdrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New doubts ahead of next fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article254856897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Chuck Schumer won this game of chicken,” Texas Sen. Ted Cruz told reporters before joining the majority of Republicans to vote against the McConnell agreement on the Senate floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake tech could soon allow anyone to create Hollywood-quality visual effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/deepfake-technology-60-minutes-2021-10-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday on 60 Minutes, Bill Whitaker demonstrates the magic of "synthetic media," allowing for the creation of photo-realistic videos and sound recordings completely generated by computers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Biden Agenda at Stake, Activists Target Sinema, Dividing Dems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/08/with-biden-agenda-at-stake-activists-target-sinema-dividing-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In the days after cellphone camera-toting protesters trailed Senator Kyrsten Sinema of Arizona into a university restroom to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sense Of Purpose Boosts Memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sense-of-purpose-better-memory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with more purpose also shared more sensory details, recalled their memories in the first-person, and had more positive feelings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing stunning levels of deaths, U.S. and Mexico revamp strained security cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/facing-stunning-levels-of-deaths-us-and-mexico-revamp-strained-security-cooperation/ar-AAPh7fU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has repeatedly criticized the Merida Intitiative, saying it promoted an ineffective “war on drugs." But the longtime leftist saw few possibilities to renegotiate it with former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Creates  'Mission Center' to Counter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cia-creates-new-mission-centers-china-and-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In announcing the changes, the CIA director referred to "increasingly adversarial Chinese government" as the "most important geopolitical threat we face in the 21st century."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing stunning levels of deaths, U.S. and Mexico revamp strained security cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/facing-stunning-levels-of-deaths-us-and-mexico-revamp-strained-security-cooperation/ar-AAPh7fU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has repeatedly criticized the Merida Intitiative, saying it promoted an ineffective “war on drugs." But the longtime leftist saw few possibilities to renegotiate it with former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Wisconsin incubator for tribal politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/wisconsin-the-incubator-for-america-e2-80-99s-tribal-politics/ar-AAPgKoo </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Hacking Group 'FIN12' Targets Hospitals, Clinics With Ransomware Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cyberattacks-ransomware-hacking-hospitals-target-foreign-groups/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ransomware attacks on hospitals during the pandemic have worsened outcomes for patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read link carefully: Scammers scoop up misspelled crypto URLs to rob wallet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/read-that-link-carefully-scammers-scoop-up-misspelled-cryptocurrency-urls-to-rob-your-wallet/ar-AAPh9mB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typo URLs, which look similar to the real URLs of cryptocurrency websites, have been used for fake versions of those sites that could steal your password -- and your money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico seek to revamp fight against cartels...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211008-us-mexico-seek-to-revamp-fight-against-drug-cartels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US, Mexico seek to revamp fight against drug cartels</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Hockney, lockdown was natural blessing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/david-hockney-lockdown-natural-blessing-061607179.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British artist David Hockney has always been a workhorse, so his months of lockdown in France were a welcome opportunity to devote himself to observing nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin police investigating 'Havana syndrome' cases at U.S. embassy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211008105911-nbu9t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-HAVANA SYNDROME/BERLIN:Berlin police investigating 'Havana syndrome' cases at U.S. embassy - Spiegel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery lingers around cause of California oil pipeline leak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-los-angeles-california-environment-and-nature-e3b2976b1986e0f4f2908cedc18f2854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON BEACH, Calif. (AP) — Investigators searching for the cause of an oil pipeline break off the Southern California coast have pointed to the possibility that a ship anchor dragged the line across the seabed and cracked it, but two videos released so far provide only tantalizing clues about what might have happened 100 feet (30 meters) below the ocean surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blast at Afghan mosque kills many, witnesses and Taliban say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-prayer-religion-2b9d9863da38661ba6fa186a72ac5352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — A powerful explosion in a mosque frequented by a religious minority group in northern Afghanistan on Friday has left several casualties, witnesses and the Taliban's spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catalytic converter thefts surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/catalytic-converter-thefts-have-surged-during-the-pandemic-police-are-fighting-back/ar-AAPgUJX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Takoma Park police have teamed up with RS Automotive to offer free etchings on catalytic converters amid a spike in thefts of the car part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Debt Now Totals $1.3 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/danalexander/2021/10/07/trumps-debt-now-totals-an-estimated-13-billion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real estate mogul should have no problem paying back his loans in the short term. But come 2024, when he might be running for president again, things could get dicey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She's 51, mother, devout Catholic. She plans to die by euthanasia Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/She-s-51-a-mother-and-a-devout-Catholic-She-16518431.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTÁ, Colombia - It began with a strange feeling in her hand, a weakness in the thumb...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL BLINKS ON DEBT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-congress-mitch-mcconnell-6e330d9fb94b73787ea70e7807b87151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate dodged a U.S. debt disaster Thursday night, voting to extend the government’s borrowing authority into December and temporarily avert an unprecedented federal default that experts warned would devastate the economy and harm millions of Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA MOVES TO TEX</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/07/tesla-moves-its-headquarters-from-california-to-texas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's growing dissatisfaction with California has been apparent for some time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
