<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The Revival of Stoicism...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxvmw/the-revival-of-stoicism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone from Silicon Valley billionaires to self-help enthusiasts is repurposing Stoicism for our modern age, with results that are good, bad, and highly indifferent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Secret History of Proud Boys' McInnes...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/the-secret-history-of-gavin-mcinnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the ’90s, he played punk rock and helped create Vice magazine. Five years ago, he founded a very different organization: the Proud Boys, the far-right group that came to personify the vilest tendencies of Trump’s America. A former Vice editor interviews one of our era’s most troubling extremists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When A City-Sized Star Becomes A Black Hole's Lunch, The Universe Roils...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/29/1011047410/city-sized-neutron-star-massive-black-hole-collide-gulps-universe-gravitational</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a smack down of one space monster by another: Scientists have made unprecedented observations of two black holes gobbling two neutron stars — among the weirdest space collisions ever detected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 40% Of San Fran Residents Plan To Move Amid Spike In Crime, Homelessness...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/29/poll-san-francisco-residents-consider-relocating-as-crime-worsen-quality-of-life-in-a-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As San Francisco tries to bounce back from the devastating impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, crime and homelessness now rank among the highest levels of concerns among local residents, many who are contemplating relocating, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations, Drownings...</title>
      <link>https://www.opb.org/article/2021/06/28/oregon-heat-wave-record-temperatures-health-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.opb.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures will begin to fall tonight and are forecast to be in the 90s for the rest of the week, bringing Oregonians some limited relief from dangerous heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letter sent in April warned damage was accelerating...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/29/us/florida-building-collapse-letter/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A correspondence from the board president of Champlain Towers South, which unexpectedly crashed to the ground last week in Surfside, Florida, describes the progression of decay at the building since 2018 saying, "the observable damage such as in the garage has gotten significantly worse since the initial inspection."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Wants to Scan Your Eyeball in Exchange for Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/sam-altman-wants-to-scan-your-eyeball-in-exchange-for-cryptocurrency/ar-AALzWOe </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson says 'Biden administration spying' on him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/560656-tucker-carlson-says-biden-administration-is-spying-on-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Tucker Carlson on Monday alleged that the Biden administration was “spying” on him in an effort to “take this show off the air.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF Australia in lockdown as Delta variant spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/australianz/half-of-australias-population-in-lockdown-as-delta-covid-19-variant-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brisbane became Australia's fourth regional capital city to restrict movement outside of homes.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 STILL MISSING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-miami-florida-a4a6051f1aa0168f73e833852617af9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Florida (AP) — The slow work of sifting through the remnants of a collapsed Florida condo building stretched into a sixth day Tuesday, as families desperate for progress endured a wrenching wait for answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans' long race to 2024 begins...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-michael-pence-election-2020-campaign-2016-government-and-politics-6c670a583ea8be1b46196ec75134623c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — In the past week alone, Nikki Haley regaled activists in Iowa, Mike Pence courted donors in California and Donald Trump returned to the rally stage , teasing a third campaign for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak in Fiji batters economy, tests health system...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fiji-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-business-health-10e9378c350adc39461e201308e92c15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUVA, Fiji (AP) — A growing coronavirus outbreak in Fiji is stretching the health system and devastating the economy. It has even prompted the government to offer jobless people tools and cash to become farmers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/heat-wave-builds-across-us-northwest-shattering-records/ar-AALxG5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unrelenting heat wave that shattered temperature records across the U.S. Pacific Northwest on Monday and threatens to smother the region for another six straight days has begun to trigger rolling blackouts in some parts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commodity Traders Making Billions...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/market/commodities/commodity-traders-make-billions-as-oil-copper-battery-metals-prices-rise-11624945411580.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From oil to steel, raw material prices are surging. As the world economy recovers, how much further does the boom have to run?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOFTBANK Mothballs Once-Hyped $1,800 Pepper Humanoid Robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/softbank-mothballs-once-hyped-1-800-pepper-humanoid-robot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SoftBank Halts Production of $1,800 Pepper Humanoid Robot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami condo parking garage flooded often before collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/champlain-towers-parking-garage-flooded-often-before-collapse-residents-and-ex-worker-say/ar-AALyroI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Columbia highest ever...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2021-06-28-record-heat-wave-northwest-washington-oregon-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's rewriting the record book. Here is a list of the records this heat wave has smashed already. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOLFF:  Giuliani was 'drinking heavily and incoherently telling Trump that Pence would overturn election results'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9734443/Book-Giuliani-drinking-heavily-telling-Trump-Pence-overturn-election-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani was 'heavily drinking' and fueling Trump's false belief that Pence could overturn the election results the day before the Jan. 6 Capitol riot, according to an upcoming book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Feinstein's Tahoe Compound For Sale at $41 Million....</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/06/26/sen-dianne-feinstein-tahoe-vacation-compound-for-sale-41-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Sen. Dianne Feinstein has put her picturesque Lake Tahoe vacation property up for sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil senators file case against Bolsonaro for malfeasance...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-senators-file-case-against-203820054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Brazilian senators formally accused President Jair Bolsonaro of malfeasance before the Supreme Court Monday over allegations he failed to have a top ally investigated for suspicions of massive corruption in the purchase of Covid-19 vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAT FIGHT:  New weight-loss tool prevents mouth from opening more than 2mm...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/jun/28/new-weight-loss-tool-dentalslim-diet-control</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DentalSlim Diet, which uses magnets, has been likened to ‘medieval torture device’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honeymoon fades as priorities downplayed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-honeymoon-with-liberals-fades-as-priorities-are-downplayed/ar-AALwmQs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s honeymoon with the most liberal wing of his party risks an abrupt and politically damaging end, with rising anxiety among progressives that the president won’t fulfill their aspirations for climate policy or expansions of voting rights and spending on social programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives say infrastructure compromise renews their doubts about Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/progressives-infrastructure-deal-gop-renews-201554001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's statement Saturday retreating from a threat to hold an infrastructure deal hostage to a bigger bill has left progressives fretting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico top court decriminalizes recreational marijuana use...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-top-court-decriminalizes-recreational-222500862.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's Supreme Court on Monday decriminalized recreational marijuana use for adults, drawing a cautious welcome from activists who said users face a "legal vacuum" until lawmakers pass a stalled legalization bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condo collapse in Miami triggers fear in coastal cities...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/condo-collapse-surfside-triggers-fear-215500288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the world spotlight shines on Surfside’s condo collapse, other coastal cities in South Florida are asking the question: Could it happen here? Those same cities want to make sure it doesn’t. Miami-Dade County is already planning an audit of older buildings after Thursday’s collapse of the Champlain Towers South condo. Coastal cities from Fort Lauderdale to Hollywood, Hallandale Beach and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo Musical Written by Harvey Weinstein Accuser, With Music from Diane Warren, Will Open Not Far from His Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/28/diane-warren-susan-stroman-musical-the-right-girl-to-get-autumn-workshop-in-upstate-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Right Girl” is the name of the musical with songs by Diane Warren, directed by Tony winner Susan Stroman. The musical is opening in the wrong place at the right time. Written by a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victim was in town for virus funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/miami-condo-collapse-man-in-town-for-covid-19-funeral-among-missing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay Kleiman traveled from Puerto Rico to go back to the condominium where he grew up north of Miami Beach for an old high school friend's funeral. But hours before the ceremony, the high-rise building in the affluent neighborhood of Surfside collapsed, leaving more than 100 people missing overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Marine shot in Midtown...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/28/police-to-flood-the-zone-in-times-square-after-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor de Blasio on Monday vowed police would “flood the zone” in Times Square in wake of the shooting that injured a tourist — as the Big Apple seeks to rebound from the COVID-19 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL says 'Football is gay'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2021/06/28/nfl-carl-nassib-football-gay-commercial/7783421002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A week after Carl Nassib publicly came out, the NFL released a new commercial, "Football is gay," showing support of the LGBTQ+ community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS:  Cracked concrete, standing water days before...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article252421658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was nothing unusual about the lobby and pool area at Champlain Towers South condo, which looked clean and well maintained to a commercial pool contractor who visited the building last Tuesday, just 36 hours before half of the building unexpectedly collapsed. Then, he saw the basement-level garage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New camo tech makes soldiers virtually 'invisible'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israels-camouflage-technology-soldiers-virtually-082656169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polaris Solutions is working with special forces units in Canada and the United States to bring the technology to North America, it was reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AS HELL: Pakistan city hottest place on EARTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3176259/pakistan-city-hottest-earth-52c-no-air-con/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PAKISTAN city is now the hottest place on Earth at 52C – where most homes don’t have air-con and it’s too hot to touch the floor. That’s far hotter than in 2015, when two heatwa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Bailout Plagued by Potential $260 Billion in Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/06/28/government-pandemic-loans-plagued-by-potential-260-billion-in-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hasty work behind the PPP and other relief loans shows the limits of big government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN staff angered at news chief's conflict of interest over Israel ambassador pick...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/28/cnn-workers-mad-at-top-news-chiefs-conflict-of-interest-over-israel-pick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN staff are furious after the husband of their top news chief was nominated for US ambassador to Israel – claiming the move is a conflict of interest, The Post is told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Nevada title won by trans woman for 1st time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nv-state-wire-nevada-entertainment-33ec7e16a75242ab51bbf19e1a816bb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — For the first time in the pageant’s history, the title of Miss Nevada USA has been won by a transgender woman. Kataluna Enriquez was crowned the winner Sunday at the South Point hotel-casino in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untold story of how racy sexts upended key Senate race and shifted power in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/opinion/article252334948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A phone call helped derail Cal Cunningham’s campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How daily lives are tracked by phones, laptops and even doorbells...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/15407421/daily-lives-tracked-doorbells-how-your-data-collected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN OXFORD professor has claimed that we are allowing more and more of our personal data to be used – and are being spied on by DOORBELLS.  Professor Carissa Veliz  has warned that o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order pushes enforcement throughout economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/exclusive-white-house-prepares-order-directing-agencies-consider-antitrust-2021-06-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is working on an antitrust executive order that aims to push government agencies to consider how their decisions will impact competition in an industry, according to two sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant eruption of Costa Rica volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210628-giant-eruption-of-costa-rica-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Giant eruption of Costa Rica volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts share new theories...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/28/florida-building-collapse-reportedly-started-from-the-bottom-of-the-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dusenberry — who has investigated other building collapses — told the New York Times that the way the building went down suggests there could be an issue with foundation of the building — such as &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pools closed...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/weather/2021/06/portland-parks-pools-max-service-schools-closed-due-to-extreme-heat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out this list of businesses and services that are closed Monday due to historic high temperatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-Pound Chunk Of Ice Crashes Through Roof Of CA Home...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/25/10-pound-chunk-of-ice-falls-through-roof-of-yucaipa-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlett Yablonsky said she and her little dog, Doodles, had just gotten up off the couch and gone to bed Thursday night when what sounded like a bomb blast shook them back awake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's oldest person aged 119' credits diet of butter, honey, cheese and egg...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3173664/gran-worlds-oldest-person-119-diet-turkey-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GRAN claimed to be the world’s oldest person has celebrated turning 119 – and puts her long life down to her fatty diet of butter and cheese. Seker Arslan was reported to be even older yest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House prepping big assault on monopolies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/28/white-house-monopolies-executive-order-496749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An executive order being crafted for President Joe Biden's signature seeks to go beyond antitrust enforcement to promote competition throughout the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals struggle with jammed ERs after exodus of nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2021/06/hospitals-struggle-to-deal-with-jammed-emergency-rooms-after-exodus-of-nurses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ER surge has added more stress to the lives of front-line health care workers who hoped for a peaceful interlude after the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AMAZON Bullies, Manipulates, and Lies to Reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2021/06/amazon-journalists-pr-tactics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company's cutthroat corporate culture cripples critical coverage—and your right to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man threatened to blow up MCDONALD's over missing dipping sauce...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/dipping-sauce-threat-416058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 28--After realizing that dipping sauce was not included with his Chicken McNuggets order, an Iowa man called his local McDonald’s and threatened to blow up the restaurant, according to investigat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abu Dhabi will only allow vaccinated in some public spaces...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/abu-dhabi-will-only-allow-vaccinated-people-some-public-spaces-aug-20-2021-06-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abu Dhabi in the United Arab Emirates will only allow vaccinated people in some public spaces, including schools, universities and nurseries, from August 20, the emirate's media office said in a tweet on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did so many homeless die while staying at LA hotel?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/homeless-housing/story/2021-06-28/la-homeless-people-died-after-entering-covid-hotel-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight people died while they were living at the Airtel Plaza Hotel in Van Nuys, where hundreds of homeless people have been housed through Project Roomkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope thanks US priest for LGBTQ outreach...</title>
      <link>https://religionnews.com/2021/06/27/pope-sends-letter-praising-priest-who-ministers-to-lgbtq-catholics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;religionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — Francis described Martin’s work, which has centered on LGBTQ Catholics, as 'continually seeking to imitate this style of God.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUESTIONS MOUNT</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/questions-mount-florida-building-could-150115820.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Questions mounted Monday about how a residential building in the Miami area could have collapsed so quickly and violently last week, as the death toll rose to 10 with more than 150 still unaccounted for, and desperate families feared the worst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Org given  deadline to persuade prosecutors not to file charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-organization-attorneys-given-monday-deadline-to-persuade-prosecutors-not-to-file-charges-against-it/ar-AALvGPp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deadline is a strong signal that charges are being considered as part of a two-year investigation into the former president’s company business dealings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands stranded in Bangladesh ahead of sweeping lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thousands-stranded-bangladesh-ahead-sweeping-070333232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people were stranded in Bangladesh's capital on Monday as authorities halted almost all public transport ahead of a sweeping lockdown imposed to combat a deadly resurgence of Covid-19 infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danish media unite to push tech giants on rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/danish-media-unite-push-tech-151859979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark's main media outlets said Monday they are banding together to negotiate copyright payments for news content used by tech platforms such as Google and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger Frustration Mounts As Lines Get Longer At Understaffed Airports...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/06/25/passenger-frustration-mounts-as-lines-get-longer-at-understaffed-airports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter where your vacation plans take you, if you're flying, you might want to listen up. People are having trouble making their flights. From TSA shortages to plane delays, passengers say they're beyond frustrated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami condo collapse echoes tragedies in Brazil, Egypt and India -- where lax oversight takes heavy toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/florida-condo-collapse-echoes-tragedies-in-brazil-egypt-and-india-%C3%A2%E2%82%AC%E2%80%9D-where-lax-oversight-takes-heavy-toll/ar-AALwW3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around the world, the conditions behind these catastrophes have become endemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman bites NYPD officer during mayhem at Washington Square Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-bites-nypd-officer-in-melee-at-washington-square-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people were arrested in Washington Square Park including a woman who bit an NYPD officer, said cops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Once-In-A-Millenium'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/heat-wave-dome-2021-seattle-portland-weather/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heat is being caused by a combination of a significant atmospheric blocking pattern on top of a human-caused climate changed world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roads buckle in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/crazy-hot-seattle-shatters-all-time-high-temperature-record/969997</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The weather was so abnormally hot over the weekend that at least one resident AccuWeather spoke with couldn't wait to get back to work on Monday -- for the air conditioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Columbia at 116!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2021-06-22-northwest-dangerous-record-heat-late-june</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This heat wave in the Northwest is rewriting the record books in places not accustomed to such extreme heat. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/refresh/AL042021_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/145037_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEACH BUILDING BECOMES MASS GRAVE SITE</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article252414358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an early morning thunderstorm gave way to sunshine, Rosana Esther Lerman didn’t miss her 8 a.m. beach walk on Monday, but the last few days haven’t been the same as before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Steer Superyachts to Greece...</title>
      <link>https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/consumer/worlds-rich-steer-superyachts-to-greece-after-covid-reopening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businesstimes.com.sg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore's Controversial Surveillance Plane Program Ruled Unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/06/25/baltimores-controversial-surveillance-plane-program-ruled-unconstitutional/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fourth Circuit U.S. Court of Appeals ruled Thursday Baltimore’s controversial aerial surveillance program is unconstitutional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Wants to Dismantle Two Weapons Richest 0.1% Use to Avoid Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/biden-wants-to-dismantle-two-weapons-the-richest-01-25-use-to-avoid-taxes/ar-AALxlWD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Provisions in the U.S. Treasury’s ‘Green Book’ proposal could disrupt dynasty trusts and other vehicles that have benefitted wealthy families for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm watch off Georgia, SC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/south-carolina-tropical-storms-storms-256d384548e18a7f5c86466af5062f28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARIETTA, Ga. (AP) — Forecasters are watching a weather a system they say has a good chance of strengthening and dropping large amounts of rain on the Georgia and South Carolina coastlines. The well-defined area of low pressure was about 190 miles (306 kilometers) east of Hilton Head Island, South Carolina on Monday morning, the National Hurricane Center said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia faces off with NATO as Putin tests nuke, hypersonic missile jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3171998/russia-launch-icbm-nato-war-games/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has launched a highly-secretive new nuke and tested military jets carrying hypersonic missiles – as NATO nations begin war games in the Black Sea. The mystery ballistic missile took of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans Boy Wins Bathroom Fight as Top Court Spurns Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-won-t-hear-dispute-over-bathrooms-transgender-students-n1272513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday's order denying review in the case means Gavin Grimm's victory in the lower courts remains intact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citing racism, UN rights chief seeks reparations for Blacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-race-and-ethnicity-government-and-politics-8fa368dced6c7e34af4e4ecc3fdbccb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The U.N. human rights chief, in a landmark report launched after the killing of George Floyd in the United States, is urging countries worldwide to do more to help end discrimination, violence and systemic racism against people of African descent and “make amends” to them — including through reparations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: 2021 BRONCO legit JEEP killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/reviews/2021-ford-bronco-preview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's real and it's spectacular. Here's why the Blue Oval's SUV is the smarter hardcore choice for more buyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald's Situation Room shouting match...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-mark-milley-protests-michael-bender-a41db287-7f6a-43d9-9a4c-1ba7a0307881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump wanted to put Milley in charge of a scorched-earth military campaign to suppress protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO  MIRACLES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/surfside-building-collapse-0628-c885818bf43a1ec3e4d825aeff06f9f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — Rescue workers digging feverishly for a fifth day Monday stressed that they could still find survivors in the rubble of a collapsed Florida condo building, a hope family members clung to even though no one has been pulled out alive since the first hours after the structure fell.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
