<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pushed AG Twice to Release Summaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/01/us/politics/mueller-letters-barr.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert S. Mueller III wrote that “there is now public confusion about critical aspects of the results of our investigation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professed ignorance prompts calls for resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Barr-s-professed-ignorance-prompts-calls-for-his-13809829.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In back-to-back congressional hearings on April 9 and 10, Attorney General William Barr disclaimed knowledge of the thinking of special counsel Robert Mueller and members of his team of prosecutors investigating Russian interference in the 2016 election.  "No, I don't," Barr said, when asked by Rep. Charlie Crist, D-Fla., whether he knew what was behind reports that members of Mueller's team were frustrated by the attorney general's summary of their top-level conclusions.  "I don't know," he said the next day, when asked by Sen. Chris Van Hollen, D-Md., whether Mueller supported his finding that there was not sufficient evidence to conclude that President Donald Trump had obstructed justice.  These statements resurfaced Tuesday following the revelation that Mueller had sent a letter to Barr two weeks earlier objecting to the attorney general's characterization of the probe.  Suggesting that Mueller's letter - only portions of which have been made public - belied the sworn testimony of the attorney general, Van Hollen recirculated a clip of his back-and-forth with Barr and declared, "He must resign."  In an interview with The Washington Post, the Maryland Democrat said he believed Barr's answer was "completely misleading because he was well aware of the fact that Bob Mueller had raised questions with the substance of the conclusions stated in the attorney general's letter."  The Justice Department didn't immediately return a request for comment on Van Hollen's accusation.  In the March 27 letter, Mueller protested that Barr's four-page memo "did not fully capture the context, nature, and substance" of his work, according to a copy reviewed by The Post. In a subsequent phone conversation between Mueller and Barr - longtime colleagues whose differences of opinion about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skies darken as millions of locusts invade Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1121121/saudi-arabia-news-locust-swarm-najran-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SWARM of locusts seemingly darken the skies and added a thick layer of insects to trees as they invaded Najran in Saudia Arabia at the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside secret world of CIA's social media team...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/441480-inside-the-secret-world-of-the-cias-social-media-team</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A government agency known for its secrecy is making a splash in a very public forum: Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Flushed Kin's Cremated Remains...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/ashes-get-flushed-482091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 30--After his mother kicked him out of her Pennsylvania residence, a 33-year-old man flushed his grandparents’ ashes down the home's toilet, a bizarre retaliatory move for which he is facing cr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifetime supply of California tap water could increase cancer risk...</title>
      <link>http://www.ktvu.com/news/ktvu-local-news/study-a-lifetime-supply-of-california-tap-water-could-increase-cancer-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study published Tuesday claims that drinking California tap water over the course of a lifetime could potentially increase your risk of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may have to stop borrowing later this year: Treasury...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-treasury-refunding/u-s-may-have-to-stop-borrowing-later-this-year-treasury-idUSKCN1S73U4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government will have to stop borrowing money between July and December ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER CHALLENGED BARR SPIN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mueller-complained-that-barrs-letter-did-not-capture-context-of-trump-probe/ar-AAAKJB8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS to start DNA testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/30/politics/homeland-security-dna-testing-immigration/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest mummies NOT in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/worlds-oldest-mummies-chile/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Space Station hit by major power shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/may/01/international-space-station-hit-by-major-power-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX delivery delayed after old power-switching unit malfunctions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Voters say Trump TWITTER use could cost him reelection...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/01/morning-consult-poll-trump-twitter-1295248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;7 in 10 voters say Trump uses Twitter too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie and Biden Circle Each Other, Using Different Rules of Engagement...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sanders-and-biden-circle-each-other-using-different-rules-of-engagement/ar-AAAKNqg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas shootings add to concerns over ex-military and extremism...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article229854289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Gateway to hell' where Mayans made human sacrifices uncovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/775835/guatemala-flores-Lake-Pet-n-Itz-mayans-gateway-to-underworld-historians</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Armageddon' rioting breaks out in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6980499/Armageddon-rioting-breaks-Paris-extremist-demonstrators-hijack-Day-protests.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Black Bloc anti-capitalist movement were involved in clashes with police this afternoon. By 1pm there had been a total of 165 arrests in the French capital with much of the city on lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President depicted in Mueller report feared being tabbed fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/677b7b2f0c184e65921afe2314e468ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The fear was persistent. As the Russia investigation heated up and threatened to shadow Donald Trump's presidency, he became increasingly concerned. But the portrait...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 4 Americans feel they have no one to confide in...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/30/1-in-4-americans-feel-they-have-no-one-to-confide-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in four people don’t feel they have someone to confide in, according to new research. Even after sharing their feelings, seven in 10 have held back how they really felt from a coworker, friend,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine under investigation for swastika boot photo...
</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/marine-corps-reservist-investigation-photo-boots-forming-swastika/story?id=62728105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Marine Corps reservist is under investigation for posting a photo on Instagram that showed four pairs of boots in the shape of a swastika.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening statement...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2019/4/30/18524880/william-barr-mueller-report-senate-testimony-read</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Attorney General’s remarks were released ahead of his appearance before the Senate Judiciary Committee on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: You SHOULD have sex on first date...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sun-men/8973401/sex-first-date-relationship-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT’S official – if you want a serious relationship, you need to have sex quickly. A new survey has revealed that more than a third of men found love after sleeping with their partner on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exiles dream of returning home as they wait for Maduro fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/30/venezuelan-exiles-dream-of-returning-home-as-they-wait-for-maduros-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exiles converge at embassies and consulates around the world to throw their weight behind the attempt to oust Nicolás Maduro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON facial-recognition supercharging police...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Amazon-s-facial-recognition-technology-is-13808193.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HILLSBORO, Ore. - When workers at an Ace Hardware here reported that a woman had walked out of the store with an $11.99 tank of welding gas that she hadn't paid for in her tote bag, an elaborate high-tech crime-fighting operation sprang into action.  A Washington County sheriff's detective, working with the agency's Special Investigations Unit, ran the store's surveillance footage through an internal facial-recognition program built by Amazon, revealing a possible match.  That woman's license plate was flagged and, three months later, a narcotics officer in an unmarked SUV saw it and radioed other patrol deputies to stop her. A deputy clapped a pair of handcuffs around her wrists, an arrest report states. She said she'd needed the gas to fix her car.  Deputies in this corner of western Oregon outside ultraliberal Portland used to track down criminals the old-fashioned way, faxing caught-on-camera images of a suspect around the office in hope that someone might recognize the face.  Then, in late 2017, the Washington County Sheriff's Office became the first law enforcement agency in the country known to use Amazon's artificial-intelligence tool Rekognition, transforming this thicket of forests and suburbs into a public testing ground for a new wave of experimental police surveillance techniques.  Almost overnight, deputies saw their investigative powers supercharged, allowing them to scan for matches of a suspect's face across more than 300,000 mug shots taken at the county jail since 2001. A grainy picture of someone's face - captured by a security camera, a social media account or a deputy's smartphone - can quickly become a link to their identity, including their name, family and address. More than 1,000 facial-recognition searches were logged last year, said deputies, who sometimes used the results to find a suspect's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives want bishops to declare pope heretic...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-heresy/conservatives-want-catholic-bishops-to-declare-pope-a-heretic-idUSKCN1S73KE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Roman Catholic priests, academics and intellectuals have issued an op...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV viewers turn to antennae to escape cable prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90342475/young-tv-viewers-turn-to-antennas-to-escape-cables-insane-prices </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Survey says 31% of U.S. households now use an antenna, with 45% adoption among 25- to 34-year-olds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating MORE rice could be protective against obesity?</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2019-04/eaft-iss043019.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE defies record fall in iPhone sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/30/apple-earnings-show-company-moving-beyond-iphone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iPhone is becoming less important to Apple's total sales as the smartphone industry stalls and shrinks globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Bet on Guaido Tested...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-01/trump-s-bet-on-guaido-is-tested-as-maduro-remains-in-caracas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange sentenced to 50 weeks prison in bail-jumping case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-48118908 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wikileaks co-founder is sentenced to 50 weeks after nearly seven years in the Ecuadorian Embassy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris on edge as thousands gather for rallies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/paris-edge-thousands-gather-may-1-rallies-111045279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands began rallying for May Day in Paris on Wednesday, with a heady mix of labour unionists, "yellow vest" demonstrators and hardline troublemakers expected to turn out in a test for France's zero-tolerance policy on protest violence. Authorities have warned that this year's marches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIAGRA could cure heart failure...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-05-sex-drug-effective-heart-failure.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drug used to treat erectile dysfunction has been found by University of Manchester scientists to slow or even reverse the progression of heart failure in sheep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Tax for Infrastructure Sparks Fears of Political Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gas-tax-infrastructure-sparks-fears-080000147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasing the gas tax is so politically fraught that it hasn’t been touched in 26 years and it didn’t even come up at a meeting at the White House Tuesday between President Donald Trump, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer to discuss an infrastructure plan. While they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr faces brutal hearing after Mueller revelation...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/01/barr-hearing-mueller-report-1295274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney general will be in the hot seat after news broke of Mueller's dissatisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt searches of phones, laptops at airports rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/transportation/us-searches-of-phones-and-laptops-at-airports-rising-lawsuit-says-20190430.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly filed papers filed in a federal lawsuit claim that U.S. government searches of phones and laptops at airports are on the rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 2 lawmakers view less-redacted document...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/30/mueller-report-redacted-1295105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats want to see a fully unredacted report. Some Republicans say they simply trust Barr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Welcomes Biden To Race With Broadsides...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/30/us/politics/joe-biden-bernie-sanders-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Biden is trying to stay above the intraparty fray, invoking his years with Obama. Mr. Sanders is taking direct aim at the former vice president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes rock Venezuela as Guaido urges uprising...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6975871/Venezuelas-Juan-Guaido-calls-military-revolt-final-phase-overthrowing-President-Maduro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy gunfire was heard near La Carlota airbase in the Venezuelan capital Caracas on Tuesday, after opposition leader Juan Guaido announced the start of an armed uprising against President Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOW OR NEVER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0153cace08c84c8fbf34f9c6a7bdd4dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Opposition leader Juan Guaidó took a bold step to revive his movement to seize power in Venezuela, taking to the streets Tuesday to call for a military uprising that drew...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. rips INSTA for censorship after pic with wounded vet deleted...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/30/donald-trump-jr-rips-instagram-for-censorship-afte/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump Jr. wants to know why his recent picture with a wounded combat veteran was deemed a violation of Instagram’s terms of service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schmidt GOOGLE Departure Follows Misconduct Cover-Up Reports...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/4/30/18524495/google-alphabet-board-eric-schmidt-steps-down-18-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Departure follows backlash over reports of sexual misconduct cover-ups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Dead, 4 Injured After Shooting at UNC Charlotte...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article229873794.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Patron told no dog inside bar. Then rammed bartender with car...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/communities/southwest/news/greenfield/2019/04/29/police-man-hit-greenfield-bartender-car-outside-fin-n-feather/3615301002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Milwaukee man has been charged with intentionally hitting a bartender with his car after he was told not to bring his dog into a Greenfield tavern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens Cuba as US supports uprising...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8a18145f858e41e88475360b9a7decee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration declared quick and enthusiastic support Tuesday for the Venezuelan opposition effort to spark a military uprising against embattled President Nicolas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg 'joke' on privacy bombs as audience silent...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/mark-zuckerberg-privacy-joke-facebook-f8-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Awkward doesn't begin to cover it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Carrying Cross On Trek Across America...</title>
      <link>https://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/us/2019/april/i-was-one-block-away-from-killing-myself-sc-man-carries-cross-sees-god-at-work-on-trek-to-grand-canyon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Acie Burleson encountered Jesus Christ as his Savior, he learned about the biblical command to deny himself, take up his cross, and follow the Lord as Matthew 16:24 states. Years later, he says he's heard from God and has started a journey to literally carry the cross all the way to the Grand Canyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Highest-paid CEOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/04/30/highest-paid-ceos-at-americas-largest-companies-tim-cook-robert-iger/39389897/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall Street reviewed CEO pay at the largest, publicly traded US companies to identify the best-paid CEOs. Tim Cook and Robert Iger make the list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anything to help get God's word out'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesdaily.com/news/local/cross-bearing-journey-reaches-colbert-county/article_43124db9-92dd-560c-9689-86e656cc3d3a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acie Burleson said when he was saved as a Christian some years ago, along with that came a calling to carry Christ's cross.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang to give voter $12,000 to demonstrate policy plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/2019/04/29/2020-presidential-candidate-andrew-yang-give-freedom-dividend-iowa-thousand-dollars-ubi-democrat/3613590002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 Candidate Andrew Yang wants to select an Iowan to receive $1,000 a month for a year out of his own pocket followed up by a hologram campaign stop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious footprints of mythical Yeti sighted, Indian Army claims...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/mysterious-footprints-of-mythical-beast-yeti-sighted-claims-indian-army/articleshow/69107428.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India News: Indian Army on Tuesday claimed that one of its teams spotted mysterious footprints of mythical creature "Yeti" close to Nepal's Makalu Base Camp. Duri</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Worker Gets 10 Years for Insanely Elaborate $4M Heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alaska-keybank-worker-gets-10-years-for-insanely-elaborate-dollar4-million-heist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gerardo Adan Cazarez Valenzuela planned every detail, down to hiring a private getaway jet, but he didn’t count on Mexican police searching his luggage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military colonel shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/americas/live-news/juan-guaido-venezuela-operation-freedom-live-updates/h_fafa4ed6517202198a3cc759bd85212b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A military colonel was reportedly shot during clashes with the opposition on the Francisco Fajardo highway, Venezuela’s Minister of Defense Vladimir Padrino tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorcyclist Crashes While Flipping Off Woman On Highway...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/04/30/police-motorcyclist-who-crashed-after-flipping-off-woman-critical-condition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A motorcyclist who lost control and crashed after allegedly flipping off a driver on a Texas highway is in critical condition, deputies said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff Hires Ex-Chief of FBI Financial Crimes Section...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/adam-schiff-hires-patrick-fallon-ex-chief-of-fbi-financial-crimes-section-to-probe-trumps-finances/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Fallon jumps from the upper echelon of the bureau to Congress as Democrats ramp up investigations of president’s finances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Final phase'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/venezuela-s-opposition-leader-juan-guaido-calls-military-uprising-n999966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Today, the armed forces are clearly on the side of the people, they are on the side of the constitution," Venezuela's opposition leader said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOMORROW:  Barr to face Mueller report questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f857b3f06c7b48db91989377b008db90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General William Barr on Wednesday will face lawmakers' questions for the first time since releasing special counsel Robert Mueller's Russia report, in what promises to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas unveil slate of series, documentaries for NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f40010a4c1d2431b82fce2ea2a9b5843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Barack and Michelle Obama on Tuesday unveiled a slate of projects they are preparing for Netflix, a year after the former president and first lady signed a deal with the streaming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball's Attendance Problem Getting Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2019/04/30/mlb-attendance-first-month/3626164002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseballâ€™s attendance problem is not going away, as a significant dip in 2018 has endured into the new season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: ESPN Kills 'The Magazine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/tech-media/2019/04/30/espn-the-magazine-shut-down-stop-print-edition-september</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN will stop publishing the print edition of its 21-year-old publication, ESPN the Magazine, in September. How did the merge of Insider and ESPN+ play a role?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair tells jail they're detectives in attempt to get 'partner' out...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article229849059.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seems like Alzheimer's -- but peek into brain shows mimic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/791c3ea82e1a40a59d603cfc109d1ad9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Some people told they have Alzheimer's may instead have a newly identified mimic of the disease — and scientists say even though neither is yet curable, it's critical to get...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'Church' Distributes Marijuana As Sacrament...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/04/30/officials-crack-down-church-that-uses-marijuana-sacrament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marijuana is still illegal in Wisconsin, but a church that recently opened its doors in Madison may have found a loophole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: ESPN Kills 'The Magazine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sportsbusinessdaily.com/SB-Blogs/Breaking-News/2019/04/ESPN-Mag.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sportsbusinessdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firm slammed after job posting seeks 'preferably Caucasian' candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/recruitment-firm-cynet-slammed-after-job-posting-seeks-preferably-caucasian-n1000066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company apologized on Twitter and said the people responsible for the post had been fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive police deployment planned for Paris May Day marches...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190430-massive-police-deployment-planned-paris-may-day-marches</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Massive police deployment planned for Paris May Day marches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet restricted...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b271ef1f15940f394343dd2027a23e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — The Latest on the political crisis in Venezuela (all times local): 1:00 p.m. The U.N. says Secretary-General Antonio Guterres is urging all sides in Venezuela...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record high homeless in NYC...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/homelessness-at-record-highs-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report gives the city and state an &amp;quot;F&amp;quot; grade for handling the homeless crisis in New York City as the numbers of people in the street continues to reach record numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abroad, sting of Trump's tweets dullzzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Abroad-the-sting-of-Trump-s-tweets-dulls-13806268.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Donald Trump tweeted Wednesday that Britain's intelligence service had helped the Obama administration spy on his 2016 campaign, the British metaphorically yawned and issued verbatim their response to the same Trump charge more than two years earlier.  "Nonsense. . . . Utterly ridiculous and should be ignored," said a spokesman for Government Communications Headquarters, the British equivalent of the U.S. National Security Agency.  The same day, when Trump tweeted for the umpteenth time that Mexico "is not doing nearly enough" to apprehend drug smugglers and migrants, and threatened to send "ARMED SOLDIERS" to the border, Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador figuratively shrugged.  Mexico would, of course, look into any U.S. concerns, López Obrador said at a Mexico City news conference. But "the most important thing is to tell [Trump] that we are not going to fight with the government of the United States. . . . We are not going to be tripped up by any provocation."  Friendly countries that have been the target of Trump's tweets have learned he is not always bluffing. Aluminum and steel tariffs really were imposed on allies, and the Pentagon is sending more troops to assist in Border Patrol operations.  But few now take Trump's Twitter fulminations at immediate face value. "He has shown us that what's black at 9 a.m. can be gray at 3 p.m. and white at 7 p.m.," said a Mexican diplomat of the president's revolving pronouncements.  Most have learned that responding in kind only makes matters worse. "If you don't pick a fight with him, you take away from Trump the possibility of further enraging himself and everybody else," said the diplomat, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to avoid fueling any fires.  Gérard Araud, France's U.S. ambassador until earlier this month, said he told his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S sales beat with free bacon...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mcdonald-s-corp-results/mcdonalds-u-s-sales-beat-as-free-bacon-value-meals-attract-diners-idUSKCN1S61CQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald's Corp lured diners with short-term bacon promotion, value meals a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol releasing thousands who were exposed to diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/border-patrol-releasing-thousands-exposed-diseases-like-tuberculosis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why does coming here illegally exempt aliens from the laws on the books that make them inadmissible?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW VIDEO SHOWS ILLEGALS FLOODING INTO ARIZONA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/04/30/video-111-central-american-migrants-cross-arizona-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New surveillance video released by CBP reveals the moment when a group of migrants crossed the border into Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA opposes giving Roger Stone full Mueller report...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2019/04/us-opposes-giving-roger-stone-full-copy-of-mueller-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal prosecutors say they oppose a request from Roger Stone to see an unredacted copy of special counsel Robert Mueller’s Russia report. Stone, a longtime confidant of President…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Star Salaries Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/celebrity-salaries-leonardo-dicaprio-margot-robbie-dwayne-johnson-will-smith-1203200508/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood stars owe Netflix a big thank-you. The streaming service is bolstering pay packages for the most famous actors in the business at a time when studios are getting downright stingy about wr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies Consider Banning ALL Physical Contact In Workplace...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/04/29/goodbye-handshakes-some-companies-considering-banning-all-physical-contact-in-workplace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey by TotalJobs found that three out of four people want all physical contact banned at work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film on Catholic priests using nuns as 'sex slaves' pulled...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/film-catholic-priests-using-nuns-sex-slaves-pulled-150331344.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hit documentary about how some Catholic priests allegedly abused nuns in different parts of the world has been pulled from the Franco-German television channel Arte after a priest complained to a German court. The big-budget media investigation, "Sex Slaves in the Catholic Church", was broadcast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal prosecution of illegal entries dramatically slows... </title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/immigration/story/2019-04-27/criminal-prosecution-of-illegal-entries-dramatically-slows-in-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol says attention has turned to handling surge of families and children crossing illegally, taking agents away from other law enforcement priorities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Demand Impeachment, But Were Staunchest Opponents During 90s...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/bill-dagostino/2019/04/30/todays-media-demand-trumps-impeachment-were-staunchest-opponents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the redacted Mueller report was released two weeks ago, TV journalists have been among the biggest advocates for impeaching President Trump. Yet curiously during the late 1990s, journalists were among the loudest voices against impeaching then-President Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test dummies fall off roller coaster, crash into hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Roller-Coaster-Test-Dummies-Fall-Crash-Ocean-City-Jersey-Shore-Hotel-Roof-509233341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president of a Jersey Shore amusement park insists that a roller coaster is safe more than a week after two test dummies fell out of it and crashed into the roof of a nearby hotel. The incident...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental tsunami warning sends Jersey Shore into panic...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Dont-Panic-Errant-Tsunami-Warning-Sent-in-Jersey-Shore-Town-New-Jersey-Tri-State-509226671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For three minutes Monday afternoon, a town along the Jersey Shore was under a tsunami alert, causing phones to ring off the hook at police headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's lack of cooperation with Congress sparks more impeachment push...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-s-lack-of-cooperation-with-Congress-sparks-13805488.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Frustration among House Democratic investigators is intensifying after President Donald Trump's refusal to cooperate with congressional inquiries, leading some to privately question whether they should try to pressure Speaker Nancy Pelosi into launching impeachment proceedings.  The chairmen and members of the six panels investigating the president are increasingly angered by the White House's unwillingness to comply as they carry out their oversight role, according to several House Democratic officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss the matter freely. But that anger extends into the ranks of Pelosi's team as well, according to leadership officials.  A recent threat by Attorney General William Barr not to show up for a scheduled hearing Thursday before the House Judiciary Committee has exacerbated the situation after the White House last week vowed to block some officials from appearing for subpoenaed depositions or interviews.  Earlier this month, several lawmakers from the most liberal wing of the caucus had called for impeachment after the release of special counsel Robert Mueller's report. But Pelosi, D-Calif., fearing 2020 election fallout from such a politically divisive step, had asked Democratic investigators to hold off and continue their inquiries.  But Trump's no-cooperation stance is blocking that mission; his team has publicly directed administration officials to ignore House Democrats, prompting several of the more-establishment Democrats to favor pursuing impeachment in a notable shift on Capitol Hill. Pelosi makes the final decision.  "The Mueller report and this assault on the legislative branch made Nancy's call to avoid impeachment much more difficult for rank-and-file members," said Rep. Gerald Connolly, D-Va., a member of the Oversight Committee. "We've moved from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAELI ENVOY CALLS FOR CRIMINALIZING ANTISEMITISM AFTER NYT CARTOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Diaspora/Antisemitism/Israeli-envoy-calls-for-criminalizing-antisemitism-after-NYT-cartoon-588234</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€œThe time for talking and having a conversation is over."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SUES TO BLOCK SUBPOENAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/29/politics/trump-lawsuit-capital-one/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump, three of his children -- Donald Jr., Eric and Ivanka -- and his business are suing two banks to block them from turning over financial records to congressional committees that have issued subpoenas for the information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers wash up 'in fragile place' after historic Midwest floods...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-midwest-farmers-20190430-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON In the weeks after flooding drowned the livelihoods of families who've farmed along the Missouri River for generations, rural advocates in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAYDAY CARACAS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190430144200-hk2yf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Venezuela's Guaido urges troops to rise, mass protests planned</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
