<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Biden Says He Doesn't See Votes to Raise Tax Rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-says-he-doesn-t-see-votes-to-raise-tax-rates-in-deal/ar-AAPObRO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden said he doesn’t think there are enough Democratic votes to raise tax rates in a deal on his economic agenda, but that he believes he’ll reach an agreement on the overall legislative package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Americans Feel Most Stressed At 36...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-most-stress-age-36/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite this — a recent survey finds the average respondent is better at managing stress now than they were a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROP GUN DEATH ON BALDWIN SET</title>
      <link>https://www.santafenewmexican.com/news/local_news/sheriffs-office-alec-baldwins-prop-firearm-kills-one-injures-another/article_9612afc6-32c5-11ec-9e2e-e3cc47b69ce5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.santafenewmexican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baldwin is one of the film's star actors and producers. He went to the sheriff's office willingly and provided a statement to investigators, sheriff's office spokesman Juan Ríos said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS LOADED</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/alec-baldwin-movie-fatal-shooting-director-crew-member-dead-rust-1234860500/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with more law enforcement information: The Santa Fe Sheriff’s Department confirmed Thursday night that Alec Baldwin “discharged” the prop gun that killed Rust cinematograp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTIGATION CONTINUES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-movies-santa-fe-alec-baldwin-25d83890a289bb9ae358f406cd3cbee9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) — Actor Alec Baldwin fired a prop gun on the set of a Western and killed the cinematographer, officials said. The director of the movie was wounded, and authorities are investigating what happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINCLAIR Workers Say TV Channels in 'Pandemonium' After Ransomware Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dypg4w/sinclair-workers-say-tv-channels-are-in-pandemonium-after-ransomware-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinclair is still struggling to go back to normal operations. Channels can’t air ads, employees had no email access for days, and there’s a lot of confusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Live Round...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2021/10/alec-baldwin-fires-gun-kills-cinematographer-wounds-director-on-rust-set-1234673555/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident took place October 21 at the Bonanza Creek Ranch in Santa Fe County. It is under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who let the dogs out? Mystery disappearance grips Spain volcano isle...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211022-who-let-the-dogs-out-mystery-disappearance-grips-spain-volcano-isle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who let the dogs out? Mystery disappearance grips Spain volcano isle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel Warns of Efforts by China to Collect Genetic Data...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/22/u-s-warns-of-efforts-by-china-to-collect-genetic-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BETHESDA, Md. — Chinese firms are collecting genetic data from around the world, part of an effort by the Chinese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing vows no concessions on Taiwan after Biden comments...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-china-beijing-taiwan-f4fdeb6e15097d55f5d4c06b5f8c9c29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China on Friday said there is “no room” for compromise or concessions over the issue of Taiwan, following a comment by U.S. President Joe Biden that the U.S. is committed to defending the island if it is attacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says USA would defend Taiwan against invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/biden-says-us-would-defend-taiwan-against-china-invasion/ar-AAPOP2E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States will defend Taiwan if China attacks it, President Joe Biden said, prompting a warning from Beijing on Friday that its determination to take back the democratic island should not be underestimated. But he warned: "I just want to make China understand that we are not going to step back."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Billionaires Snipe at Each Other on Socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/jack-dorsey-elon-musk-slam-mark-zuckerberg-facebook-google-on-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech Billionaires Snipe at Each Other on Social Media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High School Students Blame Rash Of Brawls On Pandemic Isolation: 'We Didn't Get Chance To Bond'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/10/21/lawrence-high-school-fight-jacqueline-sabino-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Lawrence mother has been ordered to stay away from Lawrence High School after her arrest on assault and disorderly conduct charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Why was I handed hot gun?'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10118665/Rust-movie-set-starring-Alec-Baldwin-LOCKED-New-Mexico.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin accidentally shot and killed cinematographer Halyna Hutchins and wounded writer-director Joel Souza on the set of the upcoming Western movie Rust, after a prop firearm discharged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Rich Form Exclusive Club R360 for Billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-10-22/super-rich-form-exclusive-club-r360-for-billionaires-high-net-worth-individuals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California teacher placed on leave after video shows her imitating Native American dance, wearing headdress...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/577967-california-teacher-placed-on-leave-after-video-shows-her-imitating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southern California high school teacher has been placed on leave after a viral video posted Wednesday showed her wearing a fake Native American headdress while chanting and dancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Award-winning teenage rapper shot to death in Sweden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-arts-and-entertainment-shootings-stockholm-sweden-2719af797baa19d583e66be368f96b72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM (AP) — An award-winning 19-year-old Swedish rapper was shot to death in southern Stockholm in an incident that media reports on Friday said was likely to be gang-related. The case has shocked the Swedish entertainment world and highlighted what officials said was the urgent need to deal with growing criminal gang activity in the Nordic country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel warns China could dominate advanced technologies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-technology-business-china-52acbd35f77084771ddeabbb2bfd0789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. officials are issuing new warnings about China’s ambitions in artificial intelligence and a range of advanced technologies that could eventually give Beijing a decisive military edge and possible dominance over health care and other essential sectors in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Jets Buzz Alaska Airspace as Tensions Spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/russia-alaska-jets-norad-warplanes-adiz-moscow-nato-1641500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident comes two days after Russia escorted U.S. military aircraft over the Black Sea, and amid a standoff between Moscow and the alliance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Unveils Stricter Trading Rules Amid Fallout From Ethics Scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/21/fed-to-ban-policymakers-from-owning-individual-stocks-restrict-trading-following-controversy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve announced Thursday a ban on officials owning individual stocks and limits on other activities as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dismay, Anger...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/halyna-hutchins-death-film-industry-reactions-1235095292/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film industry is shocked, dismayed and angry following the death of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins on Thursday. She was killed while filming “Rust” when one of the movie’s ac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin slams 'cancel culture' and trans rights; Teaching gender fluidity 'crime against humanity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Putin-slams-cancel-culture-and-trans-rights-16553959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin again attacked Western liberalism in a fiery address on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moneyman Behind Trump Media Company Runs Firm in Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/moneyman-behind-trump-media-company-233316506.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- From a WeWork office in Miami, an obscure financier by the name of Patrick Orlando has become an unlikely power behind what is, for a meme-stock minute, the ultimate MAGA stock: the nascent media company of former President Donald J. Trump.Most Read from BloombergThe Top Money Maker at Deutsche Bank Reaps Billions From SingaporeForget Palm Springs—Santa Fe Is the New Mecca for Modern ArchitectureWhy Americans and Britons Are Rushing to Buy Idyllic Homes in ItalyCities' Answer to S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet of the Apes? Ultra-ripped chimps with razor-sharp fangs...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3907951/video-sparks-planet-of-the-apes-scare/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TERRIFYING ultra-ripped chimps bearing razor-sharp fangs prove why Planet of the Apes could really happen. The chimpanzees – which suffer from the hair-loss condition alopecia – brutall…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Fleets Risk Collisions in Space, Former NASA Head Says...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/satellite-fleets-risk-collisions-space-165959559.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Thousands of communications satellites proposed by dozens of companies pose a risk of ruinous collisions in space, a former chief of the U.S. space agency said Thursday.Most Read from BloombergThe Top Money Maker at Deutsche Bank Reaps Billions From SingaporeForget Palm Springs—Santa Fe Is the New Mecca for Modern ArchitectureCities' Answer to Sprawl? Go Wild.Why Americans and Britons Are Rushing to Buy Idyllic Homes in ItalyGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Fre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Coercion and Black Boxes, Russia Installs Digital Iron Curtain...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/22/with-coercion-and-black-boxes-russia-installs-a-digital-iron-curtain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Coercion and Black Boxes, Russia Installs a Digital Iron Curtain ” class=”css-1bfqq7u ey68jwv2″&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Furor Over Student's Hijab Engulfs Liberal Town...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/22/online-furor-over-a-students-hijab-engulfs-a-liberal-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAPLEWOOD, N.J. — A 7-year-old girl came home from school earlier this month upset, impatient to tell her mother a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand Wants 90% Vax Rate. Street Gangs May Hold Key...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/22/new-zealand-wants-a-90-vaccination-rate-its-street-gangs-may-hold-the-key/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand — Rawiri Jansen, a Maori doctor, had an urgent message for the 150 people, mostly patch-wearing members</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How left and right stopped communicating...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211022-two-americas-how-the-us-left-and-right-stopped-communicating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Americas: How the US left and right stopped communicating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-govt movement rapidly expanding nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-canada-health-public-health-idaho-0d2015c826bb01a2cd04b31254c870c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — A far-right group launched by anti-government activist Ammon Bundy is rapidly expanding nationwide and making inroads into Canada, according to a new report from the Institute for Research and Education on Human Rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group says it will train Christians on 'hand-to-hand combat' at MO event...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/state/missouri/article255162407.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We’re a group of Christian men and women that go out and will stand against unrighteousness,” said a leader of the Salt and Light Brigade in Missouri. “This will be an intensive study about self defense.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVIDED STATES OF AMERICA:  Michigan abortion rate reaches  30-year high, boosted by visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/michigan-abortion-rate-reaches-nearly-30-year-high-boosted-by-visitors/article_356f25a6-fc5e-5042-809a-2baaf19085aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT — Michigan's abortion rate increased nearly 9% 2020 to to its highest level in almost three decades — an increase providers and other experts attributed to the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to campaign with McAuliffe in home stretch of Virginia governor's race... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-to-campaign-with-mcauliffe-in-home-stretch-of-virginia-governor-e2-80-99s-race/ar-AAPNSR2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McAuliffe put out the welcome mat out for a battered Biden in a way Youngkin won’t for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Tackling Supply-Chain Crisis With Few Tools, Clock Ticking...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/biden-tackles-supply-chain-crisis-with-few-tools-clock-ticking/ar-AAPMxZa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. ports are full of goods, U.S. yards and warehouses are full of goods, hardly anyone wants to drive a truck to pick up and deliver those goods and those who do sit waiting in lines, often unpaid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:   'Shrooms! Shamans! Kosher LSD! Why LA Is Tripping Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/shrooms-shamans-kosher-lsd-why-los-angeles-is-suddenly-tripping-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crewmember Dies After Prop Gun Misfire On Set Of Alec Baldwin Film... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/female-crewmember-dies-on-new-mexico-set-of-alec-baldwin-film-rust-1234860416/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 4:58 PM: The Santa Fe County Sheriff’s Office has confirmed that a female crewmember, 42, has died from injuries resulting from a prop gun misfire on the Bonanza Creek Ranch set of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iconic TARGET Store in San Fran to Close Amid Shoplifting Wave...</title>
      <link>https://californiaglobe.com/local/san-francisco/exclusive-iconic-target-store-in-mission-district-to-close-amid-a-shoplifting-tidal-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californiaglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week, after Walgreens announced that five additional outlets in San Francisco would be closing on top of the 17 that already have been shuttered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS HITS $7.59 IN CA TOWN</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/highest-gas-prices-in-the-country-gorda-ca-california-price-of/11149187/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lone gas station in a coastal California town is charging $7.59 for regular unleaded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military conducts 'successful' test of hypersonic missile technology...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211021-us-conducts-successful-test-of-hypersonic-missile-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US conducts 'successful' test of hypersonic missile technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne finally reopens...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211021212924-frlaj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (PIX, TV):Melbourne reopens as world's most locked-down city eases pandemic restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Threats Creating Mass Exodus of Election Officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkpez7/election-officials-receiving-death-threats-causing-mass-exodus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Your husband should tell the truth, or your three kids … will be fatally shot.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>106-Year-Old Credits Long Life To Daily YUENGLING...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/10/21/106-year-old-berks-county-woman-who-credits-a-yuengling-a-day-for-longevity-gets-gift-from-brewery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dilullo credits a Yuengling Lager a day with her longevity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Prosecutors Join Gaetz Case...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/21/justice-dept-adds-two-top-prosecutors-to-matt-gaetz-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department has added two top prosecutors from Washington to the child sex trafficking investigation of Representative Matt Gaetz,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos inside Rikers Island expose hellish, deadly conditions...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/21/photos-inside-rikers-island-expose-hellish-deadly-conditions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Post obtained exclusive photos showing the intake cells at the Otis Bantum Correctional Center on Rikers Island, showing dozens of men crammed together for days in temporary holding cells amid …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heated behind closed doors with Bernie...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/manchin-sanders-reconciliation-fight-789c8441-fa49-404f-9d36-4adaa8e1d908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Joe said, 'I'm comfortable with nothing,'" Sen. Jon Tester tells Axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why no tusks? Poaching tips scales of elephant evolution...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-africa-environment-and-nature-elephants-mozambique-048e181c6dadc591b1f43c6e963f0f0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A hefty set of tusks is usually an advantage for elephants, allowing them to dig for water, strip bark for food and joust with other elephants. But during episodes of intense ivory poaching, those big incisors become a liability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Preparing for 'Space Superhighway,' Complete with Pit Stops...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2021/10/military-preparing-space-superhighway-complete-pit-stops/186260/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those hubs would do more than refuel spaceships; they are seen as key to staying ahead of China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major CA quake would knock out cell service, communications, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/major-california-earthquake-knock-cell-150701362.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major earthquake in California is likely to knock out many communications services, including cellphones, for days or weeks, a USGS study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel poised to welcome foreign tourists back...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-travel-jerusalem-israel-7e821c2a2a41af3c6c463fee51e5b1b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli leaders on Thursday recommended reopening the country to fully vaccinated tourists beginning on Nov. 1, a year and a half after closing its borders to most foreign visitors due to the global coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana to Chicago cops: No vaccine, no problem!</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article255152457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Hey Chicago police officers, we’re hiring!” an Indiana State Police spokesman said. “No vaccine mandate … lower taxes, great schools, welcoming communities.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX cutting ties with MYPILLOW guy...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/10/21/rats-ship-even-far-right-channel-newsmax-is-cutting-ties-with-mike-lindell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindell claims right-wing news channel sees his Frank Speech as "too much competition." But that might not be it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal backlash against Sinema grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/21/politics/kyrsten-sinema-primary-challenge/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kyrsten Sinema is at the zenith of her influence in Washington, with the ability to dramatically reshape -- or derail -- President Joe Biden's domestic agenda simply by threatening to point her thumb down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANCHIN ADMITS MULLING LEAVING DEMS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211021173931-3z8a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CONGRESS/MANCHIN (PIX):U.S. Senator Manchin acknowledges having weighed leaving Democratic Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sleeper cell' exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/uk/exposed-sleeper-cell-of-evangelical-christians-posing-as-orthodox-rabbis-1.521679</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbis accused of secretly being Evangelical Christians...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/us-orthodox-rabbis-accused-of-secretly-being-evangelical-christians-report-682759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two rabbis reportedly performed marriages and divorces, wrote Torah scrolls and even officiated Orthodox conversions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle accused of using British royal title to meddle in US politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10115613/Meghan-accused-using-royal-title-meddle-politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royals experts have also questioned whether Americans will be impressed 'by her account of how she had to struggle' on $4.99 salads when her father Thomas put her through private school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'TRUTH' Social Defaced Within Hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pranksters-have-already-defaced-trump-e2-80-99s-new-social-media-network/ar-AAPNovh?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The site, Truth Social, said it reserves the right to ban users and safeguard itself from lawsuits with Section 230 protections -- the same measures Trump has complained about during his long and bitter battle with Big Tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOLFF:  HE LONGS TO BE A MARTYR...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michael-wolff-says-steve-bannon-would-be-in-heaven-if-he-got-sentenced-to-a-year-in-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Wolff put forth the idea that Steve Bannon wants the January 6th Committee to prosecute him because of the attention it would bring upon himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Cohen Grills Meghan McCain Over Her 'Tell-All' Book...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/andy-cohen-confronts-meghan-mccain-over-her-book-on-a-1-to-10-scale-how-hypocritical-is-it-that-you-wrote-a-tell-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andy Cohen confronted Meghan McCain over her upcoming book, asking her if it's "hypocritical" considering she's often voiced her hatred for tell-alls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Launches Weather Service...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/fox-weather-fox-news-streaming-wars-climate-change-1235094167/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a new wind blowing through the building that houses Fox News Channel. Amy Freeze and Craig Herrera spent a recent weekday afternoon in a TV studio at the company’s New York headquarters reh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP Taps Chainlink to Provide Untamperable News Data...</title>
      <link>https://decrypt.co/83867/associated-press-ap-chainlink-news-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;decrypt.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press has partnered with Chainlink to provide verifiable news data in the age of misinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas school district bans boys from wearing long hair; Students sue...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-texas-school-district-bans-boys-from-wearing-long-hair-now-some-students-are-suing/ar-AAPN9n4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the help of the American Civil Liberties Union of Texas, seven students are suing their school district to do away with a boys-only ban on long hair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condoleezza Rice said she cried on Jan. 6, but it's time to 'move on'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/condoleezza-rice-said-she-cried-on-jan-6-but-it-s-time-to-move-on/ar-AAPMQhC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On “The View” on Wednesday, Condoleezza Rice said the insurrection “was wrong,” but she added it was time for lawmakers to focus on issues impacting the American people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Deployed?</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/10/21/national-guard-could-be-deployed-to-help-with-la-port-cargo-backlog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of cargo ships have been anchored offshore from the ports of L.A. and Long Beach for weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Tackling Supply-Chain Crisis With Few Tools, Clock Ticking...</title>
      <link>https://ajot.com/news/biden-tackles-supply-chain-crisis-with-few-tools-clock-ticking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ajot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
