<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Americans in voluntary quarantine to stop spread of coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/431674/coronavirus-voluntary-quarantine-thousands-california-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of travelers are doing a voluntary self-quarantine after returning to the US from coronavirus-ridden China, officials say. These US citizens are being asked to stay home for two weeks for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pressure on Barr...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/20/us/politics/trump-attacks-justice-system.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In lashing out at the prosecution of his adviser Roger Stone, the president once again disregarded the attorney general’s pleas to stop publicly commenting on individual cases involving his friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely voters say they'll vote in 2020. Who will that benefit?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/unlikely-voters-say-theyll-vote-in-2020-who-will-that-benefit/ar-BB10cGIz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT PAGE ONE FRIDAY:  Russia Backs Trump's Re-election, and He Fears Dems Will Exploit Its Support... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/russia-backs-trump-e2-80-99s-reelection-and-he-fears-democrats-will-exploit-its-support/ar-BB10dBOd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Drags Paul Ryan Into His War on FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-fumes-at-fox-news-over-analysis-by-hater-on-cavuto-blames-fox-board-member-paul-ryan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is stewing over a Fox News segment in which a guest analyst offered a harsh critique of his 2016 debate performances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic locust swarm stops traffic as sky turns black...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/apocalyptic-locust-swarm-stops-traffic-21543509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swarm of locusts was filmed bringing cars to a standstill in Bahrain. The plague of bugs has been destroying crops across Africa and the Middle East and since crossed the border in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joaquin Phoenix Rescues Cow And Her Calf From L.A. Slaughterhouse...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/watch-joaquin-phoenix-rescue-a-cow-and-her-calf-from-l-a-slaughterhouse-1202864856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than 48 hours after Joaquin Phoenix hoisted the first Oscar of his career the Joker star was cradling a newborn calf that he rescued from a Los Angles slaughterhouse. A just-released video fro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Jury Wants To Review Testimony From Annabella Sciorra; Day 3 Of Deliberations... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-annabella-sciorra-miriam-haley-jury-deliberations-1202864285/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, end of day: The jury in the Harvey Weinstein sexual misconduct trial completed its third day of deliberations today without a verdict – but with a last-minute request to review even …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG VOWS TO KEEP FIGHTING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f487bca6e473646b7a7d69b2a97685f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — His aura suddenly shattered, a defiant Michael Bloomberg sent a pointed message Thursday to a political world grappling with his underwhelming presidential debate debut: He's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected Americans flown home against CDC's advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/coronavirus-infected-americans-flown-home-against-cdcs-advice/ar-BB10ddna</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi Comes Out Swinging...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections/Benjamin-Netanyahu-to-Post-Democratic-president-cant-stop-Trump-plan-618271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What I do in an hour, my opponents can’t do in a year," the prime minister said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN warns of stock market correction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/20/investing/goldman-sachs-stocks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks keep reaching record highs. Goldman Sachs is worried that leaves investors vulnerable to surprises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: TITANS, RAIDERS Favorites To Land Tom Brady...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/02/20/tom-brady-update-tennessee-titans-favorite-right-now-patriots-ranked-third/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're all just guessing. The latest educated guesses involve the Titans as the top dog to land Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find novel antibiotic to kill superbugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/02/20/machine-learning-finds-novel-antibiotic-able-to-kill-superbugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When tested in mice, the molecule treated the gastrointestinal bug clostridium difficile, a common killer of hospitalized patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds charge man for threatening whistleblower attorney...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/20/man-charged-threatening-whistleblower-attorney-116379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man allegedly emailed the attorney in November, calling him a “traitor” who “must die a miserable death.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President hints pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-tweeting-a-tucker-carlson-segment-hints-of-possible-pardon-for-roger-stone/ar-BB10bYpw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI stocks up on hand sanitizer, face masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/20/fbi-orders-40000-in-hand-sanitizer-and-face-masks-in-case-of-a-coronavirus-pandemic-in-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration last month declared the virus a public health emergency, but the virus has not yet met world health officials' designation of a global pandemic that spreads widely throughout the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC issues record $1 billion in traffic, parking tickets...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/features/7-on-your-side/dc-issues-a-record-1-billion-in-traffic-and-parking-tickets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (WJLA/ABC7) &amp;ndash; D. C. has long been considered one of the most onerous places in the country for traffic fines, seeing a steady climb year to year in tickets issued and revenue generated. But recently the District broke into stunning new territory, issuing more than $1 billion in tickets in just three years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuees greeted with air kisses...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/20/tone-deaf-princess-cruises-president-greets-coronavirus-ship-evacuees-with-air-kisses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shows Jan Swartz forming a heart over her head as she faced the Diamond Princess ship in Yokohama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROHRABACHER: I DID OFFER ASSANGE PARDON...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rohrabacher-confirms-he-offered-trump-pardon-to-assange-for-proof-russia-didnt-hack-dnc-email-131438007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former congressman Dana Rohrabacher confirmed to Yahoo News he told Julian Assange President Trump would pardon him if he turned over information proving Russians weren't the source of Democratic emails published by WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli criminal investigation into Netanyahu challenger's failed company jolts election...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-february-20-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue and White chief expresses confidence in law enforcement, accuses Likud of pushing for investigation into Fifth Dimension; Netanyahu: 'The public must know the truth'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER testing new ways to fight 'misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/twitter-testing-new-ways-fight-misinformation-including-community-based-points-n1139931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leaked demo features bright red and orange badges for tweets that have been deemed “harmfully misleading."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport worker with no pilot license takes plane for spin near DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/airport-worker-no-pilot-license-takes-plane-spin-near-d-n1139956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan Guy Parker allegedly "bounced" the landing and spun out when he touched down at the end of one harrowing flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Omar did marry brother, reveals Somali community leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8013283/Ilhan-Omar-DID-marry-brother-reveals-Somali-community-leader.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Congresswoman Ilhan Omar told friends years ago that the man who went on to become her second husband was in fact her brother, DailyMail.com can confirm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro pushes political incorrectness to the limit...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-pushes-political-incorrectness-limit-182454696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro regularly offends opponents with political incorrectness and far-right diatribes, but he is taking heavier fire than usual for suggesting a respected journalist tried to get dirt on him with offers of sex. The man dubbed the "Tropical Trump" has racked up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33.5 MILLION VIEWERS!</title>
      <link>http://press.nbcnews.com/2020/02/20/nbc-news-and-msnbc-break-ratings-record-again-with-the-most-watched-democratic-debate-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;press.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will have to turn over tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/429826/roger-stone-jail-time-trump-pardon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROGER Stone was sentenced to three years and four months in prison today for lying to Congress – but Trump has hinted at a pardon. The longtime Trump ally was branded an “insecure person who …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fiscal hawks' now endangered as US shrugs at debt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fiscal-hawks-now-endangered-us-shrugs-debt-015153979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At their national convention in 2012, Republicans mounted a clock counting the growing US national debt on the wall, a warning of the looming financial catastrophe they said imperiled Americans. Eight years later, the clock has stopped under Republican President Donald Trump, and the "fiscal hawks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secession fever spikes in five states as conservatives seek to escape blue rule... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/19/secession-fever-spikes-conservatives-seek-escape-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separation fever is sweeping the nation as quixotic but tenacious bands of frustrated rural dwellers, suburbanites and conservatives seek to break free from states with legislatures increasingly controlled by liberal big cities and metropolitan strongholds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Ring Surveillance Controversy Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cybersecurity/2020/02/house-subcommittee-knocking-amazons-door-over-ring-data/163224/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of a House Oversight panel wants a briefing with Amazon officials about the consumer security tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian couple facing death penalty in Saudi Arabia declare love for each other live on TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/lesbian-couple-saudi-arabia-facing-21536871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lesbian couple 'Fad' and 'Nanz', from Saudi Arabia, feared being killed in their home country, but have now found happiness in London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Iran regime plan to destroy tomb of Esther and Mordechai?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Does-Irans-regime-plan-to-destroy-the-tomb-of-Esther-and-Mordechai-618155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US religious group blasts Iran for threats to Esther and Mordechai tomb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG RATINGS</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/democratic-debate-criminal-minds-tv-ratings-wednesday-feb-19-2020-1280119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary figures for the ninth face-off, and the first featuring Mike Bloomberg, are ahead of NBC's last debate broadcast in June 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human brain seized at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickondetroit.com/news/local/2020/02/19/cbp-human-brain-inside-jar-seized-at-blue-water-bridge-in-port-huron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickondetroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection discovered something very unusual during a routine truck inspection last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE NEXT WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/south-carolina-democratic-debate-moderators-cbs-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"CBS Evening News" anchor Norah O'Donnell and "CBS This Morning" co-host Gayle King will moderate the debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone declines to address court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f25972591780e9750d6fc17bcff506b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roger Stone, a staunch ally of President Donald Trump, faces sentencing Thursday on his convictions for witness tampering and lying to Congress. The action in federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USS Nimitz captain reveals his pilots have to watch out for UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8013327/USS-Nimitz-captain-says-crew-obligation-ensure-airspace-clear-UFOs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Captain Max Clark, commanding officer of the USS Nimitz, tells DailyMail.com it is important his ship and everybody on it is kept safe from UFOs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Trump Job Approval Steady at 49%...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/286280/trump-job-approval-steady.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval rating is holding steady at 49%. U.S. satisfaction is at a 15-year high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey cancels tour on doctor's orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thefader.com/2020/02/20/lana-del-rey-cancels-european-tour-illness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thefader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lana Del Rey has cancelled her European and U.K. tour dates due to illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Mardi Gras Parade Float Runs Over and Kills Woman in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/crime_police/article_8bcc8086-538e-11ea-8960-3305004323e0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was run over by a Krewe of Nyx parade float and killed in New Orleans on Wednesday night, devastating paradegoers and krewe members on what is typically a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Pop Smoke murder 'was targeted hit'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8024249/Pop-Smokes-murder-targeted-hit-not-robbery-gone-wrong.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop Smoke was shot dead at a Hollywood Hills home early Wednesday morning in what was initially thought to be a botched robbery but is now reportedly being treated as a gang-related hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devil worship...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2020/02/20/german-gunman-shared-far-right-conspiracy-theories-killing-nine-people-12272458/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He killed nine people when he opened fire at two shisha bars in Hanau, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two former cruise ship passengers die in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4030470d394aec0c982acb55744b1648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Two elderly passengers taken off the quarantined cruise ship Diamond Princess because they were infected with the new virus have died, Japan's Health Ministry said Thursday, becoming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Devastating': Alcoholic liver disease soars among younger people...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/02/20/alcoholic-liver-disease-rates-soar-among-millennials/4802917002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors are worried over a surge in alcohol-related liver diseases such as hepatitis and cirrhosis in people in their 30s and 40s, particularly women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague of locusts threatens economies as UN sounds alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/20/plague-of-locusts-threatens-east-african-economies-as-un-sounds-alarm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst desert locust infestation in 70 years is ravaging East Africa, potentially endangering economies in a region heavily dependent on agriculture for food security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals across USA prepare for pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/19/hospitals-across-the-us-prepare-for-coronavirus-outbreak-to-become-global-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COVID-19 outbreak across the U.S. could overwhelm emergency rooms and cause shortages of face masks and other crucial medical supplies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea on high alert as cases soar at 'cult' church...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/20/south-korean-city-daegu-lockdown-coronavirus-outbreak-cases-soar-at-church-cult-cluster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 61-year-old woman is believed to have infected dozens of worshippers at the Shincheonji Church of Jesus in Daegu, taking the national total to 82</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kills mother, self at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/19/shooting-germany-hanau-dead-several-people-shisha-near-frankfurt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say shooting suspect killed nine people at two shisha bars then killed his mother and himself at home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fecal Transmission May Be Behind Rapid Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/fecal-transmission-may-be-behind-coronavirus-s-rapid-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fecal Transmission May Be Behind Coronavirusâ€™s Rapid Spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In USA, leftist local prosecutors make inroads...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-leftist-local-prosecutors-inroads-031346649.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the national level, President Donald Trump is appointing judges by the dozens to positions on US federal courts, ensuring a conservative tilt for a generation. Parisa Dehghani-Tafti -- who is now the top prosecutor in northern Virginia's Arlington county in the Washington suburbs -- knows she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In America's Richest Town, $500k a Year Now Below Average...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-richest-town-500k-now-100000759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- You could easily drive through this leafy Silicon Valley suburb without realizing you were in America’s richest neighborhood. From the road, it’s all high brick walls and opaque gates.It takes Google Maps to get a glimpse of what lies behind. Satellite images of Atherton, California –-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nazi terrorist' massacres 9 in hookah bars near Frankfurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11000481/terrorist-drive-by-shooting-in-germany-hanau/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NINE people were shot dead when a far-right terrorist opened fire on two shisha bars in the German town of Hanau, near Frankfurt, overnight. Cops this morning confirmed the suspect’s body …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China sends 100,000 ducks to border to fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-sends-army-100000-ducks-21531853</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plague of locusts that has devastated east Africa reached the coronavirus-stricken country earlier this week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone set to be sentenced... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/20/donald-trump-friend-roger-stone-set-to-be-sentenced-for-lying-to-congress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has criticized the case against Republican operative Roger Stone, who lied to Congress about his contacts with Trump's campaign related to WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brokered convention 'nightmare' likelier...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/483751-former-skeptics-now-warning-of-brokered-convention-nightmare-for-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats who were initially skeptical of the prospects for a brokered convention now see it as a likelier scenario with eight candidates still b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes dogs so special? Science says love...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2020-02-dogs-special-science.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea that animals can experience love was once anathema to the psychologists who studied them, seen as a case of putting sentimentality before scientific rigor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Administration Sees No Threat to Economy From Monopolies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/20/trump-administration-sees-no-threat-to-economy-from-monopolies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Trump and his economic team see “no need to hastily rewrite the federal government’s antitrust rules,” drawing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON: Testimony wouldn't have changed impeachment outcome...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c269df302e881e972137be6c128c88a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Former national security adviser John Bolton on Wednesday denounced the House's impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump as ”grossly partisan” and said his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BEST EVER'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/19/nevada-democratic-debate-was-the-greatest-debate-in-human-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget Lincoln and Douglas. Forget Nixon and Kennedy. Hell, forget the Athenians and the Melians back during the Peloponnesian War. Last night’s Democratic primary slagfest in Nevada was the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire on Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2020-02-19/trumps-pick-of-richard-grenell-as-dni-draws-fire-from-a-top-senate-democrat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**DRUDGE POLL** WHO WON DEM DEBATE IN VEGAS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10508591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Info of 10 MILLION MGM guests including Justin Bieber and TWITTER CEO leaked online!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/427375/mgm-resorts-data-breach-10-million-justin-bieber/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE than 10.6 million users who stayed at MGM Resorts hotels have had their personal details published on a hacking forum, according to a report. Within the leaked files was information belonging …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests Barr with more tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-fires-off-more-tweets-about-Justice-15067614.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump continued to test his relationship with Attorney General William Barr on Wednesday by amplifying conservative allies demanding he "clean house" at the Justice Department and target those involved in the Russia investigation that once threatened his presidency.  The grievances shared by Trump in a flurry of morning tweets included claims of a "seditious conspiracy" against him, and attacks on a "criminal gang" at the FBI and Justice Department.  A day after it was revealed that Barr told people close to Trump he had considered quitting, the president and his attorney general seemed to reach a detente of sorts. Officials inside the Justice Department said they were watching the situation closely, mindful that a new string of tweets or comments could quickly upend the situation, but there were no indications that Barr would leave imminently. The attorney general did not mention the controversy when he spoke during an event at FBI headquarters Wednesday.  The fragile equilibrium may be tested again Thursday, when Trump's longtime friend Roger Stone is scheduled to be sentenced for lying to Congress and obstruction. Trump's tweets about Stone last week prompted Barr to speak out publicly, saying the president's declarations "make it impossible for me to do my job."  If Trump continues to tweet, and Barr continues to stay in his job, "I think he is in danger of getting into 'Boy Who Cried Wolf' territory," said Matthew Miller, a former Justice Department spokesman in the Obama administration. "He's already said the president's commenting made his job impossible, and the president kept commenting, and then he apparently told people that he was considering resigning if the president didn't stop. So if the president doesn't stop now and he doesn't quit, he looks feckless and insincere."  In the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman suspected of crossing border illegally gives birth at Border Patrol office...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2020-02-19/guatemalan-woman-gives-birth-at-border-patrol-office-after-being-arrested-crossing-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Guatemalan woman and her baby girl were taken to a hospital after she gave birth in a Chula Vista station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-blog/watch-live-las-vegas-democratic-presidential-debate-n1137966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor Mike Bloomberg will take the stage for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 8 dead in gun attacks on hookah bars near Frankfurt... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8022475/Police-report-people-shot-death-German-city.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people have been killed and another six injured in drive-by shootings outside two shisha bars in the German city of Hanau. A dark coloured vehicle was seen fleeing the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10508591/results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**DRUDGE POLL** WHO WON DEM DEBATE IN VEGAS...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com**DRUDGE POLL** WHO WON DEM DEBATE IN VEGAS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com**DRUDGE POLL** WHO WON DEM DEBATE IN VEGAS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged GRINDR cannibal found unresponsive after not eating, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/02/18/mark-latunski-accused-grindr-cannibal-hospitalized-kevin-bacon/4802504002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latunski is accused of killing Kevin Bacon who was found dead, naked and hanging by his ankles in Latunskiâ€™s basement on Dec. 28.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grenell Head of Intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/19/politics/trump-grennell-acting-dni/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is expected to name US Ambassador to Germany Richard Grenell as the next acting director of national intelligence, according to two sources familiar with the decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration backs ORACLE in Supreme Court battle against GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/483750-trump-administration-backs-oracle-in-supreme-court-battle-against-google</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is siding with software company Oracle over Google in the pivotal Supreme Court battle that has pitted the U.S. government against some of the top titans of the tech industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 is not the new 70, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eae1a9a5088313b2868188d0e91b801c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People are more likely to buy things when prices end in 99 cents rather than rounded up to the next dollar, or cars with mileage under 1,000 instead of past that mark. Now researchers say...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Catholic diocese seeks bankruptcy after abuse deals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d12fc153df9ed07d774e0b0f4d947f78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — The Roman Catholic Diocese of Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, filed for bankruptcy Wednesday, six months after disclosing it had paid millions of dollars to people sexually abused...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorneys take aim at Boy Scouts 'dark history'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3604ce6f0a1b95fd81fcb25fa78eb9db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Like millions of other Americans in the 1950s and '60s, Duane Ruth-Heffelbower spent his formative years learning to tie knots, build campfires and pitch tents with the Boy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE BALKS AT MEDICAL RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/019b6618cb74063df43c40d95765c2fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Bernie Sanders says he doesn't plan to divulge additional information about his health, months after suffering a heart attack on the campaign trail and subsequently pledging to...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
