<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Aggressive Deer Attacks Dozen Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/07/13/aggressive-deer-targeting-dogs-in-georgia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Peachtree City, GA some aggressive deer have been targeting local pets, injuring at least a dozen and forcing one dog to be euthanized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle children going extinct...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/07/13/middle-children-going-extinct-because-millennial-family-planning/782220002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of National Middle Child Day (it’s Aug. 12, if you forgot), women's lifestyle magazine The Cut points out that middle children could go extinct because of Millennial family planning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel chief warns of cyber threats to US infrastructure...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/u-intel-chief-warns-cyber-threats-u-infrastructure-175730150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Jonathan Landay WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. intelligence chief warned on Friday that the threat was growing for a devastating cyber assault on critical U.S. infrastructure, saying the "warning lights are blinking red again" nearly two decades after the Sept. 11, 2001, attacks. Russia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS COLLECT RECORD TAXES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/feds-collect-record-individual-income-taxes-through-june-still-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Paul Ryan and Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (Screen Capture)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON on track to take 50% of US e-commerce!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/amazon-to-take-almost-50-percent-of-us-e-commerce-market-by-years-end.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company is expected to take almost 50 percent of the U.S. e-commerce market by year's end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson Exits Trans Movie Amid Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/scarlett-johansson-exit-rub-and-tug-trans-backlash-1202872981/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scarlett Johansson has exited the drama film “Rub and Tug” a little more than a week after her casting sparked backlash amid trans groups and activists, a source with knowledge of the s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Forbids Staff From Expensing Meals With Meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-13/wework-tells-employees-meat-is-permanently-off-the-company-menu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Co-working giant WeWork Cos. thinks it can save the environment quicker than Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator sets up phony health news website...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/07/13/bob-hugin-bob-menendez-sets-up-a-fake-health-news-website/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A site run by the reelection campaign for Sen. Bob Menendez does plenty to leave the impression it is a site run by a news organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dispute over booting truck lands parking enforcer in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/local/crime/article214748115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perry police arrested parking enforcer Mason Parker, 23, who allegedly assaulted Arthur Emons who was having his booted truck towed from Walmart Supercenter parking lot on St. Patricks Drive in Perry, Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Papa John name removed from stadium, college...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-u-louisville-stadium-removes-papa-johns-name-171927911--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Louisville is removing the Papa John's name from its football stadium. The school is taking action after the pizza chain's founder, John Schnatter, reportedly complained that Kentucky Fried Chicken's Colonel Sanders never faced a backlash for using a racial slur. University</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her legs tingled. Tapeworm in her spine...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/07/13/tapeworm-parasite-womans-spine-causes-tingling-sensation/781931002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tapeworm was discovered as the source of a French woman's inability to walk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheese prices crumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cheese-prices-crumble-but-the-global-trade-dispute-could-halt-their-drop-2018-07-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record U.S. supplies of cheese have contributed to a drop in prices this year, but prices may find hope of a turnaround in a prolonged global trade dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  France on Brink of World Cup Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/france-on-the-brink-of-a-world-cup-win-have-the-bleus-1531498212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans, while ecstatic as their team prepares to face off with Croatia in Sunday’s final, are also disappointed by the team’s non-French, workmanlike approach; ‘We had to be pragmatic’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Warning Signs: Dems Register 12 Million More Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/2018-democrats-lead-gop-by-12-million-registered-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats hold a massive voter lead in states that require party registration, a gap of 12 million that could be key to whether the party takes control of the House and Senate in the fall midterm congressional elections, according to a new analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDICTMENT:  U.S. v. Viktor Borisovich Netyksho, et al...</title>
      <link>https://www.justice.gov/file/1080281/download</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.justice.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She killed herself on FACEBOOK; Took family days to get photo taken down...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/she-killed-herself-on-facebookand-it-took-her-family-days-to-get-the-photo-taken-down-2018-07-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pamela Elarabi posted a photo of herself on the social networking site last month moments before she took her own life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein speaks out...</title>
      <link>https://usa.spectator.co.uk/2018/07/harvey-weinstein-i-offered-acting-jobs-in-exchange-for-sex-but-so-does-everyone-they-still-do/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;usa.spectator.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He used to ring me via his assistants and make me wait on hold. It was normal; he was, after all, the biggest Hollywood tycoon of them all. This time he called me directly, there was no ‘Harvey…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders Blasts DISNEY Iger Over $400 Million Pay...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/bernie-sanders-attacks-disney-ceo-bob-igers-400-million-dollar-pay-package-1202426145/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders renewed his long-running attack on the Walt Disney Company and the pay disparity between the executive suite and those who work at its flagship theme park, today taking …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands hit streets of London in Trump protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tens-thousands-gather-london-anti-trump-protests-001747259.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of protesters demonstrated in London on Friday against US President Donald Trump, whose four-day visit to Britain has been marred by his extraordinary attack on Prime Minister Theresa May's Brexit strategy. "#DumpTrump", "This is the carnival of resistance"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Rashes Plaguing Northern CA Community... </title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/did-nearby-fires-cause-mystery-rashes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With grass fires popping up in that area over the last few weeks many wondered if poison oak could be a cause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon presses Trump, Kim for breakthrough in nuke talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/moon-presses-trump-kim-breakthrough-nuclear-talks-072055425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — South Korean President Moon Jae-in on Friday urged President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un to try harder to achieve a breakthrough in their nuclear negotiations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jet plunges 25,000ft after pilot vaping in cockpit...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-5950691/Air-China-jet-plunged-25-000ft-pilot-vaping-cockpit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drama was triggered when the Air China pilot sought to turn off a system to prevent his smoke spreading but switched off air-con instead, leading to cabin oxygen levels dropping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach Man Vowed To Burn Down Condo Building To 'Kill All The Jews'...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/07/13/man-plotted-to-burn-down-condo-kill-all-jews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Miami Beach man upset with his Jewish neighbors after he was evicted from his condo reportedly vowed to burn down the building with "all the f***ing Jews."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Force Will Guard America From Above, NASA Chief Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/2018/07/12/trump-s-space-force-will-guard-u-s-from-above-nasa-chief-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA’s administrator is a strong defender of President Donald Trump’s proposals for space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Ambani Topples Jack Ma as Asia's Richest Person...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/13/tycoon-ambani-set-to-topple-jack-ma-as-asia-s-richest-person</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambani is poised to overtake Jack Ma to become Asia’s richest person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY WATER WARNING DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Boil-Water-Advisory-in-Effect-for-Major-Portion-of-DC-488088441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DC Water is advising thousands of residents of Northwest and Northeast D.C. to boil their tap water before drinking it or cooking with it because of a problem that made it possible for contaminants to enter the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade deficit with China keeps growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/2018/07/13/china-s-exports-hold-up-though-imports-slow-more-than-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The yuan’s decline in June was the worst in any month since 1994, dropping more than 3 percent against the dollar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS Bans Plastic Straws, Winds Up Using More Plastic...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2018/07/12/starbucks-straw-ban-will-see-the-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Reason investigation reveals that the coffee giant's new cold drink lids use more plastic than the old straw/lid combo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK pound falls, UK politicians reel after Trump broadside...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c6caedb5d97a4a8a93513444c555671d/UK-pound-falls,-UK-politicians-reel-after-Trump-broadside</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The British pound fell and U.K. politicians reeled Friday from the tornado-blast of U.S. President Donald Trump, who humiliated Prime Minister Theresa May, dashed ho</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS INTERVIEW 'FAKE'</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/13/trumps-got-the-tapes-says-sun-interview-is-fake-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I didn't criticize the prime minister'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX taken to court in India over portrayal of former PM...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/netflix-taken-court-india-over-portrayal-former-pm-111429575--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Shilpa Jamkhandikar MUMBAI (Reuters) - An Indian politician has taken streaming giant Netflix to court, asking that it delete "offensive scenes" and derogatory remarks about former Prime Minister Rajiv Gandhi in its first Indian original series. The Delhi High Court adjourned the case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese hotel denies raising rates for Americans amid trade war...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/chinese-hotel-bumps-rates-americans-25-percent-amid-071329268--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hotel in the southern Chinese city of Shenzhen on Friday denied a report that it would charge U.S. guests an extra 25 percent amid an escalating trade war between Washington and Beijing. The Global Times, a hawkish tabloid published by the ruling Communist Party's People's Daily, said in a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First space tourist flights could come NEXT YEAR!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/first-space-tourist-flights-could-come-2019-064622743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two companies leading the pack in the pursuit of space tourism say they are just months away from their first out-of-this-world passenger flights -- though neither has set a firm date. Virgin Galactic, founded by British billionaire Richard Branson, and Blue Origin, by Amazon creator Jeff Bezos,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting 'fake news' with the law...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fighting-fake-news-law-042157977.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some countries are bringing in legislation to fight "fake news", a particular menace during election campaigning, but critics warn of the danger to freedom of expression and the media. Under the law social media platforms like Facebook and Twitter can be punished with fines of up to 50 million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The online battle for truth...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/online-battle-truth-doc-17h6381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'gatekeeper' role... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fake-news-media-industry-strikes-back-032610136.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The viral spread of hoaxes and misinformation ahead of the US election and Brexit referendum two years ago was a wake-up call for many established news media, who have gone on the offensive to shore up their credibility and help filter out fake news. Major media organizations, often in partnership with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KHAN: 'We think you're wrong'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/13/trump-is-wrong-london-mayor-sadiq-khan-says-the-uk-is-not-afraid-of.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump should understand the U.K. will always be prepared to challenge his views in a respectful way — regardless of whether his feelings get hurt, London Mayor Sadiq Khan told CNBC Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour Party rips: 'What did his mother teach him?'</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/international/396839-uks-labour-party-rips-trumps-behavior-what-did-his-mother-teach-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spokeswoman for the U.K.'s Labour Party slammed President Trump's "behavior" on Friday after he criticized British Prime Minister Theresa May's plan for leaving the European Union and attacked mass immigration as a source of terroris</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  JP MORGAN hits record profit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/jpm-earnings-q2-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JPMorgan beats estimates on higher than expected trading results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands hit streets of London in protest over Trump...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5949835/US-President-heads-talks-Theresa-tea-Queen-trip-Scotland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US President's relationship with the Prime Minister is on the rocks after he blasted her 'softer' exit from the EU saying it would kill off chances of a trade deal with America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK TRUMPED</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6766531/trump-may-brexit-us-deal-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump today accuses the PM of wrecking Brexit — and warns she may have killed off any chance of a vital US trade deal. The US President delivers his incendiary verdict on her negotiating str…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Smirking, Squirming Peter Strzok...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/video-clip-of-smirking-squiriming-peter-strzok-at-hearing-is-giving-people-the-creeps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands hit streets of London in protest over Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/huge-anti-trump-demos-attract-12910802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US President has already said he is not visiting the capital because he does not feel welcome, but this has not stopped campaigners rallying together in a huge show of force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern-Day 'Bonnie &amp; Clyde' Robbing People At Gunpoint -- For Their Shoes...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/07/11/cute-young-couple-robbing-shoes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They could be a modern-day Bonnie and Clyde, but instead of robbing banks, they’re stealing shoes in Fort Worth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Dems blast former Trump attorney for 'selling access' to White House...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/senate-democrats-blast-trump-attorney-selling-access-white/story?id=56556814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen’s relationship with the Swiss drug company Novartis was more extensive than the company previously disclosed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: 800-Pound Boulder Flies Off Moving Truck Onto Car, Killing Mother, Daughter...</title>
      <link>http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/07/12/arrest-made-after-boulder-falls-off-vehicle-kills-mother-daughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police is Rosemount say an arrest has been made after an 800-pound boulder dislodged from a commercial vehicle and struck another vehicle, killing a mother and daughter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth, 'the devil's drug,' is back and killing more people than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/meth-the-devil-drug-back-and-killing-more-people-than-ever/sjs9kSaof8vMkGFwEAVvUO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All of Georgia faces the worst meth epidemic in history, like much of America. It's a problem in Gwinnett, DeKalb, Cobb, Fulton, Chatham, Bibb, Dougherty, Richmond and, authorities say, everywhere else in Georgia. The problem is made worse because of Mexican cartels and politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citing health study, mayor wants to ban workplace necktie requirements for city employees...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-lancaster-necktie-ban-20180712-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lancaster's mayor has proposed outlawing dress codes by local employers that force workers to wear neckties on the job. The proposal by R. Rex Parris cites a German study that found neckties may lower blood flow to the brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Picassos went missing from the LA TIMES.  What happened to them?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/picassos-went-missing-from-the-los-angeles-times-what-happened/article_319aafeb-7942-5b00-a1a5-cda6d3130eaa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The downtown complex that has housed the Los Angeles Times for decades is filled with notable spaces: the pristine test kitchen, the bustling newsroom and the historic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump dishes up fresh dose of chaos aimed at May, Londoners...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/191883cbd468439499c495b0410ac3a2/Trump-dishes-up-fresh-dose-of-chaos-aimed-at-May,-Londoners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLENHEIM PALACE, England (AP) — Dishing up a fresh dose of chaos on his European tour, President Donald Trump left behind a contentious NATO gathering in Brussels and moved on to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash flood sends tourists to high ground near Grand Canyon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/11d3f78a517f43a3a5541288938b4e79/Flash-flood-sends-tourists-to-high-ground-near-Grand-Canyon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLAGSTAFF, Ariz. (AP) — Torrents of water rushed Thursday through an Arizona canyon famous for its towering blue-green waterfalls, sending tourists scrambling to benches, trees an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Prince Alwaleed pledges support for crown prince's reforms...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/saudi-prince-alwaleed-pledges-support-crown-princes-reforms-202059867--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabian billionaire Prince Alwaleed bin Talal, who was detained for three months in an anti-corruption campaign under Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, pledged support on Thursday for the young leader's program of sweeping reforms. It is the first publicly disclosed meeting between the two</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate milk may be better than sports drinks for exercise recovery...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/chocolate-milk-may-better-sports-drinks-exercise-recovery-210222009--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Lisa Rapaport (Reuters Health) - Athletes who drink chocolate milk during exercise or after a hard workout may recover just as quickly as they would with sports drinks, a research review suggests. What people eat and drink during intense exercise and afterward can impact how well their muscles recover</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sending top team to Mexico to woo next president...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-sending-top-team-mexico-woo-next-president-224428356.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is sending a team of top officials to meet Mexico's president-elect on Friday to show the importance he places on the countries' relationship, the US said, after months of deeply strained ties. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo will lead a high-level delegation for meetings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strip club charges dropped, lawyer slams 'setup'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/lawyer-porn-star-stormy-daniels-says-she-arrested-054601132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charges were dropped against adult film star Stormy Daniels on Thursday after an Ohio strip club arrest that her lawyer slammed as a "politically motivated" setup against the woman suing President Donald Trump. Police approached Daniels, who was topless and wearing a G-string, after she was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Always-On Listening Devices -- Soon EVERYWHERE... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/all-ears-always-on-listening-devices-could-soon-be-everywhere-1531411250 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiny microphones are moving us toward a world in which all gadgets can respond to a voice command. For those worried about privacy: meet a $200 trash can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three arrested in attempted breaches of White House, Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Three-men-arrested-in-unrelated-attempted-13070448.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Three men were arrested in the past week after authorities said they tried to breach security barriers at the White House or violated orders to stay away from the U.S. Capitol and other government buildings. The incidents were unrelated. The latest arrest occurred about 3:50 a.m. Tuesday when uniformed Secret Service officers arrested Dirk Renard Estes of California after, they said, he moved and walked past a security barrier near the East Wing of the White House. Police said Estes was carrying a Yorkshire terrier along with two book bags filled with clothes, a wallet and a District of Columbia Department of Corrections bracelet. He was wearing a Trump-branded fleece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juncker DRUNKER? World leaders forced to hold stumbling EU leader... </title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/988000/Jean-Claude-Juncker-NATO-news-countries-members-Donald-Trump-European-Union</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORLD leaders were forced to step in and help on Wednesday when European Commission President Jean-Claude Juncker was seen stumbling and losing his balance ahead of a Nato dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS $200K TICKET TO SPACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/12/reuters-america-exclusive-jeff-bezos-plans-to-charge-at-least-200000-for-space-rides-sources.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE, July 12- Jeff Bezos' rocket company plans to charge passengers about $200,000 to $300,000 for its first trips into space next year, two people familiar with its plans told Reuters. The company, based about 20 miles south of Seattle, has made public the general design of the vehicle- comprising a launch rocket and detachable passenger capsule- but has been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHACKED: 'GOTTI' Lowest Box Office for Travolta in 20 Years...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/07/12/john-travolta-gotti-movie-will-end-theater-run-with-4-3-million-lowest-box-office-for-actor-in-over-20-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Gotti” rolls to the end of its theater release today, ending its ignominious 28 day run with $4.3 million. “Gotti” may linger, like a virus, but it’s basically over. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX NEW KING OF TV; SCORES MOST EMMY NOMINATIONS...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-et-st-emmy-nominations-hbo-netflix-20180711-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO's "Game of Thrones" scored the most nominations, but Netflix eked out a win in total nominations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Emails Were Sent To A 'Foreign Entity'...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/12/ig-clinton-foreign-emails/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It was going to an unauthorized source'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Tom Cruise Spectacular in new 'MISSION: IMPOSSIBLE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/mission-impossible-fallout-review-1126693 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Cruise reunites with director Christopher McQuarrie for the sixth spectacularly action-packed entry in the series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masquerade As Vet Felony?</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/entertainment/could-sacha-baron-cohens-stunt-with-sarah-palin-land-him-in-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SACHA BARON COHEN FIGHTS BACK!</title>
      <link>https://www.tvguide.com/news/sacha-baron-cohen-sarah-palin-who-is-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tvguide.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Billy Wayne Ruddick Jr., PhD" responds to Palin's claim that Cohen punk'd her for his Showtime show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska's last 2 BLOCKBUSTERS closing, leaving just 1 in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/business-economy/2018/07/12/the-last-two-blockbuster-stores-in-alaska-are-set-to-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The locations, one in Fairbanks and one in Anchorage, will start selling off inventory next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major League Baseball tix going biometric...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90201535/major-league-baseball-tickets-are-going-biometric-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pilot program will bring biometrics to select stadiums later this season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHERIFF JOE TARGETED...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/07/12/exclusive-sheriff-joe-sacha-baron-cohen-duped-me-posing-finnish-comedian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking in a Breitbart News interview, Joe Arpaio, the former Sheriff of Maricopa County, Arizona, detailed allegedly being duped into an interview with Sacha Baron Cohen, who Arpaio says posed as a famous comedian from Finland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama loses 2,346,119 fake TWITTER followers so far...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/obama-loses-2-million-followers-in-twitters-crackdown-on-fake-accounts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter’s purge of locked accounts hits the ex-president’s social media hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Havilland's 'FEUD' Petition Denied By CA Top Court; SCOTUS Next?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/olivia-de-havilland-feud-california-supreme-court-petition-denied-1202425561/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Nine days after Olivia de Havilland turned 102, the California Supreme Court has rejected the two-time Oscar winner’s desire to have them review her feud with FX Networks and Ryan Murphy…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend of reporters leaking to FBI...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/12/journalists-source-fbi-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I shared a copy of the dossier'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM SEN: 'WILD-EYED' RACE TO LEFT DANGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2018-07-12/sen-chris-coons-democrats-need-to-abandon-wild-eyed-race-to-left</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ghost' particle found mile beneath Antarctica...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/07/12/let-light-ghost-particle-found-mile-beneath-antarctica-holds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secrets of the origins of light are set to be unlocked by the discovery of an elusive &amp;ldquo;ghost&amp;rdquo; particle a mile beneath Antarctica, scientists have announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Destroyed Proof of Life On Mars?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/science/space/news/2018-07-12-mars-proof-of-life-organic-material-curiosity-rover-nasa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evidence of life on Mars possibly burned up by NASA decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping man shocked as BOA CONSTRICTOR falls from ceiling in New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Snake-Boa-Constrictor-Falls-Ceiling-Sleeping-New-York-Man--487975391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A central New York man got a rude awakening when a large snake fell from his bedroom ceiling and landed on him while he slept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear as social giant labels Russians as 'interested in treason'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jul/11/facebook-labels-russian-users-as-interested-in-treason</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firm removes category, which affected 65,000 people, from ad tools, following safety fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moviegoer stabbed during fight over seat at 'PURGE' screening...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/patron-stabbed-at-purge-screening-194065</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 11--As patrons awaited the start of the latest blood-soaked “Purge” movie, a dispute over a reserved seat ended with a Texas man plunging a knife six inches into the abdomen of a fellow moviegoe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ted Koppel Was Duped...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-sacha-baron-cohen-duped-ted-koppel-his-showtime-show-1126560</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran broadcaster, who was tricked into an interview (but didn't sign a release), explains how it happened to him.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
