<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Feds use fake university in pay-to-stay immigration sting...</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/feds-used-fake-metro-detroit-university-to-identify-illegal-immigrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents from the Homeland Security Investigations unit used a fake university located in Farmington Hills to help find nonimmigrant aliens who were allegedly scamming the system to stay in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Builds image of itself from scratch...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2019/01/30/New-robot-can-simulate-a-self-image-learn-what-it-is/5551548881593/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineers at Columbia University have built a robot capable of building an image of itself from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Romo Predictive Powers Get Super Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/radiotvtalk/super-bowl-cbs-tony-romo-predictive-powers-tested-the-biggest-stage/xVw4qIQzRRiZysgw7EGTjI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Originally posted Wednesday, January 30, 2019 by RODNEY HO/rho@ajc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Takes First Steps Towards Killing URLs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-chrome-kill-url-first-steps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google wants to get rid of URLs. But first, it needs to show you why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Self-aware' robot operates without instructions...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1080325/science-robots-self-aware-mechanical-arm-artificial-intelligence-columbia-university</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have created a self-aware robot capable of operating on its own without any instructions, in a major scientific breakthrough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisons Quietly Build Databases Of Inmate Voice Prints...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/30/prison-voice-prints-databases-securus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The voice-print technology allows authorities to mine call databases and cross-reference the voices of individuals prisoners have spoken with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hot Ted Bundy' memes part of NETFLIX PR strategy?</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/quartzy/1537986/netflix-probably-loves-all-the-hot-ted-bundy-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the release of its new documentary, Netflix said not to joke about the infamous serial killer. But each time someone does, Netflix's marketing strategy flourishes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage shows potential persons of interest in 'EMPIRE' star attack...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/video-shows-potential-persons-of-interest-in-empire-actor-attack-police-say/5113489/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video captured potential persons of interest in the attack on "Empire" actor Jussie Smollett in the Streeterville neighborhood, Chicago police said Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMX Urges Rappers To Stop Promoting Drugs In Music...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/01/30/dmx-wishes-todays-rap-didnt-promote-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If that’s what you wanna do, that’s your business, but you ain’t gotta promote it like it’s cool and make it cool, know what I’m saying?“ the rapper said in an interview.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos erupts inside FACEBOOK as employees unable to open apps on iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/facebook-chaos-after-apple-blocks-internal-iphone-apps-report-2019-1-1027910304</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Violent neighbor ordered to pay Rand Paul $580,000...</title>
      <link>http://www.wave3.com/2019/01/30/jury-awards-sen-rand-paul-upwards-civil-suit-against-neighbor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wave3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul sued his neighbor, Rene Boucher, for an attack that left him with multiple broken ribs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baristas given instructions on handling 2020 questions...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/30/starbucks-baristas-told-how-to-handle-schultz-2020-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks baristas have received instructions on how to handle “aggressive” customers who might be upset about Howard Schultz’s presidential ambitions. The employees were provided…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court Orders Release of BUZZFEED Dossier Suit Records...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/30/buzzfeed-dossier-lawsuit-unsealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents to be released by Feb. 8</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says Warren Asked Him for Campaign Cash!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/politics/howard-schultz-warren-asked-me-for-money-in-the-past</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz said Wednesday that Democratic Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren once asked him to make a campaign donation — and he refused because he feared her brand of politics would lead towards socialism in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret underground tunnel found, leads toward FL bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/pembroke-pines/fl-ne-pembroke-pines-hole-20190130-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI and Pembroke Pines police are investigating whether someone was trying to dig a secret path to Chase bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON hauling cargo in self-driving trucks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/30/amazon-is-hauling-cargo-in-self-driving-trucks-developed-by-embark.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embark and other firms working on self-driving trucks aim to alleviate industry pains by making existing truck drivers safer and more efficient. Amazon is using Embark's trucks for some loads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: 'No proof' Assange charged, refuses to unseal...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dfd74baf6b2f46c28d7b22138f59c034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FALLS CHURCH, Va. (AP) — A federal judge on Wednesday rejected a request to unseal criminal charges against Wikileaks founder Julian Assange that were mistakenly revealed in another case. U.S. District Judge Leonie Brinkema said in a 10-page ruling that free-press advocates seeking to unseal the charges have no proof Assange has actually been charged. The Reporters Committee for the Freedom of the Press sought to unseal the charges after a federal prosecutor inadvertently typed a reference to "the fact that Assange has been charged" in an unrelated case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.'s patrolling plastic-straw cop leaves eateries rattled...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2019/01/30/on-patrol-with-washingtons-plastic-straw-cop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the nation’s capital, as of this month, plastic drinking straws are out. Straws made from eco-friendly materials are in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'deepfakes' video scarily convincing...</title>
      <link> https://www.dailydot.com/debug/jennifer-buscemi-deepfake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER: Russians using investigation materials in disinformation effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/mueller-says-russians-using-his-discovery-materials-disinformation-effort-n964811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel says the Russians are attempting to use his investigation's findings in a disinformation campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Sonar scaring whales to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/sonar-can-scare-whales-death-new-study-shows-ncna964801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say banning military exercises in certain areas could help save the deep-diving sea mammals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Push 'No First Use' Nuke Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/congress/2019/01/30/warren-smith-introduce-bill-to-bar-us-from-using-nuclear-weapons-first/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two key Democratic lawmakers have introduced legislation Wednesday to ensure the U.S. does not fire nuclear weapons first in a potential future war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 injured in DC motorcade accident; protester arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6650029/Two-injured-accident-involving-Trumps-motorcade-president-not-hurt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are unconfirmed reports that it occurred when a protester jumped in front of the motorcade. Another unconfirmed report is that a police officer was hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biochemist Sells 'Gene-Editing Kit' for the Masses...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/01/29/east-bay-biochemist-sells-gene-editing-kit-for-the-masses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An East Bay entrepreneur wants to put the power of gene-editing in everyone's hands through his company's "Genetic Design Kits."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wurst night ever? Taste takes holiday at German sausage hotel...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wurst-night-ever-taste-takes-holiday-german-sausage-025503632.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgensgmünd (Germany) (AFP) - Sausages on the menu, sausage motifs on the wallpaper, sausage mobiles hanging from the ceiling -- and to top it off, a sausage-shaped pillow on your bed. What sounds like a vegetarian's nightmare is the audacious dream come true of Claus Boebel, a fourth-generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada reduces Cuba staff after another diplomat falls mysteriously ill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/866795d7b77b4044a2277e552fe8bc5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Canada announced Wednesday it is removing up to half of the Canadians at its embassy in Cuba after another diplomat was found to have fallen mysteriously ill. Canada has confirmed 14 cases of mysterious health problems since early 2017. Twenty-six American embassy workers in Cuba have also been affected, suffering a range of symptoms and diagnoses including mild traumatic brain injury, also known as concussion. Global Affairs Canada said in a statement Wednesday that tests confirmed a 14th case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA high school football participation plunges...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/01/30/football-recruiting-the-pac-12s-primary-talent-pool-is-shrinking-faster-than-those-of-other-power-five-conferences/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pac-12 is facing numerous competitive challenges as it attempts to keep pace with the SEC and Big Ten. Perhaps none are more ominous than the drop in high school participation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-con robs bank, hoping to be sent back to prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/crime/2019/01/29/real-life-shawshank-redemption-ex-con-robs-bank-go-back-prison/2704306002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A career criminal from New York robbed a Milwaukee bank hoping that a judge will send him to a Wisconsin prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vasectomy Zoning' Making Childless Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.citylab.com/perspective/2019/01/family-planning-day-care-costs-zoning-cities-children/580279/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.citylab.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Municipalities shouldn’t block or raise the cost of things young parents need, like day-care centers and two-bedroom houses or apartments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters Blames Trump...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/maxine-waters-blames-president-trump-for-attack-on-empire-actor-jussie-smollett/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA Gov. Advocates Post-Birth Abortion...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/northman-on-40-week-abortion-bill-infant-would-be-delivered-and-then-a-discussion-would-ensue-between-the-physicians-and-the-mother/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam (D.) commented Wednesday about a controversial 40-week abortion bill and in so doing said the law allows an abortion to take place after the infant's birth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used Car Dealers Charged With Rolling Back Odometers...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/01/29/federal-heights-afg-auto-odometer-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two used car dealers in Federal Heights are formally charged for theft and forgery after prosecutors say they were part of an odometer rollback scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Loss of newspapers contributes to polarization...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ecf440606c824f9d9671f2fb22a2ffce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The steady loss of local newspapers and journalists across the country contributes to the nation's political polarization, a new study has found. With fewer opportunities to find out about local politicians, citizens are more likely to turn to national sources like cable news and apply their feelings about national politics to people running for the town council or state legislature, according to research published in the Journal of Communication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After ghoulish allegations, brain-preservation seeks redemption...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/01/30/nectome-brain-preservation-redemption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert McIntyre and Nectome are determined to claw their way out of scientific purgatory and show they can preserve brains and perhaps memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump phones Guaido...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/trump-phones-venezuelas-guaido-as-u-s-pushes-for-maduro-to-go-idUSKCN1PO08V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump spoke to Venezuela's self-proclaimed interim pr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKKI HALEY CASHES IN: $200K SPEAKING FEE!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/30/ex-un-ambassador-nikki-haley-charging-200000-per-speaking-gig.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former U.S. Ambassador to the United Nations Nikki Haley is quoting $200,000 and the use of a private jet for domestic speaking engagements, according to people with knowledge of the arrangement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tests world's most powerful naval gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/30/china-naval-gun-ready-for-warfare-by-2025-us-intelligence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The weapon is capable of striking a target 124 miles away at speeds of up to 1.6 miles per second, according to sources. For perspective, a shot fired from Washington, D.C., could reach Philadelphia in under 90 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic shift: More Hispanic than black voters in 2020, whites decline to 66%...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/historic-shift-more-hispanic-than-black-voters-in-2020-whites-decline-to-66</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a major shift that appears to help Democrats and liberals, one third of the eligible voters in the upcoming 2020 presidential election will be non-white, the first time ever, according to a new analysis of U.S. Census data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iCloud bug 'let anyone read private notes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8313049/iphone-icloud-breach-bug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE reportedly covered up a major privacy breach that gave hackers partial access to user iCloud accounts. The supposed flaw was allegedly “kept secret” by Apple – and quietly fixed w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian pop bands dress as Nazis in new craze...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8314783/bts-asian-pop-bands-keyakizaka46-dress-nazi-troopers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOME of the world’s biggest pop stars have been given a huge dressing down for taking to the stage looking like NAZI troopers. The trend was highlighted when a Thai starlet was caught on came…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Launches Investigation Into Leaked Texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bezos-launches-investigation-into-leaked-texts-with-lauren-sanchez-that-killed-his-marriage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon chief’s security consultants suspect the leak to the National Enquirer may have been politically motivated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns of socialism coming to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/01/30/howard_schultz_elizabeth_warrens_programs_will_lead_to_socialism_in_america.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Starbucks CEO and independent candidate for president Howard Schultz said he does not support the tax policies of Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) in an interview Wednesday on MSNBC's 'Morning Joe.' Schultz said Warren "believes in programs that will lead to a level of socialism." Schultz also revealed that when Warren sought a donation for her Senate campaign he declined because of her socialist agenda. "I've also been criticized for being a billionaire," Schultz said Wednesday. "Let's talk about that. I'm self-made. I grew up in the project in Brooklyn, New York. I thought that was the American dream, the aspiration of America. You're going to criticize me for -- for being successful when in my company over the last 30 years, the only company in America that gave comprehensive health insurance, equity in the form of stock options, and free college tuition? And Elizabeth Warren wants to criticize me for being successful?" "I don't believe what Elizabeth Warren stands for," Schultz said Wednesday. "I don't believe the country should be heading to socialism." "I think she believes in programs that will lead to a level of socialism in America. She's a smart woman. I respect her. This isn't personal. I just don't agree with her," he added. WILLIE GEIST, 'MORNING JOE' CO-HOST: So Senator Warren, as you know, put out a plan -- HOWARD SCHULTZ, INDEPENDENT CANDIDATE FOR PRESIDENT: Yes. GEIST: A 2-percent tax on people with $50 million or more in assets. SCHULTZ: Yes. GEIST: You called that plan ridiculous. SCHULTZ: Yes. GEIST: We show a poll earlier in the show that said the American public likes that idea a lot. And they hear someone like you with billions of dollars calling it ridiculous and say, of course, he wants to protect his own money. SCHULTZ: No. GEIST: What do you say to that? SCHULTZ: Well, if that plan was put in place, it probably could fund the government for a day or two. So that's not the answer. The answer is, let's take a step back from this. Let's not send out a tweet or a press release that make news. Let's get serious people around the table and solve this problem once and for all, which is comprehensive tax reform. GEIST: Do you think Elizabeth Warren's a serious person on taxes? SCHULTZ: I think she's a serious person, yes. MIKA BRZEZINSKI, 'MORNING JOE' CO-HOST: Yes. SCHULTZ: She -- she came to see me a few years ago and asked me for a contribution for her Senate race? BRZEZINSKI: Did you give it to her? SCHULTZ: I did not. BRZEZINSKI: OK. Wow. MIKE BARNICLE, 'MORNING JOE' CO-HOST: Why? SCHULTZ: I don't believe what Elizabeth Warren is -- what -- stands for. I don't -- I don't believe the country should be heading to socialism. BARNICLE: Do you think she's a socialist? SCHULTZ: I think she believes in programs that will lead to a level of socialism in America. She's a smart woman. I respect her. This isn't personal. I just don't agree with her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXCONN not building in Wisconsin after all?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/foxconn-may-not-build-10b-wisconsin-plant-trump-touted-n964411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20-million square foot campus was praised by President Donald Trump as proof of his ability to revive American manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm A Billionaire, I Thought That Was The American Dream!</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/01/30/howard_schultz_im_a_billionaire_i_thought_that_was_the_american_dream.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC: Former Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz is considering an Independent 2020 presidential bid, and he tells 'Morning Joe' why he doesn't believe what the Democratic Party stands for, why he sees himself as a legitimate Independent choice and what he really thinks about Elizabeth Warren. Schultz responded to critics of his personal fortune and being a billionaire in America. "I've also been criticized for being a billionaire," Schultz said Wednesday. "Let's talk about that. I'm self-made. I grew up in the project in Brooklyn, New York. I thought that was the American dream, the aspiration of America. You're going to criticize me for -- for being successful when in my company over the last 30 years, the only company in America that gave comprehensive health insurance, equity in the form of stock options, and free college tuition? And Elizabeth Warren wants to criticize me for being successful?" Interview highlights: Schultz: The government is not going to suddenly start working if a Democrat is elected. Schultz on criticism of being a billionaire: "I'm self-made. I grew up in the project in Brooklyn, New York. I thought that was the American's dream, the aspiration of America." He was incredulous that people like Sen. Elizabeth Warren would criticize him for being successful. Schultz said the government needs to be "interrupted" because it is not working and challenged the panel to name anything in government that works. "I'm not a Democrat," Schultz told the 'Morning Joe' panel. "I don't affiliate myself with the Democrat Party who is so far left, who basically wants the government to take over health care, which we cannot afford, the government to give free college to everybody and the government to give everyone a job, which basically is $40 trillion on the balance sheet of $21.5 trillion. We can't afford it." Schultz also revealed that Warren sought a donation from him for a Senate campaign and he declined because she's a "socialist." "She came to see me a few years ago and asked me for a contribution for her Senate race," he shared. "Did you give it to her?" co-host Mika Brzezinski inquired. "I did not," Schultz answered. "I don't believe what Elizabeth Warren stands for," Schultz said Wednesday. "I don't believe the country should be heading to socialism." "I think she believes in programs that will lead to a level of socialism in America. She's a smart woman. I respect her. This isn't personal. I just don't agree with her," he added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Jackson to make BEATLES doc using unseen footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/peter-jackson-beatles-documentary-let-it-be-paul-mccartney-john-lennon-split-a8753981.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tipsy Christie claims he'd be better prez than Trump...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/820632/chris-christie-says-hed-better-president-than-trump-boozy-late-show-stephen-colbert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie was Stephen Colbert's guest on Tuesday's Late Show, and at his request, they began the interview with tequila shots. "Where do you think the wheels came off during the shutdown?" Colbert asked. "The president blew it," Christie replied. "When?" Colbert asked, and Christie answered: "When he shut the government down with no plan on how to reopen it." Christie said he warned Trump beforehand that "if you're going to do this, you'd better have an exit plan." That obviously didn't happen, "and he got goose egg," Colbert said. "Yes, in politics, we call that getting rolled," Christie said. Christie said it hurts him "personally" when Trump undermines democracy by attacking the Justice Department and the FBI. So after two years, "do you regret at all helping this man get elected?" Colbert asked. Christie grabbed the bottle of tequila. He said in 2016 he preferred Trump to Hillary Clinton, "and I still agree with what his policies are more than I agree with Hillary Clinton's," but it's true Trump "has turned the Republican Party into something different that it was when I started to run for president." "Yeah, the Kremlin," Colbert joked. Colbert asked what Christie gets out of his 17-year friendship with the infamously transactional Trump. "He demands loyalty, he doesn't seem that loyal himself," Colbert said. "He'll toss anybody under the bus." "You think I don't know?" Christie asked, laughing. "I'm the guy who got fired from the transition." That stung, but "we have one president at a time, and if I can do anything to make him better, if I can do anything that helps the country, that's my job to do," he said. "Believe me, my wife ain't happy about it either." "Would you have been a better president than Trump?" Colbert asked. "Yes," Christie said, no hesitation. They ended with a spirited discussion of who exactly likes Christie anymore. Watch below. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifting Stories Cloud Claims of Alleged Hate Crime Attack Targeting 'EMPIRE' Actor...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/shifting-stories-cloud-claims-of-alleged-hate-crime-attack-targeting-empire-actor-jussie-smollett/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police have not found video of alleged "MAGA" assailants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Threaten Mariah Carey...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/mariah-carey-threats-come-after-months-of-isis-supporters-urging-concert-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women's rights activists have been urging the pop singer to cancel the event in protest over the Saudi regime jailing human rights advocates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atheist blogger appeals for funds to help him 'Escape Egypt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/atheist-blogger-appeals-funds-help-him-escape-egypt-125300425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — A prominent atheist video blogger says he has given up hope on life in Egypt and has launched a crowdfunding page called "Help Me Escape Egypt" to aid him in purchasing another nationality so he can override an exit ban imposed by the secret police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 36,000 Pounds of Chicken Nuggets Recalled; Might Contain Rubber...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/01/29/tyson-chicken-recall-rubber-may-contaminate-nuggets-usda-says/2717993002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Certain products labeled "Tyson white meat panko chicken nuggets" may be contaminated with rubber, USDA says. This comes a day after one from Perdue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Wheelhouse LA: Modern Hollywood networking and influence-peddling on amphetamines...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/guy-made-360m-reality-tv-now-he-wants-real-money-1180612 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the recent reality television boom, small-time producers that were once "the Rodney Dangerfields" of Hollywood sold their companies for hundreds of millions. Now many are looking for second acts, and for 'Pawn Stars' creator Brent Montgomery, that involves a high-stakes “VC to TV” business, Jimmy Kimmel and an invite-only L.A. "incubator” (just don't call it a party house).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAT NUTS TO BOOST SPERM...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/health/1080051/fertility-nuts-nut-male-fertility-sperm-cell-almonds-hazelnuts-walnuts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FERTILITY: Recent research has shown including certain nuts in your diet can boost sperm quality and support male fertility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind-altering parasite spread by CATS 'may lead to schizophrenia in humans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6648545/Mind-altering-parasite-spread-CATS-lead-schizophrenia.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with the infection were 50 per cent more likely to have schizophrenia, Danish researchers found. Findings add to previous research showing a link to mind-altering behaviours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of supersonic jets could create sonic booms 'every five minutes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/30/new-supersonic-jets-could-create-sonic-booms-every-five-minutes.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parts of North America and Western Europe could experience sonic booms every five minutes if supersonic jets become commercialized, a new study said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President blasts intel chiefs as 'passive and naive'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/427608-trump-blasts-intel-chiefs-for-wrong-iran-assessment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday blasted top intelligence leaders for being "wrong" about their new assessment on Iran's nuclear developments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA driver sleeping behind wheel on autopilot down highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/motors/8310833/tesla-driver-sleeping-autopilot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN has been caught sleeping behind the wheel in a Tesla Model X car while driving on Autopilot. He was filmed by a neighbouring driver as they cruised down a road in Las Vegas, USA. The drivers …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic smog forces Bangkok to close hundreds of schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/30/toxic-smog-forces-bangkok-to-close-hundreds-of-schools</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thai capital has been shrouded in murky haze for weeks, forcing residents to don masks and sparking criticism of government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High school football dying slow death?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/jan/30/high-school-football-numbers-drop-brain-trauma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions will watch the Rams and Patriots play this weekend. But participation in high-school football is falling, and fears over brain trauma could be to blame</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early risers enjoy better mental health, major genetic study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/29/early-risers-enjoy-better-mental-health-major-genetic-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early risers are less likely to suffer mental health problems than those who prefer to lie in, a major genetic study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private companies add 213K jobs in Jan; Top expectations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/30/private-companies-add-213000-jobs-in-january-easily-topping-expectations-adpmoodys-analytics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private payrolls grew in January at a much faster pace than expected as the labor market shrugged off the longest U.S. government shutdown in history, according to ADP and Moody's Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has compromise in DC become unattainable?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/426887-has-compromise-in-washington-become-unattainable</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The partisan gap, the divisions between Republicans and Democrats on fundamental political values, continues to increase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Space Plane Wings Past 500 Days on Mystery Mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/43153-x-37b-military-space-plane-500-days.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secretive mission of a U.S. Air Force X-37B miniature space plane just winged past 500 days in Earth orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay men kept vanishing in Toronto. Now, serial killer confessed...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Gay-men-kept-vanishing-on-the-streets-of-Toronto-13572990.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the better part of a decade, rumors about a serial killer haunted Toronto's Gay Village, a gentrifying neighborhood of rainbow-flag street signs and historic Victorian homes where bathhouses and X-rated video stores were slowly being replaced by banks and chain coffee shops. As one gay man after another disappeared under mysterious circumstances, residents canceled plans to go out, carried pepper spray on walks and made sure their neighbors knew when to expect them home. But in December 2017, the Toronto Police Service assured residents that there was no reason to believe that the community had a mass murderer on its hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone faces gag order. He has plan to resist it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/30/roger-stone-mueller-case-1136430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The political rabble-rouser has a well-known First Amendment attorney on his legal team and has designated a pair of close friends as spokesmen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns Americans against new 'Vietnam'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Maduro-offers-dialogue-to-Venezuelan-opposition-13573039.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela - Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro offered dialogue to the increasingly vigorous opposition Wednesday while warning the American people that intervening in his country could create new Vietnam-style quagmire. The dialogue offer, which has been made before, was immediately praised by Russian and drew a tweet from President Donald Trump, who said it came after increased U.S. pressure on the Venezuelan government and economy. "I am ready to sit down at the negotiating table with the opposition so that we could talk about what benefits Venezuela," Maduro said in an interview with Russian state media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth and murder: New kind of drug war has made Tijuana one of deadliest cities on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/mexico-americas/la-fg-mexico-tijuana-drug-violence-20190130-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bloodshed, fueled by cristal — methamphetamine — is fundamentally different from previous iterations of violence in Tijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Lawn Mower...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/irobot-s-follow-up-act-to-the-roomba-vacuum-mowing-the-lawn#gs.2RWKZmg9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Creator of the Roomba Just Launched a Lawn Mower</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird Paris debut of immersive Stalinist reality show 'DAU'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8f2327bd93a64247bc52c4025138b072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Imagine setting aside two years of your life to work, sleep and procreate in a fake Stalinist physics lab. A place where secret police or hidden microphones monitor every utterance. Where you're not allowed to check your phones or don modern underwear, or mention anything that's happened in the last half-century — or acknowledge that the whole thing is really just a film set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Tons of Gold Ready to Ship. Address Unknown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/venezuela-20-tons-gold-ready-004013962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just another outlandish comment from a lawmaker trying to draw attention to the plight of crisis-torn Venezuela? For one thing, Guerra is a former central bank economist who remains in touch with old colleagues there. For another, a person with direct knowledge of the matter told Bloomberg News Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$150 Million Plot of Land Hits Market in Bel Air, House Not Included...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/-150-million-plot-of-land-hits-market-in-bel-air-house-not-included</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;$150 Million Plot of Land Hits MarketÂ in Bel Air, House Not Included</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Group Urges Residents To Help Protect Feral Cats During Deep Freeze...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/01/29/feral-cats-shelters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dangerously-cold temperatures plaguing Chicago this week could be deadly for many outdoor creatures, including the estimated 200,000  feral cats that live in the Chicago area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Muslims demand NIKE recall shoes with 'Allah written on sole'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8285782/muslims-nike-recall-air-max-trainer-allah/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIKE has been urged to recall “offensive” Air Max trainers because they have “Allah’s name in Arabic” on the sole. Saiqa Noreen was appalled when she spotted text on the bottom of the shoe and accu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates face political risks when pressed on healthcare specifics...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democratic-candidates-face-political-risks-when-13571912.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Sen. Kamala D. Harris spoke about health care at a CNN forum Monday evening, she threw her support behind a "Medicare-for-all" plan, sounding similar to other candidates seeking the Democratic presidential nomination. But when pressed for details, the senator from California explained the idea in a way most Democrats assiduously avoid: She agreed that Medicare-for-all also means private insurance for none. "Let's eliminate all of that," Harris said, referring to private health insurance. "Let's move on." In a single flourish, Harris, D-Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro pummels Venezuelan slums as his power comes under attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/world/south-america/maduro-pummels-venezuelan-slums-as-his-power-comes-under-attack-20190130-p50ujg.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former STARBUCKS CEO has spent months researching presidential bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Former-Stabucks-CEO-has-spent-months-researching-13571868.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before announcing his presidential ambitions this week, former Starbucks chief executive Howard Schultz secretly undertook a months-long effort to prepare an independent presidential campaign against the nation's two-party political system, deploying more than six national polls and laying the groundwork for paid advertising that could debut in the next two months. The full reach of the project suggests that his stated goal of disrupting the U.S. political process is not likely to fade away anytime soon, despite enormous historical barriers to success and Democratic predictions that his entry in the race will help President Donald Trump get reelected. An early advertising effort, made possible by Schultz's net worth of about $3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT SOAP OPERA DRAGS ON...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/brexit-vote-summary-7-key-13925303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May is now stronger and ready to fight the EU - but the battle's impossible and it could all still turn against her. We've learned a lot tonight - here's the Commons drama decoded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD investigates Turkish flags hung at Armenian schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-turkish-flags-armenian-schools-20190129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Armenians, the flags call to mind the million-plus that died at Turkish Ottoman hands beginning in 1915.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  APPLE to fix FaceTime bug that allows eavesdropping...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/947951d023a844d09129895877d3c7a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has disabled a group-chat function in FaceTime after users said a software bug could let callers activate another person's microphone remotely. With the bug, a FaceTime user calling another iPhone, iPad or Mac computer could hear audio — even if the receiver did not accept the call. The bug is triggered when callers add themselves to the same call to launch a group chat. That makes FaceTime think the receiver had accepted the chat. The bug, demonstrated through videos online , comes as an embarrassment for a company that is trying to distinguish itself by stressing its commitment to users' privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court bars opposition leader from leaving nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/314d3842c81f426cb03b2702cd0b3e23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela's Supreme Court barred opposition leader Juan Guaido from leaving the country Tuesday, a move certain to heighten tensions as the man challenging President Nicolas Maduro's claim to the presidency presses forward with establishing a transitional government and the U.S. warns of "serious consequences" if he is harmed. The government-stacked high court announced the order just hours after chief prosecutor Tarek William Saab announced that he was opening a criminal investigation into Guaido's anti-government activities and requested that restrictions be placed on his movements abroad. The court also approved Saab's request that all of Guaido's financial assets be frozen.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
