<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Death toll jumps again...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/asia/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-02-09-20-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He spoke out. Now his family fears he's been silenced...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/09/asia/wuhan-citizen-journalist-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As people across China mourned the death of a whistleblower doctor in an almost unprecedented outpouring of grief and anger on Thursday, little did they know that another truth-teller of the coronavirus outbreak was being silenced, according to friends and family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Barbara Walters 'Not Doing Great'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/2020/02/09/barbara-walters-not-doing-great-the-view-jenny-mccarthy-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid reports that legendary news anchor, Barbara Walters has been struggling with her health, the [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Peterson's year of 'absolute hell': Professor retreats because of addiction...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/jordan-petersons-year-of-absolute-hell-professor-forced-to-retreat-from-public-life-because-of-tranquilizer-addiction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial author and professor is recovering from addiction to tranquilizers and near-death in Russia, his family says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Over Sex Work Raging Inside Biggest Feminist Group...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-national-organization-for-women-is-tearing-itself-apart-over-sex-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a growing divide within the feminist movement on whether the sale and purchase of consensual, adult sex should be decriminalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver runs van through Republican voter registration tent...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/local/2020/02/08/police-van-drives-through-republican-partys-voter-registration-tent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers with the Jacksonville Sheriff’s Office are looking for a brown Chevrolet van they said drove through a tent Sunday where volunteers were registering people to vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA agent tricks traveler into showing her breasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/tsa-agent-tricked-traveler-baring-herself-officials-say-n1132971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 22-year-old agent was arrested for deceiving a traveler into twice showing him her breasts as she went through security at Los Angeles International Airport, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so many married couples sleep in separate beds...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/02/09/separate-beds-married-couples-can-help-relationship-experts-say/4657215002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey says almost a quarter of married couple sleep in separate bed. Here's why some are opting to part ways at nighttime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Out of Gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/joe-biden-is-running-out-of-gas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former VP has lost the plot, voters say. And they’re wondering if he will ever get it back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online preschool gains momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.concordmonitor.com/Online-preschool-32456408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.concordmonitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We read with concern David Brooks’s Jan. 28 article about the New Hampshire Department of Education’s goal of enrolling 200 families in a pilot program for online preschool called Upstart. Although Brooks’s article did not mention the concerns about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg booms...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/02/08/nh-primary-poll-sanders-buttigieg-klobuchar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All week long, the story has been the rise of Pete Buttigieg to co-frontrunner status with Bernie Sanders. The latest exclusive WBZ/Boston Globe/Suffolk University tracking poll shows they're still co-leaders within the poll's 4.4% margin of error, with Sanders holding steady at 24% and Buttigieg slipping a bit to 22%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where did they go? Millions left Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/9/millions-left-wuhan-china-coronavirus-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials finally began to seal the borders on Jan. 23. But it was too late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed573fec92465305a5e3256cda62160c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Two U.S. soldiers were killed and six wounded in a so-called insider attack in eastern Afghanistan's Nangarhar province late Saturday when an Afghan dressed in an Afghan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD: Officer shot, wounded in 'assassination attempt'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/nypd-officer-shot-wounded-assassination-attempt-68856407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's police commissioner says an officer was wounded by gunfire in the Bronx in “an assassination attempt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid gang peril, a Mexican village arms its children... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Amid-gang-peril-a-Mexican-village-arms-its-15041386.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AYAHUALTEMPA, Mexico - Before he picked up a rifle and joined a squad of armed children, Alex wanted to become a schoolteacher. He'd teach anything - "whatever the principal asks" - because spending his days in a classroom sounded pretty good.  He was 13, a B student with a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles bicycle who got nervous around the girls in his middle school.  Then, in November, as violence surged in the mountains of Guerrero state, the men of Ayahualtempa decided it was time for their sons to take up arms.  Alex was handed a hunting rifle and told to show up for daily training on the village basketball court. He and his young comrades, some as young as 6, marched and crawled with loaded guns almost as tall as they were. Their uniforms said "Community Police" in yellow letters.  When the photographers started coming, the boys were told to cover their faces with handkerchiefs. Arming children to defend the town against a violent gang wasn't a media stunt, Alex's commanders insisted. Yet if the images drew the government's attention to a place Mexico's security forces had forgotten, it would be a triumph of its own.  But were the boys training to defend their village, or were they being paraded in front of visiting photographers to send a message to the government, a plea for more resources? Sometimes even Alex wasn't sure. What he knew was that the gun was heavy and loaded, and the training felt real enough to him.  Alex's father, Santos Martínez, looked at his son's face, trying to gauge whether Alex was mature enough to join the force.  "There was no fear in his eyes," Martínez said. "That's how I knew he was ready."  Alex repeated the words of his commander: "I'm preparing to defend my village."  Mexico suffered 35,588 homicides in 2019, a record. It was another data...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  LOW KEY OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75ca3451d6974bfa1228025fa4790be2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Oscars are here, already. After the shortest awards season in decades, the 92nd annual Academy Awards will get underway Sunday evening at the Dolby Theatre in Los...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUSH TO ENSURE FOOD SUPPLY IN HOT ZONES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48256188e39d4e2db49e8e8d68a6bd90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The rate of increase in new cases of the virus in China rose again after a brief respite, as the death toll rose to 722 on the mainland and countries around the world enforced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zirinsky defends anchor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b8a3ad60aa2728fa721fb69e4af4b63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The CBS News chief called threats against journalist Gayle King “reprehensible” Saturday as backlash grew against rapper Snoop Dogg and others critical of King for an interview...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor-comedian Orson Bean, 91, hit and killed by car in LA...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/5912587/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran actor Orson Bean was struck and killed by a car in the Friday night in Venice, California, authorities said. He was 91.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 DEAD...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200208231736-g2njf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AFGHANISTAN/ (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-American, Afghan soldiers killed in shootout in Afghanistan-NY Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  The Don Strikes Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/08/opinion/sunday/trump-vindman-sondland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An enraged and ebullient Trump ups the body count.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban claims multiple US soldiers killed in Afghan gun fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-taliban-claims-multiple-soldiers-21459283</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US military spokesman Col. Sonny Leggett said in a statement that both Afghan and US personnel were "engaged by direct firing"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg leads in latest poll...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/02/07/new-hampshire-primary-tracking-poll-pete-buttigieg-leads-bernie-sanders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg continued his rise in Friday night's exclusive WBZ/Boston Globe/Suffolk University poll, for the first time taking a narrow lead that falls within the survey’s 4.4% margin of error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.I. PICKS PETE TO BEAT</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/ai-picks-buttigieg-the-candidate-to-beat-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An artificial intelligence analysis of Friday night's Democratic debate picked former Mayor Pete Buttigieg as the clear winner and said that voters believe he can beat President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishment eyes Bloomberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/this-guy-has-some-guts-democratic-establishment-eyes-bloomberg-as-biden-falters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic establishment may be gravitating toward Michael Bloomberg after Joe Biden finished a disappointing fourth in the Iowa caucuses and appears to be flatlining in New Hampshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Putin blogger murdered in hotel room after vocally opposing Russian president...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/376364/anti-putin-blogger-has-his-throat-slit-in-a-hotel-room-after-vocally-opposing-the-russian-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PUTIN critic has been found with his throat slit in what police are calling a “politically motivated” assassination in a French hotel. Imran Aliev, 44, was found lying on the ground w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COSTA:  Trump's resilience causes Dems to sound alarm... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-s-resilience-causes-Democrats-to-sound-the-15040965.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Anxiety is coursing through the Democratic Party as President Donald Trump emerges from his impeachment proceedings as a potent threat for reelection, with party leaders and activists uncertain about how to beat the incumbent and worried about a nominatingrace that remains crowded and is growing more acrimonious.  While Democrats see Trump as a corrosive figure and a threat to the nation, they also see the president and his well-funded campaign tailoring a reelection bid around the strong economy and visceral appeals to his ardent supporters.  Trump's robust political standing came into view this past week, as he claimed vindication from his acquittal in his Senate trial despite damaging House testimony about his conduct with Ukraine - and set off on a path of retribution by ousting some officials who were witnesses. At the same time, his Gallup approval rating ticked up to 49 percent, its highest point yet.  The developments have generated convulsions of angst among Democrats, who watched their first-in-the-nation Iowa presidential caucuses conclude in a chaotic fiasco and deliveran inconclusive result. Many in the party are now soundingthe alarm that denying Trump a second term could be far more difficult than they had calculated.  "We have a president who isn't merely unconventional or challenging institutions and elites, or coloring outside the lines. He's unmoored," Sen. Christopher Coons, D-Del., said. Yet, Coons added, he is "very aware" that Trump could win reelection "with these economic numbers at his back, all as millions of Americans grow numb to his behavior."  Since Democratic presidential hopefuls began running through the starting gates a year ago, party activists have been consumed with the question of electability - specifically, which of the roughly two dozen initial candidates could best...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More quarantine centers set up at US military bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article240078853.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans raise $100 million during impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article240094513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires could 'leave Earth for space colony' as 'climate collapses'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/billionaires-could-leave-earth-behind-21445413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's growing speculation that the the trend for billionaires like Elon Musk and Jeff Bezos to research space travel is more than just 'boys and their toys' – it could be a lifeboat to escape a dying Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing begins mass arrest of suspected virus patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7980883/Video-shows-officials-protective-suits-dragging-suspected-coronavirus-carriers-homes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One clip, thought to be taken in Wuhan, shows a man sprinting away from a group of officials. Some officials appear to be carrying large metal sticks as they run after him along nearly-deserted streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden mocks small city mayor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/111f8ae7bf4122d690b53a024ef9c457</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. (AP) — Scrambling to salvage his presidential campaign, Joe Biden escalated his criticism of Pete Buttigieg on Saturday, mocking Buttigieg's experience as a small city mayor and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Death is inevitable'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/08/at-least-17-dead-in-thailand-shooting-after-soldier-opens-fire-in-shopping-mall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police identified the suspect as Jakrapanth Thomma. He had posted on his Facebook page earlier in the day that “Death is inevitable for everyone.” He also posted a picture of what appea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Confronts Perilous Moment...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/08/wobbly-after-iowa-biden-confronts-a-perilous-moment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. — Former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr.’s fourth-place finish in Iowa and his wobbly standing here in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Satanist claims he went to hell, converted to Christianity...</title>
      <link>http://bronx.news12.com/story/41669638/to-hell-and-back-exsatanist-claims-he-went-to-hell-converts-to-christianity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bronx.news12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Satanist John Ramirez shocked the world when he claimed his discovery of hell in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to plow ahead with probes post-acquittal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/482025-democrats-to-plow-ahead-with-trump-probes-post-acquittal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats say even though President Trump was acquitted in the Senate, that doesn’t mean they are going to ease off their investigations into his administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry over land dispute?
</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9be83e8622f7737226875899f27335a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAKHON RATCHASIMA, Thailand (AP) — A soldier who holed up in a popular shopping mall in northeastern Thailand shot multiple people on Saturday, killing at least 20 and injuring 31 others,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM JITTERS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ded7ac0881136001f1ebbcd7c007640c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, New Hampshire (AP) — For Democrats, this was supposed be a moment to begin easing three years of built-up of anxieties. Instead, the launch of the 2020 presidential primary has left the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRIDAY NIGHT PURGE: Trump ousts officials who testified on impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2bc056ec4cab05b7c5069cbac5e3fa9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Exacting swift punishment against those who crossed him, an emboldened President Donald Trump ousted two government officials who had delivered damaging testimony against him...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar Rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/amy-klobuchar-seizes-the-democratic-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We'll see Tuesday if that impression, which she’s made on previous debate nights, impacts voters this time — and which voters if so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash for banning postpartum ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/celebrities/2020/02/07/oscars-reject-postpartum-ad-being-too-graphic-busy-phillips-react/4696560002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscars catch heat before Hollywood's biggest night has even started after rejecting a postpartum television commercial for being "too graphic."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Matthews Explodes Over Socialism: 'Doesn't Frickin Work!'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/msnbcs-chris-matthews-explodes-on-democrats-over-socialism-it-doesnt-frickin-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Left-wing MSNBC host Chris Matthews exploded on the Democratic presidential candidates following Friday night&amp;#8217;s primary debate for embracing socialism, saying, &amp;#8220;it doesn&amp;#8217;t frickin work!&amp;#8221; &amp;#8220;&amp;#8230;the issue of this campaign, it is that word &amp;#8216;socialism,&amp;#8217;&amp;#8221; Matthews said. &amp;#8220;Some people like it, younger people like it, those of us like me, who grew up in the Cold [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: 'Very real threat': Four more years of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Candidates-face-very-real-threat-Four-more-15040026.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, N.H. - There was one big issue on the table when the Democratic candidates met for their debate at Saint Anselm College here on Friday: Was anyone on the stage capable of defeating a newly emboldened President Donald Trump?  There was no simple answer, but Tom Steyer, the billionaire businessman, put the issue in stark terms, warning that, after the events of the past week, there is now a "very real threat" that the president will be reelected. "Who can go toe-to-toe with Mr. Trump?" he asked. "Who can take down Mr. Trump?"  The dilemma for Democratic voters is that no one candidate has yet persuaded more than a fraction of the party that they are capable of doing so. Democrats came out of Iowa splintered and demoralized, and Friday's debate accentuated both the attributes each of the leading Democrats is offering and the limits of their appeal.  The debate plowed familiar ground, but there was an edge to it that was different from those of the recent past. Trump's acquittal in the Senate impeachment trial, fresh reports emphasizing a strong economy and a new poll showing Trump's approval at the highest point of his presidency only underscored the Democrats' current plight.  What emerged were a series of questions that Democratic voters will be considering not just here next week but in primaries and caucuses in the weeks ahead - questions from whether the party should move left or toward the center, to whether experience in Washington or freshness from outside would be more effective.  Former South Bend, Indiana, mayor Pete Buttigieg and Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., who finished in a virtual tie in Iowa's bungled caucuses and appeared to be the two candidates to beat here in New Hampshire, were principal targets of the others on the stage. And it was former vice president Joe Biden, the fourth-place finisher in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erectile dysfunction pills can permanently distort vision...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/07/erectile-dysfunction-pills-can-permanently-distort-vision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This little blue pill is giving men a big blue — or sometimes red — problem: colored vision. Erectile dysfunction drugs can lead to prolonged retinal dysfunction, a new case study published Friday …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Survive, Venezuela Leader Gives Up Decades of Control Over Oil...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/08/to-survive-venezuelas-leader-gives-up-decades-of-control-over-oil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela — After decades of dominating its oil industry, the Venezuelan government is quietly surrendering control to foreign companies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force suicides highest in three decades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6fa278e5078e3479adbe4745b765ed7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Suicides in the active-duty Air Force surged last year to the highest total in at least three decades, even as the other military services saw their numbers stabilize or decline,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
