<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TRIGGERS US MILITARY FEARS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/580248-china-triggers-growing-fears-for-us-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s military buildup and its push to develop nuclear-capable missiles is unnerving Congress and U.S. defense officials alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More men going to hospital with painful erections lasting hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4014840/men-hospital-painful-erections-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE men than ever are going to hospital with painful erections lasting for hours, worrying figures show. There were 326 admissions in England last year, up 16 per cent on a decade ago. Some suffer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion energy startup raises $500 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-zero-carbon-fusion-energy-startup-helion-raises-500-mln-2021-11-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Helion Energy, a fusion energy tech startup, on Friday said it raised $500 million to build a net positive electrical generator, one that creates more power than it uses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozen House Dems won't run for reelection, signaling midterm fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/republicans-look-advantage-house-democrats-opt-retirement-over-re-election-n1282983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The narrow 221-213 Democratic House majority could be in serious danger as members see the midterms as unwinnable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do long trips to outer space cause brain damage?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/long-trips-outer-space-brain-damage/story?id=81009631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research has linked spending a long time in outer space with possible brain damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Luxury Condos Overlook City's Worst Squalor...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/11/06/exclusive-san-francisco-homeless-luxury-condos-overlook-city-worst-squalor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A one-way, one-block alley in San Francisco has neighbors living in constant fear and afraid for their safety. Willow Street between Van Ness and Polk currently has the highest concentration of tents in San Francisco, according to the latest city data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Dressed as UPS Driver Shoots Another Woman in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/woman-dressed-as-ups-driver-shoots-another-woman-in-northeast-dc-police-say/2872317/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman dressed as a UPS delivery driver shot another woman multiple times in Northeast D.C. Friday and then attempted to take her own life, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor clinically diagnoses patient as suffering from 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.climatedepot.com/2021/11/07/b-c-doctor-clinically-diagnoses-patient-as-suffering-from-climate-change-picked-up-his-patients-chart-penned-in-the-words-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By: Stefan Labbé When a patient in her 70s came into the emergency department at Kootenay Lake Hospital in Nelson, B.C., Dr. Kyle Merritt had no idea hundreds of people were dying of heat across th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RODGERS LOSES ENDORSEMENT DEAL...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/11/07/aaron-rodgers-prevea-health-sponsorship-done/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers and Prevea Health have parted ways. The health company released a statement announcing an end to their partnership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US citizens v FBI: Will govt face charges for illegal surveillance?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/law/2021/nov/07/us-citizens-fbi-government-surveillance-guilty-9-11-muslims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Muslim citizens are suing the FBI for subjecting them to undercover surveillance after 9/11 in violation of constitutional rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigations widen...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/investigations-widen-into-deadly-stampede-houston-rap-concert-2021-11-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two investigations, one of them criminal, were underway on Sunday into the deadly stampede during rap star Travis Scott's Astroworld music festival that killed at least eight people and injured dozens in Houston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Camilla 'hasn't stopped talking about' hearing President 'break wind'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10172959/Camilla-stopped-talking-hearing-President-break-wind-chat-Cop26-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden produced a little natural gas of his own at the COP26 summit in Glasgow and it was audible enough to make the Duchess of Cornwall blush.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk using TWITTER poll to determine future of 10% of his TESLA shares...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/06/elon-musk-is-using-a-twitter-poll-to-decide-the-future-of-his-tesla-stock.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk previously indicated he was likely to sell "a huge block" of his options in the fourth quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers who fled during pandemic got more than they bargained for...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/06/all-the-dumb-mistakes-made-by-nyers-who-left-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After moving to the country during the pandemic, these former New Yorkers found idyllic “Green Acres” life to actually be “brutal.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia finally reopens to world but internal border closures persist...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/australias-uneven-covid-spread-makes-states-wary-lifting-lockdown-rcna4774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the strict Covid-19 lockdown, Australia is about to reopen to the world. Traveling between states inside the country is more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Is Kim Jong Un's Eric Clapton-Obsessed Brother?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/where-the-hell-is-kim-jong-un-s-eric-clapton-obsessed-brother/ar-AAQpH1R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where and why has North Korean leader Kim Jong Un’s older half-brother, Kim Jong Chul, disappeared? Considering the persistent doubts about the health of Kim Jong Un and his own habit of vanishing for weeks at a time—that question assumes some urgency. If 37-year-old Kim Jong Un were to die, Jong Chul, 40, never an active contender for power, would be a prime candidate to take over. “In a succession scenario, his name would surely be on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran behind attack?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/drone-attack-on-iraqi-pm-is-a-major-escalation-analysis-684244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack on Iraq’s Prime Minister is another step in drone warfare and is a message by pro-Iran groups in Iraq that the prime minister is not safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi PM survives drone attack on his home...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-59195399</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mustafa al-Kadhimi says he was not hurt in the attack by a drone carrying explosives in Baghdad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy launches ship named for gay rights leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-59196462</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USNS Harvey Milk is one of six new ships named after famous civil rights leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle the algorithms: China's delivery riders on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211107-battle-the-algorithms-china-s-delivery-riders-on-the-edge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Handing over a piping hot meal at exactly the time promised, Chinese food delivery driver Zhuang Zhenhua triumphantly tapped his job as complete through the Meituan app -- and was immediately fined h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia Grand Jury Looms in Trump Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/06/georgia-grand-jury-looms-in-trump-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol riot fights to extract testimony and documents from Donald J. Trump’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Raids O'Keefe's Home in Ashley Biden Diary Theft Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/06/f-b-i-searches-james-okeefes-home-in-ashley-biden-diary-theft-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities on Saturday searched the home of James O’Keefe, the founder of the conservative group Project Veritas, according to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems end deadlock, House hands Biden infrastructure win...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-congress-263678efec1b19d3fd22aa660ecd4544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden on Saturday hailed Congress' passage of his $1 trillion infrastructure package as a “monumental step forward for the nation" after fractious fellow Democrats resolved a months-long standoff in their ranks to seal the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 27 states filed lawsuits challenging the rule...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/appeals-court-stays-vaccine-mandate-coronavirus-biden-b235b6fa858bd23b02ab5f9c009428db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — A federal appeals court on Saturday temporarily halted the Biden administration's vaccine requirement for businesses with 100 or more workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They executed people for SC. Nearly destroyed some...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article254201328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of those who helped execute people in South Carolina prisons have never spoken publicly – until now. The closer the 10 men we spoke with were to the act of killing, the more serious the long-term consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man burst into flames after Taser used on him...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/man-burst-flames-taser-police-81000888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say an upstate New York man is in grave condition at a hospital after police used a Taser to subdue him and he burst into flames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROWD OF 50,000 SURGES TOWARD STAGE</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/astroworld-festival-travis-scotts-houston-crowds-trampled/11203827/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight people died Friday night at a concert packed with an estimated 50,000 people at NRG Park.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
