<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Natural beauty of wildlife beneath the waves revealed in stunning pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8243311/underwater-wildlife-pictures-natural-beauty-waves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE is a deep mystery to what lies beneath the surface, and these pictures certainly satisfy those with a curious eye. Below, we take a look at some of the most magical underwater photography tha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEMPS -40...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6614169/Governor-urges-New-Yorkers-stay-indoors-extreme-cold-weather-blights-state.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Andrew M. Cuomo urged New Yorkers to 'refrain from going outside over the next couple of days unless absolutely necessary' as extreme cold weather is forecast across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Suicide Bomb in Five Days Hits US Convoy in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/syria-bomb-attack-sdf-checkpoint-us-troops-shaddadi-after-manbij-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than a week after 4 Americans were killed in attack by ISIS, which Trump says is beaten, new ISIS-claimed blast hits a joint convoy in Syria's north</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At SUNDANCE, powerhouse documentaries will be everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5e4bb88431ba4229b28f1cf5bb632841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — For documentary filmmakers, there's no place like the Sundance Film Festival. The mountainside festival which kicks off Thursday in Park City, Utah, has become known for launching nonfiction films to box office successes and awards, and this year is shaping up to be no different. The slate boasts a wide array of films about fallen titans, from Harvey Weinstein to Theranos' Elizabeth Holmes, music legends Miles Davis and David Crosby, two of Michael Jackson's sexual abuse accusers, the Cambridge Analytica/Facebook scandal, Apollo 11, Mike Wallace, Toni Morrison and Dr. Ruth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF THE AGES!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ddfe599a71fc4c758d096eb63fef46fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It began in 2002, back when the Rams were in St. Louis and the Patriots were a plucky underdog standing in the way of a potential dynasty. So much has changed. This hasn't: Bill Belichick and Tom Brady. The duo, every bit as formidable now as when they won that first title, face the Rams, now back in Los Angeles, in a Super Bowl rematch of sorts that pits the NFL's past against its future. At 32, Sean McVay is the youngest Super Bowl coach. At 66, Bill Belichick has an NFL-record 30 playoff wins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Lethal Combination: Rising Property Taxes, Stagnant Incomes...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-01-20/illinois-lethal-combination-rising-property-taxes-stagnant-incomes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fliers Find Old Friend on More Planes: Empty Seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fliers-find-an-old-friend-on-more-planes-empty-seats-11548079200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. airlines are adding larger jets to their fleets and more rows to existing aircraft. The result is more open seats on many flights even as demand for air travel grows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon wins landmark 'right to be forgotten' case...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jan/21/dutch-surgeon-wins-landmark-right-to-be-forgotten-case-google</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ruling will ensure doctors no longer judged by Google on fitness to practise, lawyer says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fecal transplant researchers identify 'super-pooper' donors...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jan/21/faecal-transplant-researchers-identify-super-pooper-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study finds stool transplants from some donors are far more effective than others</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Who is more dangerous: El Chapo or Carlos Slim?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2019/jan/20/el-chapo-or-carlos-slim-who-is-more-dangerous</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While attention focuses on a mafia boss on trial in Brooklyn, the billionaire heads a power elite preserving inequality in Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antony and Cleopatra's long lost tomb FOUND and is set to be uncovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/antony-cleopatras-long-lost-tomb-13886561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists in Egypt have identified an area in Taposiris Magna, around 18 miles from Alexandria, where they believe Mark Antony and Cleopatra (VII)'s bodies are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FOX &amp; FRIENDS' graphic says Ruth Bader Ginsburg dead...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/426276-fox-friends-accidentally-shows-graphic-saying-ruth-bader-ginsburg-is-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hosts of “Fox &amp; Friends” on Monday apologized for showing a graphic saying Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg is dead, blaming a control room error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi warns of 'serious dangers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehindubusinessline.com/news/world/chinese-president-xi-warns-party-of-serious-dangers-as-risks-mount/article26051807.ece</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehindubusinessline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The party is facing long-term and complex tests in terms of maintaining long-term rule, reform and opening-up, a market-driven economy and within the external environment,” Xi said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report finds another undisclosed NKorea missile site; 19 more?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/north-korea/report-finds-another-undisclosed-north-korea-missile-site-says-there-n958801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kim regime has never admitted the existence of the Sino-ri Missile Operating Base. A new report says it's one of many undisclosed sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT: Plan B...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/21/british-prime-minister-may-to-reveal-her-plan-b-for-brexit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Theresa May is due to lay out a 'Plan B' for Brexit to lawmakers on Monday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENEZUELA UPRISING: Security forces fire tear gas against protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f54498b2dc9a430aa04d1d2b82d629c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Security forces have fired tear gas against protesters in a poor neighborhood just 2 miles (3 kilometers) from Venezuela's presidential palace after an apparent uprising by a national guard unit. The disturbance early Monday started hours after a group of men dressed in military fatigues and carrying assault weapons published a series of videos on social media saying they won't recognize President Nicolas Maduro's government. In one of the videos, a man identifying himself as 3rd Sgt. Figueroa, addressing the "people of Venezuela," urges his compatriots to take to the streets to show support for their rebellion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU antitrust cop lays groundwork for more tech scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/40c5919643104864b2db1be1f9f9adeb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Silicon Valley's notorious nemesis, Margrethe Vestager, plans to end her term as the European Union's antitrust enforcer this year with a bang, laying out a long-term plan to intensify scrutiny of the world's big tech companies. As the EU's competition commissioner, Vestager is arguably the world's most important tech regulator. Since 2014, she has slapped Google with eye-popping multibillion-dollar antitrust penalties, ordered Apple and Amazon to pay back taxes and fined Facebook over its WhatsApp acquisition — flagship enforcement cases that have struck fear into Silicon Valley while drawing attention in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Vote on Muslim Self-Rule Puts Christians on Edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/philippine-vote-on-muslim-self-rule-puts-christians-on-edge-11548039823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in a Muslim-majority region in the Philippines will decide on a proposal for greater self determination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.C. PENNEY Struggles to Avoid Fate Worse Than SEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/j-c-penney-struggles-to-avoid-a-fate-worse-than-the-sears-scenario-11548072000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.C. Penney Co.’s sales are falling, senior executive slots remain vacant and the strategy keeps changing—leading analysts to ask, Is it too late for a turnaround?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuck and Stressed: Health Costs of Traffic...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/21/upshot/stuck-and-stressed-the-health-costs-of-traffic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The physical and psychological toll of brutal commutes can be considerable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing confirms birth of gene-edited babies; Vows to punish scientist...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6614607/China-says-doctor-gene-edited-babies-acted-own.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators in China's Guangdong province concluded Dr He Jiankui organised and handled funding for the experiment without outside assistance in violation of national regulations, Xinhua said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden hometown concerned about 2020: Age, health, desire for new...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/news/joe-biden-trump-scranton-pa-20190118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Joe Biden considers another run for president, some in Scranton say they feel protective of their native son, expressing concern about the toll of another campaign. And, like many Democrats across the country, others are torn over their desire for new leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media video shows Venezuela sergeant demanding Maduro removal...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190121113753-f4r51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/ (URGENT):Social media video shows Venezuela sergeant demanding Maduro removal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Super blood Moon' eclipse stuns in remarkable pictures...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/super-blood-moon-eclipse-stuns-in-remarkable-pictures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers have been enjoying a rare ‘super blood Moon’ as the Earth’s natural satellite turned a stunning shade of red.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bible site where 'God met Moses' to be bulldozed for 'super city'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/754355/bible-news-christian-mount-sinai-saudi-arabia-neom-super-city-god-moses-ten-commandments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate builds over making Mueller report public...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/426054-debate-builds-over-making-mueller-report-public</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anticipation is building for special counsel Robert Mueller’s report, bringing to boil a debate over whether it will also be made public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil battling crime wave fueled by prison chaos...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/brazil-battling-crime-wave-fueled-prison-chaos-023050540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police and soldiers are being deployed in large numbers to Brazil's northeast to fight a wave of gang violence fueled by the overloaded, collapsing prison system. More than 400 elite federal troops have been sent to the city of Fortaleza and the rest of Ceara state to reinforce overwhelmed local</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In rare move, Israel confirms daylight air raid vs Iranian  targets...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ca4e04a7e1134cf7917608d39054be64</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — In an extraordinary statement, the Israeli military confirmed early Monday that it attacked Iranian military targets in Syria, hours after carrying out a rare daylight air raid near the Damascus International Airport. The statement was issued hours after Israeli missile defenses intercepted an incoming missile over the Golan Heights in the wake of the airport raid. "We have started striking Iranian Quds targets in Syrian territory," the military statement said. "We warn the Syrian Armed Forces against attempting to harm Israeli forces or territory."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem for Kamala: Can Prosecutor Win in Age of Black Lives Matter?</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/20/a-problem-for-kamala-harris-can-a-prosecutor-become-president-in-the-age-of-black-lives-matter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The regressive reality of what prosecutors do is proving difficult for the senator and likely presidential candidate to rationalize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady drops emotional F-bomb during live TV interview...</title>
      <link>https://ftw.usatoday.com/2019/01/tom-brady-cursing-f-bomb-live-tv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ftw.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Un-(expletive) believable, bro!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned-out billionaires taking extended multimillion-dollar 'sabbaticals' to recharge...</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/travel/themes/luxury/109786608/burnedout-billionaires-are-taking-extended-multimilliondollar-sabbaticals-to-recharge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It could be a couple of million dollars to take your family around the world with a teacher in tow."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrific case of animal cruelty as 21 dead horses found on abandoned lot...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/pets-animals/21-horses-and-a-dog-found-dead-on-southern-wake-county-property/5096730/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A horrific case of animal cruelty unfolded Friday in Wake County where 21 horses and one dog were found dead on an abandoned lot. Another dog, in bad shape, was found alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freshmen Dems balk at impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-impeachment-house-democrats-e38d068b-77a2-4438-b3b7-79961d779b9b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's been a cable news feeding frenzy over the "I" word</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 26 richest own same as poorest half of humanity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/jan/21/world-26-richest-people-own-as-much-as-poorest-50-per-cent-oxfam-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charity calls for 1% wealth tax, saying it would raise enough to educate every child not in school</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Seeks Victory in Chaos... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/20/us/donald-trump-leadership-style.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For people who have done business with the president, the protracted fight over the government shutdown reflects a time-tested playbook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers shiver through 16-hour ordeal on Canadian tarmac...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/newfoundland-labrador/united-179-goose-bay-1.4985858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A United Airlines plane diverted to Goose Bay Airport in Labrador Saturday night resulted in a lengthy stay on the tarmac for passengers stranded on the aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOS ANGELES TO SUPER BOWL</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001011973/article/rams-beats-saints-with-57yard-fg-to-advance-to-super-bowl-liii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greg Zuerlein's 57-yard field goal in overtime gave the Rams a 26-23 victory against the Saints in the NFC Championship Game on Sunday in New Orleans. Los Angeles will face the winner of Patriots-Chiefs in Super Bowl LIII.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap between rich and poor growing, fuelling global anger...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190120235327-1u1rq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVOS-MEETING/INEQUALITY (TV):Gap between rich and poor growing, fuelling global anger - Oxfam</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montreal Winter Fest Cancelled Due To Extreme Cold...</title>
      <link>http://www.climatedepot.com/2019/01/20/global-warming-update-montreals-fete-des-neiges-winter-snow-festival-cancelled-due-to-extreme-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GREEN BOOK' Wins Producers Guild Award; Becomes Oscars Frontrunner...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/green-book-wins-producers-guild-award-becomes-oscars-frontrunner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic on board jet as passengers 'suffocated and turned green'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8234795/dubai-plane-emergency-landing-cabin-poisoning-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN airliner was forced to make an emergency landing in Russia today after passengers began complaining they were “suffocating” and “turning green”. Panic swept through the cabin of the Ural Airline…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outside DC circus, shutdown havoc spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jan/20/government-shutdown-outside-washington-circus-havoc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government closure has pushed workers into hardship – and weakened the very immigration system it was meant to bolster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY:  So What If Trump Talked To Cohen About His Testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/giuliani-so-what-if-trump-talked-to-cohen-about-his-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's attorney said on Sunday that it's possible the president spoke with his former attorney Michael Cohen prior to Cohen's congressional testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Majority of world population support globalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/majority-of-world-population-supports-globalism-survey-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (BLOOMBERG) - Maybe populist political movements don't have as much support as often presumed.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From pariah to demi-god: Trans leader star at massive festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-religion-kumbh-transgender/from-pariah-to-demi-god-transgender-leader-a-star-at-massive-indian-festival-idUSKCN1PE04D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a desert tent guarded by armed police and a thick-set bouncer, Laxmi Narayan ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Beware the Furies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/19/opinion/sunday/trump-ocasio-cortez-dowd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What energized Democratic women really, really want: Trump out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCMANUS: Pelosi winning...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-mcmanus-column-pelosi-20190120-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the showdown Nancy Pelosi has been planning for, preparing for, even yearning for since President Trump was inaugurated two years ago. Trump is learning a lesson many others have learned the hard way: Pelosi may be a San Francisco progressive but there’s nothing soft about her in a fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF THE AGES!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/old-vs-young-qbs-ages-of-brady-vs-mahomes-and-brees-vs-goff-are-unique-for-conference-championships/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two future Hall-of-Famers in their 40s will square off against two of the game's young stars on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limos Versus Locals...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/davos-world-economic-forum-2019/it-s-limos-versus-locals-when-the-elite-gather-for-davos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jammed-up traffic is residentsâ€™ top complaint to mayor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davos Man Richer Than Ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/davos-world-economic-forum-2019/dimon-schwarzman-and-other-davos-a-listers-add-175-billion-in-10-years#gs.WMdjf5oF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worldâ€™s elite have prospered since the financial crash. Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCTIC BLAST FREEZES EAST COAST...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/national/news/2019-01-14-arctic-cold-midwest-northeast-south-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A big change is sweeping in right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocking beds and pillows that nudge when snore: Tech wants into bed...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/business/technology/14522280-74/rocking-beds-and-pillows-that-nudge-when-you-snore-tech-wants-into</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I've tried a mattress with water cooling and another that sways like a boat. I've worn brainwave-measuring helmets and rested on pillows that nudge you when you snore. In the hunt for better sleep, I've even snuggled up with a robot. For the gadget industry, sleep is the new exercise ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limits border wall to strategic locations?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/immigration/426192-trump-offers-to-limit-his-border-wall-to-strategic-locations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi would like more than Trump is offering, but his proposal is a reasonable compromise that warrants serious consideration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire damages C-SPAN, FOX, MSNBC studios in DC... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/426209-fire-damages-fox-c-span-studios</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire Sunday morning in Northwest Washington, D.C., damaged studios for Fox News, C-SPAN and MSNBC, and forced "Fox News Sunday" to relocate its broadcast to a local affiliate's studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DANGLES AMNESTY...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/426198-trump-defends-immigration-proposal-against-amnesty-criticism-from</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump early Sunday sought to sell his new immigration proposal, which includes funding for a wall along the southern border and extended protection for certain immigrant groups, amid pushback from Democrats and hard-line conser</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Special counsel needs to show cards now! </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/19/the-medias-gotcha-hysteria-is-shameful/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine that a scientist wanted to conduct an experiment to see if it’s true that blind hatred of President Trump has led Democrats and their media handmaidens to go ’round the bend and off the cli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Total lunar eclipse meets supermoon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae6d44cc5305425b86eed6b8a33339eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The celestial curtain will be rising soon on a lunar extravaganza. Sunday night, the Earth will slide directly between the moon and the sun, creating a total lunar eclipse. There won't be another until 2021. It will also be the year's first supermoon, when a full moon appears a little bigger and brighter thanks to its slightly closer position.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS REJECT ANY COMPROMISE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75cb070bc4414b778a13add8c13eb4a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's up with the partial government shutdown on Day 30: WHAT'S NEW President Donald Trump sought to break the government shutdown impasse Saturday, offering to extend protections for young people brought to the country illegally as children, if Democrats give him $5.7 billion for his long-promised border wall. But Democrats dismissed the offer as non-starter, calling on Trump to re-open the government first. Speaking from the White House, Trump said he was offering a "common-sense compromise both parties should embrace."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
