<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Teammate Says Tebow 'Wasn't Good', Rips JAGS For Signing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/former-nfl-teammate-says-tim-tebow-wasnt-good-as-te-says-tebow-joining-jaguars-would-be-stupid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tebow continues to face scrutiny as he awaits the Jaguars' decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese syringes getting stuck in patients' arms...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210520201457-9lz96</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-SYRINGES (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-FDA recommends not using syringes from Chinese firm after safety issues with vaccine injections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken does NOT want to buy Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210520183650-w9fyo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENLAND-USA/ (URGENT):Blinken confirms the U.S. does not want to buy Greenland after Trump proposal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall of the House of Gates?</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/society/gates-me-too-divorce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fully reckoning with Bill Gates means not just focusing on how he treats women—vital as that is—but also confronting our own deep-seated worship of wealth and hard-wired belief in hero narratives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Wants Miami Un-Woke, Pro-Bitcoin, Tech Billionaire's Paradise...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/2021/05/20/mayor-francis-suarez-wants-to-turn-miami-into-an-un-woke-pro-bitcoin-tech-billionaires-paradise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ignore the hype: Latin American immigration is (still) the city’s greatest strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance Giant Pays $40 Million in Ransom After Cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://www.swfinstitute.org/news/86466/cna-financial-pays-40-million-in-ransom-after-cyberattack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.swfinstitute.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promise and Perils of New Fertility Entrepreneurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/tech/annals-of-technology/the-promise-and-perils-of-the-new-fertility-entrepreneurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Startups are pushing a breezy but proactive attitude toward reproduction, centered on preëmptive treatments during one’s most fertile years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>43% of Millennials 'Don't Know, Care, or Believe God Exists'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2021/05/20/survey-43-millennials-dont-know-care-believe-god-exists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey from Arizona Christian University found Millennials are rejecting faith in God and looking to government to provide a better life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How dating apps became new drug of choice...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2021-5-15/where-love-goes-to-die</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing Personal, the latest book from The Bling Ring author Nancy Jo Sales, is all about dating apps. Jennifer Weiner, author of In Her Shoes, reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth gap in Tahoe town extreme...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/renotahoe/article/Incline-Village-Lake-Tahoe-Gene-Simmons-Wealth-Gap-16188867.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 10-minute drive from the California-Nevada state border, Incline Village is like the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA proposes global 15% corporate tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/us-proposes-global-minimum-corporate-tax-rate-of-15percent-with-an-eye-on-something-even-higher.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporations around the world should pay at least a 15% tax on their earnings, the Treasury Department said Thursday in its push for a global minimum levy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt database exploited by vaccine critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210520-us-government-database-exploited-by-covid-19-vaccine-critics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US government database exploited by Covid-19 vaccine critics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MD To Give Away $2M...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/05/20/governor-larry-hogan-announces-vaccine-lottery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maryland Governor Larry Hogan said the state health department has partnered with Maryland Lottery to bring $2 million in prize money for lucky vaccinated Marylanders. The grand prize is $400,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keys, Wallet, Pepper Spray: New Reality for Asian-Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/keys-wallet-pepper-spray-the-new-reality-for-asian-americans/ar-AAKbGd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last spring Annie Chen, who works in human resources, read about an Asian woman who had been punched in the face and yelled at by a stranger just a few blocks from where she lived in Midtown Manhattan. Five days later, Ms. Chen, 25, bought her first canister of pepper spray. She had been struck by the way the public perception of Asian-Americans had suddenly changed, she said, and simply wanted to protect herself. “I felt like if people had any...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ceasefire imminent...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/no-rocket-sirens-since-1-am-as-israel-hamas-ceasefire-said-to-be-close-668607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egyptian security source - whose country has been mediating between the sides - said they had agreed in principle to a mutual halt in hostilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY offers lottery scratch tickets for vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-taiwan-pandemics-coronavirus-vaccine-coronavirus-pandemic-20ce42c66cd77cdc1d557d956b9d7799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — People who get vaccinated at select state-run vaccination sites in New York next week will receive a lottery scratch ticket as the state tries to boost slowing vaccination rates. Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Logging 4,500 Steps A Day Will Add Years To Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/taking-more-steps-live-longer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find each additional 1,000 steps contributes to a 28 percent decrease in death among study participants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC new floating park a marvel...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/20/nycs-new-floating-park-little-island-is-a-marvel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers deserved a miracle after all we’ve been through. Little Island proves that one man’s vision can prevail against odds and that even after the darkest winter, spring will come again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY GIANTS Had Violent Culture Off Field, Lawsuit Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-20/n-y-giants-had-violent-culture-off-the-field-lawsuit-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Giants fostered a workplace rife with intimidation and physical violence, according to a lawsuit filed by the team’s former video director, who claims he was fired for complaining about an assault on another worker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish journalist wins legal battle against US activist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-donald-trump-europe-journalists-government-and-politics-9cb9a543a95d89b34f9a56ce8b8e6c69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — A Polish journalist who described a U.S. conservative activist as part of a global war against democracy by right-wing actors with indirect ties to Russia has won a years-long legal battle with the American.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazi Group Recruiting Again, Despite FBI Takedown...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx5n8x/neo-nazi-group-the-base-is-recruiting-again-despite-fbi-takedown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Base's founder, a former Homeland Security employee who is living in Russia, has retaken a leadership position after briefly leaving the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS EXPAND PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/feds-expand-cuomo-probe-will-look-at-whether-he-gave-family-priority-access-to-covid-testing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have reportedly expanded a probe of New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D) to look at allegations that he provided "priority access" to Covid-19 testing for "close associates" at the height of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid school reopenings may have led to thousands of cases, hundreds of deaths in TX...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/rapid-school-reopenings-led-thousands-covid-cases-hundreds/story?id=77778717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 43,000 people contracted COVID-19 and 800 died in Texas two months after reopening schools statewide, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX FIGHT:  Geraldo Throws Paper, Turns Back on Camera During Another Bongino Throwdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/stop-attacking-me-punk-geraldo-rivera-calls-out-dan-bongino-in-heated-segment-on-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geraldo Rivera continued to call out Israel and demand a ceasefire in a heated segment Wednesday night on Sean Hannity's program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Children of God' cult survivor recalls torture...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/children-god-cult-survivor-recalls-24150625</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharen Seitz, 33, of Boulder, Colorado in the US grew up inside the Children of God cult. She remembers being beaten and locked in a closet forced to memorise Bible passages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI dermatologist will diagnose 288 skin conditions in virtual appointments...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/dr-google-ai-dermatologist-diagnose-24151153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is allowing people to sign up to its outreach list which will update them on future research and early access programmes to the AI-powered dermatology assistant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's who in criminal probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9600829/Ex-Trump-Organization-exec-thinks-CFO-Allen-Weisselberg-flipped-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen Weisselberg, the longtime CFO of the Trump Organization and a key lieutenant of Donald Trump's, has turned on the former president, an ex-top executive predicted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS COMPLIANCE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/us-treasury-calls-for-stricter-cryptocurrency-compliance-with-irs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Treasury Department announced that it will require any transfer worth $10,000 or more to be reported to the IRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Drama Shaking Up NYT Styles Section...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-drama-shaking-up-the-new-york-times-styles-section</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under Choire Sicha, the section became a must-read. Why isn’t he still running it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women want 'ugly, rich men,' science says...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2920056/science-women-charm-men-looks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE confirms what we all knew ­­— women are turned on by charm and cash while men go on looks. In a discovery which surprises no one, a study found fellas value sexy bodies and attractive faces…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOULD BE KING GETS JABBED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2922001/prince-william-covid-vaccine-coronavirus-jab-over-35s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE William has shown off his guns as he received his Covid vaccine after catching the bug last year. The Duke of Cambridge, 38, shared a picture to Twitter today of himself receiving the jab as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS PLOT NEW RULES TO REIN IN CRYPTO</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/fintech/bitcoin-cryptocurrency-regulations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC, CFTC, IRS, FinCEN and Congress all want a piece of crypto oversight. The confusion has some in the industry calling for clearer regulations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Number of 401(k) and IRA millionaires hits record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/fidelity-number-of-401k-millionaires-hits-record-a-year-after-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although many Americans are still out of work and struggling, the recent stock market run up has buoyed retirement savings account balances to record levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking to boost profits, dentists push unnecessary procedures...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/looking-to-boost-profits-some-dentists-push-unnecessary-procedures/article_0a4b1523-1b9a-5a6f-be40-59140daf65be.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1993, Dr. David Silber, a dentist now practicing in Plano, Texas, was fired from the first dental clinic he worked for. He’d been assigned to a patient another dentist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER tries to curb offensive messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tinder-offensive-messages-75c8df0b-77e5-4454-8871-130081a7d6cc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tinder says it has reduced potentially disrespectful language by 10% in early testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does vaccine still protect you? Testing can't say for sure yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/how-long-do-vaccine-protections-last-science-can-t-say-for-sure/ar-AAKcfyL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protection from coronavirus vaccines is expected to wane, but no one knows when. It could be as soon as this fall for the first wave of people vaccinated last winter, and many predict that Covid boosters will soon join annual flu shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook Faces Judge With Stakes Beyond $142 Billion of Apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/apple-s-tim-cook-faces-judge-with-stakes-beyond-142-billion-of-apps/ar-AAKca1T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel shoots down armed Iranian drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-news/israel-shot-down-armed-iranian-drone-netanyahu-668658</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downing happened on sidelines of Gaza fighting. “I think that says everything about the real patron of terror in the Middle East and the world – Iran.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi defies Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/bibi-defies-biden-vows-more-strikes-101621477549394.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a 25-minute attack overnight, Israel bombarded targets including what its military said were tunnels in the southern Gaza Strip used by Hamas. Some 50 rockets were fired from the enclave, the Israeli military said, with sirens sounding in the coastal city of Ashdod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New name emerges in Gaetz investigation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/554508-new-name-emerges-in-gaetz-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scandal surrounding Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-Fla.) has now ensnared Joe Ellicot, a friend and former employee of a tax collector who has already pleaded guilty to an array of crimes associated with the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Circles of Friendship Churn, Evolve Over Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/05/robin-dunbar-explains-circles-friendship-dunbars-number/618931/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The evolutionary psychologist Robin Dunbar explains the limits on how many connections humans can maintain, and the trade-offs involved when you invest in a new relationship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quincy Jones Reflects on Career, Michael Jackson and Why He Wouldn't Work With Elvis...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/quincy-jones-michael-jackson-elvis-presley-1234955138/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a screening room in a Bel Air estate, the walls tell the story of American popular music: Framed Frank Sinatra albums hang alongside a 30-times-platinum “Thriller” certification and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt in possession of 'exotic material' from UFOs, ex-Pentagon officer claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/government-possession-exotic-material-ufos-24149071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luis Elizondo headed up the Pentagon's UFO programme before it was halted in 2012. He has since been at the forefront of UFO disclosure in the US and has played a key role in the release of footage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIDEAST TRUCE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/gaza-israel-middle-east-israel-palestinian-conflict-caac81bc36fe9be67ac2f7c27000c74b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Israel unleashed another wave of airstrikes across the Gaza Strip early Thursday, killing at least one Palestinian and wounding several, and Hamas fired more rockets, even as expectations rose that a cease-fire could be coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geraldo Throws Paper, Turns Back on Camera During Another Bongino Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/geraldo-rivera-throws-paper-turns-back-on-camera-during-another-dan-bongino-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of the on-air food fight, Hannity basically gave away the game. “Mediaite has their headline!” he crowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims new pandemic low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economist surveyed by Dow Jones had been expecting 452,000 new claims as the jobs picture continues to improve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Obama called Trump 'corrupt motherf---er,' 'sexist pig,' 'lunatic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/obama-called-trump-a-corrupt-motherf-er-a-racist-sexist-pig-and-a-f-ing-lunatic-book/ar-BB1gUSlq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the two have long clashed, the details of Obama's harsher language toward Trump have not been widely reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billy Porter Reveals Living With HIV for 14 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/billy-porter-hiv-positive-diagnosis-1234954742/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billy Porter takes a long deep breath.  “I have to start in 2007,” he says, having settled in across the table. He’s here, at Little Owl in the West Village, to get something off …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World needs 'new mindset for our survival', says Goodall...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210520-world-needs-new-mindset-for-our-survival-says-goodall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World needs 'new mindset for our survival', says Goodall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China on move...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/tensions-likely-to-grow-as-china-seeks-a-bigger-role-in-the-arctic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's ambitions to take a more significant role in the Arctic could lead to growing tensions, according to Oksana Antonenko of Control Risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese authorities order video denials by Uyghurs of abuses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-technology-f6ffda9288b1671da741c07d8f4f8afc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;URUMQI, China (AP) — China has highlighted an unlikely series of videos this year in which Uyghur men and women deny U.S. charges that Beijing is committing human rights violations against their ethnic group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Russia at odds over military activity in Arctic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arctic-russia-europe-environment-and-nature-government-and-politics-c97ac521407b897b70c72a62afee4f29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REYKJAVIK. Iceland (AP) — The Biden administration is leading a campaign against Russian attempts to assert authority over Arctic shipping and reintroduce a military dimension to discussions over international activity in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Drama Shaking Up NYT Styles Section...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/inside-drama-shaking-nyt-styles-002512513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by The Daily BeastChoire Sicha’s sudden departure as The New York Times’ Styles section editor shocked many at the paper. He left a job previously described by the Times leadership as “one of the most important features jobs in American journalism” for a newsletter position—a sign some took as a demotion.The move also took many by surprise, as some Styles employees only learned that it was Sicha’s last day on the team from a tweet posted by NBC News media reporter Dylan Byers. Six insiders at the publication suggested to The Daily Beast that Sicha’s transfer was the result of both masthead-level dissatisfaction with Sicha’s management style—including his handling of some of the paper’s higher-profile reporters—and a bit of discontent with the gig on the part of the now-former Styles editor himself. The friction is also part of the paper’s continued struggle to reconcile the buttoned-up impulses of its old guard and its newer, less traditional, digital-native staff.A spokesperson for The Times said in a statement: “You've heard a lot of false and misleading rumors. Choire is a superb journalist and a treasured colleague who has mentored journalists on the Styles desk and across the newsroom. We realized that newsletters offer us big opportunities and key to those ambitions is having expert newsroom leadership.“As our most senior leaders have made clear, there is no one better suited than Choire, an innovative thinker and a naturally entrepreneurial editor, to help build on our newsletter portfolio and showcase new voices in ways that meaningfully expand and evolve Times journalism.”NY Times Staffers Send ‘Outraged’ Letter to Bosses Demanding Reporter Apologize for Racial SlurSince taking the helm of the section in 2017, Sicha—a former Gawker editor and co-founder of The Awl—turned the Styles section into something weirder, more playful, and more engaged with how online life informs and defines cultural trends.Beyond its traditional focus on fashion, the section published lighthearted takes on how the pandemic has affected urban rat populations and the people who suspect they live in haunted houses; and expanded its coverage of the changing lives, ideas, and culture of young people in America. Sicha allowed his team broad freedom to pursue story ideas that may not have run under previous Styles editors; one Times staffer said it was rare to see him shoot down pitches. The open-mindedness and creativity paid dividends: The section was widely praised as one of the Times’ most innovative, playful, and fun.But multiple insiders who spoke with The Daily Beast said that, in recent months, some friction had grown between management and Sicha. To some senior editors, Sicha’s management style was viewed as what Times insiders described as, at best, “hands-off” and, at worst, “absentee”—a creative editor well-liked by his crew of writers, but seen as averse to the difficult conflicts or the intrapersonal headaches that may come with running one of the paper’s highest-profile sections.Others also said Sicha seemed out-of-step with Times leadership. Some masthead editors were irked, for example, when they saw Sicha’s signature on protest letters involving internal Times matters, including a note from staff critical of racist comments made by former reporter Donald McNeil Jr. during a 2019 Times-led student trip to Peru.Sicha declined to comment for this story but in an interview last year with Study Hall, he acknowledged that he had taken a fairly hands-off approach to the section, and much of the section’s success could be attributed to its rank-and-file staff.“[I]f your central question is ‘Gosh how does Choire Sicha make the Style section so magical?’ Then the answer is... I do not. It's not me doing any of it! I don't write the stories, I don't assign the stories, I don't design the stories, I don't take the photographs, I don't edit the stories. Man, I don't even do the INSTAGRAM stories,” he said. “And this can sometimes be really annoying or stressful for folks here! When things are a mess, I'll let them be a mess until someone decides to clean it up. It can be uncomfortable, or awful.”Some of those intra-management frustrations played out over Sicha’s approach to managing stars like Taylor Lorenz, a technology and internet culture reporter originally hired onto the Styles desk. After being poached from The Atlantic, Lorenz (a former Daily Beast staffer) has quickly become one of the most prominent reporters at the Times, breaking major stories on influencer culture, TikTok and other emerging social-media platforms, and prominent YouTube stars—earning wide acclaim in journalism circles as a creative and hardworking reporter.Bret Stephens Column on McNeil Scandal Didn’t Clear Editor’s ‘High Bar’ and He Freaked OutBut many of those stories were not for Styles. Over her tenure, she’s written more and more for Business and an array of other sections at the paper. The Times has rewarded her with a documentary project, as well as with an upcoming newsletter, both outside of Styles.Lorenz’s rising profile has also made her the target of many detractors. At one point, the star reporter had to apologize for misattributing a slur to prominent tech investor Marc Andreessen. Her coverage of the audio-based social platform Clubhouse prompted outrage among tech bros who took issue with their public conversations on the platform being reported. Earlier this year, Tucker Carlson and Glenn Greenwald repeatedly mocked a tweet she posted lamenting how persistent online harassment had “destroyed” her life, and criticized her reporting on teenagers who use various social platforms. It prompted the Times to release a statement labeling the Fox News far-right host’s broadsides against her to be “calculating and cruel.”Few Times staffers have a more active social-media presence than Lorenz, who has nearly a half-million followers on TikTok; she’s tweeted or retweeted more than 100 times on Tuesday and Wednesday alone, for example. And the Times has publicly struggled to develop and enforce social-media guidelines for its reporters that have been seen as both strict but fairly vague. The paper, for example, prohibits employees doing “anything else that undercuts The Times’s journalistic reputation.”Over the past year masthead editors have on occasion held internal discussions about how to respond to the wave of this persistent, heated, and often bad-faith attacks generated by Lorenz’s thousand-mile-an-hour social stream. Sicha, while technically her manager, was seen as too hands-off and too conflict averse to handle such a high-octane, highly-combustible situation. It was another sign that Sicha wasn’t perceived to be enough of a hands-on leader.Masthead editors made the case to Lorenz that by regularly engaging with her critics online, she was giving them ammunition and perpetuating the cycle of harassment. Deputy managing editor Carolyn Ryan suggested that Lorenz reach out to Pulitzer Prize-winning political reporter Maggie Haberman, a prominent Times female journalist with a large online following whose work often provoked the online wrath of political media figures like former president Donald Trump.“This did not happen,” Lorenz told The Daily Beast. “That literally did not happen.”New York Times’ Trump Tax Team Imploded When Star Reporter David Barstow Went RogueBut Lorenz did say she and Haberman had spoken on several occasions. According to three insiders, one of those conversations turned into a heated exchange that was later described as a “blow-up.” The pair allegedly argued about Lorenz's reporting on and signal-boosting of Kellyanne Conway’s teenage daughter Claudia’s social-media postings about her difficult family life, these people familiar with the matter said.“I don’t remember every single specific conversation but I have a great working relationship with Maggie and everyone else on the politics team,” Lorenz said. “It is so disappointing that people are trying to sow controversy and instigate acrimony when there is none. Maggie is amazing. She’s talented and I'm so lucky to be her colleague.”Following the conversation, Lorenz made a number of critical and disparaging remarks about Haberman in Times Slack chats, three people familiar with the matter said, including complaining about how the political reporter had treated her, and using the word “bitch” to underscore her frustration.Haberman declined to comment for this story, and Lorenz said she had never made disparaging comments about Haberman or any other colleague “in any sort of public Slack.”“People try to make me as the main character of every story about the New York Times,” Lorenz told The Daily Beast, saying she has recently questioned if she wants to have a public-facing role in journalism.NY Times Admits Newsroom Is ‘Difficult Environment’ for Staffers of ColorMeanwhile, the search for Sicha’s successor continues. Times insiders said the most likely replacement is Alexandra Jacobs, who has been acting as a sort of interim leader for the section since Sicha abruptly vacated the role. The New York Post reported that former Cut editor Stella Bugbee was in the running for the gig, but that Jacobs, a well-liked features editor who has been running the section in Sicha’s absence, is seen as having the fashion industry knowledge and editorial sensibilities necessary to take the helm of the culture, fashion, and lifestyle vertical. Dodai Stewart, the deputy editor for narrative projects at the paper and former editor-in-chief of the website Splinter, is also a potential candidate for the gig.But the process may give some observers a sense of déjà vu from the last Styles editor search, back in 2017: As Vanity Fair reported at the time, several of the candidates included Bugbee, who reportedly turned down the job, and Jacobs, as well as Times media editor Jim Windolf. The gig ultimately went to Sicha.—with additional reporting by Lloyd GroveRead more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothers Ride Oat Milk Boom to $448 Million Fortune...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/swedish-brothers-ride-oat-milk-090000849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It began with a group of scientists and a wild idea: That the byproduct remaining after making oat bran could be turned into non-dairy milk.That idea became the foundation of Oatly Group AB, the Swedish oat milk company that debuts Thursday in New York after raising $1.4 billion in an initial public offering.The share sale cements the fortunes of one of the scientists, Rickard Oste, and his brother Bjorn Oste, who co-founded the Malmo-based company. Their combined stake was worth $448 million after the shares priced at $17, according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index. Oatly is now valued at about $10 billion.“It’s a 20-year-old overnight success story,” Bjorn, who remains an Oatly board member, said last year in an interview with William Hood &amp; Co., a boutique investment bank.‘A Lunatic’Rickard, a professor of food chemistry, had for years focused some of his research on lactose intolerance and toyed with the idea of developing an oat-based milk substitute. By the mid-90s, he and a team at Sweden’s Lund University had developed a prototype. Bjorn, an engineer by training, joined his older brother’s venture in 1997 after selling a computer security company he’d built with friends from his high school and college days.His friends were skeptical of his career change, he said in the interview: “They all wrote me off as a lunatic.”In 2001, after the product had been released through various partnerships, the brothers launched Oatly as a separate brand. The company developed a small but devout following of consumers and grew slowly. It had less than 100 employees in 2015, according to a Lund University case study of the firm.Chief Executive Officer Toni Petersson, who was hired in 2012, helped develop the company’s cheeky branding and focus on environmental consciousness. Its products were first available in the U.S. in 2017 and can now be found in more than 20 countries.Blackstone StakeOatly’s largest shareholder -- a joint venture between Belgium-based investment firm Verlinvest SA and China Resources, a state-owned conglomerate -- will control roughly 48% of the company’s shares after the offering is completed, the prospectus shows. Blackstone Group Inc. owns a stake of about 7%.The company’s success was anything but certain, but that didn’t deter them, Bjorn said in the interview.“It was a cool thing and we like challenges,” he said. “We have a saying, my brother and I: ‘If it’s hard and difficult, that’s good. Then we’re going to do it.’”More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: New York AG's office opens CRIMINAL probe into Trump Org...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/manhattan/ny-trump-ag-james-nyc-manhattan-da-vance-criminal-probe-20210519-u3iuor4axrf3tadfvy6lgtunoe-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelation that Attorney General Letitia James has been investigating Trump criminally at least since March signals her probe is further along than initially thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN: HE WILL TURN ON OWN FAMILY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9598769/Michael-Cohen-claims-Trump-flip-FAMILY-Organization-faces-criminal-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen told MSNBC host Joy Reid on Wednesday he expects Donald Trump would turn on his family amid ongoing criminal investigations into the Trump Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: CRYPTO CRASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/bitcoin-btc-briefly-tops-40000-struggles-to-recover-from-sell-off.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin fluctuated between gains and losses Thursday, as the cryptocurrency struggled to recover from a major sell-off during the previous session.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIDEAST TRUCE FRIDAY?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210520095209-u02j5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 4-Renewed violence over Gaza despite ceasefire moves gaining speed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE HEAT ON THE DON...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/19/top-trump-executive-under-criminal-investigation-over-taxes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York attorney general’s office has been criminally investigating the chief financial officer of former President Donald J. Trump’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU: VISITS FOR VAXXED...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/eu-to-reopen-borders-to-those-with-accepted-vaccines/ar-BB1gU5Mf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only those with vaccines approved in the E.U. will be eligible, including Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO CRASH!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/19/bitcoin-btc-price-plunges-but-bottom-could-be-near-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negative news over the past week has dampened sentiment for bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bids for seat on Bezos rocket reach $2.8 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/blue-origin-auction-highest-bid-jeff-bezos-space-flight-2021-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The winner of the auction gets a seat on Blue Origin's New Shepard rocket for an 11-minute flight — the company's first space-tourism flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi rebuffs Biden call for rapid de-escalation...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/biden-told-netanyahu-he-wants-immediate-gaza-de-escalation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden Told Netanyahu He Wants Immediate Gaza ‘De-Escalation’</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
