<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Solar storms are back, threatening life as we know it on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/news/2021/05/solar-storms-are-back-threatening-life-on-earth-as-we-know-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While invisible and harmless to anyone on the Earth’s surface, the geomagnetic waves unleashed by solar storms can cripple power grids, jam radio communications, bathe airline crews in dangerous levels of radiation and knock critical satellites off kilter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agenda imperiled as priorities stall in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-big-agenda-is-imperiled-as-his-priorities-stall-in-congress-and-a-debt-fight-looms/ar-AAKh7Co?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are eager for legislative wins ahead of 2022 midterms, but progress has been elusive on immigration, infrastructure and policing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurovision defies virus with glittery return in Rotterdam...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/glittery-eurovision-final-lift-pandemic-025424653.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's back: the Eurovision Song Contest final got under way in a shower of glitter in Rotterdam on Saturday, returning after a year off with a kitschy message of hope in the time of coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat Eaters Hit Hardest as Inflation Sweeps Grocery Aisles...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meat-eaters-hit-hardest-inflation-183156184.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Inflation is landing in America’s refrigerators -- and it’s hitting meat-eaters most of all.About one in three U.S. adults say they’re spending more on groceries than they were at the start of 2021, according to a Morning Consult survey of 2,200 U.S. adults conducted May 17 to 19 for Bloomberg News. Red meat was the ingredient cited most often for its higher prices, with chicken right behind.Food inflation has been inching up for months, driven by soaring commodity costs, costlier transportation and challenges securing labor. Rising demand for meat, from home cooks as well as from the booming fast-food industry, has buoyed prices, too.“We’ve got these pockets of inflation without having corresponding wage growth, and that’s going to put consumers in a really tough spot,” Morning Consult economist John Leer said in an interview.To save money on their rising grocery bills, about a quarter of U.S. shoppers say they have started buying fewer items overall during the pandemic, including less meat.Rising grocery bills also appear to disproportionately impact shoppers of color. More than 40% of Hispanic and Black respondents reported higher grocery costs since the start of the year, while most White Americans reported no change in spending.Leer said that’s likely because minority communities have been hit harder by the pandemic, including job cuts, meaning those shoppers are more likely to swap restaurant spending for more economical grocery shopping, resulting in higher grocery bills but lower overall food costs. More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas defiant with military parade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hamas-israel-middle-east-health-coronavirus-pandemic-6ea82ef3966ccd0cee3dce815730d130</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Hundreds of masked Hamas fighters brandishing assault rifles paraded in Gaza City and the group’s top leader made his first public appearance on Saturday, in a defiant show of strength after the militants' 11-day war with Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES LOWEST IN YEAR</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-us-news-ap-top-news-mobile-6e9be8fced317be7c1b13d4ac37e5c92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New coronavirus cases across the United States have tumbled to rates not seen in more than 11 months, sparking optimism that vaccination campaigns are stemming both severe COVID-19 cases and the spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infections drop below 30,000 daily in continuing sign of recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2021/05/22/coronavirus-infections-drop-below-30000-daily-in-continuing-sign-of-recovery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts debate how to track the pandemic’s next stage, with the CDC criticized after it halts a count of ‘breakthrough infections’ in people with no symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indians turn to unlicensed clinics as virus spreads to countryside...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210522143050-gqwxx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science Says 'Weird Dreams' Actually Help Brain Understand Real Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/science-says-weird-dreams-actually-152445843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Dreams are there to keep you from becoming too fitted to the model of the world," a Tufts University researcher explains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Dylan at 80: In praise of mighty and unbowed singer-songwriter...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/may/22/bob-dylan-at-80-in-praise-of-a-mighty-and-unbowed-singer-songwriter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prolific, resilient and endlessly creative … as Dylan celebrates his 80th birthday, Edward Docx assesses his artistic contribution to the human story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene under fire for comparing mask policy to Holocaust...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/554894-greene-under-fire-for-comparing-mask-policy-to-the-holocaust-a-neurotic-lack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) is again finding herself at the center of controversy after she compared House Democrats’ mask policy to the Holocaust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon chief unable to talk to Chinese military leaders despite repeated attempts...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/pentagon-chief-unable-talk-chinese-military-leaders-despite-repeated-attempts-2021-05-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin has so far been unable to speak with China's top general despite multiple attempts to set up talks, U.S. defense officials said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Republican says Socrates would be canceled today. Philosopher faced different fate: Execution...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-florida-republican-says-socrates-would-be-canceled-today-the-philosopher-faced-a-different-fate-execution/ar-AAKgnVo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting canceled looked very different for the Greek philosopher, who was the subject of Florida state Rep. Anthony Sabatini's much maligned tweet on cancel culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidney from Jew killed in mob violence goes to Arab woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/22/middleeast/jewish-man-organ-donation-arab-woman-intl-cmd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Randa Aweis, 58, waited nine years for the organ donation that would change her life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W Virginia population drop largest in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/al-state-wire-west-virginia-lifestyle-census-2020-business-9b94594a74d6b7ab1bee153a425981d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — After her company told employees in 2017 to start working remotely, customer service representative Haley Miller decided to break from her lifelong home of West Virginia. The oceanfront beaches of St.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-Billion People Now Have Diabetes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/half-a-billion-people-diabetes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of diabetes cases have more than quadrupled since 1980, when there were around 108 million living with the condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cactus traffickers cleaning out deserts...</title>
      <link>https://www.deccanherald.com/science-and-environment/global-cactus-traffickers-are-cleaning-out-the-deserts-988258.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deccanherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrea Cattabriga has seen a lot of cactuses where they didn’t belong. But he’d never seen anything like Operation Atacama, a bust carried out last year in Italy. A cactus expert and president of the Association for Biodiversity and Conservation, Cattabriga often helps the police identify the odd specimen seized from tourists or intercepted in the post. This time, however, Cattabriga was confronted by a stunning display: more than 1,000 of some of the world’s rarest cactuses, valued at over $1.2 million on the black market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucille Ball's scandalous past of nude photos and casting couches...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/21/lucille-balls-scandalous-past-of-nude-photos-casting-couches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before she became America’s sweetheart, Lucille Ball’s path to stardom was filled with gangsters, nude photos and even turning tricks, according to a new book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0.03% chance: Infection after vaccinated incredibly rare in LA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/0-03-chance-getting-covid-151545902.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting COVID-19 after being vaccinated exceedingly rare in L.A. County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOOD FIGHT: Graydon Carter Dismisses 'Deranged Rant' Banning Him From Restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/graydon-carter-keith-mcnally-ban-restaurants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graydon Carter was banned from Keith McNally's restaurants, but dismissed the restaurateur's move as "deranged"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Martian rover takes first drive on Red Planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210522-china-s-martian-rover-takes-first-drive-on-red-planet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A remote-controlled Chinese motorised rover drove down the ramp of a landing capsule on Saturday and onto the surface of the Red Planet, making China the first nation to orbit, land and deploy a land…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk, Bezos rivalry intense. Now extending to moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/The-rivalry-between-Elon-Musk-and-Jeff-Bezos-16194259.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In a flyer distributed on Capitol Hill last week, Elon Musk's SpaceX warned...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar Storms Back, Threatening Life on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-22/solar-storms-are-back-threatening-life-as-we-know-it-on-earth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After absence, ticks back -- and  hungry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ticks-health-coronavirus-pandemic-7772abe5b6442a8aa99b7a709d56c865</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — A late-summer drought virtually eliminated ticks in parts of New England but they're back with a vengeance this spring. Dog ticks, which do not carry Lyme disease like deer ticks do, have been especially active since early spring in Maine, New Hampshire and Vermont.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-semitic violence explodes across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/us-seeing-wave-of-textbook-anti-semitism-amid-israel-gaza-tensions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From New York and California to Illinois and Utah, the recent conflict between Israel and Gaza has generated a disturbing backlash against American Jews – who have found themselves the targets of death threats, hate speech and violent physical attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal intrigue swirls over ex-exec Weisselberg...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/554762-legal-intrigue-swirls-over-ex-trump-exec-weisselberg-five-key-points</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s longtime chief financial officer Allen Weisselberg faces escalating legal jeopardy on multiple fronts over questionable financial activity linked to the former president and the Trump Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Russian Arctic, First Stirrings of Very Cold War...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/22/in-the-russian-arctic-the-first-stirrings-of-a-very-cold-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANZ JOSEF LAND, Russia — Chunky green trucks carry Bastion anti-ship missiles that can be prepared for launch in just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is South Florida casino in the works? ...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-gambling-session-trump-casino-20210521-es3n6yn6czaahhwu6ubooayskm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Legislature didn't approve a Trump casino, but the new gambling deal lawmakers just sent to Gov. Ron DeSantis makes one easier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most employers shy away from mandating vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/most-employers-shy-away-from-mandating-coronavirus-vaccines/ar-AAKeMAd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While scores of colleges and a handful of travel companies have made the shots compulsory, others hold back, fearing a backlash and lawsuits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's rich people could have saved local journalism. They refused...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/america-e2-80-99s-rich-people-could-have-saved-local-journalism-e2-80-94-and-perhaps-democracy-they-refused/ar-AAKfzGT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sale of the Tribune newspapers to the Alden hedge fund is a sign of trouble ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's sliding towards online irrelevance. His new blog isn't helping...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-is-sliding-towards-online-irrelevance-his-new-blog-isnt-helping/ar-AAKfval</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president’s aides said his new online empire would “redefine the game.” But his heavily promoted blog is seeing fewer visitors than the pet-adoption service Petfinder and the recipe site Delish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal govt puts out 'help wanted' notice as Biden seeks to undo cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-federal-government-puts-out-a-help-wanted-notice-as-biden-seeks-to-undo-trump-cuts/ar-AAKehUY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal bureaucracy, reeling under the effects of the former president, is struggling to make good on the current president’s promises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients develop massively enlarged tongues...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/local/covid-houston-doctor-patients-enlarged-tongues/285-5f6fd5ac-e1c0-48b2-a99c-dd41fc9e79fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors believe there might be something about the virus that is making certain people more prone to the rare condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein guards to skirt jail time in deal with prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-government-and-politics-3a0b465c080e1b0a53ce15315179d542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The two Bureau of Prisons workers tasked with guarding Jeffrey Epstein the night he killed himself in a New York jail have admitted they falsified records, but they will skirt any time behind bars under a deal with federal prosecutors, authorities said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former employees of famed pollster Luntz say work is 'scam'...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/05/21/former-employees-of-famed-gop-pollster-frank-luntz-say-his-work-is-a-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary Republican pollster claims to be "without bias"; former co-workers say that's "frankly bulls**t"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK GRILLED!</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/apple-epic-trial/tim-cook-apple-epic-grilled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gonzalez Rogers took nearly 10 minutes — the longest singular line of questioning she's put to a witness in the trial — to grill Cook about both the business model of the App Store and the very nature of its relationship with developers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bundy runs for ID governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article251599273.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bundy, who legally can’t enter the Idaho Capitol and was arrested again during the legislative session, enters a crowded field of Republicans vying for the executive seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz's ex-girlfriend to cooperate with feds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/21/politics/gaetz-investigators-cooperation-ex-girlfriend/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities investigating alleged sex trafficking by GOP Rep. Matt Gaetz have secured the cooperation of the congressman's ex-girlfriend, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHPOST Reporter Refuses to Discuss Family Ties to Slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.baconsrebellion.com/wp/shapiras-confederates-in-the-attic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baconsrebellion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside DISCOVERYAT&amp;T Deal: Cute Emails, Big Loan -- Now Media Giant...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/21/inside-the-discovery-att-deal-cute-emails-a-big-loan-and-now-a-media-giant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the predawn hours of April 1, David Zaslav, the chief executive of Discovery, arrived at a rented townhouse in</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
