<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Plans to colonize ASTEROIDS?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/710067/asteroid-nasa-cities-space-mining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Officials Rush to Support U.S. Envoy After Death Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-16/canadian-officials-rush-to-support-u-s-envoy-after-death-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Canadian officials, led by Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, rushed to express support for Ambassador Kelly Craft after a package containing a suspicious substance and a death threat was mailed to the U.S. diplomat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican to Host Conference on 'Xenophobia, and Politically Motivated Populism'...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/06/16/vatican-host-conference-migration-xenophobia-politically-motivated-populism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Council of Churches (WCC) has announced a joint venture with the Vatican to co-host a meeting next September on "migration, xenophobia, and politically motivated populism."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 killed after nightclub brawl in Caracas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/906d30f06bfa47d69433ed7865d697bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS,Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela's government says 17 people were killed Saturday after a nightclub brawl in the capital led to a stampede.        Interior Minister Nesto</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite cancer, McCain's maverick ways press on in tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/despite-cancer-mccains-maverick-ways-press-tweets-154857911--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain's legacy was thrust into focus nearly one year ago when he announced his brain cancer diagnosis. The six-term Senator and decorated Vietnam War veteran is now fighting the illness from his beloved Arizona, and filling the role of one of the few Congressional Republican voices to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's interior minister says 17 dead after nightclub brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuelas-interior-minister-says-17-dead-nightclub-brawl-160758668.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's interior minister says 17 dead after nightclub brawl .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL'S LAST WEEK?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/975166/Angela-Merkel-Germany-Bundestag-EU-migration-crisis-Kai-Whittaker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMAN Chancellor Angela Merkel could lose her powerful seat in the heart of Europe as soon as next week amid clashes within her coalition Government over EU migration policies, claimed German MP Kai Whittaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists and tech bring resilient Iceland back from the brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/16/iceland-tourists-tech-resilient-bank-from-brink-financial-crisis </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the country lets its banks go bust 10 years ago, there seemed to be no timetable for recovery. Things have changed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest stabbed in Bethlehem as religion shrinks in conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/974431/christian-persecution-christianity-bethlehem-palestine-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIEST in Bethlehem has been stabbed while protecting his congregation from thugs in the latest example of Christianity in Palestine coming under threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme body modification: Amputees risk DEATH by cutting off OWN limbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/703655/body-modification-mods-amputee-extreme-cutting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE: Break Up GOOGLE! Competitors banished into oblivion...</title>
      <link>https://apps.bostonglobe.com/opinion/graphics/2018/06/break-google/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apps.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case for ending Google's Internet domination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Deal Making Could Free CBS From VIACOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/why-media-deal-making-could-free-cbs-from-viacom-1529157600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viacom may have given up on CBS and now that media deals are in the air, CBS could get bought by another company, leaving Viacom all alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Saudi increasingly chummy; Big implications for OPEC, oil prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/16/russia-saudi-arabia-get-chummy-ahead-of-opec-may-affect-oil-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and Saudi Arabia reinforced their partnership as OPEC is set to grapple with some thorny issues, like declines of supply from Venezuela and the effect of renewed U.S. sanctions on Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast of U.S. Open  picks up rough sex talk...</title>
      <link>http://www.sportingnews.com/golf/news/fox-sports-us-open-2018-audio-rough-sex-shinnecock-hills-joe-buck-on-course-microphones-usga-headbutted/yc1ix2umw4b915c9d4jyfg4w5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sportingnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the network&amp;#39;s omnipresent on-course microphones at Shinnecock Hills gets the network in trouble; it eavesdrops on a private conversation that wasn&amp;#39;t suitable for even cable television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'd rather wake up next to severed horse head'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/15/gotti-flick-is-the-worst-mob-movie-of-all-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’d rather wake up next to a severed horse head than ever watch “Gotti” again. The worst movie of the year so far, the long-awaited biopic about the Gambino crime boss’ rise from made man to top do…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23-foot-long python swallows woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/7-meter-long-python-swallows-indonesian-woman-111050649.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7-meter-long (23-foot-long) python has swallowed a woman in central Indonesia, a village official said Saturday. The victim, 54-year-old Wa Tiba, went missing while checking her vegetable garden near her village on Muna island in Southeast Sulawesi province on Thursday evening, according to the village</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian supermarket giant says 'yes' to mass nude photograph...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/australian-supermarket-giant-says-yes-mass-nude-photograph-075347154--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 11,000 Australians who rushed for the chance to strip for American photographer Spencer Tunick will soon wear only smiles after a national supermarket chain changed its mind about allowing the shoot to go ahead on a suburban rooftop carpark. "We're over the moon," John Lotton</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Seeks Macron's Help as Asylum Crisis Threatens EU Unity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/16/merkel-seeks-macron-s-help-as-asylum-crisis-threatens-eu-unity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel Seeks Macron's Help as Asylum Crisis Threatens EU Unity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Over for Nevada's Legal Brothels? Possibility of Ban Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/is-the-party-over-for-nevadas-legal-brothels-possibility-of-a-ban-looms-1529146800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 20 Nevada brothels where prostitution remains legal face possible bans amid November ballot measures and increased scrutiny of working conditions in the #MeToo era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Ultrasonic Noise Make Sick? Devices Trigger Headaches, Dizziness...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/can-ultrasonic-noise-make-you-sick-1529147100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultrasonic signals from sensors and other devices are all around us and the health effects of their interactions aren’t clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great INTERVIEW Magazine Caper...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/the-great-interview-magazine-caper/17631047/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In November, Fabien Baron was trying to collect $498,000 in back pay for his work as editorial director of Interview. The magazine’s owner, Peter Brant, was in Kentucky buying a $2 million horse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine Used to Subdue Dozens at Request of Minneapolis Police...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/at-urging-of-police-hennepin-emts-subdued-dozens-with-powerful-sedative/485607381/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings of a draft report prompted the Minneapolis Police Department to tell officers that it's not their role to encourage sedation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover at Bilderberg: Reporter infiltrates secret society...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5850053/Undercover-worlds-elitist-secret-society.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in its 66-year history a journalist penetrated security to go undercover at the hotel where the secretive Bilberberg conference was held in Turin, Italy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hawaii it's 'raining' green crystals...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/06/14/hawaii-volcano-green-crystals-olivine/701389002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the never-ending parade of weird phenomena erupting from Hawaii's Kilauea volcano comes a "rain" of green crystals, which have been spotted on the ground after falling from the sky. "It is literally raining gems," tweeted meteorologist Erin Jordan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  National Guard soldiers sent to border are shoveling manure, changing flat tires...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/06/14/trump-ordered-troops-to-the-border-but-theyre-doing-busywork-218821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this ramshackle town, National Guard soldiers are doing everything from shoveling manure to changing tires. What they’re not doing: Watching the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hitler Of South Africa Tells White People, He Won't Kill Them -- Yet!</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-06-15/hitler-south-africa-tells-white-people-he-wont-kill-themyet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentine Peso Resumes Plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-15/dramatic-rebound-for-argentine-peso-as-caputo-takes-over-bank </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Argentine peso resumed its slide to a historic low as a major shakeup that put a former Wall Street trader at the helm of the nation’s central bank failed to curb the currency’s massive volatility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Three Californias' would give Dems more seats...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/392488-three-californias-plan-would-give-dems-more-seats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal to split the nation’s most populous state into three smaller states would give Democrats a huge boost in the perpetual battle for control of the United States Senate — likely dooming the plan even before voters have a chance t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM HOPE:  Tattooed, iron-pumping West Virginia candidate breaks mold...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/unconventional-west-virginia-candidate-heartens-democrats-162345055--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — Richard Ojeda is a retired Army paratrooper with combat medals, 26 tattoos and a 300-pound bench press — no ordinary candidate for Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another cash-strapped NYC cabbie commits suicide...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/15/another-cash-strapped-nyc-cabbie-commits-suicide/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another cash-strapped city cabbie has committed suicide — hanging himself in his Brooklyn apartment, multiple sources told The Post on Friday. Abdul Saleh is now at least the sixth financiall…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE?</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/392493-watergate-prosecutor-says-manafort-may-never-again-see-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Watergate prosecutor Nick Akerman said on Friday that Paul Manafort may never again “see the outside of a jail cell” after his house arrest arrangement was revoked on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCEAN'S 8 stars blame dominance of male critics for film's mixed reviews...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jun/15/oceans-8-dominance-men-film-reviews </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mindy Kaling and Cate Blanchett echo Brie Larson in calling for greater diversity among reviewers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup already beset by empty seats, and FIFA baffled...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/The-World-Cup-is-already-beset-by-empty-seats-12998062.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may have noticed something strange during Friday's World Cup match between Uruguay and Egypt at Ekaterinburg Arena in Russia: swaths of empty seats, helpfully visible to television viewers in bright orange. It must have come as an even bigger surprise to Russian World Cup officials, considering they added temporary seating that jutted outside of the arena in anticipation of big crowds for world soccer's quadrennial tournament. FIFA, meanwhile, is baffled. It estimates that there were 6,000 empty seats for the Uruguay-Egypt game. "We can confirm that 32,278 tickets have been allocated for the match between Egypt and Uruguay in Ekaterinburg," a FIFA spokesman told the Telegraph's Ben Rumsby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimps and orangutans could be completely extinct by the end of century...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6546359/chimps-and-orangutans-could-be-completely-extinct-by-the-end-of-the-century-scientists-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHIMPANZEES and orangutans are on the brink of extinction, a top scientist has warned. Brazil, Madagascar, Indonesia, and the Democratic Republic of Congo alone harbour two thirds of all primate sp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE signs Oprah...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/oprah-winfrey-inks-content-deal-apple-1120552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She will continue to serve as chairman and CEO of Discovery-backed cable network OWN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Agent: 'I'm Done Interviewing PRESIDENT... You Know, HRC'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/fbi-agent-who-questioned-hillary-email-probe-called-her-president-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Comey speaking at the White House, flanked by then-FBI Director Robert Mueller and President Barack Obama, on the day Obama announced he was nominating Comey to replace Mueller, June 21, 2013. (Screen Capture)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Inside Shelter for Illegal Alien Children Separated from Parents...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/california/2018/06/15/photos-inside-shelter-for-illegal-alien-children-separated-from-parents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shelter in El Cajon is a comfortable facility providing lodging, meals, clothing, medical care, education, and recreation to illegal alien children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fraud Charges Against THERANOS Elizabeth Holmes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-files-criminal-charges-against-theranoss-elizabeth-holmes-ramesh-balwani-1529096005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors filed criminal charges against Theranos founder Elizabeth Holmes and Ramesh Balwani, the blood-testing company’s former No. 2 executive, alleging that they defrauded investors out of hundreds of millions of dollars and defrauded doctors and patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCARTHY: Mueller Would Have Squeezed Clinton Tech To Roll Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2018/06/ig-report-fbi-no-bias-conclusion-may-not-supported/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But who knows? In dealing with the FBI, Clinton got kid gloves while Trump got scorched earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George P. Bush Says Don't Believe 'Liberal Media Fake News'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/texas-politics/2018/06/15/george-p-bush-greeted-boos-cries-remember-alamo-texas-gop-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO — Land Commissioner George P. Bush was met with cheers — and jeers — at the 2018 convention of the Republican Party of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter startup fastest company to reach $1B valuation...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1305719/electric-scooter-company-bird-is-the-fastest-startup-ever-to-become-a-unicorn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now the e-scooter company is zipping along to $2 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How legal drug companies helped revive heroin trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2018/06/15/how-legal-drug-companies-helped-revive-the-heroin-trade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heroin traffickers set up shop in the areas of the United States with the highest prevalence of prescription opioid addiction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketers stand to lose majority of e-mail lists as few Americans open privacy update notes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/15/gdpr-emails-going-unopened.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One email marketing company said some of their clients have lost up to 80 percent of their email lists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Stabbing followed hot sauce incident...</title>
      <link>http://www.seacoastonline.com/news/20180615/police-stabbing-followed-hot-sauce-assault-at-gilleys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seacoastonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTSMOUTH  A May 29 fight inside Gilley's PM Lunch, that led to a stabbing outside the Fleet Street eatery, began with a hot-sauce squirting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago strip club cancels Stormy shows because she wants more money...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-stormy-daniels-chicago-20180615-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels only had a one-night stand at the Admiral Theatre. The Chicago strip club owner pulled the plug after what he says is a dispute over money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozzy Osborne to serve 30 years in barber shop shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/montgomery/index.ssf/2018/06/al_man_named_ozzy_osborne_to_s.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scores Rare 0% on ROTTEN TOMATOES...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/john-travoltas-gotti-gets-zero-percent-rotten-tomatoes-score-1120603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the actor's third film to receive that dubious distinction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Strife Hits WASHPOST...</title>
      <link>https://www.futureofcapitalism.com/2018/06/washington-post-labor-strife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.futureofcapitalism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A union representing employees at the Washington Post is stepping up a public pressure campaign against the newspaper's owner, Jeff Bezos. There's also a petition the union says was signed by more than 400 employees that says in part: All we are asking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIMEWARNER unveils new name: WARNERMEDIA...</title>
      <link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/06/15/media/warnermedia-john-stankey-announcements/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Stankey, the new CEO of the company, announced the rebranding and a series of structural changes in an internal memo on Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT JAILED</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/judge-sends-trumps-former-campaign-chief-manafort-to-jail-idUSKBN1JB12X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. federal judge on Friday sent Paul Manafort to jail pending trial after he was charged with witness tampering, in the latest episode in a slow fall from grace of a man who was President Donald Trump's campaign chairman in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electromagnetic Wave Device Claims To Provide Equivalent Of 20,000 Sit-Ups...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/14/emsculpt-burns-fat-while-building-muscle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often people with stubborn fat pockets resort to liposuction, tummy tucks or some other fat-freezing and lasering techniques. Emsculpt may be the alternative many have been looking for.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
