<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SHOOTING AT CHURCH IN TEXAS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/12/29/2-dead-1-in-critical-condition-after-reported-shooting-at-church-in-white-settlement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a developing story and will be updated. Two people are dead and another is in critical condition after a shooting at a church in White Settlement,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANUKKAH HORROR</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2846e752d621824a9c2c75a89271c71e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONSEY, N.Y. (AP) — A knife-wielding man stormed into a rabbi's home and stabbed five people as they celebrated Hanukkah in an Orthodox Jewish community north of New York City, an ambush the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg's personal wealth rose by $27 billion this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10631458/facebook-chief-mark-zuckerbergs-personal-wealth-rose-27-3-billion-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK boss Mark Zuckerberg’s personal wealth rose by a mind-boggling $27.3 BILLION in 2019, says a report. The giant leap comes despite hostility from both users and lawmakers over the soc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans man has baby with sperm donated by trans woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/transgender-man-gives-birth-non-21177808</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Proud dad Reuben Sharpe has revealed how he gave birth to miracle baby Jamie with partner Jay in Britain’s most modern family - and even the couple's doctor was transgender</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete calls for decriminalization of all drugs...</title>
      <link>https://disrn.com/news/pete-buttigieg-calls-for-decriminalization-of-all-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 candidate Pete Buttigieg said in a Friday interview that he would decriminalize all drugs, not just marijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will American Jews finally get hint about dangers they face?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Diaspora/Will-American-Jews-finally-get-hint-about-dangers-they-face-analysis-612419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will this attack wake up American Jewry to the dangers they face so that all communities, even smaller and lower-profile ones, will finally get serious about security?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge triangular UFO captured gliding through sky on video above New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/huge-triangular-ufo-captured-gliding-21179400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strange object hung immobile above the clouds for several minutes, at one point ejecting a red 'orb'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DOMESTIC TERRORISM'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/mass-stabbing-at-jewish-synagogue-in-rockland-county-ny-reports/2251668/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say five people were stabbed at a rabbi’s home late Saturday night in Monsey, New York, the latest and most violent in a string of anti-Semitic attacks in the greater New York City area in the last few days. Ramapo Police Chief Brad Weidel said the suspected attacker entered the residence around 10 p.m. armed with a knife. Saturday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: USA will take action if NKorea tests missiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/US-monitoring-North-Korea-closely-finds-situation-concerning-612460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US companies forcing workers to train their own foreign replacements...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-att-outsourcing-h1b-visa-foreign-workers-1f26cd20-664a-4b5f-a2e3-361c8d2af502.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opponents of job outsourcing are making an appeal to Trump to stop the "knowledge transfer" practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass killings in USA hit record high...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/28/mass-killings-in-us-hit-record-high-in-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 210 people died this year in 41 mass slayings, making 2019 the deadliest year in massacres since at least the 1970s. The first incident happened on Jan. 19, when an Oregon man hacked his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA TO THE SUPREME COURT?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/28/biden-open-nominating-obama-supreme-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden told reporters on Saturday in Iowa he would nominate former President Barack Obama to the Supreme Court &amp;quot;if he’d take it.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin brothers found dead after 'joint suicide' named as TV stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10633932/twin-brothers-dead-kent-my-big-fat-gypsy-wedding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO brothers found dead in a suspected joint suicide have been named as stars of the hit reality show My Big Fat Gypsy Wedding. The 32 year olds – named locally as Billy and Joe Smith –…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER blames 'outage' after Trump whistleblower tweet temporarily disappears...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-retweets-deletes-post-naming-alleged-14936572.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) - President Donald Trump retweeted a post that included the alleged name of the anonymous whistleblower whose complaint ultimately led to Trump's impeachment by the House.  Just before midnight Friday, Trump retweeted a message from Twitter user @Surfermom77, an account that claims to be a woman named Sophia who lives in California. The account shows some indications of automation, including an unusually high amount of activity and profile pictures featuring stock images from the internet.  By Saturday morning, the post seemed to have disappeared on many users' feeds, suggesting Trump had deleted it, though it could still be found in other ways, including on a website that logs every presidential tweet.  The retweet then reappeared Saturday night. Twitter told The Associated Press that an outage with one of its systems caused tweets on some accounts, including Trump's, to be visible to some but not others.  Trump has repeatedly backed efforts to unmask the whistleblower. But his Friday night retweet marks the first time he has directly sent the alleged name into the Twitter feed of his 68 million followers.  Unmasking the whistleblower, who works in the intelligence field, could violate federal protection laws that have historically been supported by both parties.  The whistleblower filed a complaint in August about one of Trump's telephone conversations with Ukraine's President Volodymyr Zelenskiy and other dealings with the Eastern European nation. The complaint prompted House Democrats to launch a probe that ended with Trump's impeachment earlier this month. The matter now heads to the Senate, where the Republican majority is expected to acquit the president.  The central points from the whistleblower's complaint were confirmed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates propose trillion$ in spending amid debate over what's doable...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/we-have-the-resources-democratic-presidential-candidates-propose-trillions-in-spending-amid-debate-over-whats-doable/ar-BBYqrTE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHPOST: VA Gov 'Back from the Dead' After Blackface Scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/28/washington-post-pronounces-va-gov-ralph-northam-back-from-the-dead-after-blackface-infanticide-scandals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post editorial board pronounced Friday that Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam has miraculously come “back from the political dead.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN: He should comply!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/476145-warren-if-theres-a-lawful-order-for-a-subpoena-i-assume-biden-would-comply</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) said Saturday that former Vice President Joe Biden should comply with any lawfully-issued Senate subpoena after Biden suggested he would not comply with one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC bail reform setting suspects free after string of anti-Semitic attacks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/28/suspects-released-without-bail-after-shocking-attacks-on-jews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suspects arrested in last week’s spree of eight anti-Semitic attacks are being quickly released right back into the neighborhoods they terrorized thanks to “bail reform” legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Rikers inmates use city-funded debit cards to buy booze...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/28/ex-rikers-inmates-use-city-funded-debit-cards-to-buy-booze-juul-pods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-inmates have been flooding area booze shops, ever since the recent launch of a soft-on-crime city initiative that provides them with two $25 gift cards, merchants said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERN FAMILY: Trans man gives birth to baby with sperm donated by trans woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10634350/transgender-man-gives-birth-sperm-donor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TRANSGENDER man has given birth to his non-binary partner’s baby using sperm donated by a transgender woman. Reuben Sharpe, 39, transitioned to a man 12 years ago, but stopped taking testos…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece had long banned cremation. Then it began running out of room for bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-12-29/greece-had-long-banned-cremation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece’s first crematorium began operating in October following decades of opposition by the country’s powerful Orthodox Church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANUKKAH HORROR</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7833919/Multiple-stab-victims-reported-synagogue-upstate-New-York.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video circulated on Twitter showed emergency vehicles and ambulances hurriedly evacuating victims from a home on Forshay Road in Monsey, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left presses 2020 Dems to retake the courts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/475577-left-presses-2020-dems-to-retake-the-courts-from-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential contenders are facing increasing pressure to detail their plans for filling federal court vacancies amid angst over President Trump's success in packing the benches with conservative judges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vets alarmed by rise of dog heart problems linked to grain-free food... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/it-s-not-going-away-vets-still-seeing-cases-dog-n1107791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exotic ingredients and boutique brands may also be linked to the health issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nothing Less Than Civil War': These Voters See Doom Without Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/nothing-less-than-a-civil-war-these-white-voters-on-the-far-right-see-doom-without-trump/ar-BBYqb3O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Film Studio Ready To Stand Tall Against PC Scolds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/toto-indie-film-studio-rebeller-media-ready-to-stand-tall-against-pc-scolds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The word “brave” gets tossed around too easily in Hollywood. It might apply to stars tackling issues the entire industry supports, like removing President Donald Trump from office. It also refers to actors who obscure their beauty for Oscar-bait roles. Want true Hollywood bravery? Try making a movie about a teen who not only survives [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden leaves it unclear if he would honor Senate subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/28/biden-leaves-it-unclear-if-he-would-honor-senate-subpoena.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day earlier, the Democratic presidential contender told The Des Moines Register he stood by his position that he would defy the Republican-controlled Senate if it ordered him to be a witness in the proceedings. He later tried to clarify on Twitter but did not make it clear what he would do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man, 60, dies after beating in $1 Christmas Eve mugging...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5a20bcce32309e09bcc9d499acdd414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A 60-year-old man who was kicked and punched while defending his partner during a $1 mugging on Christmas Eve has died. Juan Fresnada died Friday afternoon at the Bronx...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Construction workers 'lose' sensitive docs during renovations at UK spy HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/27/uk/mi6-headquarters-sensitive-documents-renovations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source on background has confirmed to CNN that sensitive documents that had been reported missing by The Sun newspaper were not UK government papers, but were a construction firm's documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACHETE WIELDING MAN ATTACKS NY HANUKKAH PARTY</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/12/28/stabbing-monsey-synagogue-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS2’s Tony Aiello has confirmed a man entered Rabbi Rottenburg's Shul in Monsey and stabbed three people Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
