<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rise of sad rap: How hip-hop got blues...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/mar/17/rap-music-mental-health-issues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hip-hop artists have been articulating depression and social angst for decades. Today their commentary is more relevant than ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>88 Pounds of Plastic Found in Dead Whale...</title>
      <link>https://www.nst.com.my/world/2019/03/470524/dead-whale-philippines-had-40-kg-plastic-stomach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nst.com.my&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA: A starving whale with 40 kilos (88 pounds) of plastic trash in its stomach has died after being washed ashore in the Philippines, activists said Monday, calling it one of the worst cases of poisoning they have seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge meteor explodes over Earth with 10 times energy of atomic bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/huge-meteor-explodes-over-earth-14152245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meteor explosion occurred in December, but went largely unnoticed because it blew up over the Bering Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing life of couple living with lions...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/amazing-life-british-couple-living-14130623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The couple, aged 70 and 66, who host new nature show Big Cat Tales, have been documenting the lives of lions, tigers and cheetahs for the past 40 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun owners in New Zealand brace for big changes to their right to carry...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Gun-owners-in-New-Zealand-brace-for-big-changes-13696268.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand - Some rushed to their trusted online dealers and stores to stock up on semiautomatic assault rifles. Others unlocked their secure cabinets, picked up their firearms and turned them into police stations, no questions asked.  The estimated quarter of a million gun owners across this largely quiet, peaceful South Pacific country, many of them dedicated hunters, are bracing for what are likely to be significant reforms to New Zealand's firearm laws. Leaders have hinted the changes will impact the proliferation and availability of semiautomatic weapons in particular.  The changes, agreed to in principle by the country's coalition government Monday - just 72 hours after the deadliest act of gun violence in New Zealand history - put the country in line with others that have taken swift action following tragedy within their borders. Details of the changes will be announced within the week, and must be passed by parliament.  A gunman who pledged allegiance to white nationalist causes killed 50 people at two mosques in Christchurch on Friday, and has been remanded on one charge of murder with more to follow. He has been identified by police as 28-year old Australian Brenton Tarrant who in one day killed more than all the people murdered across New Zealand in 2017.  Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern labeled the massacre "the worst act of terrorism on our shores" and immediately promised swift action, calling for gun laws to be changed. Her declarations have been celebrated by many in New Zealand, some of whom had no idea that military-style semiautomatic weapons were so prolific in a country famously known for its extremely low murder rate.  On Monday, the e-commerce website Trade Me, similar to eBay, halted the sale of semiautomatic weapons on its platform.  "We've had a lot of contact from Kiwis over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Sanders most powerful woman not running?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bb512b6ff6174474bf7ae3ccfbead19b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Before Bernie Sanders took the stage to formally launch his 2020 presidential campaign this month, the candidate's most influential adviser took the mic. To cheers, Jane Sanders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhunt after shooting on Dutch tram wounds many... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/33892f990908436fa43371e302ff6098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — A shooting on a tram in the central Dutch city of Utrecht on Monday left "multiple" people wounded, police said, adding that they are considering the possibility of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne husband suggests Trump has narcissistic personality disorder...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/434485-conways-husband-suggests-trump-has-narcissistic-personality-disorder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, White House counselor Kellyanne Conway’s husband and a frequent critic of President Trump, on Monday suggested that the president has at least two diagnosable personality disorders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Seeks Trump Bump as He Brings Re-Election Bid to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/netanyahu-seeks-trump-bump-as-he-brings-re-election-bid-to-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu travels to Washington next week with a corruption scandal hanging over his bid for re-election on April 9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PET SEMATARY' premier leaves fans, critics terrified...</title>
      <link>https://uk.movies.yahoo.com/pet-sematary-premier-leaves-fans-critics-terrified-150122488.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen King adaptation hits all the right spots for those who watched it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Cape with 'world's cleanest air' offers smog respite...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/remote-cape-worlds-cleanest-air-offers-smog-respite-043050297.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As much of Asia wheezes, coughs and sniffles its way through another smog season, one isolated and windswept corner of Australia is serving as the global standard for clean air. With panoramic views of swaying tussock grass and the vast crystalline expanse of the Southern Ocean, Tasmania's beautiful</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Mueller Subpoena Fight Gets Supreme Court Look This Week...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mystery-mueller-subpoena-fight-gets-080000432.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dispute became a source of intrigue in part because a federal appeals court in Washington closed an entire floor of the courthouse to the public while the case was being argued on Dec. 7. The company has refused to comply with the July 2018 subpoena, and a judge has imposed sanctions that now total</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebron new low...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/26291432/lebron-blocked-late-cap-career-worst-quarter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst shooting quarter of LeBron James' career ended with the Lakers star getting blocked with seconds remaining in a road loss to the Knicks on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with distributing live stream of mosque shooting denied bail...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190318055420-hji6v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWZEALAND-SHOOTOUT/COURT:Man charged with distributing live stream of mass shooting denied bail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Scrutinize Development of BOEING 737 MAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/faas-737-max-approval-is-probed-11552868400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors and Department of Transportation officials are scrutinizing the development of Boeing Co.’s 737 MAX jetliners, according to people familiar with the matter, unusual inquiries that come amid probes of regulators’ safety approvals of the new plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigators find 'similarities' between crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/17/africa/ethiopian-lion-air-crash-data-similarities-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary data recovered from the black boxes of last week's Ethiopian Airlines crash has revealed "similarities" to October's fatal Lion Air crash, the Ethiopian Minister of Transport said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Disneyland-size crowds' create super bloom safety crisis... </title>
      <link>https://www.pe.com/2019/03/16/disneyland-sized-crowds-creating-crisis-at-poppy-bloom-lake-elsinore-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor says an employee was struck by a vehicle and a visitor was bitten by a rattlesnake Saturday. Officials urge visitors to reschedule their trips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force base underwater...</title>
      <link>https://www.omaha.com/news/military/one-third-of-offutt-underwater-at-least-buildings-damaged-in/article_631f9b34-5271-50e8-b5eb-19f488daaf32.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The damage is also far more widespread than the base suffered during massive flooding along the Missouri River in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California awash in cannabis cash. Being used to bribe public officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/california-is-awash-in-cannabis-cash-which-some-use-to/article_61a84648-0490-53ff-a3d5-d620b0af06bb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Sheriff Jon Lopey was startled when a stranger offered him $1 million if he would keep deputies away from certain illegal cannabis farms in Siskiyou County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denies...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190318-us-denies-report-it-leaving-1000-troops-syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US denies report it is leaving up to 1,000 troops in Syria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Woman not wearing shoes' sparks blood-splattering fight on flight...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/fight-breaks-out-between-two-men-on-ryanair-flight-from-glasgow-to-tenerife-11668873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement following Saturday's altercation, Ryanair said: "We will not tolerate unruly or disruptive behaviour at any time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Preparing to Leave 1,000 Troops in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-military-now-preparing-to-leave-as-many-as-1-000-troops-in-syria-11552853378</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The policy shift comes three months after President Trump ordered a complete withdrawal and is far more than the White House originally intended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds make biggest agriculture seizure in history: 1 million lbs. of pork...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/news/2019/03/feds-seize-1-million-lbs-of-pork-smuggled-from-china-to-nj-port-amid-african-swine-fever-outbreak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pork products filled 50 shipping containers and marked the largest agricultural seizure in the U.S. when it was discovered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Double jeopardy? Manafort may have way to toss N.Y. indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/manafort-s-defense-team-has-option-try-double-jeopardy-clause-n984061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: Trump's former campaign chairman may be relying on the president to issue a pardon. If he is, he should refocus his energy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Rudy's vanishing act...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rudy-giuliani-cable-television-mueller-report-d961eecc-271b-488c-bdb3-3c1c459e9027.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Trump and White House lawyer Emmet Flood have privately griped about some of Giuliani's TV appearances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 people in audience for De Blasio in NH...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/17/de-blasio-speaks-to-crowd-of-only-20-people-in-new-hampshire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, NH — Mayor de Blasio’s ongoing tease of a presidential run didn’t exactly pull in the crowds during a campaign-esque event in the Granite State. Only 20 people showed up Sunday to hear the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first remote brain surgery performed...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/454056-remote-brain-surgery-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese surgeon has performed the world’s first remote brain surgery using 5G technology, with the patient 3,000km away from the operating doctor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign national arrested after attempt to tour Ft. Bragg 'special ops facility'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fayobserver.com/news/20190314/foreign-national-allegedly-repeated-requests-to-tour-bragg-special-operations-facility</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fayobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nouran Ahmad Shihab Sueidan remains detained</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia teen stabbed 100 times, set on fire in MS-13 murder...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2019/03/5-charged-in-ms-13-related-slaying-of-va-teen-who-was-stabbed-100-times-burned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people, including two teens, have been arrested in the slaying of a Virginia teen who was stabbed 100 times before his body was dumped in a remote area of Stafford County, Virginia, and set on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rupert Murdoch begins Hollywood goodbye...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/united-states-canada/article/3002086/rupert-murdoch-begins-his-hollywood-goodbye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murdoch family will create new entity known as Fox after the breaking up of 21st Century Fox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches open doors to businesses in order to survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/churches-are-opening-their-doors-to-businesses-in-order-to-survive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday looks very different from Monday at White Rock United Methodist Church in Dallas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's iPhone 11 may have folding screen, triple camera and FART sensor...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8647084/iphone-11-features-foldable-screen-triple-camera-fart-sensor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE is keeping its rumoured iPhone 11 under tight wraps – but we can still guess at the fancy features it might boast. We’ve tracked down some of the wackiest features that could make it in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth to six babies in nine minutes defying one in 4.7 billion odds...	</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8656992/mum-gives-birth-6-babies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MUM gave birth to six babies  — two sets of twin boys and one lot of twin girls — in just nine minutes. Defying remarkable odds of one in 4.7billion, Thelma Chiaka delivered her sextuplets betwee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter, 74, among 'elite' wildlife killers after shooting dead 500 animals for fun...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8656852/brit-kills-wildlife-shooting-animals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 74-YEAR-OLD Brit has been exposed as an “elite” wildlife killer who has shot dead hundreds of animals worldwide for fun. Pensioner Malcolm King has been named as one of the world̵…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest 'ultimatum' rally in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests/violence-returns-as-frances-yellow-vest-protests-enter-fourth-month-idUSKCN1QX0B1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rioters set fire to a bank and ransacked stores on Paris's Champs Elysees a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading geneticists propose moratorium on genome editing... </title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-019-00726-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nature.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Lander, Françoise Baylis, Feng Zhang, Emmanuelle Charpentier, Paul Berg and specialists from seven countries call for an international governance framework.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: High-performing robots demoralize human co-workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-what-robots-destroy-when-they-compete-with-humans-2019-03-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has something to say about the toll of workplace automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5 million videos of attack removed by FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190317-new-zealand-mosque-attack-videos-facebook-ardern</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook said it removed 1.5 million videos globally of the Christchurch mosque attack in New Zealand in the first 24 hours after the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was called 1,800 times: When robots collect bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/16/robocalls-about-your-bills-can-pour-in-every-day-all-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A quarter of consumers receive calls each month about a debt they owe. For some people, the calls are relentless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Still Released into USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/13/ice-union-thousands-of-illegal-aliens-are-being-released-into-u-s-with-catch-and-release-in-overdrive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) union says agents are being overwhelmed by unchecked illegal immigration to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAFFTASTIC DAY!</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/beto-orourkes-gafftastic-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not ready for prime time?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Sports: Interactive, Immersive, Intense...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-future-of-sports-is-interactive-immersive-and-intense-11552827600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you’re watching March Madness, the Super Bowl or ultimate frisbee, it will soon be more interactive, more immersive—and a lot more like sitting courtside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80-year-old driver jumps out of moving car...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/bayarea/article/Elderly-Driver-Suffers-Minor-Injuries-Jumping-13694761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH SAN FRANCISCO (BCN)  An 80-year-old driver was injured Saturday night when he jumped out of his car as it rolled south on Interstate Highway 280 at the Westborough Boulevard offramp, the California Highway Patrol said.  The CHP got a call about 6:30 p.m. Saturday of a man driving on the freeway opening his driver's door and diving out of the car, CHP Officer Bert Diaz said. The elderly driver tumbled several times before coming to rest against the freeway's center divider.  The man's now-driverless car also hit the divider, and then veered back across all traffic lanes before coming to a stop on the right shoulder, Diaz said. The car didn't hit any other vehicles, Diaz said, but a minor non-injury crash resulted when a car swerving to avoid the driverless vehicle struck another car.  The elderly man suffered a cut on the head and was taken to Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital for treatment of his injury and a psychological examination.  "There was no statement, and no reason given as to why this happened," said Diaz, adding that this whole incident could have turned out far worse for the 80-year-old man and perhaps others.    Copyright © 2019 by Bay City News, Inc. Republication, Rebroadcast or any other Reuse without the express written consent of Bay City News, Inc. is prohibited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters give Kamala break on 'problematic comments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Voters-give-Harris-a-break-on-problematic-13694327.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. GEORGE, S.C. - Before Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., stepped out of her white minivan, no presidential candidate had ever visited St. George, at least as far as any local officials could remember. But the shadow of the ever-growing Democratic field fell on Harris even here, when a young voter named Essence Williams asked her about fellow Democratic candidate Andrew Yang's proposal to give $1,000 of basic income to every American ages 18 to 64.  "Do you think this program is feasible in our economic climate?" Williams asked. "And is it possible to increase the standard of living for low-income families?"  "I haven't analyzed that policy," Harris said, pivoting instead to discussions of how she hopes to reduce student loan debt and "uplift" young people.  After Harris finished, Williams said she "absolutely" still had questions about where Harris stood, even as she was grateful for the senator's candor.  "It's all about trust," she said. "I'd rather she be honest with me [like that] and tell me she hasn't looked into it."  In the first weeks of Harris' campaign, the 54-year-old has fielded criticism for equivocal and imprecise answers to questions about her stances on specific policies and her record as a prosecutor.  The language contrasts with the message Harris hammers to receptive crowds at every stop: defining herself as the candidate speaking truth and confronting the uncomfortable conversations the country needs to have. But there is little indication that the approach has cut into her popularity, and she is not shying away from further controversy.  In an interview with MSNBC on Thursday, Harris said it was "outrageous" that Vice President Mike Pence will not have one-on-one meetings with women - a critique that exaggerated a long-ago Pence comment that he does not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California awash in cannabis cash. Some used for bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-pol-ca-pot-corruption-20190317-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the two years since California voters decided to allow the restricted sale of recreational marijuana, the state has seen a rash of government corruption cases. Some in the cannabis black market are trying to game the system with the use of bribery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete says he's hit significant 65,000 donor mark...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/news/politics/2019/03/16/south-bend-indiana-mayor-pete-buttigieg-donors-dnc-debate/3184796002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mark would qualify Buttigieg to be invited to the first Democratic National Committee debate in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing movement calls on media to avoid naming shooters...</title>
      <link>https://www.daytondailynews.com/news/national/growing-movement-calls-media-avoid-naming-shooters/Z3fTVGAR8eFyUHLIIVUjhI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.daytondailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few months after teen shooters killed 12 classmates at Columbine High School, Coni Sanders was sta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video captures dozens of illegals cutting way through hole in fence...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6815035/Video-shows-dozens-migrants-crossing-California.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident, which led to the capture of 52 people, was caught on camera at California's Border Field State Park, on the border between San Diego and Tijuana, Thursday at about 4pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax refund fraud: IRS crackdown ensnares legitimate taxpayers...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/03/16/tax-refund-fraud-irs-crackdown-may-ensnare-legit-taxpayers/3166441002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the IRS efforts to reduce tax refund fraud have been successful, legitimate taxpayers have been caught up in the process, delaying refunds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES: Just another pretty face?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-beto-orourke-democrats-20190316-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most striking thing about Beto O'Rourke is that he’s so hard to pin down. He spent six years as a congressman from El Paso but has few detailed positions on issues. Instead, he mostly deploys sunny attitudes. He’s a lanky, buzzy Rorschach test: Democrats can project on him any view they like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy vet gets 10 year prison sentence for insulting Iran 'supreme leader'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/u-s-navy-vet-detained-in-iran-sentenced-to-10-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Navy veteran first detained in Iran while visiting a girlfriend was sentenced to 10 years in prison on charges of insulting the country’s supreme leader and posting a photograph on social media, his lawyer said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President threatens 'SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE' with federal investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6819181/Trump-threatens-Saturday-Night-Live-federal-investigation-Sunday-morning-tweet-storm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump began his Sunday morning venting about 'Saturday Night Live,' complaining the show should be investigated by federal regulators for mocking him but not Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iditarod dog dies after finishing race...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/outdoors-adventure/iditarod/2019/03/17/iditarod-dog-dies-two-days-after-finishing-the-race-to-nome/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oshi, a 5-year-old female, crossed the finish line with rookie musher Richie Beattie on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS CASINO SHOOTOUT:  Attempted robbery at BELLAGIO ends in gunfight...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/alleged-robber-bellagio-casino-trades-gunfire-police-las/story?id=61727817</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was shot by police and died a few hours later.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
