<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Accused of Watching INSTAGRAM Users Through Cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/facebook-accused-of-watching-instagram-users-through-cameras/ar-BB199T81?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEFS Announce Fan Infected With Covid Attended Opening Game; Other Fans Told To Quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/ten-nfl-fans-told-to-quarantine-after-coming-into-contact-with-infected-fan-at-texans-chiefs-opener/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NFL fan tested positive for COVID-19 after attending the Chiefs' opener</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Storm Landfalls This Year Are One Shy of 1916 Record...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-u-storm-landfalls-one-170754398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Hurricane Sally’s historic flooding of Florida and Alabama this week marked the eighth named storm to strike the continental U.S. this year, leaving the tally just one short of a record that dates back more than a century.With 10 weeks left in the Atlantic storm season, there’s a good</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBATE PREVIEW</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/joe-biden-cnn-town-hall-review-donald-trump-coronavirus-anderson-cooper-1234579013/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Joe Biden had to do to claim ground against Donald Trump in tonight’s CNN town hall was show up and show he cared. And that’s exactly what the former Vice-President did from the very start of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of infected doubling every week in England!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1492407/scientists-two-week-national-lockdown-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS advising the Government want a two-week national lockdown next month to battle the surge in coronavirus, it is reported. Experts suggested an October lockdown during half term before the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President contradicts health advisers on vaccine timetable...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-contradicts-health-advisers-on-vaccine-15576519.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's public rebuke of a top federal health official who did not parrot White House talking points about a fast-track coronavirus vaccine is the latest example of the president's effort to enforce an upbeat narrative about the pandemic,even if that does not square with the facts.  Robert Redfield, director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, is the most recent government physician or scientist to run afoul of Trump's coronavirus message machine. He did so in congressional testimony Wednesday, saying a vaccine greenlighted later this year would probably not be available to most Americans until sometime in 2021 because those most in need would get the first doses. Redfield also rankled Trump by saying face masks are "more guaranteed to protect me against covid than when I take a covid vaccine."  Trump said Redfield "made a mistake" on both counts, although the CDC director's projection about the timetable for vaccine approval and distribution mirrored those of other top officials, including Operation Warp Speed chief scientist Moncef Slaoui and Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases.  "It's just incorrect information," Trump said, adding that he had called Redfield after his Senate testimony.  With fewer than 50 days before the Nov. 3 election, Trump has keyed on a prospective coronavirus vaccine as a piece of good newsthat demonstrates his leadership amid a grinding pandemic, with continued job losses, school closures and disruptions to daily life. Trump argues that the worst of the crisis is past and that states should lift remaining restrictions meant to curb the spread of a disease that has killed nearly 200,000 Americans.  But health and science experts say his continued swipes at the government's own experts are undermining...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States plan to independently vet data...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2020/09/17/exclusive-states-plan-to-independently-vet-covid-19-vaccine-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials are skeptical of federal reviews of potential COVID-19 vaccines, with some planning to independently analyze clinical trial data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flat out disregard for human life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pence-s-former-top-aide-says-trump-called-coronavirus-a-good-thing-because-he-didn-t-like-shaking-hands-with-disgusting-supporters/ar-BB199CZw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW BLAMES TRUMP BUT SHOWS OBAMA CAGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/rachel-maddow-uses-photos-of-immigrant-children-held-in-cages-during-obama-administration-while-blaming-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC's Rachel Maddow used images of children held in cages during the Obama administration in a segment blasting President Donald Trump over the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Pence Covid Aide Voting for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/17/politics/former-pence-aide-coronvirus-task-force-slams-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former top aide to Vice President Mike Pence assailed President Donald Trump's response to the pandemic in a new video Thursday, adding to the growing list of former Trump administration officials who have criticized the President and, in several cases, endorsed his Democratic opponent Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE detainees complained about 'rough' treatment from Georgia doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/ice-detainees-complained-about-rough-treatment-from-georgia-doctor/S4V5UDBRKZCJZMSUPOJQRXKYNM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, women at a South Georgia immigration jail talked about Dr. Mahendra Amin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyeglasses may help protect against virus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/516945-eyeglasses-may-help-protect-against-coronavirus-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eyeglasses could offer additional protection against transmission of coronavirus, according to a study published in the Journal of the American Medical Associatio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director says antifa is an ideology, not an organization...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bdd3b6078e9efadcfcd0be4b65f2362e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — FBI Director Chris Wray told lawmakers Thursday that antifa is an ideology, not an organization, delivering testimony that puts him at odds with President Donald Trump, who has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN DRIVE-IN TOWN HALL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b4ff1bdcc7c0b6c05dd520598e349744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOOSIC, Pa. (AP) — Joe Biden on Thursday went after President Donald Trump again and again over his handling of COVID-19, calling Trump's downplaying of the pandemic “criminal” and his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  27% SAY COUNTRY HEADED IN RIGHT DIRECTION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab370b659775811cc6ee4d97375b98d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Less than seven weeks before Election Day, most Americans are deeply pessimistic about the direction of the country and skeptical of President Donald Trump’s handling of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under lockdown, Israel faces bitter start of Jewish New Year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6bfae480c85de99e6a091100330607ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Eating apples dipped in honey on Rosh Hashana is a Jewish tradition to symbolize a sweet start of the New Year. But in Israel, bitterness prevails on the eve of the holiday as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gulf between White House's words, Trump's actions on masks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/41dc3fc8f146db80754c8f5b2a474c98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — White House officials insist that President Donald Trump strongly supports face masks to prevent the spread of coronavirus and always has. But the president’s own words and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks changes that slowed mail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/27f8cfb536769d5b9b26ba354f501fca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — A U.S. judge on Thursday blocked controversial Postal Service changes that have slowed mail nationwide, calling them “a politically motivated attack on the efficiency of the Postal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before Sweetheart Deal From Trump, KODAK Sponsored His Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/before-it-got-a-sweetheart-covid-deal-from-trump-kodak-sponsored-his-celebrity-apprentice-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision to give the famous camera giant $765 million to help manufacture coronavirus drugs has raised numerous eyebrows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee will restart nursing home visits
...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/health/2020/09/17/tn-coronavirus-restrictions-nursing-home-visits-lifted/5772193002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting Oct. 1, nursing homes will be allowed to welcome visitors if they’ve gone two weeks without a new case of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>911 Call From Intoxicated Falwell's House Describes 'Lot Of Blood'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/911-called-to-allegedly-intoxicated-jerry-falwell-jrs-house-last-month-there-was-a-lot-of-blood-213552998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Becki Falwell told the operator that her husband had cuts on his face from falling after he’d been drinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sedition charge may apply to protest violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cbca8672a70f9f170a086a7a252a751e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a memo to U.S. attorneys Thursday obtained by The Associated Press, the Justice Department emphasized that federal prosecutors should aggressively go after demonstrators who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dam operator trapped for days...</title>
      <link>https://katu.com/news/wildfire-season-2020/detroit-dam-operator-mike-pomeroy-trapped-for-nearly-two-days-as-beachie-creek-fire-raged</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;katu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labor Day was windy. And Detroit Dam operator Mike Pomeroy knew there was a good chance a wildfire could threaten the dam. But by the time he was ready to evacuate, the Beachie Creek Fire was bearing down on him from the north. He jumped in his car and tried to drive east, but boulders and burning trees blocked the highway. He had no choice but to turn back and shelter in place inside the dam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKYHORSE Publishing's House of Horrors...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2020/09/skyhorse-publishings-house-of-horrors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skyhorse Publishing, literary home to Michael Cohen, Woody Allen, and Alan Dershowitz, has struggled with bigger problems than a roster of political unsavories. Interviews suggest a history of workplace toxicity and inappropriate behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple helplessly watch as thieves ransack evacuated home...</title>
      <link>https://www.koin.com/news/wildfires/looters-descend-as-fires-empty-beavercreek-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.koin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeowners have suffered huge losses as wildfires ravage Clackamas County but not all the damage is caused by flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Sues STARBUCKS After Hot Tea Burns His Genitals...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/09/17/roseville-man-lawsuit-starbucks-tea-scalding-spill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new lawsuit claims a Roseville man’s Starbucks order left him disfigured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITI employee who ran website on leave...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/17/citigroup-employee-who-ran-popular-qanon-site-put-on-leave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citigroup said it has placed an employee on paid leave after he was unmasked as the operator of a popular website linked with the conspiracy group QAnon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLM founder teams up with pro-Chinese Communist Party group...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/17/blm-co-founder-teams-up-with-pro-chinese-communist-party-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “trained Marxist” founder of Black Lives Matter has teamed up on a new venture with a pro-Chinese Communist Party organization. Alicia Garza is now behind the advocacy group Black Fut…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHOEN:  China and Russia Are Plotting to Destroy Us...</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@Douglas_Schoen/wake-up-america-china-and-russia-are-plotting-to-destroy-us-1530d0448316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an excerpt from his new book, Doug Schoen explores China and Russia’s new Cold War and how it could well undermine American democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Law and Order' Ditched for Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.sunherald.com/news/politics-government/election/article245807355.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sunherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>By drone or drive-in, Miami finding religion on holiest Jewish days...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article245605875.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of Fort Hood soldier who died in training allege foul play
...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8744827/Fort-Hood-soldier-25-collapsed-training-dead-bruises-scratches.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army said Pvt. Corlton L. Chee, main, collapsed during training at the Texas base, inset, on August 28. His family allege foul play after his body 'was found with bruises and scratches'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Rapper Facing Criminal Prosecution for Antisemitism...</title>
      <link>https://www.algemeiner.com/2020/09/17/french-rapper-freeze-corleone-facing-criminal-prosecution-for-antisemitism-holocaust-denial-on-hit-debut-album/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.algemeiner.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half million homes are gay marriages 5 years after ruling...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/587455c1d71f6363b2d272253f916b88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Five years after the U.S. Supreme Court legalized same-sex marriages around the U.S., more than a half million households are made up of married same-sex couples, according to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College football game canceled due to quarantines...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2020/09/17/north-carolina-game-against-charlotte-cancelled-covid-quarantines/3479424001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No. 11 North Carolina will not face Charlotte this weekend with the 49ers offensive line depleted due to quarantines following COVID-19 protocols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX star charged for child porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/criminal-justice/ct-jerry-harris-cheer-child-pornography-charges-chicago-20200917-dddpvpsk7ra2hb72c67b47j6uq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Harris, star of the Netflix docuseries “Cheer,” was arrested Thursday and charged in federal court in Chicago with producing child pornography, according to the U.S. Attorney’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ to impose 'millionaires tax'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/17/nj-to-impose-millionaires-tax-on-residents-earning-1m-and-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-earning New Jersey residents will face an increased “millionaires tax” under a new budget deal announced Thursday — despite warnings from critics that it could lead the wealthy to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  US billionaires' wealth grew $845 billion during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/us-billionaires-wealth-net-worth-pandemic-covid-billion-2020-9-1029599756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality TV Series Sending Contestants To Space In 2023...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/space-hero-astronaut-reality-series-international-space-station-reality-tv-1234575932/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Following the success of SpaceX’s Crew Dragon mission, which marked the return of the U.S.’ capability for manned flights and the first private company to get people into orb…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN CNN TOWN HALL TONIGHT</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/biden-faces-us-voters-town-155740894.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House hopeful Joe Biden on Thursday holds his first extended face-to-face with real voters since winning the Democratic nomination, a town hall where he will likely savage President Donald Trump's handling of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second defector reveals details of bioweapons program...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/16/second-china-defector-gives-biological-weapons-inf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. intelligence agencies recently increased their knowledge of China’s covert biological weapons program with the help of a defector from the People’s Liberation Army, according to people familiar with the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour market recovery stalling;  Nearly 30 million on unemployment benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSKBN2681Y1?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits fell less than expected last week and applications for the prior period were revised up, suggesting the labour market recovery had shifted into low gear amid fading fiscal stimulus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: WE MAY NEVER KNOW ELECTION RESULTS!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-baselessly-states-election-result-may-never-be-accurately-determined-minutes-after-fox-friends-segment-airs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump baselessly questioned the validity of the November 3rd general election in a Thursday morning tweet that criticized what he called "unsolicited ballots," and cited the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> WHO warns Europe cases higher than March...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/rich-nations-snap-vaccine-stocks-041922669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization on Thursday warned of "alarming rates of transmission" of Covid-19 across Europe and cautioned against shortening quarantine periods as countries in the region scrambled to find ways to reduce infections without resorting to new lockdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODBYE, LA:  SHAPIRO MOVING MEDIA COMPANY TO NASHVILLE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/the-daily-wire-ben-shapiro-jeremy-boeing-1234577589/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Wire, the conservative media company started by Ben Shapiro, Jeremy Boreing and Caleb Robinson, plans to move its headquarters from Los Angeles to Nashville. Boreing said that the move wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAIWAN TICK TOCK:  CHINA WARNS STONES BECOME TORPEDOES...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2020-09-17/china-threatens-us-over-taiwan-visit-stones-may-become-torpedoes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-model claims Trump forced tongue down throat...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/sep/17/donald-trump-accused-of-sexual-assault-by-former-model-amy-dorris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Amy Dorris alleges Trump forced his tongue down her throat and groped her at 1997 US Open</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to tell when your iPhone is listening or watching you...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1487788/iphone-listening-ios-14-update-microphone-active/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you’ve ever panicked that an app might be listening through your iPhone’s microphone, Apple has got you covered. The latest iPhone update adds a new “warning dot” that al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly revealed USPS documents show an agency struggling to manage Trump, AMAZON and the pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/New-documents-detail-USPS-s-spring-in-crisis-15574142.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - It would be months before Louis DeJoy took the reins of the nation's mail system, and the U.S. Postal Service already was mired in crisis.  Mail carriers were revolting, fearful they had few protections against the newly emerging coronavirus. The Trump administration was bearing down on its finances, sending USPS officials scrambling over what they saw as a potential illegal takeover of agency operations. And then there was a looming standoff with Amazon, which privately signaled it could take some of its lucrative delivery business elsewhere.  The tensions surfaced at an April 9 meeting, when Amazon executives "stated their concerns" about the Postal Service's economic plight amid the pandemic and questioned its "viability to them as a continued shipping partner," according to a once-secret memo circulated within the agency, which described the situation as an "inflection point." (Amazon founder Jeff Bezos owns The Washington Post.)  The wide-ranging headaches that so troubled the USPS in April ultimately foreshadowed a summer of upheaval, thrusting the once-venerated mail service into a political maelstrom months before a presidential election. Newly disclosed details of these struggles are laid bare in nearly 10,000 pages of emails, legal memos, presentations and other documents obtained by The Washington Post from American Oversight, a watchdog group that requested them under the Freedom of Information Act.  The documents, which mostly span March and April, depict an agency in distress, as its deteriorating finances collided with a public-health emergency and a looming election that would be heavily reliant on absentee ballots. During that period, the USPS occasionally relied on the legal counsel of well-connected Republicans, including Stefan C. Passantino, who once served as a top White House lawyer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family films monster alligator swimming in floodwaters outside home...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/hurricane/article_641f9412-f83c-11ea-a35f-d743591502f8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mobile, Alabama meteorologist Thomas Geboy points out, debris and possibly downed power lines aren't the only reasons residents should stay out of Hurricane Sally floodwaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election: Battleground Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/magazine/2020/10/05/election-battleground-arizona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could be the tipping-point state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> WHO warns Europe cases higher than March...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-who-warns-serious-situation-22698326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia 'has enough uranium' for nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/saudi-arabia-has-enough-uranium-22698903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential reserves have been identified at three deposits in the kingdom, according to a Chinese report. One expert said it would be “well in excess” of what a few power plants would need</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE KILLERS NEW SPACE WEAPON...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-russia-have-weaponised-space-22697271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Secretary of Defense Mark Esper claimed Moscow and Beijing have "turned a once peaceful arena into a war-fighting domain" which threatens the country's air superiority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK MAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-map-new-cases-infections-united-states-6aee486c-d136-47c7-a865-052f90426316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nationwide, cases were up slightly while testing was down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREZ DEBATE IN A WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/516810-the-memo-warning-signs-flash-for-trump-on-debates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The upcoming debates offer President Trump his best chance to shift momentum in an election campaign he appears to be losing — but some signs don’t augur well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF ISIS 2020;  New Leadership Chain Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://cgpolicy.org/articles/exclusive-look-into-the-islamic-states-new-leadership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cgpolicy.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homicides up 52% in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/09/17/chicago-covid-shootings-homicides-surge-affecting-people-color/5804396002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's second-largest county has recorded more homicides this year than in all of 2019, the Cook County Medical Examiner’s Office said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Declares Venus -- a Russian Planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencetimes.com/articles/27334/20200917/venus-russian-planet.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's space chief has claimed that Venus is a 'Russian planet' after news of biosignatures were detected which could indicate that there is life on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr under fire over comparison of virus lock-in to slavery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/843dcf4c766a1684164e428752939e07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General William Barr drew sharp condemnation Thursday for comparing lockdown orders during the coronavirus pandemic to slavery. In remarks Wednesday night at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daytime TV's Dark Side: 'TMZ on TV,' 'ELLEN,' 'ROSIE' Employees Detail Abusive Work Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/daytime-tvs-dark-side-former-tmz-on-tv-ellen-and-rosie-employees-detail-abusive-work-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines selling tickets for scenic 'flights to nowhere'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/938039/airlines-are-now-selling-tickets-scenic-flights-nowhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They take off and land at the same airport, but for some jetsetters, these 'flights to nowhere' are enough. The Association of Asia Pacific Airlines says because of the coronavirus pandemic, there has been a 97.5 percent drop in international travel in the region. Taiwan's EVA Air and Japan's ANA wanted to find a way to make money and ensure their pilots could keep their licenses, so they started offering special scenic flights. Last month, an ANA plane that is typically bound for Honolulu instead flew around for 90 minutes with 'a Hawaiian experience on board,' Reuters reports. Qantas is now following in their footsteps, offering a flight that takes off from Sydney and, after flying low over the Australian Outback and the Great Barrier Reef, lands back in Sydney seven hours later. Tickets ranged in price from $575 to $2,765, and with 134 seats available, the flight sold out in 10 minutes. A spokeswoman told Reuters on Thursday it was 'probably the fastest selling flight in Qantas history. People clearly miss travel and the experience of flying. If the demand is there, we'll definitely look at doing more of these scenic flights while we all wait for borders to open.' Chen Shu Tze, an engineer from Taipei, took advantage of Tigerair Taiwan's flight to nowhere that travels over South Korea's Jeju island. For $236, she got a seat on the plane and a one-year voucher for round-trip tickets from Taiwan to South Korea, as soon as travel bans are lifted. 'The pandemic has a devastating impact on the tourism and airline industry, so I want to help boost the economy, and I miss flying,' she told Reuters. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK MOVES ARIZONA BLUE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/516842-cook-political-report-moves-arizona-to-lean-dem-in-biden-trump-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cook Political Report shifted the presidential race in Arizona toward D</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys could have 'fundamental rights' as Switzerland holds historic vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/monkeys-could-fundamental-rights-switzerland-22698723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country's top court gave the go-ahead for citizens to decide on amending their region's constitution to include "fundamental rights to life for nonhuman primates"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Topples Virgin Mary Statue Outside NYC Church In Broad Daylight...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/09/16/caught-on-video-man-topples-statue-of-virgin-mary-outside-brooklyn-church-in-broad-daylight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video shows a man in a hat climbing a fence outside Our Lady of Solace and clambering up a religious shrine. He grabs the statue of the Blessed Mother, knocks it over and hurls it onto the sidewalk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudes wear masks in Tunik installation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nudes-wear-masks-spencer-tunick-093717454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteers strip (nearly) naked, for a socially distanced art installation at Alexandra Palace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone lands in outfield at WRIGLEY FIELD, causing delay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1126c1238ac4ebb536ec8b593d567f3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Umpires hastily cleared the field during a game between the Cleveland Indians and Chicago Cubs on Wednesday night when a small drone flew into Wrigley Field over the bleachers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrapped plan to ship masks. Standoff with AMAZON. Docs detail USPS in crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2020/09/17/usps-trump-coronavirus-amazon-foia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wide array of political, legal and financial headaches troubled the U.S. Postal Service in March and April, foreshadowing a summer of upheaval, nearly 10,000 pages of emails, memos and other private agency documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON launches 'invitation only' site for luxury items...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1484098/amazon-invite-only-luxury-stores/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON has revealed an invitation-only section of its website called Luxury Stores. The ‘luxury’ experience is currently only avaliable for select Prime members in the US. Those who fit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Mask Pastor in ICU...</title>
      <link>https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2020/sep/16/after-balking-at-masks-pastor-and-church-staff-in-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spokesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Coeur d’Alene pastor who opened his large church in early May for in-person services that allowed and even encouraged unmasked congregants to gather has been recovering from COVID-19 at the Kootenai Health intensive care unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Zuckerberg 'Alliance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/facebook-and-mark-zuckerberg-need-trump-even-more-than-trump-needs-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Needs Trump Even More Than Trump Needs Facebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruised Branson Seeking $400 Million to Fund Next Business Foray...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/richard-branson-joins-blank-check-230048592.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Richard Branson is on the hunt for his next big business opportunity after staving off a crisis in his empire of travel and leisure-focused companies hit hard by the coronavirus pandemic.Branson is inviting investors to buy shares of a listed shell firm, known as a special purpose acquisition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future is cyborg: Study finds support for human augmentation...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSKBN2680KP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two thirds of people in leading Western European countries would consider augmenting the human body with technology to improve their lives, mostly to improve health, according to research commissioned by Kaspersky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evangelicals Taking on QAnon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/17/the-evangelicals-who-are-taking-on-qanon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Seth Brown, the executive editor of the Biblical Recorder, a Southern Baptist newspaper in Cary, N.C., delivered a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing mounting economic woes, Hawaii to launch pre-travel testing program...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2020/09/16/live-governor-discuss-states-covid-response-new-infections-slowly-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But months after first announcing the plan, key details of the testing program still have to be worked out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After early virus warning, 10 days of distraction...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/After-early-virus-warning-10-days-of-distraction-15573335.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In explaining why he repeatedly misled the American public about the early dangers posed by the novel coronavirus, President Donald Trump has argued that he did not want to engender panic - and suggested that his actions showed he took the looming pandemic seriously.  But a detailed review of the 10-day period from late January, when Trump was first warned about the scale of the threat, and early February - when he acknowledged to author Bob Woodward the extent of the danger the virus posed - reveals a president who took relatively few serious measures to ready the nation for its arrival.  Instead, enabled by top administration officials, Trump largely attempted to pretend the virus did not exist - spending much of his time distracted by impeachment and exacting vengeance on his political enemies. He also carried on as usual with showy political gatherings and crowded White House events.  The period would presage Trump's disjointed and often dismissive approach to the virus in the months to come, as the president and his aides repeatedly sought to diminish the danger of a pandemic that has now claimed nearly 200,000 American lives while leaving millions more infected or out of work. Trump and White House officials disagree, arguing that the president took definitive steps in the early days of the virus that showed his resolve and helped limit the death toll.  Joe Grogan, former head of the Domestic Policy Council, said that the analyses now, more than half a year later, are "all ex post facto about where this was going to go." Grogan said Trump was "focused on the issue but getting frustrated with others internally who were panicking about it because they were raising their voices and being hyperbolic."  "The president didn't want to panic people," Grogan said. "Taking a step back, messaging was a challenge....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As smoke continues to shroud LA County, residents worry about long-term exposure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/smoke-continues-shroud-l-county-202301478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hardware stores have seen a run on portable air purifiers as smoke from the Bobcat and El Dorado fires continues to blanket Southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC Poll highlights key barriers for Trump and Biden in final weeks before election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/poll-highlights-key-barriers-trump-110041315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With seven weeks to go, Biden finds resistance from swing voters who think he&amp;#39;s too liberal. Trump needs to motivate supporters uncertain about voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human footprints dating back 120,000 years found in Saudi Arabia! </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ancient-footprints-saudi-arabia-show-180200239.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 120,000 years ago in what is now northern Saudi Arabia, a small band of homo sapiens stopped to drink and forage at a shallow lake that was also frequented by camels, buffalo, and elephants bigger than any species seen today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House offered tests to Big Ten to resume football...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/white-house-offered-tests-big-ten-resume-football/story?id=73062256</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House offered to provide the the Big Ten with enough COVID-19 tests for play to begin, but it sourced the tests from a private company instead, officials said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
