<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Device Makes Seawater Drinkable In Minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drinking-water-device-makes-seawater-drinkable-freshwater-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 785 million people around the world lack a clean source of drinking water, according to the World Health Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Afghan 'Helpers' Cling to Planes as USA Escapes Kabul...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/desperate-afghan-e2-80-98helpers-e2-80-99-cling-to-planes-as-us-abandons-them-at-kabul-e2-80-99s-airport/ar-AANnnlD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than 24 hours after the Taliban regained power in Afghanistan, scenes of chaotic desperation played out at Kabul’s main airport as people climbed onto the wings and sides of departing military jets and clambered up gangplanks to try to get onto the last flights out of the capital. At least five people were reported killed after the U.S. military, which has control of the airport, opened fire. It was yet unclear on Monday if they were shot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE FROM KABUL...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/16/afghans-cling-to-us-air-force-plane-as-it-takes-off-in-kabul/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Afghans have been filmed desperately chasing after and clinging to a US Air Force plane as it taxied down the runway, as the frightened civilians frantically attempt to flee the countr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edgar Allan Poe's Final Macabre Mystery: His Own Death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/edgar-allan-poe-final-macabre-090516044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos GettyImagine a 19th century mystery that begins with a man slipping in and out of consciousness in a Baltimore hospital bed in clothes that are not his own. While he has periods of semi-lucidity, he is more often wracked by delirium, incoherently babbling and shouting out the name “Reynolds” to the puzzlement of all around him. After a short period of recovery, he suddenly takes a turn for the worse, says “Lord, help my poor soul!” and dies.This is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detainee says China has secret jail in Dubai, holds Uyghurs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-dubai-uyghurs-60d049c387b99b1238ebd5f1d3bb3330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young Chinese woman says she was held for eight days at a Chinese-run secret detention facility in Dubai along with at least two Uyghurs, in what may be the first evidence that China is operating a so-called “black site” beyond its borders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Helicopters Chase Afghans Swarming C-17...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42007/apache-helicopters-chase-afghans-swarming-a-c-17-on-kabul-airports-runway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever security perimeter existed at Kabul International appears to have collapsed with Afghans running freely across its runway and taxiways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinal who criticized shot caught covid. Days later, he was on ventilator...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-conservative-cardinal-who-criticized-the-vaccine-caught-covid-days-later-he-was-put-on-a-ventilator/ar-AANmYSg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cardinal Raymond L. Burke was an outspoken vaccine skeptic and criticized the Catholic Church for supporting social distancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking video shows people falling off plane mid-air...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiatvnews.com/news/world/afghanistan-shocking-video-shows-people-falling-off-from-plane-mid-air-kabul-airport-us-troops-latest-updates-726876</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiatvnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortly after a video of a huge crowd jostling to get into an aircraft at Kabul airport flooded the social media on Monday, another unforeseen video splashed TV screens all over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE FROM KABUL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/16/chaotic-scenes-at-kabul-airport-as-afghans-flee-taliban.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Afghans have amassed on the tarmac at Kabul's international airport in the hours following the Taliban's breach of the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heaps misery on crisis-hit nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/15/haitians-heartbroken-as-deadly-quake-heaps-misery-on-crisis-hit-nation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aftershocks sow fear, hospitals swamped and aid workers race to provide food as tropical storm looms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHENEY:  Mess Was Caused by Trump and Worsened by Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/liz-cheney-criticized-on-twitter-for-suggesting-afghanistan-withdrawal-mess-was-caused-by-trump-and-worsened-by-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Liz Cheney (R-WY) is taking heat on Twitter for suggesting that the messy withdrawal of troops from Afghanistan was caused by the Trump administration and exacerbated by President Joe Biden. Cheney is the daughter of Dick Cheney, vice president to George W. Bush, whose administration initiated the U.S. invasion of Afghanistan in the aftermath […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC Deletes Page Supporting Troop Withdrawal From Website...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/donald-trump/donald-trump-calls-on-joe-biden-to-resign-in-disgrace-over-afghanistan-as-rnc-deletes-webpage-supporting-troop-withdrawal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump called on President Joe Biden to “resign in disgrace” on Sunday over the messy withdrawal of troops from Afghanistan. “It is time for Joe Biden to resign in disgrace for what he has allowed to happen to Afghanistan, along with the tremendous surge in COVID, the Border catastrophe, the destruction of […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-year mission collapses in single day...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/15/the-fall-of-kabul-a-20-year-mission-collapses-in-a-single-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Ashraf Ghani flees Afghanistan as Taliban sweep into city to seize control of country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDISPUTED VICTOR OF 20-YEAR WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/15/talibans-abdul-ghani-baradar-is-undisputed-victor-of-a-20-year-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Return to power of movement’s co-founder embodies Afghanistan’s inability to escape history of conflict</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis refuses state of emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98health-care-system-is-really-hurting-e2-80-99-but-florida-isn-e2-80-99t-under-a-covid-19-state-of-emergency/ar-AANl0hq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite record hospitalizations, Florida isn’t under a state of emergency as the highly transmissible delta variant sends cases soaring, frustrating one Central Florida emergency manager’s response and tying the hands of other local leaders confronting the new pandemic challenge. Gov. Ron DeSantis declined to reinstate Florida’s emergency declaration, even as the number of people needing to be ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President known for empathy takes cold-eyed approach...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Defiant-and-defensive-a-president-known-for-16388916.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Taliban fighters poised to rout the U.S.-backed Afghan government - and with it the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Market Retakes $2 Trillion Market Cap Amid Bitcoin Gains...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-market-retakes-2-trillion-071352079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The total market value of cryptocurrencies rose above $2 trillion again as Bitcoin continued to climb and the likes of Cardano, XRP and Dogecoin advanced as well.Crypto’s market value rose to $2.06 trillion on Saturday, according to CoinGecko, which tracks more than 8,800 coins. Bitcoin reached as high as $48,152, the highest level since May 16, as it showed staying power above its 200-day moving average.It wasn’t just Bitcoin holding up the overall market advance, however. As of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural population losses add to farm and ranch labor shortage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/census-2020-farm-ranch-labor-business-83107b136c2c92b6c4b7830b12f5bd96</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — Rural America lost more population in the latest census, highlighting an already severe worker shortage in the nation's farming and ranching regions and drawing calls from those industries for immigration reform to help ease the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC school district back to virtual classes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-education-coronavirus-pandemic-eedc8bd21e55ea0eb190902e5a3fa457</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — COVID-19 cases have prompted the largest South Carolina school district already back open to return to virtual lessons as students in more than 60 other districts prepared to return to class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Trump 'peace' plan released 5,000 Taliban...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/chris-wallace-confronts-mike-pompeo-asks-do-you-regret-giving-taliban-legitimacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Do you regret pressing the Afghan government to release 5,000 prisoners, which they did, some of whom are now back on the battlefield fighting with the Taliban?” Wallace asked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-MOBILE probes 'huge breach' after hackers claim to have stolen data of 100 MILLION customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3478344/t-mobile-data-hack-100-million-customers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;T-MOBILE is currently investigating claims of a massive customer data breach which hackers claim has affected 100 million users. The data breach reportedly includes social security numbers, phone n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top general warns terrorists will reemerge on American soil...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3478882/general-milley-warns-terror-threat-afghanistan-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOINT Chiefs of Staff chair Mark Milley warned of an increased threat of terror attacks on US soil after Afghanistan fell to the Taliban on Sunday, according to a new report. Milley told a bipartis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabbed, reporter attacked at vax protest in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9894631/Man-stabbed-LA-fight-breaks-protest-pushing-against-vaccine-mandates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was stabbed outside City Hall in LA when a fight broke out during anti-vaccine protest on Saturday. The protest was held to push back against recent vaccine mandates .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TO FILL VOID...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2021/07/21/china-taliban-afghanistan-biden-troop-withdrawal-belt-road-geopolitics-strategy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing has its eyes set on using Afghanistan as a strategic corridor once U.S. troops are out of the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Supreme Court blocks mask mandates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-joe-biden-africa-business-health-6f4274885665ec886b779ff6aeaf3dae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas — The Texas Supreme Court has blocked mask mandates ordered by two of the nation’s largest counties that defied Republican Gov. Greg Abbott as COVID-19 cases surge and hospitals are stretched thin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUGHT BY SURPRISE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-afghanistan-taliban-5934ef05b0094d0189b5d900d2380179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden and other top U.S. officials were stunned on Sunday by the pace of the Taliban's nearly complete takeover of Afghanistan, as the planned withdrawal of American forces urgently became a mission to ensure a safe evacuation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden boosts food stamp benefits by 25%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-9832ab299bd1a5953f305ec1ae2b8ea9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration has approved a significant and permanent increase in the levels of food stamp assistance available to needy families—the largest single increase in the program's history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll of powerful Haiti quake soars over 1,000...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/haiti-earthquake-98f06a322e12f732f94485238d13558c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LES CAYES, Haiti (AP) — The death toll from a 7.2-magnitude earthquake in Haiti climbed to 1,297 on Sunday, a day after the powerful temblor turned thousands of structures into rubble and set off franctic rescue efforts ahead of a potential deluge from an approaching tropical storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3473432/haiti-earthquake-huge-magnitude-7-quake-strikes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN EARTHQUAKE with a 5.8 magnitude shook Haiti on Saturday night – less than 24 hours after the country was hit by a massive 7.2 quake that claimed at least 304 lives. The 5.8 magnitude quake was m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFTERSHOCKS RATTLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/environment/magnitude-7-quake-strikes-western-haiti-usgs-2021-08-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 304 people died and hundreds were injured after a major earthquake struck southwestern Haiti on Saturday, authorities said, reducing churches, hotels, schools and homes to rubble in the latest tragedy to hit the impoverished Caribbean nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/pictureshow/2021/08/15/1027792264/photos-scenes-from-the-haiti-earthquake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say entire towns were destroyed and more than 300 people have died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROP STORM NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/14/1027707629/haiti-earthquake-strikes-magnitude</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People in the capital of Port-au-Prince felt the tremor and many rushed into the streets in fear. The U.S. Geological Survey predicts the death toll could reach into the thousands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Strangeness of Catholic Church's Latest Scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-deep-strangeness-of-the-catholic-church-s-latest-scandal/ar-AANl655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outing of a top administrator of the nation’s conference of Catholic bishops as a regular Grindr user was clearly a story. But what kind?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILDINGS COLLAPSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-two-massive-magnitude-7-24759921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houses and churches were reduced to rubble as a major earthquake - bigger than the 2010 tremor that killed an estimated 300,000 - hit just west of Port-au-Prince, haiti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/haiti-earthquake-08-14-21/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7.2 magnitude earthquake struck near Haiti on Saturday morning. Follow here for the latest updates on Haiti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHURCH CRUMBLES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/haiti-earthquake-7-2-magnitude-today-2021-08-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death toll rose to at least 304 after the 7.2 magnitude quake, which was felt in neighboring countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/haiti-earthquake-live-search-survivors-083453052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow the latest updates from recovery efforts in the Caribbean</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT GHANI LEAVES</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210815135818-u91av</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/ (WRAPUP 10, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 10-Taliban enter Afghan capital, official says President Ghani has left for Tajikistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAITI QUAKE HORROR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-haiti-earthquakes-e067bc2ba933fb40c6d98d34a41a7729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — A powerful magnitude 7.2 earthquake struck southwestern Haiti on Saturday, killing at least 304 people and injuring at least 1,800 others as buildings tumbled into rubble.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
