<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STONE:  'Naive' to say will not be convicted by Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/25/roger-stone-naive-to-believe-donald-trump-will-not/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone, President Trump’s former election campaign adviser, gave a rare interview Friday ahead of standing trial for federal criminal charges related to the 2016 race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>41% of world's people are under 24. And they're angry!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/oct/26/young-people-predisposed-shake-up-established-order-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Hong Kong to Chile, young people are rising up to fight injustice and inequality. Their elders should be grateful</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  Americans hate partisanship, but they're more partisan than they were... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Americans-hate-all-the-partisanship-but-they-re-14564537.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three years ago, the Pew Research Center released a study detailing the depths of partisan polarization across the country. A follow-up study released this fall found that, since the election of President Donald Trump, those divisions are even worse. Given the impeachment inquiry unfolding in Washington, things are almost certain to deteriorate further.  These divisions represent one of the great political challenges of these times, though there appears to be no immediate answer. Politics has become steadily more poisonous and the stakes with each election increase as fears of "the other side" having power course through the electorate. People talk longingly about restoring civility or returning to an earlier time. Little suggests that could happen soon.  There are moments when the light of hope breaks through. Friday's funeral in Baltimore for Rep. Elijah Cummings was a tribute to a politician who fought as hard as he could for the causes in which he believed but made few enemies in the process. But even his funeral conveyed the partisan differences that are today endemic.  Friendships across the political spectrum and within legislative bodies do exist, as Cummings' life showed. But such personal friendships struggle against the deep-seated animosities that now permeate politics. Many Americans decry these conditions and lament that political leaders do not do more to change them. But they contribute to the divisions.  The long-standing bipartisan Battleground Poll, produced by from The Tarrance Group and Lake Research Partners under the auspices of Georgetown University's Institute of Politics, reported last week that almost 9 in 10 Americans say they are "frustrated by the uncivil and rude behavior of many politicians."  About as many Americans say that "compromise and common ground should be the goal for political...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former top aide asks court on testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/25/charles-kupperman-bolton-impeachment-058254</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's strategy shifts as efforts to stymie probe fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/newspolitics/trump-frustrated-as-white-house-effort-to-defy-impeachment-inquiry-fails-to-halt-witness-testimony-advisers-say/ar-AAJncqt?li=AAggFp4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow Torches NBC Bosses over Farrow book...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/maddow-scorches-nbc-over-accusations-network-execs-shielded-weinstein-lauer-very-very-hard-to-stomach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Maddow scorches NBC over claims that network execs killed Ronan Farrow's exposé on Harvey Weinstein: 'Those accusations are very, very hard to stomach'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  SOUTHWEST AIRLINES flight attendant caught pilots watching livestream of passengers using toilet...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona/2019/10/25/southwest-airlines-lawsuit-pilots-livestreamed-plane-bathroom-flight-attendant-claims/2458570001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Phoenix-based Southwest Airlines flight attendant says she was retaliated against after reporting two pilots for livestreaming a plane's lavatory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China financial threat to 2020 elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/2019/10/article/chinas-financial-threat-to-the-2020-us-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI wants to prevent financial warfare and a disinformation campaign that could trigger a market collapse to influence voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKOUTS LOOM FOR MILLIONS IN CA</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/717/millions-face-power-cuts-california-fires-spread-doc-1lr3x61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>