<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady's heir? Patriots draft Stidham...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/patriots/2019/04/27/2019-nfl-draft-patriots-jarrett-stidham-quarterback-tom-brady/3599751002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots' selection of Auburn's Jarrett Stidham in the fourth round of the NFL draft adds some intrigue to their quarterback room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA PUSHED BIDEN NOT TO RUN IN '16</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/politics/the-long-run-biden-and-obamas-odd-couple-relationship-aged-into-family-ties/ar-BBWmF5i?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 85:  JOAN COLLINS SHARES #METOO MOMENTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6969285/Joan-Collins-says-studio-head-offered-Liz-Taylors-Cleopatra-role-slept-him.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joan Collins touched on some of the may men in her life, from her love affair with Warren Beatty and on-set romance with Harry Belafonte to her five husbands - whom she ranked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/sunday-profile-dynasty-star-joan-collins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the scheming Alexis Carrington on the '80s TV series "Dynasty," British actress Joan Collins was really good at being bad. Mo Rocca talks with Collins about her film and TV career, her five husbands, and her catfights with "Dynasty" co-star Linda Evans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Attorney General Investigates...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/oliver-north-out-as-nra-president-11556376506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York attorney general’s office is investigating potential financial and disclosure problems at the National Rifle Association, amid boardroom turmoil at the group that led Saturday to the departure of NRA President Oliver North after a bruising internal political battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Whistleblower Complaints Emerge against BOEING 737 MAX... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/more-whistleblower-complaints-emerge-in-boeing-737-max-safety-inquiries-11556418721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators are looking into complaints by roughly a dozen purported whistleblowers alleging safety problems with Boeing’s 737 MAX jets, according to officials familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD OF CONDEMNATIONS OF NYT FOR ANTISEMITIC CARTOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Diaspora/Antisemitism/Flood-of-condemnations-of-NYT-for-anti-Semitic-cartoon-588044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressmen join former ambassador to Israel and journalists in slamming the newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite record diversity, 70-something white men rule 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/despite-record-diversity-70-something-white-men-rule-013121612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats seeking to reclaim the White House are calling for generational change. President Donald Trump is a 72-year-old billionaire, and for many he epitomizes the white male privilege that Democrats often decry. Former vice president Joe Biden, who jumped into the race Thursday, is 76 and has spent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENTS DINNER OPENS WITH DARK SERMON ON TRUMP ENDANGERING JOURNALISTS...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-lieu-comedy-whcd-opens-dark-sermon-trump-endangering-journal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘My son asked me, “Is Donald Trump going to put you in prison?”‘</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' $1.2 BILLION Weekend!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/798efe76562549c687eceb78820838e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — "Avengers: Endgame" has shattered the record for biggest opening weekend with an estimated $350 million in domestic ticket sales and $1.2 billion globally. The Marvel Studios...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation reels from deadly synagogue attack on final day of Passover...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14d2196c6d584b1287bc862a0e53c00a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWAY, Calif. (AP) — The rabbi who led a service on the last day of Passover suffered a gunshot wound to his hands and two others endured shrapnel wounds as political, civic and religious leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model dies on catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8956363/model-tales-soares-dies-catwalk-sao-paulo/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MALE model has died after collapsing on the catwalk during Sao Paulo’s Fashion Week. Tales Soares, 26, was attended to by paramedics in front of horrified onlookers after being taken ill du…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Relaunches as Global Platform...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/04/the-sri-lanka-bombings-were-a-preview-of-isiss-future/588175/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sri Lanka bombings were a preview of the Islamic State’s future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio pioneer emerges as alleged scam artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/sports/2019/04/26/marty-tirrell-kxno-the-jock-troy-aikman-steve-luebke-sports-radio-federal-prosecutors-scam-iowa/3578354002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts native brought his shrill radio voice to Des Moines in 1995; he also allegedly brought a penchant for cheating people out of money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr testimony to House on Mueller in doubt amid dispute...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/06c8721db0b944d192cddef2bfdaa8a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department has informed the House Judiciary Committee that Attorney General William Barr may not attend a Thursday hearing to review special counsel Robert Mueller's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACT CHECK: Unraveling Cow Fart Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2019-04-28/ap-fact-check-unraveling-the-mystery-of-whether-cows-fart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nominate a woman? Dem women not so sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.mynews13.com/fl/orlando/ap-top-news/2019/04/28/nominate-a-woman-some-democratic-women-arent-so-sure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mynews13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democratic women say they&amp;#39;re worried about nominating a woman for president after Hillary Clinton&amp;#39;s loss to Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed while protecting rabbi...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/28/us/california-synagogue-shooting-victims/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a gunman opened fire in a synagogue in California, killing one and injuring three others, Lori Kaye jumped between the shooter and the rabbi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Predicts Own Blue 'Wave' In 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/rubycramer/bernie-sanders-blue-wave-winning-organizing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My friends, you are going to see a wave — a wave up and down the Democratic ballot."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How inmates extort families from behind bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/2019/04/alabama-inmates-extort-families-beyond-the-walls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Justice Department's investigation of Alabama prisons for men uncovered details about prisoners who extort money from other inmates' families. The Alabama Department of Corrections says its Investigations and Intelligence Division has looked into 18 extortion cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone delivers kidney for transplant...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2019/04/earth-shattering-drone-delivers-kidney-for-transplant-over-baltimore/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unmanned aircraft system’s flight last week through the city of Baltimore was less than 3 miles, but it represented a huge first step. See photos and video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record UK stabbing homicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/04/27/knife-crime-britain-wales-national-emergency-record-stabbing-homicides/3470942002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-hundred and eighty-five people died in knife-related homicides in England and Wales in 2018. It's being call a national crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man on lam after stealing police car while en route to jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/local/sumner/2019/04/27/sumner-sheriffs-looking-man-stole-police-car/3599974002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sumner County Sheriff's Office saidÂ a corrections officer was transportingÂ Dreon Key when Key took control of the jail car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model dies after taking ill on catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Model-in-Sao-Paulo-dies-after-taking-ill-on-13801184.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) - A model participating in Sao Paulo's Fashion Week has died after getting sick and falling on the catwalk.  A statement from organizers said Tales Soares took ill Saturday while in a parade of fashion brand Ocksa. A medical team attended to him on the catwalk and Soares was later taken to a hospital, where he was pronounced dead.  The statement did not provide more details.  Daily Folha de S. Paulo reported that Soares tripped on his shoelace and fell. According to the paper, people in the crowd initially thought his fall was part of a performance.  A photo in the newspaper showed the model lying face down on the catwalk while paramedics attended to him. The paper reported Soares was 26 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far from glitzy tech hubs, Chinese city bets big on VR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a7dfb8061bc64be182cf9d57fe88e13b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NANCHANG, China (AP) — Liu Zixing craned his neck forward for help with fastening the goggles for his first ever taste of virtual reality. He took a break from the mining ore business to travel to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran foreign minister to visit NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/28/mohammad-javad-zarif-iran-foreign-minister-visit-n/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s foreign minister, Mohammad Javad Zarif, says he will visit North Korea as both countries struggle under U.S. sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital cemetery: When FACEBOOK controls human history...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190428-facebook-zuckerberg-dead-orwell-oxford-internet-institute</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Facebook profiles of people who have died may exceed the number of living profiles in just 50 years, according to a new study. As such, the social network could become the keeper of a significant part of humanity’s memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finders keepers? Police say no way after $30K spills on road...</title>
      <link>https://fox4kc.com/2019/04/27/finders-keepers-michigan-police-say-no-way-after-30k-spills-on-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox4kc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAND HAVEN, Mich. -- Police in Michigan are appealing to people to surrender their instant riches after a box with $30,000 fell off the back of a truck. Authorities in Grand Haven say drivers stopped Thursday to pick up cash for themselves. Only $2,500 was immediately recovered and returned to the owner, who had forgotten that a cash box was on the truck's bumper. Traffic was backed up on U.S. 31 after money hit the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities search for arsonist who set fire outside National Archives...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/authorities-search-arsonist-who-set-fire-outside-national-archives-washington-n999161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Archives houses beloved historical documents such as the Constitution and the Declaration of Independence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unions, leftwing parties, join 'yellow vests' march in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/unions-leftwing-parties-join-yellow-vests-march-202111249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of trade unionists and left wing activists joined "yellow vest" protesters in Paris Saturday in rejecting French President Emmanuel Macron's proposed tax cuts as too little too late. The march in the capital, organised by the militant CGT union, came ahead of the main rally in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May have tried to live stream shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/crime-courts/2019/04/27/California-synagogue-shooting-injuries-Chabad-of-Poway/stories/201904270048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in anti-Jewish hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/la-me-poway-jewish-hate-synagogue-20190427-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack at a Poway synagogue in San Diego County that killed one and injured three others comes amid a rise in hate crimes and anti-Semitic incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead after construction crane crushes cars in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/crane-falls-on-multiple-cars-on-boren-and-mercer-blocking-eastbound-lanes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people are dead after a construction crane collapsed on several cars on the west side of Fairview Ave North and the Mercer Street intersection Saturday, according to the Seattle Department of Transportation. According to the Seattle Fire Department, two crane operators were killed and two people in cars on the ground died. Three others were taken to Harborview Medical Center in Seattle. Their condition is unknown at this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan Markle due to give birth as Britain awaits royal baby...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8954862/meghan-markle-due-give-birth-today-baby-sussex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUM-to-be Meghan’s due date is today, The Sun on Sunday can reveal. She and Prince Harry are on standby but relaxed about the arrival of baby Sussex. Harry, 34, still plans to attend today’s London…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left a manifesto?</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/04/poway-synagogue-shooter-left-a-manifesto-admits-to-arson-at-mosque-calls-trump-a-zionist-anti-white-traitorous-ccksucker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 19 YEAR OLD SUSPECT... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6967437/Several-injured-gun-man-opens-fire-San-Diego-Synagogue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident is said to have taken place at the Chabad of Poway house of worship sometime after 11:30 local time, the San Diego County Sheriff's Office reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members of congregation attempted to overpower gunman....</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/27/us/san-diego-synagogue/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 19-year-old man was in custody after a shooting at a synagogue in the California city of Poway left at least one person dead and several others wounded, Mayor Steve Vaus said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson's name to remain on L.A. school auditorium despite sex abuse claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/entertainment/entertainmenttoday/s-2202300?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES -- The on-again, off-again relationship between Michael Jackson and Gardner Street Elementary School in Hollywood is still on, although perhaps more tenuously so than at the height of the pop star's popularity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaido makes new appeal to Venezuela army ahead of Mayday protests... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/guaido-makes-appeal-venezuela-army-ahead-mayday-protests-230013926.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's opposition leader Juan Guaido used his latest mass rally on Saturday to reiterate an appeal to the army to end its support for Nicolas Maduro's regime, and announced massive Mayday protests to oust the embattled president. Despite support from more than 50 states who recognize him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 DEAD:  Four people shot at San Diego synagogue... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/poway-synagogue-shooting-chabad-way-san-diego-sherrifs-department-509162631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person has died after shots were fired inside a Poway, California synagogue filled with people celebrating the last day of Passover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS powerhouse Lou Dobbs shaping Trump immigration policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/04/27/hard-line-views-made-lou-dobbs-a-fox-powerhouse-now-hes-shaping-trumps-border-policy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The relationship between President Donald Trump and Fox star Lou Dobbs has become an object of curiosity and amusement, but also something more profound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooter taken into custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbs8.com/article/news/local/man-detained-multiple-injuries-reported-after-shooting-incident-at-synagogue-in-poway/509-70fe3d8c-050d-4bba-a3bf-21d2bf0137e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbs8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shots were fired at Congregation Chabad in Poway. Police have confirmed multiple injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi conducting service suffered hand injuries...</title>
      <link>https://www.10news.com/multiple-people-gunned-down-at-poway-synagogue-police-search-for-shooter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How eight 'bad grandpas' pulled off daring $20 million jewel heist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/27/how-eight-bad-grandpas-pulled-off-a-daring-20-million-jewel-heist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some senior citizens with too much time on their hands pick up bocce or dominoes as a hobby. And then there are the “Bad Grandpas”: Eight old men who pulled off one of Britain’s most audacious jewe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Last day of Passover... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/36c8a77e02e4448ca1ef78e0b90ac2c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWAY, Calif. (AP) — A shooting at a synagogue outside San Diego where worshippers were celebrating the last day of Passover sent four people to the hospital Saturday, but the extent of their...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
