<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Grandmother kills rabid bobcat with bare hands...</title>
      <link>http://www.onlineathens.com/news/20180615/hart-county-grandmother-kills-rabid-bobcat-with-bare-hands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rabid bobcat recently attacked a Hart County grandmother in her yard, spurring a furious battle that ended with the cat’s strangulation death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girlfriend broke into email account to reject full-ride scholarship...</title>
      <link>http://montrealgazette.com/news/local-news/mcgill-music-student-awarded-350000-after-girlfriend-stalls-career</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;montrealgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She wrote an email posing as him, turning down a $50,000-a-year scholarship so that he wouldn’t leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican's stolen Christopher Columbus letter found in Atlanta...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/vatican-stolen-christopher-columbus-letter-found-atlanta/vxIpLCpeVlN0m4NyGBLa3O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For at least 14 years, investigators searched the world for a stolen letter written by Christopher C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD CUP RATINGS FALL HARD...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/06/world-cup-ratings-opening-game-russia-saudi-arabia-fox-1202411344/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The opening game of the 2018 World Cup was a winner for Vladimir Putin but not so much for Rupert Murdoch, at least when it comes to the ratings. The Russian President got to strut his stuff on the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress Test: Saliva Swab Detects Workplace Burnout...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/stress-test-saliva-swab-detects-workplace-burnout-162145768.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A simple saliva test can show within hours whether someone on the job is overly stressed and at risk of burnout, researchers said Friday. Measuring levels of the anti-stress hormone cortisol at different times of the day more accurately reveals stress levels than more complicated measures, including</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stands firm against demands to close borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/merkel-ally-bavarian-governor-acting-bonsai-trump-075051510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German Chancellor Angela Merkel remains firmly opposed to unilateral moves to turn some refugees back at the border, her spokesman said Friday, warning such action — demanded by conservative allies in her own government — would weaken the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says Cohen no longer his lawyer...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/392463-trump-says-cohen-is-no-longer-his-lawyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday sought distance from Michael Cohen, his longtime personal attorney, who is under criminal investigation in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, China announce new tariffs in escalation of trade war...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-imposes-import-taxes-on-Chinese-goods-and-12996976.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump followed through Friday on his threat to crack down on China for its "very unfair" trade practices, announcing that he is imposing a 25-percent tariff on $50 billion in Chinese imports. Beijing quickly responded. In a late-night statement, China's Ministry of Commerce said it would impose trade barriers of the "same scale and the same strength." The Chinese government said Trump's tariffs were "damaging" relations and "undermining the world trade order." U.S. and Chinese officials in recent weeks had made progress on a deal that involved up to $70 billion in additional purchases of American products. But the Chinese offer was now "invalid," the statement said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAIL FOR MANAFORT</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/federal-judge-jails-ex-trump-campaign-chair-paul-154529077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal judge jails ex-Trump campaign chair Paul Manafort ahead of trial, citing recently filed obstruction charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DISEASE X' FEAR:   New strain of bird flu kills half of those who contract it...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/2790957/terrifying-new-strain-of-bird-flu-that-kills-nearly-half-of-those-who-contract-it-discovered-in-china-amid-fears-of-new-global-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW strain of deadly bird flu which kills 38 per cent of those infected and could spark a global pandemic has been identified in China. Scientists around the world believe the new pathogen, dubbe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage Over White Woman Selected To Perform Selena Tribute...</title>
      <link>http://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/controversy-white-selena-tribute-singer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of the Hispanic community in North Texas are upset that a Dallas concert venue picked a white singer to perform songs by Tejano legend Selena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Opens Up To Oprah On Anthem Kneeling, Spirituality...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/14/oprah-tom-brady-kneeling-national-anthem-spirituality-gisele/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady sat down for an interview with Oprah Winfrey, and it's a conversation that involves some topics that generally don't get covered in Brady's usual press conferences at Gillette Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok denies throwing 'cocktail party' for judge on surveillance court...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/peter-strzok-denies-throwing-cocktail-party-for-judge-on-surveillance-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior FBI official Peter Strzok says he didn't arrange a cocktail party with a federal judge who serves on the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court, despite telling his mistress in a text message that he would.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORIOLES $161 Million Slugger In Danger Of Worst Season Ever By Player...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/06/15/orioles-chris-davis-is-on-pace-for-historically-bad-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To say that the O's first baseman has struggled out of the gates this season would be an understatement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'I'm With Her'... </title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/eric-felten/meet-the-other-amorous-fbi-staffers-who-texted-about-the-clinton-email-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parsing the Inspector General’s report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Fueling L.A. Comedy Club Gold Rush; 'I Sold the Same Special Twice!'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/netflix-is-driving-la-comedy-gold-rush-1119236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hollywood Reporter tags along with a top agent as he pops into packed venues to take in veteran comics trying out new material, newbies attempting to stand out from the crowd and everyone hoping to land that career-changing deal with the dominant streamer: "That's what’s selling tickets these days."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo fined $20 million, two years suspended jail after tax fraud case...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/football/6540542/cristiano-ronaldo-accepts-two-year-suspended-prison-sentence-and-ordered-to-pay-16-5m-fine-after-tax-fraud-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRISTIANO RONALDO has “agreed to accept a two-year suspended prison sentence and pay a whopping £16.5million fine”, according to reports in Spain. The Real Madrid superstar had been see…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOTTI' SCREENING FROM HELL; AUDIENCE WALKS OUT AS MOVIE TRASHED BY CRITIC...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/15/john-travoltas-gotti-movie-is-as-bad-as-you-thought-the-all-you-can-eat-buffet-version-of-goodfellas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Gotti” starring John Travolta is just as bad as you might imagine, and then some. I can’t say I blame director Kevin Connolly, who took over from a long series of unfortunate inc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  CHECK DRUDGE!</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-well-crush-midterms-check-top-drudge-best-jobs-numbers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We have the strongest economy in the history of our nation’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/15/trump-matt-drudge-is-great/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'He really, has ability'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise ship CARNAGE as 'drug-fuelled orgies erupt on lawless trip'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/travel/travel-news/709863/Cruise-ship-carnage-Anchored-drug-fuelled-orgies-Spain-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT PRAISES DRUDGE...</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/trump-calls-matt-drudge-a-great-gentleman-2018-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump called conservative media personality Matt Drudge "a great gentleman" and his website Drudge Report as "great" in an interview with Fox News on Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freak gust of wind sends portable toilet 100ft into air, sprays 'liquid' on screaming crowd below...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5847587/Freak-gust-wind-sends-Porty-Potty-flying-air.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the moment a freak gust of wind sends a set of Porty Potty flying into the air. People were forced to diver for cover after a huge blast of wind whipped through a park in Commerce City, Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea creatures fall from sky after 'sucked from ocean by waterspout'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5847383/Storm-photos-appear-starfish-octopus-flying-streets-China.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The images, taken in the coastal city of Qingdao in eastern China's Shandong Province, went viral on social media after a ferocious tempest blew through the town on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY 'CRIMINAL'</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5848345/Trump-says-Comeys-conduct-criminal-den-thieves-ringleader.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Friday that James Comey's actions prior to his firing were 'criminal.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP wants Trump in 2020, more popular than Obama, JFK, Reagan...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/gop-wants-trump-in-2020-more-popular-than-obama-jfk-reagan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican voters are demanding that President Trump run for reelection in 2020, the latest evidence that support among his backers is stronger than it was for nearly every recent president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mysterious explosions in past 2 months rattle Pennsylvania residents...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/mysterious-explosions-past-months-rattle-pennsylvania-residents/story?id=55916084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating a string of suspicious explosions in Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo 'accepts two-year prison sentence' as soccer star strikes agreement over tax evasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/cristiano-ronaldo-accepts-two-year-12714662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Real Madrid superstar was accused by Spanish prosecutors in June last year of defrauding tax authorities of €14.8m (£12.9m).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RIPS FBI 'SCUM'</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/15/trump-unloads-on-comey-scum-on-top-fbi-day-after-damning-ig-reports-release.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday broke his silence on the damning Justice Department IG report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GISELE: I'm too old and wise for INSTA...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/06/14/gisele-bundchen-is-too-old-and-wise-for-instagram-modeling/?_ga=2.129027724.1021424398.1529053503-591381504.1529053502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s not my generation — I have to be honest about that. I’m older, wiser.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major League Baseball Sees Sharp Drop in Attendance...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/major-league-baseball-sees-a-sharp-drop-in-attendance-1529063246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;League-wide attendance of 27,328 per MLB game is down 6.6% from this time last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAIL FOR MANAFORT?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/former-trump-campaign-chief-manafort-to-ask-judge-not-to-jail-him-idUSKBN1JB12X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort is set to ask a federal judge on Friday not to revoke his bail and send him to jail pending trial after Special Counsel Robert Mueller filed new charges of witness tampering last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky man to be sentenced in Rand Paul attack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1fd104e391d7451482b6226aa666f2ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOWLING GREEN, Ky. (AP) — U.S. Sen. Rand Paul's neighbor is set to be sentenced in federal court for an attack last year in the lawmaker's yard.        Rene Boucher pleaded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaraguans flood migration offices in bid to flee crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nicaraguans-flood-migration-offices-bid-flee-crisis-013829885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One evening as she watched some local kids play outside in her Managua neighborhood, Nicaraguan Mireya Alegria was shocked to see police, motorcycles and a white van carrying hooded men speed past. Now Alegria is one of the thousands of Nicaraguans desperately seeking to process migration documents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand to tax tourists as influx grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/zealand-tax-tourists-fund-infrastructure-052910321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists to New Zealand are to be charged a special tax, under new government plans announced Friday to deal with the growing influx of holidaymakers coming from overseas. Visitor numbers have surged by nearly a third in the past three years to 3.8 million in the 12 months to April -- almost as big</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President preps China tariff target list, Beijing ready to retaliate...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-prepares-china-tariff-target-list-confrontation-escalates-014628928--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump on Friday was due to unveil a final list of Chinese imports that would face punishing tariffs, fanning fears of a trade war as Beijing warned that it could swiftly strike back. The threat of massive duties on billions of dollars of goods sent Shanghai stocks to their lowest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawking's voice to be beamed into space during memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hawkings-voice-beamed-space-during-memorial-044308410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A message from late British astrophysics giant Stephen Hawking will be beamed towards the nearest black hole as his remains are laid to rest in London's Westminster Abbey on Friday. As the ashes of the British theoretical physicist are interred, a specially-written composition featuring his famous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban chief who ordered Malala assassination 'killed in airstrike'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/taliban-chief-ordered-malala-assassination-104729550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the Pakistan Taliban has been targeted in a United States drone strike in eastern Afghanistan. Afghan officials said Mullah Fazlullah, who is one of the world's most wanted militant leaders, had been killed in Kunar province, but Pakistan security sources said his death had not yet been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Flee and Thieves Loot Venezuela's Reeling Oil Giant...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/workers-flee-and-thieves-loot-venezuela-s-reeling-oil-giant/17628941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL TIGRE, Venezuela — Thousands of workers are fleeing Venezuela’s state-owned oil company, abandoning once-coveted jobs made worthless by the worst inflation in the world. And now the hemorrhaging is threatening the nation’s chances of overcoming its long economic collapse, union leaders, oil executives and workers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's World Cup star accused of helping drug lord...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/mexico-americas/la-fg-mexico-rafael-marquez-20180615-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican soccer legend Rafael Marquez, who is preparing to compete in his fifth World Cup, was sanctioned last year by the U.S. Treasury Department for allegedly aiding a notorious drug trafficker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man On Horse Charged With DUI...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/06/15/horse-dui-boy-trampled-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armando Martinez Ruiz is now facing DUI charges. The spooked horse trampled an 8-year-old boy in the crowd, breaking his leg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITZ-CARLTON Crackdown Still Haunts the New Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/15/ritz-carlton-crackdown-still-haunts-the-new-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A climate of fear permeates the kingdom months after the government’s corruption purge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Immigration Drama Could Spell End For Merkel...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/angela-merkels-battle-with-bavaria-refugees-migration-masterplan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Looking to Dodge Property Tax Caps Turn to Alaskan Trusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/06/15/rich-looking-to-dodge-property-tax-caps-turn-to-alaskan-trusts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Looking to Dodge Property Tax Caps Turn to Alaskan Trusts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For House Flippers, Reality Meets Reality TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/15/realestate/for-house-flippers-reality-meets-reality-tv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new generation of real estate investors inspired by HGTV is discovering that renovation isn’t nearly as easy as it looks on television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We'll stop becoming president'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/fbi-agents-text-reportedly-disclosed-by-justice-watchdog-well-stop-trump-from-becoming-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI agent who worked on the special counsel's Russia probe texted another investigator that 'We'll stop' Donald Trump from getting elected president, The Washington Post reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed: GDP estimate rises to 4.8%...</title>
      <link>https://www.fxstreet.com/news/atlanta-fed-q2-gdp-estimate-rises-to-48-from-46-201806141617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fxstreet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key conservative presses for shield law after seizure of NYT reporter's records...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/392322-key-conservative-presses-for-shield-law-after-seizure-of-nyt-reporters-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department’s seizure of a New York Times reporter’s private email and phone records has sparked one of President Trump’s top GOP allies in Congress to say he’ll aggressively pursue legislation to protect journalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump campaign chief Manafort to ask judge not to jail him...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/former-trump-campaign-chief-manafort-to-ask-judge-not-to-jail-him-idUSKBN1JB12X </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort is set to ask a federal judge on Friday not to revoke his bail and send him to jail pending trial after Special Counsel Robert Mueller filed new charges of witness tampering last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Viva Le Resistance': Attorney removed over  texts...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5846147/FBI-lawyer-working-Muellers-Russia-probe-texted-colleague-Viva-le-Resistance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI lawyer exchanged messages after the election with another colleague and proclaimed: 'Vive la resistance.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-ray vision will soon give soldiers superhero ability to see through walls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6536698/x-ray-vision-soldiers-able-see-through-walls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIONIC soldiers with X-ray vision could soon be a reality thanks to a new wireless system that uses radio-waves to map people’s movements behind walls. Researchers at MIT trained artificial i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allies see report on FBI as path to undercut Mueller probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-allies-seize-on-DOJ-report-as-they-seek-to-12995738.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Thursday's report from the Justice Department's inspector general gave new and potent ammunition to President Donald Trump and his allies in their ongoing efforts to undermine special counsel Robert Mueller III's investigation of Russian interference during the 2016 presidential campaign. Even as Trump faces his own legal complications, Republicans quickly seized on the report as a meaningful development that they believe will further bruise Mueller's credibility with the public and bolster the president, whose administration has long been gripped by the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENTS RECEIVED FREE HANDOUTS FROM JOURNALISTS... </title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/14/agent-journalist-gifts-could-be-federal-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IG promises further reports on potential leaks for gifts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rollercoaster terror at Daytona Beach: Riders flung 34 FEET, others left hanging...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5846887/Daytona-Beach-Boardwalk-rollercoaster-derailed-two-people-fall-34-feet-ground.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screams filled the air at the Daytona Beach Boardwalk on Thursday night after a rollercoaster car derailed, dropping two people 34 feet to the ground and leaving eight others trapped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Employees Referred for Investigation...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/14/inspector-general-refers-five-fbi-employees-for-investigation-over-hostile-political-messages.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department inspector general has referred five FBI employees for investigation in connection with politically charged texts, revealing in its report on the Hillary Clinton email case that more bureau officials than previously thought were exchanging anti-Trump messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York files suit against Trump...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180614145037-m3zna</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/TRUMP FOUNDATION:New York sues to dissolve Donald J. Trump Foundation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Viva Le Resistance': Mueller attorney removed over anti-Trump texts...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/14/mueller-lawyer-resisted-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENTS REGULARLY RECEIVED FREE HANDOUTS FROM JOURNALISTS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/14/ig-report-fbi-agents-bribed-journalists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FULL REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.justice.gov/file/1071991/download</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.justice.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Used GMAIL for FBI business...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/james-comey-used-gmail-for-official-fbi-business-numerous-times.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comey's use of a private email account was inconsistent with Justice Department policy, according to a report by the Office of the Inspector General.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCHDOG SLAPS 'INSUBORDINATE' COMEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/99ed3059a42e4ed99e71d2486a18856c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on a report by the Justice Department's internal watchdog on the FBI's handling of the Hillary Clinton email investigation (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Festival chemists forensically examine drugs for attendees...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/14/drug-tests-festivals-wont-stop-getting-arrested-save-life-7631688/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you ever safely say you know what's inside your drugs?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of daylight saving time inches closer...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article213187609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Assembly Bill 807, the first step to ending daylight saving time, passed the state Senate on Thursday, April 14, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT APPROVES $50B IN TARIFFS ON CHINA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/donald-trump-approves-tariffs-on-about-50-billion-of-chinese-goods-1529016073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump approved assessing tariffs on about $50 billion of Chinese goods, said individuals familiar with the decision, as the U.S. ratcheted up its trade fight with Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians Prep 5,000 Kite Bombs In Gaza To Mark End of Ramadan...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Palestinians-prep-5000-kite-bombs-to-mark-end-of-Ramadan-in-Gaza-559981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli media report Palestinians plan to launch 5,000 such devices into southern Israel to mark Eid al-Fitr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild animals become nocturnal to avoid humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/06/14/party-animals-quite-the-contrary-humans-cause-wild-critters-to-adopt-the-night-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans are influencing the behavior of wild animals, causing them to flee daylight and seek the cover of darkness for protection, according to a new study from UC Berkeley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Probe Cohen for Possible Illegal Lobbying...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/prosecutors-investigating-michael-cohen-for-possible-illegal-lobbying-1529012696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors in Manhattan are investigating whether Michael Cohen, the longtime personal lawyer for Donald Trump, illegally engaged in secret lobbying, people familiar with the investigation said, as part of a broader investigation into Mr. Cohen’s business dealings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>99-Million-Year-Old Frogs Found In Amber...</title>
      <link>https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/06/oldest-frogs-fossils-amber-cretaceous-dinosaurs-science/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It was exhilarating to hold these small fossils up to the light to reveal the frogs within.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indigenous Chileans fight loggers by burning forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/14/chile-mapuche-indigenous-arson-radical-environmental-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chile’s Mapuche people are resorting to increasingly radical tactics to reclaim their ancestral land from exploitive industries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermassive black hole imaged eating star for first time...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-06-astronomers-distant-eruption-black-hole.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, astronomers have directly imaged the formation and expansion of a fast-moving jet of material ejected when the powerful gravity of a supermassive black hole ripped apart a star that wandered too close to the cosmic monster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S BEST BIRTHDAY!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5845629/Ivanka-Eric-lead-tributes-Donald-Trump-72nd-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka and Eric Trump have lead the tributes to President Donald Trump on his 72nd birthday by posting throwback photos from their childhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hawaii it's 'raining' green crystals...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/06/14/hawaii-volcano-green-crystals-olivine/701389002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the never-ending parade of weird phenomena erupting from Hawaii's Kilauea volcano comes a "rain" of green crystals, which have been spotted on the ground after falling from the sky. "It is literally raining gems," tweeted meteorologist Erin Jordan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Close To Deal For Future Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-14/apple-is-said-to-near-deal-for-animated-movie-in-hollywood-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. has decided on its next Hollywood act: making feature films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man running for mayor killed in Mexico, 16th candidate dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-running-mayor-killed-mexico-16th-candidate-dead-202407926.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — The mayor of a small town in western Mexico who was running for re-election has been killed, the 16th candidate murdered ahead of the July 1 elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top FACEBOOK Strategist Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/top-facebook-strategist-to-step-down-1529006487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s top policy and communications executive, Elliot Schrage, is stepping down after a decade at the social-media giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMORGAN: Economy Growing At 4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/trumps-forecast-of-4-percent-gdp-growth-close-to-coming-true-as-americans-spend-tax-bill-proceeds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surging consumer spending is driving GDP well above prior estimates, and it is now tracking near 4 percent for the second quarter, almost doubling the pace of the first quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: IQ Scores On Decline For Decades...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/iq-scores-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds the decline in IQs is related to the environment, not genetics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leslie Jones wants 'SNL' to do fewer political jokes...
</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/06/14/leslie-jones-wants-snl-to-do-fewer-political-jokes-next-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I do hope that next year will be a lot more funny-funny based stuff, more comedy-based stuff instead of a lot of political stuff.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macrons' new $580,000 dinner plates spark cash row...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-44480957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's presidential couple are the centre of claims that a fortune is being spent on porcelain.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
