<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AP:  WHITE HOUSE KNEW IN 2019!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/425e43fa0ffdd6e126c5171653ec47d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top officials in the White House were aware in early 2019 of classified intelligence indicating Russia was secretly offering bounties to the Taliban for the deaths of Americans, a full year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Free Speech Alternative' PARLER Already Banning Users It Doesn't Like...</title>
      <link>https://www.techdirt.com/articles/20200627/23551144803/as-predicted-parler-is-banning-users-it-doesnt-like.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techdirt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, that did not take long at all. On Friday we predicted that just like every other social media platform out there, the new favorite among people who falsely say that Twitter is censoring conservatives, would start taking down content and shutting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymptomatic Carriers Easily Contaminate Surroundings...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/asymptomatic-covid-19-carriers-easily-contaminate-their-surroundings-study-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even asymptomatic COVID-19 patients can not only infect others directly, but also contaminate the surrounding environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican lawmakers confirm intelligence reports...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-says-U-S-intelligence-did-not-find-reports-15373347.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- Leading Republican lawmakers on Monday confirmed that U.S. intelligence agencies have developed information about a Russian military operation targeting U.S. and allied forces in Afghanistan. But they said that any U.S. response should wait until intelligence agencies fully review the material, some of which was shared with members of Congress in a classified briefing at the White House.  Current and former intelligence officials familiar with the intelligence said it was less ambiguous than White House officials and some lawmakers have portrayed and indicated that Russian military intelligence had offered bounties to Taliban-linked militants who killed U.S. military personnel.  The CIA in particular has been analyzing the intelligence for several months and has assessed that the Russian program is real, according to these people. The CIA declined to comment.  The intelligence was considered significant and credible enough that it was included in the President's Daily Brief, according to two individuals familiar with the matter, who like others spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss sensitive intelligence. The brief is a collection of the most significant analysis on issues affecting national security and foreign policy and is prepared for the president and his top advisers.  Some officials think the Russian operation led to the deaths of several U.S. service members, according to intelligence gleaned from captured militants in recent months. It was unclear exactly how many Americans or coalition troops from other countries may have been killed or targeted, several people familiar with the matter said.  "There was intelligence reported on the allegation that the Russians were offering a bounty to the Taliban to kill Americans, but at the same time there was a very strong dissenting view from another...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sets New Daily Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-usa/california-has-record-jump-in-covid-19-cases-arizona-clamps-down-idUSKBN2401Z8?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California marked a record jump in new COVID-19 infections on Monday, a Reuters tally showed, as Los Angeles reported an "alarming" rise that put it over 100,000 cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'white power' retweet set off 'five alarm fire' in White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/trump-s-white-power-retweet-set-five-alarm-fire-white-n1232495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aides couldn't immediately reach the president to get him to take down the offending tweet because he was on the course at his golf club and had put down his phone, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBERTS JOINS LIBERALS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-strikes-down-restrictive-louisiana-abortion-law-n1231392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The measure would have required doctors who provide abortions to have admitting privileges at hospitals within 30 miles of a clinic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins's tracker has become gold standard, but creators say many miss real story...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Johns-Hopkins-s-coronavirus-tracker-has-become-a-15374750.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She found herself listening for the sirens all the time. Before, they had been just background noise, ambulances regularly blasting through Beth Blauer's neighborhood in Baltimore to or from a nearby critical-care facility for the elderly.  Now she knew every emergency trip from the nursing home could turn up later as a statistic on her computer screen.  The novel coronavirus was working its way through the United States, and Blauer - along with dozens of colleagues at Johns Hopkins University - was actively tracking its path.  "The sirens now feel different," she said recently. "They come with a different flood of emotions."  The noise outside her window was a tangible reminder of the human lives hidden in the maze of anonymous data that had come to dominate her days.  Since launching in January, the university's Coronavirus Resource Center had exploded in scope and popularity, garnering millions of page views and popping up in news coverage and daily conversation. Through numbers, the tracker has told the story of what the virus is doing while the story is still unfolding, offering a nearly real-time picture of its silent march across the globe.  But even as data has jumped to the forefront of international discussions about the virus, the Johns Hopkins team wrestles with doubts about whether the numbers can truly capture the scope of the pandemic, or whether the public and policymakers are failing to absorb the big picture. They know what they are producing is not a high-resolution snapshot of the pandemic, but a constantly shifting Etch a Sketch of the trail of covid-19, the disease caused by the virus.  Case counts are consistently inconsistent. Reporting practices differ from country to country, state to state, even county to county. If authorities fail to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT ROCKED</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-strikes-down-louisiana-abortion-restrictions/ar-BB166JCf?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those seeking tests meet long lines and delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-hot-spot-states-those-seeking-tests-meet-long-lines-delays/ar-BB167CHz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervisor pushes to remove Zuckerberg's name from Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvu.com/news/supervisor-pushes-to-remove-zuckerbergs-name-from-sf-general-hospital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hospital was renamed after Zuckerberg and his wife, Dr. Priscilla Chan, who donated $75 million to the hospital's foundation in 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Players Opt Out of Baseball Season...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/29/us/mlb-players-opting-out-season-mike-leake-ryan-zimmerman-joe-ross-spt-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three players have decided to opt out of the rescheduled Major League Baseball season due to health concerns amid coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence on Russian bounty plot WAS included in President's Daily Brief earlier this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/29/politics/russia-bounties-presidential-daily-briefing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The intelligence that assessed there was an effort by a Russian military intelligence unit to pay the Taliban to kill US soldiers was included in one of President Donald Trump's daily briefings on intelligence matters sometime in the spring, according to a US official with direct knowledge of the latest information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA To Paint 'Black Lives Matter' On Sides Of Courts... </title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/nba-to-paint-black-lives-matter-on-sides-of-courts-at-disney-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA will also allow players to put social justice messages on the back of their jerseys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacksonville Imposes Mask Mandate as Convention Approaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/06/29/city-jacksonville-imposing-mask-mandate-gop-convention-looms-large/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City of Jacksonville, the host-city of President Trump's upcoming nomination celebration, is issuing a mask mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE shuts far-right channels over 'hate'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/youtube-shuts-down-far-channels-over-hate-speech-011652766.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube on Monday shut down six far-right channels for violating rules against "supremacist" content, booting videos by David Duke, Stefan Molyneux and Richard Spencer. The video sharing platform pulled the plug on the channels as online social media platforms face increasing pressure to crack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact unclear...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-ad-boycott-enters-phase-impact-unclear-012131779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The advertiser boycott of Facebook has morphed into a global digital activist campaign aimed at curbing hateful and toxic content on the social media giant. The unprecedented move has been joined by major brands like Unilever, Starbucks, Levis and Coca-Cola, with nearly 200 firms pausing advertising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5-4 SPLIT</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200629143043-ezva9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the three clinics that perform abortions in Louisiana would have been forced to close if the law had taken effect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASCAP Says Campaign Can't Use Any Rolling Stones Songs...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/06/donald-trump-campaign-rolling-stones-songs-ascap-1202973371/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: President Donald Trump may be looking for a new walk-off song at his campaign rallies now that the Rolling Stones and BMI have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES STRIKE DOWN ABORTION RESTRICTIONS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9c6eee97277d6e8e71f568cde830e46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A divided Supreme Court on Monday struck down a Louisiana law regulating abortion clinics, reasserting a commitment to abortion rights over fierce opposition from dissenting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of 'cured' patients still suffer...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/its-frightening-doctors-say-half-of-cured-covid-patients-still-suffer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bnei Brak woman tells The Times of Israel that a month after testing negative she has severe fatigue and anxiety - and her husband is worse than he was when hospitalized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  WARNERMEDIA to Sell Atlanta's CNN Center...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/warnermedia-selling-cnn-center-keeping-some-operations-in-atlanta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Some employees moving from CNN Center will be relocated to our Techwood campus in Midtown Atlanta," says company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY going non-profit?</title>
      <link>https://www.niemanlab.org/2020/06/newsonomics-the-next-48-hours-could-determine-the-fate-of-two-of-americas-largest-newspaper-chains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.niemanlab.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tribune and McClatchy are both approaching critical deadlines that could lead to mergers, divisions — or even the first big nonprofit newspaper chain in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 killed, 2 injured in targeted shooting outside warehouse in Jacksonville...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/local/2020/06/29/1-person-shot-outside-amazon-warehouse-in-jacksonville/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 20-year-old man who was standing in line to apply for a job at an Amazon warehouse in Jacksonville was shot and killed Monday afternoon, according to the Jacksonville Sheriff’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-end NYC hotels not sanitizing rooms, changing sheets...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/29/high-end-nyc-hotels-not-sanitizing-rooms-changing-sheets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some high-end Manhattan hotels aren’t thoroughly cleaning rooms between guests amid the coronavirus pandemic, a new report found. Three different Midtown hotels didn’t even bother to ch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad sales plunge...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/29/ad-sales-drop-31-in-may-as-nba-delay-hurts-disney-warnermedia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus continued to wreak havoc on the advertising market in May, new data shows. Last month, US advertising revenue plummeted 31 percent with the postponement of big-ticket sporting event…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not just Confederate statues: Activists want conquistadors, missionaries removed...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/06/29/indigenous-activists-protest-spanish-conquistadors-missionary-statues/3249899001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Junípero Serra, Juan de Oñate, Diego de Vargas, and Juan Ponce de León: Why the statues of these figures are being protested and removed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA issues dire warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-06-29/l-a-county-issues-dire-warning-amid-alarming-increases-in-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the scenario that L.A. County health officials most feared — that reopening would coincide with sudden jumps in coronavirus transmission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unprecedented surge' as infected cross US-Mexico border for medical care...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/29/health/border-hospitals-coronavirus/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Van Gorder says he's seeing a telling trend in the hospitals he runs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden State Killer confesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/crime/article/Joseph-DeAngelo-earons-guilty-plea-hearing-15372192.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday morning, DeAngelo, 74, began the long process of pleading guilty to over a dozen felony charges - and admitted to many more uncharged crimes - in a Sacramento State ballroom, the unusual venue needed to safely accommodate the many victims, witnesses and media with social distancing.  In exchange for pleading guilty, DeAngelo will avoid the death penalty and instead spend the rest of his life in prison. He also agreed to waive his appellate rights and will pay to-be-determined restitution to his victims. A formal sentencing hearing will be held in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing crisis, Cuba calls on citizens to grow their own food...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-cuba-urban-gardens/facing-crisis-cuba-calls-on-citizens-to-grow-more-of-their-own-food-idUSKBN2402P1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the courtyard of a temple belonging to the Abakua Afro-Cuban religious brotherhood in Havana, Nelson Piloto is pulling up the lawn to plant bell peppers and cassava in the face of Cuba's looming food crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Call For Reopening Schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2020/06/29/884638999/u-s-pediatricians-call-for-in-person-school-this-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dangers of social isolation outweigh the risks of in-person classes for most children, says the American Academy of Pediatrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cube Tells Tapper 'Watch Your Mouth' After He Slams Louis Farrakhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/ice-cube-tells-jake-tapper-watch-your-mouth-after-he-slams-anti-semitic-misogynist-louis-farrakhan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Popular rapper Ice Cube told CNN host Jake Tapper to "watch" his "mouth" on Monday after Tapper called Nation of Islam leader Louis Farrakhan a "vile anti-LGBTQ anti-Semitic m</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People defecating outside Queen's vacation home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/balmoral-outdoor-toilet-scli-gbr-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walkers are relieving themselves in the grounds of Queen Elizabeth's Scottish residence, staff have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More states hit pause...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/29/health/us-coronavirus-monday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 14 states have hit pause on their reopening plans as the United States sees a surge in coronavirus cases across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ restaurants NOT reopening indoor dining; 'Knuckleheads' at bars ruin...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/coronavirus/2020/06/nj-restaurants-not-reopening-for-indoor-dining-this-week-after-knucklehead-crowds-at-bars-ruin-it-for-everyone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indoor dining was set to reopen on Thursday, ahead of the July 4th weekend, but Gov. Phil Murphy pulled the plug on Monday citing concerns it could cause a coronavirus surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half US population is without job...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/29/nearly-half-the-us-population-is-without-a-job-showing-how-far-the-labor-recovery-has-to-go.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To get the employment-to-population ratio back to where it was at its peak in 2000 we need to create 30 million jobs," said Torsten Slok, Deutsche Bank's chief economist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV treatment found to have no benefit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200629180702-hlcq0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/HIV (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-HIV treatment found to have no benefit for hospitalised COVID-19 patients in trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES pulls out of APPLE News...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/29/the-new-york-times-pulls-out-of-apple-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times said on Monday that it was exiting its partnership with Apple News, as news organizations struggle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIRQUE DU SOLEIL bankrupt...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/entertainment/entertainment-columns/kats/cirque-du-soleil-files-for-bankruptcy-protection-plans-to-rebuild-2064149/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move that would have been unheard of even a year ago, Cirque du Soleil, the Las Vegas Strip’s preeminent production company for more than two decades, has filed for bankruptcy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters in deep-red Oklahoma weigh Medicaid expansion as virus cases climb...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/29/oklahoma-first-expand-medicaid-during-pandemic-341841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ballot measure on Tuesday, if successful, could also set back Trump's efforts to block grant Medicaid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead, 1 wounded...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8471219/One-man-dead-wounded-Seattle-CHOP-zone-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said the deadly shooting unfolded just before dawn on Monday in Seattle's CHOP, or Capitol Hill Organized Protest, zone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India bans dozens of Chinese apps including TIKTOK...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/505041-india-bans-dozens-of-chinese-apps-including-tiktok</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India on Monday banned dozens of Chinese apps including TikTok, pointing to privacy and security concerns, a move that comes less than two weeks after a deadly skirmish along the border of the two nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo trolls... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1056080/cuomo-trolls-trump-mask-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NY Gov Andrew Cuomo appeared to troll Donald Trump by photoshopping a mask on the President’s face. During his daily coronavirus press briefing on Monday, Cuomo included an image of Trump wea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men's Makeup Goes Mainstream With CVS Rollout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/men-e2-80-99s-makeup-goes-mainstream-with-cvs-rollout/ar-BB166vRN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO:  Pandemic 'not even close to being over'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200629152349-5vn0x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-TEDROS (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Pandemic 'is not even close to being over', WHO chief says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiji tries to attract billionaire tourists: 'Escape pandemic in paradise'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/coronavirus-fiji-tries-to-attract-billionaires-as-nations-pm-says-escape-the-pandemic-in-paradise-12017435</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 40% of Fiji's GDP is generated by international tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Virus Brings American Decline Out in the Open...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coronavirus-brings-american-decline-open-123041932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The U.S.’s decline started with little things that people got used to. Americans drove past empty construction sites and didn’t even think about why the workers weren’t working, then wondered why roads and buildings took so long to finish. They got used to avoiding hospitals because</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILD:  St. Louis couple draws firearms on protesters outside home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/def4fbb664edeac24746cc7af0c5c555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS (AP) — A white couple stood outside their mansion and pointed guns at protesters in St. Louis as the group marched toward the mayor's home to demand her resignation. Mark...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haitians landing on Palm Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.wpbf.com/article/possible-immigrant-landing-on-palm-beach/32965883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wpbf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach police are asking residents to report suspicious activity as officers investigate possible immigrant landing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage Grows on Capitol Hill... </title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2020-06-29/trump-denies-russia-bounty-claim-as-bipartisan-outrage-grows-on-capitol-hill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Sing-Along Prank at Militia Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sacha-baron-cohen-pulls-epic-prank-on-right-wing-militia-event-in-olympia-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian got the rally’s conservative crowd to sing along with him about injecting Obama, Dr. Fauci and others with the “Wuhan flu.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines' new shotgun taser can electrocute enemies from 300 feet away!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1053673/us-marines-specter-taser-weapon-electrocute-deadly/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhausted by face mask rage, taco chain closes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article243867532.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany extends lockdown in hard-hit district...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-germany-meat-idUSKBN2401US</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The western German state of North Rhine-Westphalia (NRW) said on Monday that as a precaution it would extend by one week a lockdown in one of two districts affected by an outbreak of the coronavirus at a slaughterhouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS  fined $1.1M for filming sidelines...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/patriots-docked-third-round-pick-fined-1-1m-for-filming-bengals-sideline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots were fined $1.1 million and docked a 2021 third-round draft pick by the NFL following an investigation into the filming of the Bengals' sideline during the 2019 season, NFL Network's Mike Garafolo reported Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump dismisses virus, polls and recession to tell winning story...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-dismisses-virus-polls-and-recession-to-tell-winning-story/ar-BB164hTY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRUNI:  Biden's Best Veep Pick Is Obvious...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ae/news/other/biden-e2-80-99s-best-vice-president-pick-is-obvious/ar-BB163Bs9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most fertile woman with 44 children stopped from having any more...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-most-fertile-woman-44-22269476 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror groups deploying 'spreaders'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/terror-groups-aiming-deploy-coronavirus-22270619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to anti-terror cops in Russia, sick Jihad groups are encouraging new members to spread coronavirus in public places. The disease sparked a pandemic earlier this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Shopper without a mask slammed against wall by deputy...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/coronavirus/article243865902.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duckworth!</title>
      <link>https://twnews.us/us-news/tammy-duckworth-is-biden-s-best-running-mate-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twnews.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen to This Op-EdAudio Recording by AudmTo hear more audio stories from publishers like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android.Whatever his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSTON: ICU beds filled with young people...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/922590/nearly-onethird-icu-coronavirus-patients-houston-hospital-system-are-reportedly-under-50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas has emerged as one of the United States' coronavirus hot spots in recent weeks, and data shows the recent spike doesn't completely match up with the early days of the pandemic in terms of demographics. Back in April, when the virus first peaked, most of the patients testing positive in the Houston Methodist Hospital system were over 50, The New York Times reports. Now, the majority are reportedly relatively young. And while it's widely believed younger, healthier people are at a lower risk of developing severe infections or dying, there are no guarantees. In the Methodist system, nearly one-third of intensive care patients are under 50, which the Times notes is higher than the previous surge. Meanwhile, The Texas Tribune and Fox4 in Dallas previously reported that people under 50 made up 50 percent of those hospitalized with the virus in June, as well as 30 percent of those in intensive care. Of note: hospitals are seeing younger patients now in June compared to March around when coronavirus started appearing in North Texas. Seeing a sharp jump in hospital patients ages 21-40. 50% of hospitalizations are under 50, 30% critical care under 50. @FOX4 pic.twitter.com/kUqFl8a7Zt â€” Lynnanne Nguyen (@LynnanneFOX4) June 22, 2020 The trend doesn't appear to be confined to Texas, at least anecdotally. Last week, The Wall Street Journal reported that states like Arizona, Florida, and California were also seeing more patients in their 20s, 30s, and 40s testing positive and winding up in the hospital. Read more about Houston Methodist Hospital's experience with the coronavirus at The New York Times. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 200 gym patrons potentially exposed in WV...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/06/29/planet-fitness-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials are warning hundreds of people who went to a Planet Fitness in West Virginia that they may have been exposed to the Coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran asks Interpol to help arrest Trump for killing general...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-asks-interpol-help-arrest-trump-killing-general-151842214.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran said Monday it has called for Interpol to help arrest President Donald Trump and 35 other US officials for the January killing of its top general in an American drone strike. Tehran prosecutor Ali Qasi Mehr, quoted by state news agency IRNA, said 36 US political and military officials "involved</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House denies knowledge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/02975c59e71e65327e2f582cd1a91f43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has denied he was made aware of U.S. intelligence officials’ conclusion that Russia secretly offered bounties to Taliban-linked militants for killing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland Earthquake Swarm Hits 9,000 in 10 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/iceland-earthquake-swarm-9000-1514079</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutation has taken over world. Scientists trying to understand why...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Coronavirus-mutation-has-taken-over-the-world-15373472.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the first coronavirus cases in Chicago appeared in January, they bore the same genetic signatures as a germ that emerged in China weeks before.  But as Egon Ozer, an infectious-disease specialist at the Northwestern University Feinberg School of Medicine, examined the genetic structure of virus samples from local patients, he noticed something different.  A change in the virus was appearing again and again. This mutation, associated with outbreaks in Europe and New York, eventually took over the city. By May, it was found in 95 percent of all the genomes Ozer sequenced.  At a glance, the mutation seemed trivial. About 1,300 amino acids serve as building blocks for a protein on the surface of the virus. In the mutant virus, the genetic instructions for just one of those amino acids - number 614 - switched in the new variant from a "D" (shorthand for aspartic acid) to a "G" (short for glycine).  But the location was significant, because the switch occurred in the part of the genome that codes for the all-important "spike protein" - the protruding structure that gives the coronavirus its crownlike profile and allows it to enter human cells the way a burglar picks a lock.  And its ubiquity is undeniable. Of the approximately 50,000 genomes of the new virus that researchers worldwide have uploaded to a shared database, about 70% carry the mutation, officially designated D614G but known more familiarly to scientists as "G."  "G" hasn't just dominated the outbreak in Chicago - it has taken over the world. Now scientists are racing to figure out what it means.  At least four laboratory experiments suggest that the mutation makes the virus more infectious, although none of that work has been peer-reviewed. Another unpublished study led by scientists at Los Alamos National...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick Life to Become NETFLIX Series...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/colin-kaepernicks-life-become-netflix-series-ava-duvernay-1300841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Colin in Black &amp; White' will tell the story of the athlete and activist's adolescent life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypervigilant mom followed every guideline. She still caught virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/article/A-hypervigilant-mom-followed-every-health-15373512.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the Thursday night before Memorial Day weekend when Rebecca Drobis, a 43-year-old mother of an infant daughter in Northwest Washington was suddenly awakened by a faint feeling of chills and wondered if she might be getting sick.  Drobis, a freelance photographer (she has previously worked for The Washington Post), had done everything she could think of to avoid the coronavirus. Her experience, recounted in a recent interview, captures how even a mild case of covid-19 can still be a harrowing ordeal - and how the myriad unknowns of the illness leave its victims without a clear sense of closure or control.  The following account has been edited for length and clarity.  We took the pandemic very seriously right from the outset. My husband's brother was stationed with the Navy in Beijing, so we'd been following the pandemic very closely since January. My daughter, Rosie, was 7 months old in March. Babies under the age of 1 are considered in the high risk category. My parents are in their 70s, and we're very close with them. They used to watch my daughter once a week, and we decided right away to have them stop coming over.  My father is a retired doctor, so we've always been hyper-aware of germs and washing our hands, and after you have a newborn, you're just crazy about wiping everything down. I ordered masks right away. We stopped going to the grocery store. We had everything delivered. We took the stay-at-home orders very seriously.  We were only leaving our house to go for a walk. Sometimes, to maintain distance, I would push Rosie's stroller into the bike lane or the street. You make these decisions every time you go out: Is the danger from an oncoming car or from all the people around us walking their dogs who aren't wearing masks? We do our best, but you can't always stay six feet apart on the sidewalk.  I...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Seizes Moment to Rule Until He's 83...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/putin-seizes-moment-to-rule-until-he-s-83-amid-fading-popularity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What better time for Putin to seek to extend his presidency for potentially 16 more years?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITTLE CAESARS Workers Fired For Swastika Pizza...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/06/29/ohio-little-caesars-swastika-pepperoni/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Little Caesars workers have been fired after an Ohio couple found pepperonis placed to form a backward swastika on their pizza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iconic 'SPACE ODYSSEY' suit to hit auction block...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iconic-2001-space-odyssey-suit-hit-auction-block-132448484.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The elusive "2001: A Space Odyssey" spacesuit believed to have been worn by Dr. David Bowman when he "killed" HAL in the groundbreaking 1968 film goes on the auction block next month. The highlight of a Hollywood and space exploration memorabilia show that's set for July 17-18</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUNT JEMIMA Relatives Want Reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/aunt-jemimas-relatives-want-reparations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larnell Evans, Jr., the great-great-grandson of Anna Short Harrington, who allegedly inspired Aunt Jemima, is far from satisfied by the company’s recent rebrand and cash donation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Unmanned Craft Seen Off Florida May Be Secret Spy Vessel...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidhambling/2020/06/29/mystery-unmanned-craft-seen-off-florida-may-be-sharc-spy-vessel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strange vessel seen off Florida looks like a SHARC, a stealthy experimental spy craft developed by the U.S. Navy. Or it might be Russian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Decries Discarding Elderly Like 'Waste Material'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/faith/2020/06/29/pope-francis-decries-discarding-the-elderly-like-waste-material/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis urged Christians Monday to treasure the presence of elderly family members and not to discard them like “waste material.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The 'see no evil' president...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/922549/trump-no-evil-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What Trump's unbelievable ignorance tells us about his governance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Capital Faces 'Swarmageddon' of Locusts...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/29/indias-capital-faces-a-swarmageddon-of-locusts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI — A miles-long cloud of locusts swarmed India’s capital region over the weekend, flying through metro stations and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists Set Up Guillotine In Front Of Bezos Home, Call For AMAZON To Be Abolished...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/activists-set-up-guillotine-in-front-of-jeff-bezoss-d-c-home-call-for-amazon-to-be-abolished</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fringe activists set up a guillotine in front of Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos&amp;#8217;s home in Washington, D.C., on Sunday where they reportedly demanded that Amazon be abolished. One of the demonstrators said on a bullhorn in front of Bezos&amp;#8217;s home, &amp;#8220;it is still exploitation and when they become threatened, and we have no voice, the [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fall of QUIBI: How did starry $1.75 billion NETFLIX rival crash so fast?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2020/jun/28/quibi-netflix-jeffrey-katzenberg-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Katzenberg’s short-form content platform has struggled to make an impact with bad reviews, lack of interest and legal issues swirling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun Belt time bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/29/sun-belt-coronavirus-trump-reelection-343694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising Covid-19 caseloads in Florida, Arizona and Texas raise fresh doubts about the president's reelection prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could he drop out?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-polls-republican-gop-operatives-possible-drop-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stretch of lackluster polling for President Trump has some Republican operatives nervous about the president’s reelection prospects in November – with some even floating the possibility that Trump could drop out if his poll numbers don’t rebound</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild moment St. Louis couple draws firearms on protesters outside home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8467075/St-Louis-couple-point-firearms-protesters-outside-home-marching-demand-mayors-resignation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Husband and wife, Mark and Patricia McCloskey could be seen aiming the guns at demonstrators who walked by their property in St. Louis at around 6pm on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country singers criticize Chase Rice for concert in front of hundreds...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Country-singers-criticize-Chase-Rice-as-selfish-15373220.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country singer Chase Rice played his first in-person concert in months on Saturday night and appeared thrilled to do so. "We back," he wrote in an Instagram story with a smiley face sunglasses emoji, accompanied by video of hundreds of people singing along to his recent hit, "Eyes On You."  But on social media, many were horrified to see images of a packed crowd, with no masks and no social distancing - especially as the concert took place in Tennessee, which is experiencing a significant spike in coronavirus infections. As the videos started circulating on Twitter, other country singers took the unusual step of calling out Rice by name.  "Imagine being selfish enough to put thousands of people's health at risk, not to mention the potential ripple effect, and play a NORMAL country concert right now. @ChaseRiceMusic," Kelsea Ballerini tweeted to her million followers. "We all want (and need) to tour. We just care about our fans and their families enough to wait."  Mickey Guyton responded and included Rice's Twitter handle: "An absolute selfish act. Shame on him." Maren Morris replied to one of Guyton's tweets and simply said, "No masks," with head-exploding and frowning-face emojis.  Bobby Bones, the format's most powerful radio personality, tweeted the video and wrote, "Aside from the obvious .... probably also heavy liability here. Just talked to two different attorneys about this."  The concert took place at Historic Brushy Mountain State Penitentiary, a former prison turned tourist destination that has a distillery, paranormal tours and a concert series called "Live at Brushy" - it's located in Petros, Tenn., a 2½-hour drive from Nashville. Brian May, vice president of the Brushy Mountain Group, said in a statement Sunday evening that fewer than 1,000 people attended Rice's show, even though the venue's maximum...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraft Prostitution Case Heads to Appellate Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/sports/new-england-patriots/2020/06/28/robert-kraft-case-update</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case will be argued via videoconference and livestreamed on the court’s website because of coronavirus concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I saw devil': Patients have terrifying delirium...</title>
      <link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/spotlight/06/29/20/i-saw-the-devil-many-covid-patients-have-terrifying-delirium</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.abs-cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Called hospital delirium, the phenomenon has previously been seen mostly in a subset of older patients, some of whom already had dementia, and in recent years, hospitals adopted measures to reduce it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Bank Lines Reemerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/food-bank-lines-reemerge-covid-paralyzes-households</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash cliff spells trouble for unemployed, and everyone else...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy-cliff-analysis-idUSKBN24014U?taid=5ef9c889d50dbc00016bc39d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judith Ramirez is bracing for July. That's when the hotel housekeeper and her electrician husband - who have both been out of work for three months - expect their combined unemployment benefits to drop by more than half, and their deferred $1,500 monthly mortgage payment on their Honolulu home to come due.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China forces birth control on Muslims to suppress population...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/269b3de1af34e17c1941a514f78d764c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese government is taking draconian measures to slash birth rates among Uighurs and other minorities as part of a sweeping campaign to curb its Muslim population, even as it encourages some...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
