<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Sparks Outcry for Calling Capitol Police Officer 'Angry Left-Wing' Activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fox-news-tucker-carlson-harry-dunn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Carlson sparked outcry Wednesday when he called Black Capitol police officer Harry Dunn an "angry left-wing political activist."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Reveals Trump Gushing Over Jan. 6 Mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/audio-reveals-trump-gushing-over-loving-jan-6-crowd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president got misty-eyed about the Capitol rioters in a newly released audio clip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MAGA's Biggest Porn Star on Being Booted from TPUSA Event...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/maga-biggest-porn-star-brandi-082351801.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ethan Miller/GettyBrandi Love is the most famous MAGA porn star on the planet. The adult-industry veteran boasts 831.5K followers on Twitter, has starred in hundreds of XXX films, penned the book Getting Wild Sex from Your Conservative Woman, and is a columnist for The Federalist. She enthusiastically supports Donald Trump and loathes antifa, BLM, and the Squad.And yet, on Saturday, she was banned from a conservative political conference just for being a porn star.Love, 48, had attended a number</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: The people who signed up for MAGACOIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/pro-trump-cryptocurrency-magacoin-has-racked-up-over-1000-sign-ups-since-launching-report-says/ar-AAMqWWE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most holders of magacoin have only been allocated the 100 free tokens users receive after registering, The Guardian said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young getting very sick. Next Covid chapter worries experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/22/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Covid-19 cases rising and vaccination rates on the decline, health experts say they are concerned about the next chapter in the pandemic -- especially for younger Americans, who they say are feeling the impacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims unexpectedly rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/22/us-weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial claims for unemployment insurance were expected to total 350,000 for the week ended July 17, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most expensive Manhattan listing drops for $169M...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/21/the-432-park-avenue-penthouse-can-be-yours-for-196m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The penthouse would be the second most expensive known New York City real estate sale ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Dunn Lawyers Berate Tucker Carlson for Attack on 1/6 Riot Officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/harry-dunn-lawyers-berate-tucker-carlson-attack-january-capitol-riot-officer-1612072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawyers called out the Fox News host and said: "Frankly, the last thing Carlson wants is for the truth to emerge of what happened that day and why."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 98 and facing cancer, Bob Dole reckons with legacy of Trump, ponders future of GOP...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/98-facing-cancer-bob-dole-100314687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm a Trumper," said Dole, the only former GOP presidential nominee to attend Trump's convention in 2016. But he added, "I'm sort of Trumped out."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye  to reveal album at massive Atlanta event...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-atlanta-37e148408bef5c3da511d2b69137310a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Kanye West knows how to make a splash even with a listening event. West is expected to unveil his 10th studio album, “Donda” during a listening event Thursday night at the Mercedes Benz Stadium in Atlanta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smog tower to help Delhi breathe?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-smog-tower-to-help-delhi-breathe-but-experts-sceptical</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smog tower to help Delhi breathe but experts sceptical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era of Olympic champions eye glory...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-new-era-of-olympic-champions-eye-tokyo-glory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New era of Olympic champions eye Tokyo glory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With cutting-edge hypersonics, Russia leads in new arms race...</title>
      <link>https://www.spacewar.com/afp/210722095748.vpeqhadk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spacewar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Hamptons Home Prices Surge to Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/hamptons-home-prices-surge-to-a-record-as-pickings-get-slimmer/ar-AAMqbgc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamptons home prices reached a record high as New Yorkers stepped up their bidding for a dwindling supply of listings in the Long Island resort towns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate braces for nasty debt ceiling fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/564223-senate-braces-for-a-nasty-debt-ceiling-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are digging in on the federal debt limit, warning Democrats that it will be up to them to avoid a default as President Biden pushes for trillions more in spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubles in Florida putting pressure on DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/564195-pressure-mounts-for-desantis-in-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. – Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis is facing mounting pressure on the homefront as he looks to cement his superstar status among Republicans nationally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Everyone Has Worst Summer Cold Ever...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/why-everyone-has-the-worst-summer-cold-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, the summer cold and cough season really is worse than usual. “I’ve had bad colds, but I’ve never experienced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grizzly Bear Terrorized Man for Days in Alaska. Coast Guard Saw SOS...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/a-grizzly-bear-terrorized-a-man-for-days-in-alaska-the-coast-guard-saw-his-sos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was sleep-deprived and nearly out of ammunition, alone in the wilderness of Alaska. Well, not really alone. For several</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China opposes studying lab leak in any new origins probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2021/07/22/asia-pacific/china-opposed-virus-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China pushed back against the World Health Organization’s call for another probe into the coronavirus’s origins that includes examining whether it leaked f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening ceremony director fired over old Holocaust skit...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-tokyo-olympics-opening-ceremony-director-fired-over-old-holocaust-skit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tokyo Olympics opening ceremony director fired over old Holocaust skit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyacht Staff Secrets From Cannabis Buffets to Caviar, Sex, Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-07-22/superyacht-staff-secrets-from-cannabis-buffets-to-caviar-sex-and-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From cannabis buffets to choppering in caviar, posh charter life can be a rough ride for the crew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym Banning People Who HAVE Been Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dbjg8/fearless-boxing-gym-is-banning-people-whove-been-vaccinated-against-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless Boxing Club claims it doesn't want members who "received the experimental Covid vaccine."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hottest Games on record?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jul/20/tokyo-olympics-fears-athletes-could-face-hottest-games-on-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beach volleyball players have already found sand too hot for their feet during practice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TO LIVE AND DIE IN LA:  Wheelchair-bound Weinstein pleads not guilty; Faces 140 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3325141/harvey-weinstein-not-guilty-charges-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEELCHAIR-bound Harvey Weinstein pleaded not guilty to 11 counts of sexual assault in a Los Angeles courtroom today. Weinstein entered the plea just one day after he was seen with a support strap …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk trolls by supporting rocket-themed dildos...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3324532/elon-musk-trolls-jeff-bezos-rocket-dildos-blue-origin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has trolled Jeff Bezos by lending his support to a new range of rocket-themed sex toys modeled on his rival’s Blue Origin space craft. The Tesla founder replied to a tweet about the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic Athletes Take Knee Against Racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/tokyo-olympics-live-updates/2021/07/21/1018811516/players-take-a-knee-at-tokyo-olympics-as-the-first-competitions-kick-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We want to fight all forms of discrimination, and as a group of women, we wanted to kneel against it," said Steph Houghton, a co-captain of Britain's soccer team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Experiment Placed Foster Children with Pedophiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/07/26/the-german-experiment-that-placed-foster-children-with-pedophiles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the approval of the government, a renowned sexologist ran a dangerous program. How could this happen?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Dream Dying?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-california-dream-is-dying/ar-AAMoqBq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The once-dynamic state is closing the door on economic opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE DEBATES NEW MASK PUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/White-House-officials-debate-masking-push-as-16330915.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Top White House aides and Biden administration officials are debating...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron's 'SPACE JAM' Blocked By Xi?</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2021/07/21/lebron-james-bent-the-knee-to-dictator-xi-but-china-still-isnt-releasing-space-jam-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While LeBron James has consistently capitulated to China, Xi Jinping has yet to greenlight the NBA star's new film 'Space Jam: A New Legacy' for release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City hospitals turning away patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tipping-point-kansas-city-hospitals-193117650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If we don’t take it seriously, we could easily end up back where we were in November,” one Kansas City doctor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electric car revolution, designed to save planet, unleashes toll on it...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-electric-car-revolution-designed-100041571.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the name of climate action, California pushed the world toward electric cars. But building enough of them is creating its own environmental crises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA RESTAURANTS CLOSE</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/21/la-restaurants-close-response-rising-numbers-breakthrough-cases-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurants throughout the region are already struggling to staff up to meet the high demand for dine-in meals, but now they are also being hit disproportionately hard by the rise in new infections, especially among people who are unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls Biden 'super human being'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barrack-held-forth-trump-real-120035863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A week before he was charged with illegal lobbying for the United Arab Emirates, Tom Barrack traveled to New York for an on-camera interview in Midtown Manhattan.Dressed casually in dark jeans and a gray, long-sleeve top by Zegna, he gave no indication that he knew federal prosecutors across the East River in Brooklyn were preparing a seven-count indictment.The investor, 74, spoke comfortably and confidently about his relationships in the Middle East, some of which go back a half-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked Florida Woman, Busted For Skinny-Dipping In Stranger's Pool...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/florida/skinny-dipper-popped-790521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upon returning home from a doctor’s appointment Monday afternoon, a Florida retiree discovered a naked woman skinny-dipping in his pool, according to cops who arrested the intruder on trespass and r</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inevitable Weaponization of App Data Is Here...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbxp8/grindr-location-data-priest-weaponization-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Substack publication used location data from Grindr to out a priest without their consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For First Time Ever, Scientists Witness Chimps Killing Gorillas...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/for-the-first-time-ever-scientists-witness-chimps-kill-1847330442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surprising observation could yield new insights into early human evolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Staggering scale of China prisons, detention camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/meghara/china-camps-prisons-xinjiang-muslims-size</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is the most complete picture yet of the staggering scale of China’s prisons and detention camps for Muslims in Xinjiang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin's 50% Drop From Peak Hammers Crypto Loans, Derivatives...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-50-drop-peak-hammers-151328225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The 2021 Bitcoin bubble is deflating and hitting a $1.3 trillion industry built on to-the-moon speculation and rampant leverage.The damage from the latest selloff is spreading across the world of crypto loans, options and futures -- wiping out money-spinning strategies from the famous basis trade to yield farming.Even with Wednesday’s rebound, Bitcoin at around $31,700 is still trading near the lower end of its range over the past two months, and down about 50% from the April peak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai makes fake rain to tackle 120-degree heatwave!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/dubai-makes-fake-rain-created-24585337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the United Arab Emirates sizzles in temperatures of up to 50C, Dubai has trialled a rain-enhancing technology that sees drones unleashing electrical charges in clouds so they produce rain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Reilly Gets Restraining Order Against Andrea Mackris Appearance on 'THE VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bill-oreilly-gets-restraining-order-against-andrea-mackris-appearance-on-the-view</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrea Mackris was slated to tell her story on national TV—until O’Reilly went to court to say she is breaching her NDA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor gave meth to teen girl and raped her, cops say...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article252907653.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 15-year-old girl was admitted to a hospital with complications from smoking meth, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Catholic Church official resigns over report linking him to gay bars, GRINDR...</title>
      <link>https://www.pillarcatholic.com/p/pillar-investigates-usccb-gen-sec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pillarcatholic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pillar Investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone photos reveal shocking truth of parched landscape...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/drone-photos-reveal-the-shocking-truth-of-californias-parched-landscape/ar-AAMom1V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lake Orville, Lake Folsom and Lake Trinity give a glimpse into the state's dry spell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runaway bull escapes slaughterhouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/runaway-bull-is-still-on-the-loose-in-suffolk-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Wednesday morning, a runaway bull is still on the loose in Suffolk County on Long Island after it escaped from a slaughterhouse in Manorville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamma Sweeps Illinois...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/07/20/covid-19-gamma-delta-variant-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Illinois while COVID-19 cases continue to rise quickly, the Delta variant is not the variant of most concern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN APPROVAL 53%...</title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big companies quietly complain about tax hikes, while preparing to profit from infrastructure deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/some-big-companies-quietly-complain-about-potential-tax-hikes-while-preparing-to-profit-from-infrastructure-deal/ar-AAMoJbr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least a dozen profitable major U.S. companies paid little or no U.S. income tax in 2020 and today are active in industry groups that object to helping fund with taxes the same public work projects they want to profit from, according to interviews and data compiled by The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA HOSPITALIZATIONS HIGHEST IN MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/california-coronavirus-hospitalizations-hit-highest-point-in-months-as-delta-spreads/ar-AAMotGz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Statewide, the number of coronavirus-positive patients in the hospital more than doubled in the last month, and the rate has climbed further in the last two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway scrambles warplanes to escort Russian bombers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210721133849-yhgka</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-NORWAY/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Norway scrambles warplanes to escort Russian bombers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's so hot in Dubai, government paying scientists to make it rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/its-so-hot-in-dubai-the-government-is-paying-scientists-to-make-it-rain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent rainstorm was the result of one of the UAE's newest efforts to increase rainfall in a desert nation that gets about four inches a year on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FAA reports 100 cases of unruly airline passengers in week...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/564071-faa-reports-nearly-100-cases-of-unruly-airline-passengers-in-past-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) has recorded nearly 100 cases of unruly airline passengers in the past week amid a surge in aggressive and violent behavior at airports and on flights as more people return</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Water Witches of California...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/21/meet-the-water-witches-of-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good morning. I first heard about the occult practice of water divining in Australia. There, much like in California, heat,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Monkeypox fears as CDC monitors 200 people in 27 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3320002/monkeypox-fears-cdc-tracking-200-people-exposure/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE CDC is monitoring more than 200 people in 27 states for possible exposure to monkeypox after contact with an infected Texan. The infected individual contracted the disease in Nigeria before tra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More trouble surrounds The Don...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9807631/Trumps-friend-Tom-Barrack-ARRESTED-acting-agent-UAE.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melania's former advisor and once best friend, Stephanie Winston Wolkoff told DailyMail.com, 'this could be the beginning of the end' of the Trumps after Barrack was arrested on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pegasus scandal: Are we all becoming unknowing spies?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-57910355</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We may be stepping into a world in which we are all spies - and at the same time are all spied on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA GRIPS USA</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/07/21/mayo-doctors-strong-warning-over-covids-delta-variant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota Department of Health say 99% of new cases in Minnesota are in unvaccinated people, and 75% of those new cases are the Delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team chiropractor sorry for virus protocol-Nazi post...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-health-coronavirus-pandemic-protocols-e3a6242ff6a618742db589e9d0371824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The chiropractor for the American women's wrestling team has apologized after comparing Olympic COVID-19 protocols to Nazi Germany in a social media post. Rosie Gallegos-Main, a chiropractor for women's wrestling since 2009, said in a letter to the USA Wrestling Diversity, Equity and Inclusion Committee on Wednesday she was sorry “for my poor judgment and my choice to share this message.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems blast Bezos space trip, demand he pay 'fair share' of taxes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/21/dems-blast-jeff-bezos-space-trip-demand-he-pay-more-taxes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin founder Jeff Bezos is being slammed for his “despicable” comments following his space flight Tuesday, in which he thanked Amazon employees and customers for financing his tr…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
