<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court embarks on most dramatic reckoning for abortion rights in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-embarks-on-most-dramatic-reckoning-for-abortion-rights-in-decades/ar-AAQ8aUQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a one-month span, court will take up cases from Texas and Mississippi that could alter constitutional right to abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/10/30/alec-baldwin-speaks-first-time-on-camera-halyna-hutchins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baldwin breaks his silence in person while laying low in Vermont.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin speaks out about fatal shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/30/alec-baldwin-breaks-silence-on-fatal-shooting-of-halyna-hutchins-on-rust-set/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A haggard looking Alec Baldwin broke his silence Saturday, declaring his friendship with Halyna Hutchins — the cinematographer he accidentally shot and killed on the set of his film “Ru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Gas Used As Weapon?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russia-close-using-natural-gas-weapon-europes-gas-crunch-biden-energy-adviser-2021-10-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Joe Biden's global energy security adviser said on Monday that Russian President Vladimir Putin is getting close to using natural gas as a political tool if Russia is holding back fuel exports to Europe as it suffers an energy crunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Pipeline Changes Direction, and Energy Politics Come to Fore...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/a-russian-pipeline-changes-direction-and-energy-politics-come-to-the-fore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW — Natural gas, already in short supply in Europe this fall, began moving away from Germany on Saturday and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 83% Have Witnessed Paranormal Activity In Homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/moved-because-house-haunted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;83 percent of respondents say they have witnessed some paranormal activity inside their own home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Anti-'White Lotus' Giving Voice to Native Hawaiians and Their Colonialist Struggle...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/anti-white-lotus-giving-voice-030018485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HandoutChris Kahunahana has been trying to make films for nearly 30 years.Finally, his debut feature Waikiki has seen the light of day, first screened to audiences at the Hawaiian International Film Festival amid the ongoing pandemic in December 2019. It is credited as the first narrative feature-length film written and directed by a native Hawaiian filmmaker.In Hawaii, there is no shortage of stories to tell. “Our traditions were passed down orally. So storytelling is just a part of what we do</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hey Joe!' Leaders josh around at G20 summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211030-hey-joe-leaders-josh-around-at-g20-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When world leaders finally got together for the G20 summit in Rome after over two years apart, the mood was festive, with formalities temporarily ditched in favour of fist-pumping and football quips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They never forget face. Research delves into how 'super-recognizers' do this...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/they-never-forget-a-face-research-delves-into-how-e2-80-98super-recognizers-e2-80-99-can-do-this/ar-AAQ8gDF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people with this skill can recall a face even years later — and if they’ve seen it only once and briefly — whether in person or in a photo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERIC SCHMIDT: WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO COEXIST WITH MACHINES...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/a-i-is-not-a-ok/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first time I interviewed Eric Schmidt, a dozen years ago when he was the C.E.O. of Google, I had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS FEAR VIRGINIA DISASTER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-elections-virginia-terry-mcauliffe-b956177300be965ec34b1ddb75bb5042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — For four years, nothing rallied Democrats like the push to get Donald Trump out of office. Now, they're not sure what to do without him. Democrats in Virginia are scrambling to stave off disaster in the state's governor's race — the most competitive major election since Trump left the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC VAX FALLOUT: LESS COPS, MORE TRASH...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-police-new-york-new-york-city-52cc12e52d33f664e8e144aa59436590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Mounting trash. Closed firehouses. Fewer police and ambulances on the street. That’s the possibility New York City is bracing for come Monday as a COVID-19 vaccine mandate looms and thousands of municipal workers remain unwilling to get the shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG's in 10 states join fight against Biden order...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/579240-attorneys-general-in-10-gop-states-join-fight-against-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten attorneys general in states with GOP governors shave joined the fight to push back against a Biden administration vaccine mandate for federal contractors, arguing that it is “unconstitutional, unlawful, and unwi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving the Western some swagger in 'HARDER THEY FALL'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-movies-race-and-ethnicity-c8886f2624016af756ae5672af5fef89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — If you had any doubt that Jeymes Samuel, the director of “The Harder They Fall” and the British musician known as the Bullits, loves Westerns, then you haven't heard him sing Dean Martin's “My Rifle, My Pony and Me” from John Ford's “Rio Bravo.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrett, Kavanaugh Supply Majority to Deny Religious-Liberty Claim on Jab Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/10/barrett-and-kavanaugh-supply-majority-to-deny-religious-liberty-claim-on-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They joined Roberts and Court progressives in declining relief to Maine health-care providers, who must now be vaxxed against their beliefs or lose their jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden's 'gentle art' of house cleaning before death...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211030-sweden-s-gentle-art-of-house-cleaning-before-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her elegant apartment in the centre of Stockholm, 84-year-old Lena Sundgren looks at her crowded bookshelf, lit by the glow of a candle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subpoenas real worry for lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/579175-subpoenas-are-a-real-worry-for-lawmakers-facing-jan-6-questions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers who may have been involved with the planning of rallies on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossilized charcoal shows once-temperate Antarctica was often hit by wildfires, report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/antarctica-temperature-wildfire-fossil/2021/10/29/a6bd1f82-3770-11ec-8be3-e14aaacfa8ac_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports says “lightning strikes, fireballs, sparks and volcanic activity” were regular phenomenon in what is now an icy continent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two doors, few windows, 4,500 students: Architect quits over billionaire mega dorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/two-doors-few-windows-and-4500-students-architect-quits-over-billionaire-e2-80-99s-mega-dorm/ar-AAQ7Nkq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11-story, 1.68-million-square-foot building, made up of eight-person living units, would house 4,500 students, 94 percent of whom would not have windows in their compact single-occupancy bedrooms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA's Hidden Billionaire: How  Retail Trader Made $7 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-hidden-billionaire-how-lretial-trader-leo-koguan-made-usd-7-billion-040715825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore-based Leo KoGuan — who picked up stock trading in 2019 — has quietly amassed one of the single biggest stakes in Elon Musk’s company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'Let's Go Brandon' became code for insulting Biden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lets-go-brandon-what-does-it-mean-republicans-joe-biden-ab13db212067928455a3dba07756a160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When Republican Rep. Bill Posey of Florida ended an Oct. 21 House floor speech with a fist pump and the phrase “Let’s go, Brandon!” it may have seemed cryptic and weird to many who were listening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX employees file federal labor charge over Chappelle controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/netflix-employees-file-labor-charges-023520645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two trans Netflix employees have filed labor charges alleging the company retaliated against them for speaking out against Dave Chappelle's special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency of violent threats on Capitol Hill unnerves staffers...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Frequency-of-violent-threats-on-Capitol-Hill-16576979.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - It was her first bomb scare on the job, and yet the work day Wednesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida activist says cop warned her not to wear condo costume to Halloween party...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/florida-activist-says-cop-warned-her-not-to-wear-condo-costume-to-halloween-party/article_d0392bd1-3a1c-5a56-a3e6-678e9ab7b310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Imagine getting a spooky call from a cop warning you not to wear a boxy condo costume to a Halloween party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Thinks Unthinkable: Life After Elizabeth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/what-happens-when-queen-elizabeth-ii-dies-britain-must-confront-the-question</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything will change — from the head on bank notes to the sense of certainty and continuity Elizabeth II has so calmly embodied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Hasn't Left China in 21 Months. Covid Only Part of Reason...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/xi-hasnt-left-china-in-21-months-covid-may-be-only-part-of-the-reason/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the presidents and prime ministers of the Group of 20 nations meet in Rome this weekend, China’s leader, Xi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Assaults Worsening Crisis at Rikers, Jail Officers Say...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/sexual-assaults-are-worsening-a-crisis-at-rikers-jail-officers-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One female correction officer was attacked and choked by a man who had been convicted of sexual assault. Another, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Rural West, Residents Taking Firefighting Into Own Hands...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/in-the-rural-west-some-residents-are-taking-firefighting-into-their-own-hands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALISADES, Wash. — Molly Linville vividly remembers the “wall of flame” that tore through the grasslands of her 600-acre ranch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did The Don's $300 Million SPAC Deal Skirt Securities Laws?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/29/trumps-300-million-spac-deal-may-have-skirted-securities-laws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just days after Donald J. Trump left the White House, two former contestants on his reality show, “The Apprentice,” approached</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew Mounts Attack Against Woman Who Accused Him of Sex Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/29/prince-andrew-mounts-attack-against-woman-who-accused-him-of-sexual-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Prince Andrew on Friday issued a blistering attack on a woman who has accused him in a lawsuit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants call logs, aide's notes hidden from Jan 6 panel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-lawsuits-united-states-capitol-siege-4e55ed79b42043fbdef1628d684e1495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump is trying to block documents including call logs, drafts of remarks and speeches and handwritten notes from his chief of staff relating to the Jan. 6 Capitol insurrection from being released to the committee investigating the riot, the National Archives revealed in a court filing early Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ HOSPITAL MANDATES BOOSTERS</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article255384931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers at a New Jersey hospital have until Dec. 24 to get a COVID booster shot if they got the Johnson &amp; Johnson shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Deadliest September Since WWII With Virus Untamed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-suffers-deadliest-september-since-world-war-ii-with-covid-untamed/ar-AAQ6yVy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia suffered its deadliest September since World War II, according to figures published Friday, even before the peak of its current wave of the Covid-19 pandemic forced authorities to order non-working days for the first week of November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD preparing for crush of retirements ahead of vax mandate... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/28/nypd-preparing-for-slew-of-retirements-amid-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is bracing for mass resignations over the city’s COVID-19 vaccine mandate — issuing numerous guidance Thursday for cops who would rather quit than get the jab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  VA GOV RACE TOSS UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/virginia-governor-s-race-a-toss-up-as-election-day-nears-post-schar-school-poll-finds/ar-AAQ69nW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin are locked in a tight race for the Executive Mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  MORE REST FOR QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10145583/Queen-advised-doctors-continue-rest-TWO-WEEKS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 95-year-old will not undertake any official visits and will be confined to 'light, desk-based' duties only, a Buckingham Palace statement said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian had right to mock disabled teen, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/oct/29/canada-jeremy-gabriel-mike-ward-discrimination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legal battle had waged for more than a decade and raised questions over satire and the need to protect vulnerable children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Munger bankrolls windowless dorm. Architect quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/29/business/ucsb-munger-hall/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Charlie Munger is bankrolling the design of a massive dormitory at the University of California, Santa Barbara. The $1.5 billion project comes with a major catch — 94% of the dorm's single occupancy rooms have no windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy agencies may never be able to identify origins...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029205834-bc0i1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ORIGINS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-U.S. spy agencies may never be able to identify origins of COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Ramp Up Patrols: Potential Threats to Malls...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/local/virginia/fairfax-police-ramp-up-police-presence-for-halloween-weeken/65-976cff2b-5f34-4e62-91f6-24c29509cf62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fairfax County Police Chief Kevin Davis said his department had received information about "potential public safety impacts" to malls and shopping centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising ESPN personality taken off air after DUI arrest...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/29/espn-personality-harry-lyles-jr-off-air-after-dui-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up-and-coming College GameDay personality Harry Lyles Jr. will be off the show Saturday because of a DUI arrest after last week’s program in Los Angeles</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
