<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fish suffer pain and stress, claims report that criticizes welfare failings...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/apr/02/farmed-fish-suffer-pain-and-stress-says-report-that-criticises-welfare-failings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of Atlantic salmon and trout, the aquaculture sector should focus on cultivating species with less complex needs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St. fixation on quick profits 'wreaking havoc in real economy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Wall-Street-s-fixation-on-quick-profits-wreaking-16073231.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast sums of money sloshing around the financial sector are enriching shareholders but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America passes 25 million corona infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/latin-america-passes-25-million-coronavirus-infections/ar-BB1ffqJI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin America and the Caribbean passed the 25 million mark Friday for recorded coronavirus cases as a surge in infections saw countries place restrictions on travel and movement while vaccine campaigns catch up. An AFP tally showed the region reaching the grim milestone of 25,001,533 infections, putting it in third place after Europe with 44.2 million cases and the United States and Canada with over 31.5 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risked player walkout if not moved...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/mlb-risked-player-walkout-star-230256192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseball risked having several top players boycott the All-Star Game had it not been moved from Atlanta, according to some who celebrated Friday's announcement by commissioner Rob Manfred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA PASSES 100 MILLION VACCINATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-million-vaccines-europe-hiccups.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States reaped the fruits Friday of its vaccination campaign against Covid-19 as it became the first nation to reach 100 million people, but Europe's rollout faced fresh impediments and South America tightened restrictions in the face of Brazil's soaring infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops open criminal investigation into Texans QB Watson after flood of sex harassment claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2630281/houston-police-department-investigating-deshaun-watson-texans-qb-allegations/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deshaun Watson is being investigated by the Houston Police Department after another person filed a complaint against the Texans quarterback. “Today, a complainant filed a report with the Hous…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA HERO IN MEGA MESS!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Gaetz-is-said-to-have-boasted-of-his-access-to-16073588.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Matt Gaetz repeatedly boasted to people involved in Florida politics...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With new immigration role, Kamala gets perilous assignment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-new-immigration-role-harris-gets-a-politically-perilous-assignment/ar-BB1ffEWc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democrats worry that the vice president’s new task will collide with her long-term ambitions and that, for better or for worse, she could own much of what happens on the border in coming months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS:  NFI...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/matt-gaetz-appeared-on-fox-news-18-times-in-march-his-scandal-has-gotten-zero-mentions-on-the-network-in-april/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz is such a regular presence on Fox News that when it was reported he was eyeing an early retirement from Congress for a gig at Newsmax, the biggest surprise was the choice of network. Gaetz appeared on Fox News 18 times in March. According to a Washington Post analysis, in the last […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossings in March jumped to highest in 15 years!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Border-crossings-in-March-jumped-to-highest-level-16073570.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Preliminary enforcement data for March confirms what border officials have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Federal Taxes for Dozens of Big, Profitable Companies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/02/no-federal-taxes-for-dozens-of-big-profitable-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as the Biden administration is pushing to raise taxes on corporations, a new study finds that at least 55 of America’s largest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few  rush to defend...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prosecutors-possible-payments-for-sex-gaetz-investigation-b43b8340f9e81f6c6eebf95e956be962</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The political peril for conservative Republican Rep. Matt Gaetz deepened Friday as the often outlandish, Trump-styled provocateur appeared politically isolated amid a federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOU'RE OUT:  MLB All-Star Game moved from GA after voting law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mlb-baseball-rob-manfred-georgia-voting-rights-e1cf72c8b2d61afad049cae498ccbbe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Atlanta lost Major League Baseball’s summer All-Star Game on Friday over the league’s objections to sweeping changes to Georgia voting laws that critics — including the CEOs of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin Airport arrests after 2 refuse mandatory quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-56617914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irish broadcaster RTÉ says it's understood the two women had travelled for a cosmetic procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMA fighter has finger severed in match...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mixed-martial-arts-philadelphia-martial-arts-2867c4cd67ba048c1dd1efe287b40f5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — A mixed martial arts fighter had his finger severed during a match in Philadelphia, but doctors were eventually able to reattach it. Khetag Pliev was injured Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos mulling CHARGERS purchase?</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/is-jeff-bezos-checking-out-opportunity-to-purchase-chargers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ownership of the Los Angeles Chargers may be in jeopardy, and former Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos just might swoop in to save the day. That is, if you really</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Northern Edge' brings firepower to Alaska, with eye on Arctic jockeying...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/04/01/northern-edge-brings-firepower-to-alaska-with-an-eye-on-arctic-jockeying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pacific Air Forces will lead the Army, Navy, and Marine Corps in the biennial, 12-day Northern Edge exercise beginning May 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVES Blast Move: Victimizes Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/02/braves-respond-after-mlb-moves-2021-all-star-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlanta Braves are digging in their cleats. Shortly after Major League Baseball announced it would be moving the 2021 All-Star Game from Atlanta amid backlash over new Georgia voting laws, the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida prohibits passports, citing 'freedom'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210402-florida-prohibits-vaccine-passports-citing-freedom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida prohibits vaccine passports, citing 'freedom'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVES Blast Move: Victimizes Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/Braves/status/1378072546088738818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO: GOOD COVID NEWS THREATENS AGENDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the U.S. and Iran agree to indirect talks next week in a possible breakthrough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth to 'super twins' conceived 3 weeks apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/super-twins-superfetation-three-weeks-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Roberts said when she found out she was pregnant with a second baby, she was shocked. "It was a good job I was laying on the couch or I would have fainted on the floor," she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Friend has been singing to the feds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9430921/Matt-Gaetzs-arrest-imminent-sources-say-Joel-Greenberg-singing-feds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep Matt Gaetz is expected to be indicted within the next few weeks as sources say former Florida official and friend Joel Greenberg has been 'singing to the feds' in the investigation against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB All-Star Game moved from Atlanta after voting law...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/sports/atlanta-braves/mlb-will-move-all-star-game-out-of-atlanta/TCUEJPUPZZD2RCO3DY5OZH62OU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game, a marquee event that had been scheduled for Truist Park in July, will be moved out of Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerable Dems fret after getting shock: AOC campaign cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/02/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-campaign-contributions-478943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez's largesse — and an oversight at the campaign headquarters — has raised awkward questions among her colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider-trading indictment shows ties to BLOOMBERG scoops...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/business_of_news/an-insider-trading-indictment-shows-ties-to-bloomberg-news-scoops.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more than six months, federal prosecutors say, a New York man used inside information to make illegal profits in the stock market—and a core element of his alleged scheme was his interaction with Bloomberg News, which published several stories shortly after the trader arranged to make significant purchases of the companies’ shares. Last month, […]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite Public School Changes Admissions To Help Whites, Hurt Asians...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/04/02/thomas-jefferson-asian-admissions-plf-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the name of helping racial minorities, officials are adopting a plan that would boost whites at the expense of Asian Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After year of 'hibernation,' cities wake up...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/after-year-of-coronavirus-hibernation-israels-cities-wake-up-663884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATIONAL AFFAIRS: “When the shuk is full, the heart is full,” a vendor in Mahaneh Yehuda told a television reporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% of adults dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/about-40-percent-of-adults-in-the-united-states-have-received-one-dose-of-a-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America is hitting a milestone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians mark Good Friday amid lingering virus woes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/christians-good-friday-coronavirus-93d314d71d1b64ee936c5727c4c2c76b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Christians in the Holy Land are marking Good Friday this year amid signs the coronavirus crisis is winding down, with religious sites open to limited numbers of faithful but none...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer crashes through school bus, lands on sleeping student!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/wild-video-shows-deer-crashing-through-school-bus-landing-sleeping-n1262896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He’s laying there asleep and the deer comes in, lays on top of him and rolls off onto the floor,” a Virginia school official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonic origins aside, checks please evangelical critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/demonic-origins-aside-checks-please-biden-s-evangelical-critics/article_527e4235-367d-51cd-b160-9a940b0087e9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelical Christians and small-government activists, among the fiercest critics of President Joe Biden and the Democratic Congress, are finding solace in $1,400 stimulus checks that some are sharing with churches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a prescription to die remains tricky even as aid-in-dying bills gain momentum...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/montana-medical-aid-in-dying-legal-gray-zone-reviving-legislation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access to physician-assisted death is expanding across the U.S., but the procedure remains in Montana’s legal gray zone more than a decade after the state Supreme Court ruled physicians could use a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER STRAIN FEARS ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2627827/covid-super-mutation-beat-vaccines-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID could mutate into a new super variant which could beat vaccines, make people sicker and reinfect victims in a devastating new outbreak, leading experts have warned. Scientists told The S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torches 'Looneyville' FOXNEWS and 'nut' hosts...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/john-boehner-spills-on-shocking-meeting-with-roger-ailes-to-try-to-put-a-leash-on-fox-news-hosts-like-nut-sean-hannity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former House Speaker John Boehner did not hold former Fox News founder Roger Ailes, or current prime time host Sean Hannity, in the highest esteem. Politico has just published an excerpt adapted from his book On the House, to be published by St. Martin’s Press on April 13, 2021, in which Boehner calls out the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of new witnesses to testify at Netanyahu trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/hundreds-of-new-witnesses-to-testify-at-netanyahus-trial-663890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu’s trial hears witnesses, and the public will hear what the cases are about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Grew by 136,000 Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/national/terence-p-jeffrey/government-grew-136000-workers-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal, state and local governments in the United States increased their employment by a combined 136,000 in March, according to the numbers released today by the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACKER...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-variant-tracker-where-different-strains-are-spreading-ffd71934-1596-43e6-923d-32c4698e2f8b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our live tracker keeps you updated with the need-to-know info on the new coronavirus variants now spreading through the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUPER MUTATION' FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14509332/covid-super-mutation-beat-vaccines-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID could mutate into a new super variant which could beat vaccines, make people sicker and reinfect victims in a devastating new outbreak, leading experts have warned. Scientists told The S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby boy 'first in world born with three penises', doctors say...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/baby-boy-first-world-born-23841946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unidentified child, from Duhok city, Iraq, has a rare condition called triphallia and it was only diagnosed after three months when his parents discovered swelling in his scrotum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang hospitalized with likely kidney stone...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210402132703-55zwe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/YANG-NEW YORK (PIX):Andrew Yang, New York City mayoral candidate, hospitalized with likely kidney stone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Gov Was Tested by Pandemic. Now Recall Looms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/02/californias-governor-was-tested-by-the-pandemic-now-a-recall-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — Things have been looking up in California. Vaccines will soon be available to everyone over 16. Los Angeles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just living his life'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210331224231-zj3vm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/GEORGEFLOYD (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-'Just living his life': Jurors see videos taken before and after Floyd's deadly arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Atmosphere of terror': Bloody rise of Mexico's top cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-atmosphere-of-terror-the-bloody-rise-of-mexicos-top-cartel/ar-BB1feRlt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was mid-spring when residents of the wasteland behind Guadalajara’s international airport noticed a dog roaming their community with a strange object in its mouth: a human forearm. Search teams in the ramshackle neighbourhood of La Piedrera entered a roofless red brick shack flanked by trees decked with bright orange mistletoe. Under several layers of dusky earth they made an even more grotesque discovery. “There were 26 of them here. We...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas GOP candidate bashes Chinese immigrants: 'I don't want them here at all'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Texas-GOP-candidate-bashes-Chinese-immigrants-16071973.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a political forum on Wednesday, GOP congressional candidate Sery Kim falsely suggested...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TEXT MESSAGES</title>
      <link>https://uk.sports.yahoo.com/news/text-messages-led-feds-matt-132534243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GettyIn late January 2020, U.S. Secret Service agents received information that Rep. Matt Gaetz had accompanied a Florida county tax official they were already investigating on an unusual nighttime visit to a government office—where the local official was allegedly making fake IDs, a source close to the investigation told The Daily Beast.That tip to the feds came in a text message conversation that Seminole County Tax Collector Joel Greenberg had with an employee explaining why they were both in the office one weekend two years earlier, according to this person.A timestamp visible in the text message thread indicated the conversation took place on Monday, April 16, 2018.The Creepy, Disturbing Case That Ensnared Matt GaetzAccording to three people with direct knowledge of the incident: Greenberg visited the Lake Mary, Florida branch of his tax collection agency that weekend. Grainy surveillance footage captured Greenberg standing near a manager’s desk with another man. Greenberg forgot to set the alarm on the way out, which concerned the assistant branch manager when she walked into the office Monday morning. That employee was surprised to find that driver licenses—which are normally turned in when expired at the tax office for shredding—were scattered all over the desk instead of in the appropriate disposal basket. She reviewed the camera footage and alerted her boss, who in turn contacted Greenberg via text.“Did you happen to visit the Lake Mary Office on the weekend?” the text message read.The image obtained by The Daily Beast shows that Greenberg allegedly responded: “Yes I was showing congressman Gaetz what our operation looked like. Did I leave something on?”When Greenberg later came under investigation by the Secret Service for identity theft and stalking, agents approached former employees at the tax office to obtain proof of the public official’s activities. That’s when they were suddenly directed to Gaetz.According to the source who provided the text message conversation, who spoke on condition of anonymity to guarantee their safety, Secret Service agents directed them in the final days of January 2020 to print out the full text message conversation with Greenberg from online AT&amp;T records. That source said those text messages were delivered to the Secret Service, Florida Department of Law Enforcement, and most recently, another federal agency.Gaetz, a Florida Republican, is now the target of a Justice Department investigation that is focusing on allegations that the Republican congressman and Greenberg recruited young women and paid them for sex, according to The New York Times.CNN first reported the existence of text messages on Thursday. The Orlando Sentinel confirmed their existence as well.On Wednesday, The Daily Beast attempted to file a public records request to obtain a copy of the video surveillance that is believed to show Gaetz with Greenberg on that weekend in April 2018. However, a Seminole County representative indicated that the video is unavailable because the government agency has a policy of deleting all surveillance footage after 60 days. County officials would not comment on what exactly employees have told federal investigators about their recollection of the incident.The Daily Beast also attempted to reach the former employee who interacted with Greenberg via text message, but was unsuccessful. That employee eventually signed a $50,000 settlement with the Office of the Seminole County Tax Collector over claims of unfair retaliation at work after Greenberg allegedly used a circle of personal friends he hired at the agency to harass and intimidate her and her family. That settlement bars her from “false or defamatory statements” about her former employer, but importantly does not prevent her from speaking to government investigators, according to a copy obtained by The Daily Beast.Republicans Have Been Waiting for a Matt Gaetz Scandal to BreakHer attorney, Daniel A. Pérez, declined to comment on any current efforts to assist federal law enforcement.The U.S. Attorney’s Office for the Middle District of Florida would not confirm the existence of an ongoing investigation into Gaetz.Prosecutors there do have an ongoing case against Greenberg, who came under federal scrutiny after he repeatedly angered fellow county officials with his bizarre, erratic behavior.According to people familiar with the investigation, Secret Service agents were initially interested in Greenberg’s failed attempt to allow Seminole County residents to pay their taxes in Bitcoin. Attorneys have revealed in court that the federal probe quietly began by April 2019. That began to heat up when Greenberg ran for re-election and faced political opposition from a fine arts teacher at Trinity Preparatory School.Federal agents arrested him at his Lake Mary home on June 17, 2020, and the case initially hinged on accusations that Greenberg had set up fake online profiles to defame the teacher and had sent several letters to the school with lurid accusations that his opponent had engaged in sexual misconduct with a student.As of Tuesday, that case has now vastly expanded to a 33-count indictment that includes a diverse list of crimes that range from wirefraud to sex trafficking. Investigators say Greenberg recruited at least one teenager between 14 and 17 years old to engage in a “commercial sex act” between May and November 2017 in Central Florida and elsewhere.Matt Gaetz Keeps Digging Deeper Holes for HimselfInvestigators also say that Greenberg used his privileged access to Florida’s driver license database to look up private information on “individuals” with whom he “was engaged in ‘sugar-daddy’ relationships.”Additionally, Greenberg is also accused of making fake IDs—potentially explaining why the 2018 surveillance footage raised concerns that led to that text message conversation handed to investigators.The Daily Beast obtained text messages handed to federal investigators that allegedly show Greenberg acknowledging that he visited the office on the weekend of August 4, 2018, where there were driver licenses “scattered across the desks and not put away in an organized manner.”Greenberg has maintained a close relationship with Gaetz for several years. Both were rising stars in Florida’s Republican Party in 2016. They have taken selfies together with political operative Roger Stone in 2017, at AIPAC in 2018, and at the White House in 2019. Gaetz publicly lent his support to Greenberg, cheering him as “a disrupter” who should run for Congress.They were also together in the Florida panhandle region on July 4, 2019 when they called a state legislator, Rep. Anna V. Eskamani, and left her a peculiar voicemail that has been obtained by The Daily Beast.“My dear Anna, this is your favorite tax collector. I’m up in the panhandle with your favorite U.S. congressman, Mr. Gaetz,” Greenberg starts to say.“Hi Anna!” Gaetz jumps in.“And, uh, we were just chatting about you, and talking about your lovely qualities,” Greenberg continued.“We think you’re the future of the Democratic Party in Florida!” Gaetz said.On Thursday, Eskamani told The Daily Beast that she maintained Greenberg at arm’s length for years. Their interactions started when she called him out over Islamaphobic comments then helped him connect with the Muslim community to recover from that. Eskamani said she cautiously entertained “weird” contacts from Greenberg and Gaetz that made her uncomfortable.“We were not friends. We never hung out. We didn't talk ever, really. I just played nice. For so many women you're either very blunt and be called a bitch, or you try to play nice and pivot and deflate,” she said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD: Border officials say more sneaking past them as crossings soar, agents overwhelmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Border-officials-say-more-people-are-sneaking-16071962.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 1,000 people per day are sneaking into the United States without being identified...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden opens up about family intervention, addresses laptop reports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hunter-biden-joe-family-intervention-laptop-reports-memoir/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunter Biden described an emotional intervention his family staged at his father's home in Wilmington during the 2020 presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
