<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>In baseball first, YANKEES name woman to manage minor league team...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/baseball-first-new-york-yankees-name-woman-manage-minor-league-team-rcna11603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Yankees are promoting Rachel Balkovec to manager of the Low A Tampa Tarpons, making her the first woman to skipper a team affiliated with Major League Baseball, according to two people familiar with the move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike in autoimmune diseases blamed on fast food...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/10/spike-in-autoimmune-diseases-blamed-on-fast-food-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asia and the Middle East have seen the biggest upswing in inflammatory bowel disease — these regions have experienced a boom of the fast food industry during that time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Durst, real estate heir and convicted killer, dead at 78...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/10/nyc-real-estate-heir-robert-durst-dead-at-78/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Durst, the bizarre New York real estate scion and long suspected serial killer, has died. He was 78.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Western troops sick in Wuhan months before Covid outbreak officially began...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4427364/western-troops-ill-wuhan-months-before-covid-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WESTERN troops allegedly fell ill with a mystery illness after attending the World Military Games in Wuhan shortly before the Covid outbreak officially began. A long-serving Canadian officer was am…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagine another Civil War, but this time in every state...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/10/1071082955/imagine-another-american-civil-war-but-this-time-in-every-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If America has another civil war, it is more likely to be a war within the states than between them. Citizens of any state of any size, red or blue, may not have to go far to find a fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge prehistoric 'sea dragon' fossil discovered in reservoir...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/prehistoric-sea-dragon-ichthyosaur-fossil-discovered-uk-reservoir-rcna11565</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The skeleton of an extinct prehistoric reptile predator, known as a sea dragon, is the largest and most complete ever discovered in the U.K., researchers said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable Cabinet: Texts reveal influence of hosts on previous White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-cable-cabinet-new-texts-reveal-the-influence-of-fox-hosts-on-previous-white-house/ar-AASADdl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petition for $2,000 monthly stimulus checks has 3 million signatures...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/10/petition-for-2000-stimulus-checks-reaches-3-million-signatures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurant owner Stephanie Bonin started a petition for monthly payments in March 2020. Nearly two years later, the cause still resonates with many Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Deadliest NYC blaze in 30 years tears through Bronx building, 17 killed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/10/bronx-fires-death-toll-revised-down-to-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Eric Adams said during a press briefing Monday that the toll is actually currently 17, with eight children and nine adults dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOUND BY HOUSEKEEPING AFTER MISSING CHECKOUT</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4433230/bob-saget-found-dead-ritz-carlton-orlando/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOB Saget was reportedly found dead by hotel housekeeping on Sunday afternoon after he failed to checkout on time. The iconic actor and comic was found dead at the Ritz Carlton in Orlando, Flo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coldest air in years coming to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/weather/coldest-air-three-years-coming-parts-country-rcna11618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday started the work week with 15 million people under wind chill alerts stretching from the Northern Plains and Upper Midwest into the interior Northeast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More commentary, less news?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/media/jesse-watters-fox-7pm-host/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesse Watters, the right-wing talk show host who throughout his career has courted controversy with incendiary commentary, will be Fox's new 7 p.m. host, the network announced on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duluth -18&amp;#8457;...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/coldest-air-of-the-season-to-send-midwest-northeast-into-deep-freeze/1122650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bitter cold is expected to keep temperatures in the teens and single digits in spots, with one location not expected to climb above zero on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson to launch 'Living with Covid' plan in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/what-living-covid-boris-johnson-25900277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson is reportedly drawing up plans for a "living with Covid" strategy which aim to avoid any long-term restrictions in England from March this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Deltacron' likely result of lab error...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/10/deltacron-variant-prompts-doubts-among-experts-as-possible-lab-error.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global experts are casting doubts over reports of a new possible Covid strain appearing to combine both the delta and omicron variants and dubbed "deltacron."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IDOL' star Aiken will run for NC seat in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article257130772.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former “American Idol” star and Raleigh native declared a run for North Carolina’s 6th Congressional District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jesse Watters named permanent host of 7pm hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/jesse-watters-named-permanent-host-of-7-pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesse Watters has been named the permanent host of the 7 p.m. ET timeslot on Fox News Channel with a new hour-long program "Jesse Watters Primetime," FOX News Media CEO Suzanne Scott announced on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How virus could turn into common cold, or something far worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/living-with-covid-19-how-the-virus-could-turn-into-the-common-cold-or-something/article_95e04922-c47d-58fa-8dce-a931937a03ac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As it races around the world, the COVID-19 omicron variant shows tantalizing hints that it could morph into the ideal virus: highly transmissible, to be sure, but tamed by vaccines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officers rescue pilot seconds before train hits crashed plane on tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2022/01/10/plane-hit-by-train-california/9155052002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers pulled a pilot to safety moments before a train barreled into the downed aircraft on Sunday in Pacoima, Cal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Target for Epstein Prosecutors Could Be His Assistant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/epstein-prosecutors-next-target-after-ghislaine-maxwell-could-be-his-assistant-sarah-kellen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Kellen’s name came up in court time and again as victims of Ghislaine Maxwell and Jeffrey Epstein testified about the rich duo’s sex-trafficking ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran tower now leaning 26 inches with tilt set to progress three inches year...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10384831/Ritzy-San-Francisco-condo-tower-leaning-26-INCHES.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennium Tower has snuck tilted an additional four inches since this summer after construction work cause it to tilt even more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/LAPDHQ/status/1480363436311670784</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENOUGH: More Saying They're 'Vaxxed and Done'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2022/01/covid-omicron-vaccination-rashomon/621199/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID has always divided Americans. The Omicron wave is even dividing the vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet dog ran off into mountain wilderness. Four months later, rescuers found it trapped in 5 feet of snow...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-pet-dog-ran-off-into-the-mountain-wilderness-16763376.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With snow five feet deep and temperatures expected to drop to minus-2, the rescuers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gutfeld has risen to top at FOXNEWS -- and that's no joke...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/Greg-Gutfeld-has-risen-to-the-top-at-Fox-News-16763479.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Greg Gutfeld is picking through a long, narrow closet. He wrenches a painting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES Investigates Pilot's 'Lets Go Brandon' Bag Tag...</title>
      <link>https://simpleflying.com/american-airlines-investigates-pilots-lets-go-brandon-bag-tag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;simpleflying.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines is investigating a disgruntled tweet regarding one of its pilots. The tweet, posted by a passenger,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Children Who Exercise Regularly Get Better Grades In School...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/children-exercise-grades-education-cardiorespiratory-fitness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a correlation between a child's cardiorespiratory health and their grades, particularly in language and math, according to a recent study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort book set for August publication...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/588961-manafort-book-set-for-august-publication</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former top campaign aide to former President Trump is planning a new book set to be published late this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In much of West, walls closing in on anti-vaxxers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-much-of-the-west-the-walls-are-closing-in-on-anti-vaxxers/ar-AASBLqy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM: 40% of Israel could be infected in current wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20220110-40-of-israel-could-be-infected-with-covid-19-in-current-wave-says-pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel could see up to nearly 40 percent of the population infected by coronavirus during the current wave, Prime Minister Naftali Bennett said Sunday, as testing facilities nationwide buckled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrowing tales of escape...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-new-york-bronx-87dc39e8eb2a54643e153c157608942e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Rancid black smoke filling hallways, rising from floor to floor. People tripping and falling as they rushed down darkened stairwells, unable to see. Panic turning to sorrow, as residents who escaped a fire at a high-rise Bronx apartment building learned of neighbors who did not survive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian judge says Djokovic can stay but saga not over...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-novak-djokovic-sports-health-australia-3e4fd65e0ac87c85e6fcc6b968a62869</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia (AP) — Tennis star Novak Djokovic won a court battle Monday to stay in Australia to contest the Australian Open despite not being vaccinated against COVID-19, but the drama might not be finished, with the government threatening to cancel his visa a second time and deport him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFTs Creep Into Politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/nfts-offered-by-candidates-as-crypto-creeps-into-u-s-politics-1.1705343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressional candidates are beginning to break into the world of cryptocurrency by selling non-fungible tokens to help finance their campaigns in the midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T Cells Triggered by Common Cold Also Fend Off Covid...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/home/science/t-cells-triggered-by-common-cold-also-fend-off-covid-study/articleshow/88810374.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science News: High levels of protective immune cells that fight some common colds also made people less likely to contract Covid-19 in a study. Researchers found hi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Inflation up, virus down as priorities in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-business-health-elections-bb16c5c52e2bf719ec8a0c5415aaf66c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Heading into a critical midterm election year, the top political concerns of Americans are shifting in ways that suggest Democrats face considerable challenges to maintaining their control of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Diehards About to Find Out If Bubble...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-diehards-really-bubble-154108904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- To cryptocurrency true believers, Bitcoin is the ultimate store of value, the most solid hedge against the rampant inflation manufactured by reckless central banks and their money-printing. To skeptics, the crypto world as a whole is a mirage whose massive run-up past $2 trillion was simply the speculative byproduct of the extraordinary amount of easy cash that’s been sloshing around in the global economy — in effect, a big bubble.Most Read from BloombergCypriot Scientist Says Del</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GLOBES NO ONE SEES; NOT EVEN A LIVESTREAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-twitter-golden-globes-were-a-chaotic-mess?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Succession,’ ‘The Power of the Dog’ and ‘West Side Story’ won big at the 79th Golden Globe Awards, which were announced on Twitter, while ‘Pose’ actress Mj Rodriguez made history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  WINNERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/09/updating-live-golden-globes-announce-winners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE manipulating browser extensions to stifle competitors, DUCKDUCKGO CEO says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/google-is-manipulating-browser-extensions-to-stifle-competitors-duckduckgo-ceo-says/ar-AASsyan?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian judge offers Djokovic glimmer of hope in deportation fight...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/djokovic-opens-dramatic-court-battle-222827975.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Australian judge demanded Monday to know what more Novak Djokovic could have done to meet the country's strict pandemic entry requirements, offering a glimmer of hope to the detained tennis superstar as he fights deportation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House worried Iran is plotting assassination attempts against Trump administration officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/white-house-worried-iran-is-plotting-assassination-attempts-against-trump-administration-officials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s imposition of “sanctions” on dozens of Americans amounts to an assassination threat against members of former President Donald Trump’s administration, according to a senior U.S. official who threatened “severe consequences” for any harm done to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAGET DEAD IN ORLANDO HOTEL ROOM</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/09/bob-saget-dead-dies-hotel-comedian-full-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary comic and star of 'Full House' was found dead in his Florida hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable Cabinet: New texts reveal the influence of FOXNEWS hosts on previous White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-cable-cabinet-new-texts-reveal-the-influence-of-fox-hosts-on-previous-white-house/ar-AASADdl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Bannon Sought Bizarre Loan as His Woes Spiraled...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/steve-bannon-sought-bizarre-loan-as-his-january-6-woes-spiraled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid mounting legal problems, Bannon seems to have tried to borrow against property linked to a nonprofit he founded with a Chinese billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crazy trends we'll be following this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4399238/pizza-vending-machines-make-up-trends-2022-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS we step into another year filled with uncertainty, what can we look forward to in 2022? A host of outlandish trends promise to make the next 12 months anything but dull – from pizza vending mach…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where you are most likely to catch?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4425231/covid-spreading-hotspots-sage-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOU’RE most likely to catch Covid while going to the shops, experts have warned as they released a list of the most contagious activities. A Government-led study based on the daily activities…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B'WAY:  Michael Jackson Musical Poised to Be Major Hit if Pandemic Doesn't Do It In...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/07/first-look-mj-the-michael-jackson-musical-poised-to-be-a-major-hit-if-the-pandemic-doesnt-do-it-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 1973, 'SOYLENT GREEN' envisioned the world in 2022. It got a lot right...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/entertainment/in-1973-soylent-green-envisioned-the-world-in-2022-it-got-a-lot-right/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The year is 2022. Our overpopulated planet is experiencing catastrophic climate change, megacorporations have excessive power over the government, and clean living is a luxury only the 1 percent can afford. It may read like a scan of the front-page...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 4 Americans plan to quit their jobs in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/worker-resignation-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of those employees want to switch to industries like IT and finance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>106-year-old credits longevity to Big Macs!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/106-year-old-philadelphia-woman-credits-longevity-to-faith-big-macs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dorothy Nedd, a South Philadelphia resident, turned 106-year-old on Friday. She credited her faith and her love for McDonald's Big Mac for her longevity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Pelosi Stumbles Off Podium...</title>
      <link>https://www.eagnews.org/2022/01/video-nancy-pelosi-stumbles-off-presidential-podium-nearly-tumbles-to-floor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eagnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi stumbled off the presidential podium during Harry Reid's funeral service in Las Vegas on Saturday, nearly taking a header in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deltacron' discovered in Cyprus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/08/cyprus-reportedly-discovers-a-covid-variant-that-combines-omicron-and-delta.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strain is being called "deltacron."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco hotel replaces housekeepers with robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/south-bay-hotel-solves-staffing-shortages-with-robot-service</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With staffing shortages created by the coronavirus pandemic, a new robot named “Wall-E” is making the room service rounds at the Radisson Hotel in Sunnyvale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence against mandates piles up...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/how-vaccine-mandates-became-a-political-weapon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden is using them to punish his enemies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  Was January 6 an Inside Job?</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/was-january-6-an-inside-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus, Ask Matt Labash explores the "ick" in politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Deadliest NYC blaze in 30 years tears through Bronx building, at least 19 killed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/09/nyc-fire-leaves-numerous-people-injured-people-jumping-from-windows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze is at 333 E 181st St, a 19-story building in the West Bronx.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
