<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BUZZFEED Cuts 47 HUFFPOST Jobs After Acquisition...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/buzzfeed-huffpost-layoffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed announced last November it would acquire HuffPost in a deal with Verizon Media that went through in February</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN: 'RECOLLECTIONS MAY VARY BUT WE TAKE THEM VERY SERIOUSLY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14283067/royal-family-respond-meghan-harry-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE “saddened” Queen today responded to Meghan Markle’s race claims in her bombshell interview, saying: “Some recollections may vary”. Her Majesty finally responded to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY+ pulls 'DUMBO', 'PETER PAN', 'THE ARISTOCATS' for 'racist' stereotypes...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2479490/disney-pulls-iconic-movies-dumbo-the-aristocats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISNEY+ has stripped its kid’s menus of classic movies like Dumbo, The Aristocats and Peter Pan because of their “racist” stereotypes. Settings on the streaming site’s app will prevent children und…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleared for takeoff? World eyes 'health passports'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210309-cleared-for-takeoff-world-eyes-health-passports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cleared for takeoff? World eyes 'health passports'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskless UBER Passengers Assault, Cough On, Pepper Spray Driver...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/08/video-maskless-uber-passengers-assault-cough-on-pepper-spray-driver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Uber driver in San Francisco was assaulted and coughed-upon by a woman riding with two other women after he refused them service for not wearing masks, in an attack the driver captured on video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL star slammed for killing huge gator then posing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/14280662/nfl-wyatt-teller-alligator-hunting-backlash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star Wyatt Teller has received a fierce backlash from animal rights activists after he shot, killed and then posed with a 10-foot long alligator. The Cleveland Browns guard, 26, was captured on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>42% Now Consider Themselves Germaphobes!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-curse-many-americans-consider-themselves-germaphobes-over-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find constantly stressing over safety is getting old fast for Americans -- as the world enters year two of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only one New York governor has ever been impeached. Some lawmakers hope Cuomo will be second...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/only-one-new-york-governor-has-ever-been-impeached-some-n1260048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo has been besieged by bipartisan calls to resign or be impeached over dual scandals that have rocked his administration in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD DOG:  Major sent home to Delaware after biting incident...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/08/politics/president-joe-biden-white-house-dogs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two German Shepherds belonging to President Joe Biden and first lady Jill Biden were returned to the Biden family home in Delaware last week after aggressive behavior at the White House involving Major Biden, two sources with knowledge tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA ISSUES HEALTH PASSPORT</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14285224/china-issues-world-first-covid-vaccine-passport-and-plans-to-accept-other-countries-passes-soon-in-boost-for-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has issued what’s thought to be the world’s first Covid vaccine passport. In a boost to international travel, Beijing also plans to accept other countries’ vaccine health ce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINATED RECLAIM THEIR LIVES</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210309095717-w8o28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-SENIORS (PIX):After year of isolation, vaccinated older Americans start to reclaim their lives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palace silence on Harry, Meghan allegations adds to furor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/buckingham-palace-meghan-harry-interview-allegations-c1f78e3d617595fcb0534fbaa8f298ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Racism. Bullying. Insensitivity. Prince Harry and Meghan’s allegations of ill treatment by Britain's royal household are so serious that some observers say Buckingham Palace’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psych eval ordered for man caught having sex with stuffed animals inside TARGET...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/olaf-psych-eval-376215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 8--A judge today ordered a psychological evaluation to help determine the competency of a Florida Man charged with having sexual contact with a pair of large stuffed animals at a Target store,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York prosecutors investigating Trump Chicago skyscraper loan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/08/politics/trump-chicago-subpoena/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney's office subpoenaed documents from an investment company that loaned the Trump Organization millions of dollars for its Chicago skyscraper in a sign that the investigation into the former president's finances continues to expand, according to people familiar with the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Land of Lincoln, what's wrong with statues of Honest Abe? And should Ulysses S. Grant be taken off his high horse?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/in-land-of-lincoln-what-s-wrong-with-statues-of-honest-abe-and-should-ulysses/article_0a67b3e0-09fe-52d9-bd7e-56e391a8a727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — In the Land of Lincoln, it might be hard for some to imagine what could tarnish the legacy of “Honest Abe,” the nation’s 16th president, who led the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA, FL took vastly different approaches to COVID-19. Here's how it turned out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-florida-took-vastly-different-130025306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California and Florida took vastly different approaches to COVID-19, generating debate about which state fared better. Here's what the numbers show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial for ex-cop charged in Floyd's death forges on, for now...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/police-trials-minneapolis-racial-injustice-death-of-george-floyd-11a74447df93a49e50357b395d290a8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The trial of a former Minneapolis police officer charged in George Floyd's death is forging ahead with jury selection, even though a looming appellate ruling could halt the case...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrimination allegations no surprise to Black Britons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/meghan-harry-oprah-interview-racism-fdee9570666fd6a9dff6215ba7882fa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RussiaChina To Build Joint Lunar Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/russia-and-china-plan-to-build-joint-lunar-space-station-2387155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and China agreed Tuesday to build a lunar space station, as Moscow seeks to modernise its extraterrestrial might and catch up with the United States in the space race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTY IN ISRAEL</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/post-vaccine-israel-reopens-party-095637907.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GettyThe text message came in early Sunday morning from an Israeli friend with a question in Hebrew (and most other languages) that hadn’t been posed in months: “We going out tonight?”After a full year of pandemic and repeat lockdowns, the second of which in September shuttered all of Israel’s—and go-go Tel Aviv’s—restaurants and bars and cafes, the country almost fully reopened yesterday on the back of its globe-leading COVID vaccination campaign. The locals, for their part, took full advantage and went out in force.“Back to life, first in the world,” long-serving Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu crowed from a cafe during a live Facebook broadcast over cappuccino and cake. “First” was a loose concept: many countries, especially in East Asia and Oceania, never even closed or are already open after driving infection rates down to zero.But for most other countries in the world similarly hard-hit by the coronavirus, Israel is indeed a test case for how to get our lives back—thanks to the vaccines—and what such a life may look like. On the basis of the first night out in Tel Aviv, it’s definitely celebratory, decidedly surreal, and deceptively normal—bordering on reckless.On central Tel Aviv’s Dizengoff Street, home to high-end shopping and many low-end bars, the scene Sunday evening was of a massive party: balloons tied to awnings, people walking on sidewalks with beers, and young revelers overflowing from most drinking establishments as electronic music played.At one such bar, Fasada, a table of 10 friends, all in their late twenties, were sipping red wine and beers, catching each other up on life and work and romances. Next to them were two guys industriously rolling and smoking joints, worried more about quotidian concerns like a dropped piece of pizza. Nearby, three girlfriends worked on a bottle of white wine together as they eyed the crowd.“It’s wonderful to be back,” Sapir, 28, the waitress, told me, beaming. “This is what Tel Aviv used to be like.”Seemingly the only allowances for the unpleasantness of the past year were the masks hanging below some chins and tables more spaced out than usual. A big part of the government’s reopening plan is tied to the “Green Passport” scheme for all those vaccinated or recovered from COVID.At current writing 40 percent of Israel’s entire population of 9 million people has been fully inoculated via the two-shot Pfizer-BioNTech vaccine, including 90 percent of those over the age of 50 who are most at risk. Health authorities have even begun vaccinating teenagers in a bid to fully stop transmissions that increasingly skew younger.But overall hospitalizations and those critically ill due to the virus are decreasing, even in the face of daily COVID infection rates that are still, on a per capita basis, one of the world’s highest (almost wholly amongst those not yet vaccinated). Multiple studies by Israeli researchers in recent weeks point to one clear fact: the vaccines work. The Israeli Health Ministry this week released official data showing that out of more than 3.3 million people considered fully vaccinated, less than 5,000 had gotten infected and out of those only some 900 had developed symptoms.Hence the grand reopening of the economy via the “Green Passport” scheme, which aims to return daily life to a semblance of normalcy, responsibly.Available via a government-launched app or electronic PDF issued by the Health Ministry (that can be printed out), the small document grants indoor entry to restaurants, bars, event halls, concerts, and other such public gathering spaces—with capacity restrictions and other safeguards still in place. For those not yet vaccinated, the option still exists to sit outside, which in Tel Aviv’s mild late-winter Mediterranean climate most of those on Dizengoff Street were doing.Not that they necessarily had to. On the face of it, the Green Passport was more a recommendation than a hard and fast law, with masses of people inside and outside at multiple bars mixing freely (and mask-less) for the most part.“No one really looked at the Green Passport,” Tor, 25, an alternative medicine professional out with friends at a bar on nearby Rothschild Boulevard, told me.And indeed, Tel Aviv has more than 1700 nightlife spots and cafes and restaurants—an impossible number for local authorities to monitor. The bar code at the bottom of the “Green Passport” is, at this point, an adornment; all that’s required for entry so far, The Daily Beast learned first-hand, is a quick flash to a doorman of a document that may or may not be the holder’s.Vaccine or no vaccine, though, people went out to enjoy what Rebecca, 35, a British journalist friend, called “our new old way of life”: a nice meal at a restaurant with her cousin that wasn’t served on plastic take-out dishes or the ubiquitous plastic crates set up during lockdown outside many eateries (in lieu of tables and chairs).The scene at the restaurant, similar to the rest of town, was “like the last year never happened,” she said. “The excitement was palpable, people were dancing on tables to cheesy Israeli pop songs, as if it was a holiday weekend.”There were those, of course, who found the entire thing difficult to process—at least at first.“It was weird going out after such a long time and being around so many people,” Tor, the alternative medicine specialist, said. “But at the end it became normal, especially after the alcohol.”In a nod to reclaiming such lost normalcy, Baruch and Lauren, both 29, were enjoying a quiet drink together outside a cocktail bar further up Dizengoff Street away from the hordes. “It’s déjà vu of the lives that we had,” Baruch, who runs a human resources company, told me in reference to being out. “It’s our first date after corona,” he added.“Our second date,” Lauren, his fiancée, jokingly corrected him. “We went to a café this morning.”A manager at a bar services company, Lauren had been furloughed as the entire industry shut down because of the pandemic. Yet both she and Baruch hadn’t been vaccinated yet—a recurring theme amongst many younger Tel Avivis who aren’t so much anti-vaxxers as vaccine-hesitant.“I don’t want to be the first one to jump in the pool,” Baruch said metaphorically. “We’ll see in future.”Others seem angrier with the government for making their lives contingent on receiving a vaccine—and with those who inquire. “It’s no one’s business if I did or didn’t,” Sapir, the waitress, responded when asked, now rather less smiling. “The government shouldn’t tell us what to do… and if a restaurant asks me for the Green Passport I’ll turn around and won’t go in.”It was a lacuna in the arrangement, to be sure: sitting inside a club or restaurant after showing a vaccine document while the bartenders or wait staff may themselves not be vaccinated. But there is no way to legally force employees to get inoculated.Tor, for his part, was furious at those that haven’t yet availed themselves of Israel’s copious vaccine supply and easy access.“I have lots of family in the U.S. and they’re going crazy [trying to get a vaccine]… People here in Israel don’t understand what the situation is in the rest of the world,” he said.For Ohad, 22, a waiter at Baruch and Lauren’s cocktail bar, it was an easy decision. He had just gotten his first jab, and was—like his colleagues—wearing a plastic facemask.“I want the customers that I serve to feel safe and comfortable,” he said. “I’ve been waiting six months to start this job – because really, how much time can you sit at home [on unemployment] losing yourself?”It was an important point: a whole generation of younger people in the hospitality industry (and other hard-hit sectors of the economy) who have lost a year of their lives to the pandemic.It was the first night of the rebirth after nearly half a year, and both sides of the nightlife equation were thirsty to get back to normal.Idan, 42, the majority owner of the Jasper Bar, a Dizengoff speakeasy known for its nonexistent closing hours, said it hadn’t been easy. “Everything was stress—there was no dialogue with the industry from the government, and their financial support basically covered our rent.”He considered himself one of the lucky ones, though: his staff remained loyal and came back, and judging by the heavy traffic both inside and outside his establishment, so did the customers. He hugged and kissed one goodbye as he told me, haltingly, “Tel Aviv… Tel Aviv… things should just return to what they were.”After the first day of reopening, it seems like they will. And as goes Tel Aviv, so goes Israel—and as goes Israel, with both its high vaccination numbers and infection rates, so likely will go most other countries battling the pandemic.If the vaccine succeeds in keeping down the number of seriously ill people as the economy and daily life remain open, then the world will have a model for how to really live with the virus. And if it doesn’t, then Sunday night will have been the first step towards yet another lockdown.In the meantime, though, Tel Aviv will stay open, and routine will have returned.“We’re going out this weekend, right?” my friend asked at the end of the night, a sign perhaps of how ordinary it had all already become.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report claims evidence of Beijing genocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/09/asia/china-uyghurs-xinjiang-genocide-report-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese government's alleged actions in Xinjiang have violated every single provision in the United Nations' Genocide Convention, according to an independent report by more than 50 global experts in human rights, war crimes and international law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi tells military 'be prepared to respond' in unstable times...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3124733/xi-jinping-tells-chinas-military-be-prepared-respond-unstable</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President also stresses need for ‘high-level strategic deterrence’ and more tech innovation, after defence minister’s call for PLA to be battle ready amid ‘high-risk phase’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLUMN: My pity for these sad, naive, damaged souls...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-9340079/BEL-MOONEY-pity-sad-naive-damaged-souls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEL MOONEY: Somebody told me there is a 'Team Meghan' and a 'Team Queen' and you have to pick your side. Now, having watched, I feel a sympathy that has surprised me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden challenged by cyber threats...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/542230-biden-challenged-by-early-cyber-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is grappling with two major cyber incidents in its first 50 days in office, underscoring the challenge the new White House faces from foreign actors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is it?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/meghan-markle-prince-harry-london-queen-elizabeth-ii-oprah-winfrey-c1f78e3d617595fcb0534fbaa8f298ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Racism. Bullying. Insensitivity. Prince Harry and Meghan’s allegations of ill treatment by Britain's royal household are so serious that some observers say Buckingham Palace’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You Transplant Human Head, Does Consciousness Follow?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/if-you-transplant-human-head-does-consciousness-follow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her new book, Brandy Schillace recalls the unbelievable legacy of a Cold War era neurosurgeon’s mission to preserve the soul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cow cuddling has become a thing for lonely hearts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/weddings/cow-cuddling-has-become-a-thing-for-lonely-hearts-in-the-pandemic/ar-BB1emwkG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can't hug your friends or most of your family members. But you can hug a cow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From prolonged pandemic, rethink of life's milestones?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-pandemics-coronavirus-pandemic-39d8d3cc185944964011fbb5d9c1d2aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wedding anniversaries for Elizabeth O'Connor Cole and her husband, Michael, usually involve a dinner reservation for two at a fancy restaurant. Not this time around. As the pandemic raged...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California recall threat puts pressure on Newsom speech...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-elections-california-gavin-newsom-recall-elections-0201416f3a00e5133a1910c5638f9e79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California Gov. Gavin Newsom is set to give perhaps the most important speech of his political life Tuesday, and he’s spent weeks laying the groundwork for an upbeat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How USA, China could go to war...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/How-the-U-S-and-China-could-go-to-war-16011156.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's 2034 and a war is about to begin. A flotilla of three U.S. naval destroyers is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus surge in Brazil poses threat far beyond its borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Virus-surge-in-Brazil-poses-a-threat-far-beyond-16011169.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO - The people started queuing up before first light. The line of cars soon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Forces Quietly Using Armed Robots?</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidhambling/2021/03/09/are-us-special-forces-quietly-using-armed-robots/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palace silent over Meghan's claim of racist remark...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210309091545-jt6ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii's Maui orders evacuation after dam breach that damaged homes, bridges...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210309081141-ftg4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HAWAII/FLOODS-EVACUATION (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-Hawaii's Maui orders evacuation after dam breach that damaged homes, bridges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Snotty' Harry...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14280763/thomas-markle-hung-up-prince-harry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOMAS Markle today revealed he HUNG UP on “snotty” Prince Harry when he called him about the royal wedding as he lay in hospital. Meghan Markle’s estranged father this morning hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula Now Free to Run for President. This Could Be End for Bolsonaro...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lula-is-now-free-to-run-for-president-this-could-be-the-end-for-bolsonaro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his corruption convictions scrapped, Brazil’s ex-President Lula is now free to run for the presidency—making way for a fiery showdown against Bolsonaro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causes tremors...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/vermont-meteor-fireball-explosion-1574737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space agency said it had received over 100 eyewitness reports and also detected the sound made by the fireball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Meteor explodes over VT with force of 440 pounds of TNT...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/vermont-meteor-explodes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the size of a bowling ball but exploded like 440 pounds of TNT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rattles buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/09/us/vermont-meteor-spotted-trnd/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buckingham Palace reaction in focus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/09/buckingham-palaces-reaction-after-harry-and-meghans-oprah-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All eyes are on Buckingham Palace for a reaction to the explosive interview given by Prince Harry and the Duchess of Sussex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules 'QANON shaman' too dangerous to be released from jail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/542241-federal-judge-rules-qanon-shaman-too-dangerous-to-be-released-from-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jacob Chansley, the self-proclaimed "QAnon Shaman" who participated in the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol, will not be released from jail ahead of his trial, a federal judge determined on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Faces Challenge From Surge of Migrants at Border...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/08/biden-faces-challenge-from-surge-of-migrants-at-the-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Thousands of migrant children are backed up in United States detention facilities along the border with Mexico, part</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale Old and New as Another Royal Wife Breaks Free...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/08/a-tale-old-and-new-as-another-royal-wife-breaks-free/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone who remembers the funeral of Diana, the Princess of Wales, in 1997 can’t help being haunted by the wrenching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC says vaccinated should STILL wear masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2473079/covid-vaccinated-people-gather-without-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FULLY vaccinated Americans can gather in groups indoors without masks, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said. However, those who have had the jab should still wear a face covering in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLOWEST SPREAD SINCE PANDEMIC!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-coronavirus-cases-post-slowest-spread-since-pandemic-began/ar-BB1emYPF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the U.S. vaccination effort picking up speed, new coronavirus cases in the U.S. rose 1.5% in the week ended Sunday, the slowest increase since the pandemic began almost a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piers Morgan Storms Off Set After 'Diabolical' Commentary Called Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/piers-morgan-storms-off-set/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan's harsh criticism of Meghan Markle had fellow presenter Alex Beresford calling him out, which led to Morgan storming off the set of Good Morning Britain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I was fully vaccinated and still caught it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/i-was-fully-vaccinated-and-still-caught-corona-heres-why-661336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pfizer and Moderna vaccines are around 95% effective but some people still get sick. Here is why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden dogs sent home to Delaware after 'biting incident'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-house-dog-house-bidens-035013863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has sent his two dogs back to his family home in Wilmington, Delaware, after the younger of the two German Shepherds was involved in a "biting incident" with a White House security agent, US media said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan's father suggests she exaggerated royal racism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/meghans-father-suggests-she-exaggerated-095255661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan Markle's estranged father on Tuesday suggested that his daughter exaggerated racism in the British royal family during her interview with US chat show host Oprah Winfrey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beats EMMYS and GLOBES Combined...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/meghan-markle-prince-harry-oprah-interview-ratings-cbs-1234709005/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan Markle and Prince Harry are no Stormy Daniels and certainly no Michael Jackson, but their sit-down with Oprah Winfrey on Sunday night was certainly a royal payoff for CBS. The two-hour Oprah…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA offers residency to 320,000  Venezuelans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-south-america-immigration-financial-markets-41cf6301ecee234ce8b5cee60a4c9bed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration said Monday it is offering temporary legal residency to several hundred thousand Venezuelans who fled their country’s economic collapse and will review...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Scientists Are Infecting Healthy Volunteers...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/03/08/974903666/why-scientists-are-infecting-healthy-volunteers-with-the-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exposing people to a potentially fatal disease could hasten understanding of COVID-19 and development of new vaccines and treatments. But the risks of such studies raise serious ethical questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endangered Tiger Dies After Artificial Insemination Procedure At Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/03/08/endangered-amur-tiger-dies-artificial-insemination-procedure-cheyenne-mountain-zoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials with the Cheyenne Mountain Zoo announced that an endangered Amur tiger died after an artificial insemination procedure last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA gas price rises for 47th time in 48 days...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/gas-prices-in-los-angeles-near-me-why-are-going-up-today-california-2020/10397544/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAS PRICES ON THE RISE: The average price of a gallon of self-serve regular gasoline in Los Angeles County rose Monday for the 47th time in 48 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPA JOHN FOUNDER: Been Working '20 Months' to Stop Using N-Word...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/papa-johns-founder-rejects-charges-of-racism-by-revealing-hes-been-working-for-20-months-to-get-the-n-word-out-of-his-vocabulary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Schnatter, the founder and former CEO of pizza chain Papa John’s appeared on OAN to reject charges of racism against him, claiming he's been working "for the last 20 months" to "get rid of this N-word" from his vocabulary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg bets on smart glasses -- to combat climate change...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/08/mark-zuckerberg-how-smart-glasses-could-help-combat-climate-change.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg's remarks are notable because he identifies software that could be the hook to get people to wear advanced headsets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US journalist arrested while covering protest goes on trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrea-sahouri-trial-7dbc1b7ebc37c3a88f0192251b7d5395</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — A journalist went on trial Monday on charges stemming from her coverage of a protest against racial injustice in Des Moines last year, after Iowa prosecutors defied...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barefacers threaten to call ICE on Mex restaurant in Tex...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article249761688.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s just heartbreaking.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>78% of people hospitalized were overweight...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/08/covid-cdc-study-finds-roughly-78percent-of-people-hospitalized-were-overweight-or-obese.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An overwhelming majority of people who have been hospitalized, needed a ventilator or died from Covid-19 have been overweight or obese, the CDC said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURGER KING Slammed For Women's Day Tweet: 'Women Belong In The Kitchen'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/burger-king-uk-backlash-international-womens-day-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burger King is facing fierce backlash over what many have dubbed a misogynistic tweet intended to [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apparently did NOT secretly marry before public ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/03/08/meghan-harry-not-secretly-wed-before-public-ceremony-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan Markle told Oprah Winfrey, “Three days before our wedding, we got married.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syria president Assad tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/08/syrian-president-wife-test-positive-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAMASCUS, Syria — Syrian President Bashar Assad and his wife have tested positive for the coronavirus, the president’s office said Monday, with both having only mild symptoms of the illness. In a s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Rep. Reports Thousand$ in Questionable Income from Bank of China Account...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2021/03/08/exclusive-democrat-congressman-vicente-gonzalez-reports-thousands-in-questionable-interest-income-from-bank-of-china-account/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Rep. Vicente Gonzalez (D-TX) has on his three most recent financial disclosure forms reported holdings worth more than...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE: WH admits not doing enough to deter illegals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/08/white-house-says-it-needs-to-work-more-on-migrants-entering-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of illegal immigrants are being set free across the country as the crisis on the southern border escalates — and the White House admitted Monday it isn’t doing enough to disco…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing wants babies to expand workforce...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/politics/article/3124440/china-wants-more-babies-chinas-women-have-other-plans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing has tinkered with policies to encourage population growth but looking at the gender balance of its core leadership might be a starting point, say observers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: White supremacists trying to join cops, military...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9339107/White-supremacists-trying-join-law-enforcement-military-terrorize-minorities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency's San Antonio branch said right-wing extremists sought to join law enforcement and the military in an effort to 'further' their ideologies, according to a leaked report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas parties, celebrities and booze: How legal titan kept power...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vegas-parties-celebrities-boozy-lunches-130030877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Girardi and his firm were sued more than a hundred times between the 1980s and last year, with at least half of those cases asserting misconduct in his law practice. Yet, Girardi's record with the State Bar of California remained pristine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside LINCOLN PROJECT's Secrets, Side Deals and Scandals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inside-the-lincoln-project-s-secrets-side-deals-and-scandals/ar-BB1eniwf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few days before the presidential election, the leadership of the anti-Trump Lincoln Project gathered at the Utah home of Steve Schmidt, one of the group’s co-founders, and listened as he plotted out the organization’s future. None of the dissident Republican consultants who created the Lincoln Project a year earlier had imagined how wildly successful it would be, pulling in more than $87 million in donations and producing scores of viral...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope weighed Iraq virus risk but believes God will protect...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pope-francis-iraq-coronavirus-risk-a59ec54c27afe1a45dc84b9a38cd07ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABOARD THE PAPAL PLANE (AP) — Pope Francis said Monday he weighed the risks of a high-profile trip to Iraq during the coronavirus pandemic, but said he decided to go ahead with it after much...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
