<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Libertarian candidate Jo Jorgensen advocates end to big govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article244996385.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY corralled virus. What's California's excuse for surge?</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/new-york-corralled-coronavirus-whats-californias-excuse-for-case-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts and those with ties to both states say New Yorkers gained a healthy respect for the virus’ deadly potential after it hammered the state in the spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convention season set to begin, with [virtual] spotlight on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-convention-season-set-begin-201227357.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Democrats on Monday open an unprecedented virtual convention, the party&amp;#39;s disparate factions are projecting a united front behind Joe Biden, brought together by their common determination to defeat Donald Trump in November&amp;#39;s election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First major Mediterranean cruise liner sets sail since pandemic... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-major-cruise-line-set-082146808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first major cruise ship to resume tours of the Mediterranean since the coronavirus pandemic hit Europe set sail from the Italian city of Genoa on Sunday, as the industry tries to regain ground after a bruising hiatus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND NIGHT OF ROLLING BLACKOUTS IN CALI...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-worst-power-shortage-years-130019359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People staying home with air conditioners blasting, plus a dearth of power from other states results in the worst statewide energy shortage in nearly 20 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy closes nightclubs as cases rise among young...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200816173142-jjf0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY-NIGHTCLUBS (PIX):Italy closes nightclubs as coronavirus cases rise among young</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival rallies face off in Warsaw over gay rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200816160439-m28p6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nationalists burnt a rainbow flag, while the LGBT activists painted one on the street</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey in a Stir Over Old Biden Remarks Backing Erdogan Ouster...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/turkey-stir-over-old-biden-133025340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- An old video of Democratic presidential hopeful Joe Biden calling for the removal of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has set off a furor in Turkey while earning U.S. President Donald Trump a shout-out.In a Dec. 16 meeting with New York Times editors, Biden called Erdogan an “autocrat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst heatwave in 70 years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-faces-second-night-blackouts-020525955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- First, it was the prospect of wildfires that took down large swaths of California’s power grid. Now, it’s the worst heat wave in 70 years.Climate change is contributing to increasingly extreme weather in California. Less than a year ago, millions of people were plunged into darkness in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New White House virus doc has no expertise in public health or infectious diseases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/886b59d445a3d20739e2f77600976ea0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has found a new doctor for his coronavirus task force — and this time there's no daylight between them. Trump last week announced that Dr. Scott...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm Determined UK Students' Grades. Chaos Ensued...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/an-algorithm-determined-uk-students-grades-chaos-ensued/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's A-Levels, the high-stakes exams taken in high school, were canceled due to the pandemic. The alternative only exacerbated existing inequities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest woman in USA celebrates turning 116 with drive-thru birthday...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-8632493/Oldest-woman-200-grandchildren-celebrates-116th-birthday-style.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hester Ford, from Charlotte, North Carolina, blew out 116th candles this weekend. The great grandmother, who has 200 great-grandchildren, is believed to be the oldest person living in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universities drastically reshaped...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/16/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The return to college campuses this month has offered a preview into how the coronavirus pandemic has drastically reshaped the university experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter films own arrest at Proud Boys rally...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/16/michigan-reporter-filmed-arrest-at-proud-boys-rally-in-kalamazoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Jesus — I’m being arrested!” Samuel Robinson suddenly cried, his camera shaking as officers were shown around him. He repeatedly shouted, “I’m media!” bef…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems in conservative S.C. see opportunity for gains...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-conservative-c-see-opportunity-122218359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It&amp;#39;s been nearly 15 years since a Democrat won a statewide office and 44 years since a Democratic presidential candidate claimed the state. In the U.S. Senate race, Democrat Jaime Harrison has raised more money than GOP incumbent Lindsey Graham for two quarters in a row. A Democrat captured a longtime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama 'uses loopholes to bypass coastal protection laws in Hawaii' to build compound...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8631723/Planning-loopholes-bypass-coastal-protection-laws-Hawaii-compound-tied-Obama.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials and community members confirmed to ProPublica that Obama plans to reside in the compound on Oahu, which was purchased for $8.7 million by his close friend Marty Nesbitt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KODAK loan: Insider trading in new garb?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/512174-the-kodak-loan-insider-trading-in-a-new-garb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DFC loan to Kodak is the first of its kind under the Defense Production Act, and so it is not surprising that it raised a number of new issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden looks to make inroads with evangelicals...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/511809-biden-looks-to-make-inroads-with-evangelical-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden is seeking to make inroads with evangelical voters, a demographic that overwhelmingly sided with President Trump during the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's Been Pacifist for 75 Years. Missile Proposal Challenges That...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/16/japans-been-proudly-pacifist-for-75-years-a-missile-proposal-challenges-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO — Shinzo Abe is facing some of the toughest challenges of his record-setting tenure as Japan’s prime minister, with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no balloon drops, what's a convention for?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/08/16/joe-biden-kamala-harris-keys-to-democratic-convention/3368123001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Joe Biden, the to-do list at this week's virtual convention includes spanning a political spectrum from John Kasich to AOC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defund police? Already happening thanks to Covid-19 budget crunch...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/15/defund-the-police-coronavirus-budget-395665</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision about how much spending needs to be cut, and from where, will be up to each state’s bank balance and the political makeup of its government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian surfer punches shark to save wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200816-australian-surfer-punches-shark-to-save-wife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian surfer punches shark to save wife</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fire tornado' warning? Weather service issues what could be first...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fire-tornado-warning-weather-issues-001717718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Fire tornadoes happen, but the issuance of a tornado warning on one is a first.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Cult of Priests Who Hate Pope Francis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/this-secret-cult-of-priests-still-wont-recognize-pope-francis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A priest in Sacramento, California, has been excommunicated for not accepting Pope Francis as the real pope. He’s not the only one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA clears saliva test opening door to wider testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/08/15/fda-clears-saliva-test-for-covid-19-opening-door-to-wider-testing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA granted emergency use authorization for a saliva test for the virus that causes Covid-19, which could improve testing capability in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND NIGHT OF CALI ROLLING BLACKOUTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article244996275.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington QB Alex Smith cleared to play after horrific injury...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29671320/washington-qb-alex-smith-cleared-football-activity-team</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Football Team quarterback Alex Smith, who suffered a leg injury in 2018 that nearly cost him his life, will be cleared for football activity and be activated off the physically unable to perform list, a source told ESPN's John Keim on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea Warns of New Mass Infection After Church Flareup...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/south-korea-confirms-279-new-covid-19-cases-most-since-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korea Warns of New Mass Infection After Church Flareup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telephone service begins between UAE, Israel amid deal...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/middle-east/2020/08/telephone-service-begins-between-uae-israel-amid-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Telephone service between the United Arab Emirates and Israel has begun as the two countries open diplomatic ties. Associated Press journalists in Jerusalem and…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
