<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Self-pitying, spoilt and brattish'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/spencer-film-review-kristen-stewart-princess-diana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice 2021: Chilean director Pablo Larrain's film has the potential to become a gothic, almost camp classic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN DEATH PLAN LEAKED</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16044176/buckingham-palace-furious-queens-secret-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“FURIOUS” Buckingham Palace aides have launched a mole-hunt after detailed papers for the Queen’s death sensationally leaked today. Top officials are said to be on the warpath, wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no tourist handouts, hungry Bali monkeys are raiding homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/with-no-tourist-handouts-hungry-bali-monkeys-are-raiding-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deprived of their preferred food source — the bananas, peanuts and other goodies brought in by tourists now kept away by the coronavirus — hungry monkeys on the resort island of Bali have taken to raiding villagers’ homes in their search for something tasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless attack family of 5 with machete in Malibu...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/family-of-5-allegedly-attacked-by-two-homeless-people-with-machete-in-malibu-dad-loses-eye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dad loses his eye after a homeless man slashed his face with a machete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America is in a covid funk...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/americas-in-a-covid-funk-c6167b08-914c-46b8-8316-b140a8791d85.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Americans are giving up on public health measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  8.4% ADVANTAGE...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/california-recall-polls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do voters in California want to remove Gov. Gavin Newsom from office?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Officials Advise White House to Chill on Booster after Booster After Booster...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/03/health-officials-advise-white-house-to-scale-back-booster-plan-for-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Top federal health officials have told the White House to scale back a plan to offer coronavirus booster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buckingham Palace 'furious'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3595325/buckingham-palace-furious-queens-secret-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“FURIOUS” Buckingham Palace aides have launched a mole-hunt after detailed papers for the Queen’s death sensationally leaked today. Top officials are said to be on the warpath, wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark side of INSTA fame; Rise in stalkers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3589100/instagram-fame-stalkers-kills-mercedes-morr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH her glamorous posts to her 2.7million followers, Instagram star Miss Mercedes Morr was much loved and regularly contacted by her fans from all over the world. But her shocking death this …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Delta Effect'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/this-is-terrible-news-cnbc-breaks-down-dismal-jobs-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts on CNBC's Squawk Box assessed September's abysmal jobs report on Friday, calling the net gain of 235,000 jobs "terrible news" for the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Tumbles Further Behind Conservative 'Freight Train'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trudeau-tumbles-further-behind-conservative-freight-train</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trudeau Tumbles Further Behind Conservative ‘Freight Train’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN:  Forever Cripple His Foreign Policy?</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/commentary/patrick-j-buchanan/has-bidens-end-forever-war-forever-crippled-his-foreign-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Franklin D. Roosevelt addressed Congress on Dec. 8, 1941, the day after the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor, the country was united behind him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lonely journey of UFO theorist in age of distrust...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/lifestyle/article/The-lonely-journey-of-a-UFO-conspiracy-theorist-16433429.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER - All day long, Douglas Wilson had tended to cracked sidewalks and overgrown...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAN 6: McCarthy phone records under scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/02/politics/kevin-mccarthy-preserve-phone-records/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy is among a group of GOP lawmakers whose phone records are of interest to the select committee investigating the deadly January 6 riot on Capitol Hill, CNN has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kristen Stewart's turn as Princess Diana woos Venice...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210903141150-7fomg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FILMFESTIVAL-VENICE/SPENCER (PIX, TV):Kristen Stewart's turn as Princess Diana woos Venice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: Awful Precedent that Conservatives Should Hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/wsj-editorial-board-blasts-texas-abortion-law-blunder-an-awful-precedent-that-conservatives-should-hate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WSJ editorial board has come out against a controversial anti-abortion bill recently passed in Texas that the Supreme Court has thus far refused to block.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Eye Taxes on Stock Buybacks, Excess CEO Pay...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/senate-democrats-eye-taxes-stock-134145006.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democratic lawmakers are discussing a range of tax proposals targeting corporations and the wealthy -- including levies on stock buybacks, carbon emissions and executive compensation, a wider set of measures than President Joe Biden had proposed to help fund a ramp-up in spending on social programs.One idea is applying an excise tax on stock buybacks or treating them as taxable dividends to shareholders, according to two people familiar with Senate Finance Committee discussions. C</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School ordered student to quarantine. His dad, two men confronted principal with zip ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-school-ordered-a-student-to-quarantine-his-dad-and-2-men-confronted-the-principal-with-zip-ties-official-says/ar-AAO3OTj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a live video posted to Instagram, one of the two men who joined the dad told his followers that they were about to “confront this administration” for “breaking the law.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looting...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/09/02/south-lake-tahoe-looting-arrests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two suspected looters were arrested in evacuated South Lake Tahoe this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Britain's plan for when Queen dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/queen-elizabeth-death-plan-britain-operation-london-bridge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLITICO has obtained documents laying out Operation LONDON BRIDGE in granular detail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid surge in ransomware attacks, cities taking biggest hits...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Amid-a-surge-in-ransomware-attacks-cities-are-16433183.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ransomware attacks have become a scourge for local governments, robbing millions of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tower key tenants have fallen behind on rent and moved out. But Donald has one reliable customer: His own PAC...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-Tower-s-key-tenants-have-fallen-behind-on-16433133.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Inside Trump Tower, swank suit-maker Marcraft Clothes once rented the entire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does EU need own army? Afghanistan withdrawal revives old debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Does-the-European-Union-need-its-own-army-16433159.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS - When President Joe Biden refused to keep U.S. troops in Afghanistan past the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau's first Canada election debate a slugfest...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210903-trudeau-s-first-canada-election-debate-a-slugfest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trudeau's first Canada election debate a slugfest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-fi blockbuster 'DUNE' brings stars to Venice...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sci-fi-blockbuster-dune-brings-052611694.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most hotly anticipated sci-fi blockbusters in years was finally set to land on Friday, as the world premiere of "Dune" arrived at the Venice Film Festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 years after 9/11: 'We will live with scars' forever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-25b508156f7888e2634f2ebe2228de95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEBBLE BEACH, Calif. (AP) — Twenty years later, Jack Grandcolas still remembers waking up at 7:03 that morning. He looked at the clock, then out the window where an image in the sky caught his eye — a fleeting vision that looked like an angel ascending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho hospitals nearly buckling in relentless surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-idaho-09941b507483a5c7b0183dcbf03a8254</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — The intensive care rooms at St. Luke's Boise Medical Center are full, each a blinking jungle of tubes, wires and mechanical breathing machines. The patients nestled inside are a lot alike: All unvaccinated, mostly middle-aged, paralyzed and sedated, reliant on life support and locked in a silent struggle against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First flames, then fees: Evacuees report price-gouging...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-environment-and-nature-5f8e3d5c22a55ef82a8a012d8ffa531e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STATELINE, Nev. (AP) — As fearful Lake Tahoe residents packed up belongings and fled a raging wildfire burning toward the California-Nevada border, some encountered an unexpected obstacle: price gouging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collectible Prices Skyrocket, to Dismay of Hobbyists...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2021-09-03/collectible-prices-skyrocket-to-the-dismay-of-hobbyists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have become obsessed with collectibles, bidding up prices for trading cards, video games and other mementos of their youth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ Gov Who Backed Bolsonaro Now Wants Brazil's Top Job...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/lgbtq-governor-who-backed-bolsonaro-now-wants-brazils-top-job/ar-AAO3EbV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eduardo Leite is young, investor-friendly and vying for the Brazilian presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dearth of Employees Risks Even Higher Food Prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2021-09-03/supply-lines-latest-dearth-of-workers-risks-even-higher-food-prices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milkshakes are missing from U.K.’s McDonald’s branches, tomatoes are rotting on Italian farms, and soldiers mingle with farmers on Vietnam’s rice paddies. All because of shortage of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Uses More Electricity Than Many Countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2021/09/03/climate/bitcoin-carbon-footprint-electricity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most popular cryptocurrency wastes energy by design. Why is that, and could it ever be greener?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Sparks Political Controversy With Taiwan Films Name Change...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/venice-film-fest-political-controversy-taiwan-movies-name-change-1235007855/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Festival organizers have rankled Taiwanese officials by listing two films in its lineup as being from "Chinese Taipei."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jab snob' travelers flock to Guam for sun, sea, shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Vaccine-snob-travelers-flock-to-Guam-for-sun-16433041.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TUMON, Guam - Passport: check. Coronavirus test: negative. Temperature: normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no tourist handouts, hungry Bali monkeys raid homes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-monkeys-da48c1eda07af577f5ffe38ae397179f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANGEH, Indonesia (AP) — Deprived of their preferred food source — the bananas, peanuts and other goodies brought in by tourists now kept away by the coronavirus — hungry monkeys on the resort island of Bali have taken to raiding villagers’ homes in their search for something tasty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS-inspired extremist stabs six in New Zealand terror attack...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/zealand-police-shoot-dead-isis-inspired-extremist-stabs/story?id=79808759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand is reeling from a knife-wielding rampage at a supermarket that left six fighting for their lives and the assailant dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats coming down with diseases caused by stress of lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9952167/Cats-falling-ill-life-threatening-STRESS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As coronavirus took hold early last year and the government told people to stay home for work and school, our pets started to get more attention than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most NYC victims were trapped in basement apartments...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/nyc-flooding-kills-several-residents-of-basement-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flooding from the remnants of Ida proved fatal for several New Yorkers living in a particularly vulnerable type of abode: the basement apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban feel 'angry and betrayed' after troops destroyed aircraft before fleeing Kabul...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/taliban-feel-angry-betrayed-troops-24899396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Government has been heavily criticised after leaving millions of dollars worth of sophisticated weaponry and aircraft in the hands of the terror group in Afghanistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  Approval of Labor Unions at Highest Point Since 1965...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/354455/approval-labor-unions-highest-point-1965.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-thirds of Americans approve of labor unions, marking the highest reading since 1965. Union membership among U.S. adults is steady, at 9%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of  Small Businesses Have Unfilled Positions...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/half-u-small-businesses-unfilled-173237603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for the New Economy Daily newsletter, follow us @economics and subscribe to our podcast.A record share of U.S. small-business owners said they had vacant positions in August, and an unprecedented number boosted wages to lure workers, the National Federation of Independent Business said Thursday.Fifty percent of firms had job openings they could not fill last month, up 1 percentage point from July and the largest share in monthly data back to 1986, according to the NFIB dat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to roll out its own TV...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-roll-own-tv-u-001236974.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc is planning to launch its Amazon-branded TV in the United States as soon as October, Business Insider reported on Thursday. The launch, involving teams from Amazon Devices and Lab126, has been in the works for almost two years, the report https://bit.ly/3t9bzrZ said, citing people familiar with the matter. The TVs, which will be powered by voice assistant Alexa, are currently designed and manufactured by third parties, one of which is TCL, the report added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow Returns to ESPN...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/tim-tebow-espn-first-take-stephen-a-smith-sparring-partner-1234826748/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Tebow was announced today by ESPN as one of the initial debate partners on Stephen A. Smith’s First Take. Tebow, who was cut from the NFL’s Jacksonville Jaguars in his latest pro spots co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of 'Shadow Docket' Fuels Criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/texas-abortion-ruling-renews-criticism-173730197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of lawmakers in both parties have questioned how the Supreme Court handles emergency appeals through its so-called shadow docket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  THREE Doses to Become Standard Covid Regimen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fauci-defends-covid-boosters-says-three-shots-will-likely-be-the-new-norm-210524610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci defended the administration’s decision to recommend coronavirus vaccine booster shots and said that three doses of an mRNA vaccine, not two, would be the new standard of full vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABBA unveils 'sensational' musical comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9951979/ABBA-releasing-new-songs-40-YEARS-play-hologram-tour.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABBA have revealed they are releasing their first new songs for 40 YEARS in the form of a studio album and will play a 'greatest hits'  tour as digital characters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested, charged over MSNBC TV confrontation...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/benjamin-eugene-dagley-msnbc-shaquille-brewster-assault-suspect-arrest-warrants-1234825163/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with arrest information: U.S. Marshals arrested Benjamin Eugene Dagley on Thursday at a shopping plaza in Dayton, Ohio, and the Gulfport Police Department in Mississippi has filed criminal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flights resume, SOME power restored in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hurricane-ida-business-environment-and-nature-louisiana-hurricanes-840ac80b55ad6a6b3201631044a0dce5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Commercial flights resumed in New Orleans and power returned to parts of the business district Thursday, four days after Hurricane Ida slammed into the Gulf Coast, but electricity, drinking water and fuel remained scarce across much of a sweltering Louisiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scuba diver has head bitten by tiger shark...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3589753/shocking-moment-tiger-shark-attacks-divers-head/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a massive tiger shark dubbed “Big Mama” chomps down on a diver’s head before pals kick the beast away. Real-time underwater footage shows the hungry sh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELLEN'S REDEMPTION TOUR...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3589770/ellen-degeneres-show-guests-kim-kardashian-jennifer-aniston-support/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIM Kardashian and Jennifer Aniston are two of the celebrities lending their support for Ellen DeGeneres by agreeing to appear on her talk show. Despite claims of Ellen’s show having a “toxic workp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: 3 shots for everyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/covid-vaccine-fauci-says-he-would-not-be-surprised-if-full-regimen-is-three-doses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Giving people an additional dose several months after they've received their initial vaccination helps the immune system mature, Fauci said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female Draft Tucked Into Defense Bill...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/democrats-tuck-female-draft-into-defense-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon will have to start drafting women in order to receive funding after House Democrats amended the defense budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF THE ROE?</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/supreme-court-just-effectively-overturned-201416160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And opened the door to armies of private vigilantes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOKer Rallies Fans to Bombard 'Whistleblower' Site With Fake Tips...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tiktoker-creates-script-to-bombard-texas-abortion-whistleblower-site-with-fake-tips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TikTok “hacktivist” has created a script to flood a Texas website used to solicit information on people seeking abortions with fake reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDI unveils new concept car as 'private jet for road'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/audi-unveils-grandsphere-concept-car-as-a-private-jet-for-the-road.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the vehicle can't fly, Audi said it designed the electric car with such luxury private travel in mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LISTEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/02/abba-drops-2-songs-announces-new-album-avatar-tour-now-look-like-steely-dans-becker-and-fagen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benny and Bjorn from ABBA now look like Donald Fagen and Walter Becker from Steely Dan. Forty years later, they’re releasing a new album on November 5th called “Voyage.” Two of th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk declines to address law after Gov. suggests he supports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/texas-abortion-law-elon-musk-reacts-to-gov-greg-abbotts-comments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk declined to directly weigh in on Texas' abortion law after Gov. Greg Abbott said the Tesla CEO supported his state's "social policies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel now world's Covid hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9951117/Israel-worlds-Covid-hotspot-0-2-population-catching-yesterday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country recorded 1,892 cases per million people on Wednesday - nearly 0.2 per cent of the entire population in a single day - stats compiled by an Oxford University research team show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHARK TANK' stars sued for fraud...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/02/shark-tank-stars-kevin-oleary-kevin-harrington-sued-for-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty hopeful entrepreneurs claim the famed business investors manipulated them into paying their companies and received no help in return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Gets Jab...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/02/tom-brady-vaccinated-bruce-arians-buccaneers-100-percent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buccaneers head coach Bruce Arians told the media on Thursday that 100 percent of the team's players, coaches, and staff have been vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular surfing instructor, Q, and an unspeakable horror...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/popular-surfing-instructor-qanon-unspeakable-120045161.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Barbara residents are struggling to make sense of a tragedy involving Matt Coleman, head of a local surf school, and the killings of his two young children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning into landslide...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/Newsom-recall-poll-election-California-yes-Elder-16430710.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's Newsom's most favorable recall poll in a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vows 'whole-of-government' response...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/unconstitutional-chaos-biden-vows-whole-government-response-after-texas-abortion-n1278380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden called the U.S. Supreme Court’s 5-4 ruling “an unprecedented assault on a woman’s constitutional rights under Roe v. Wade."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma Company Ready to Jab Dogs, Cats, Zoo Animals...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/09/01/although-covid-19-rare-in-cats-dogs-pharmaceutical-company-says-theyre-ready-with-a-vaccine-if-needed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If or when cats and dogs need COVID vaccine, Zoetis pharmaceutical company is ready to provide. At this time the virus is rare in pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK to Want to Exterminate People, Greece's New Health Minister Once Argued...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kv3za/its-ok-to-want-to-exterminate-people-greeces-new-health-minister-once-argued</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanos Plevris, the man in charge of Greece's pandemic response, has apologised if comments he made about Auschwitz while defending his own dad from Holocaust-denial offended any Jewish people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaxxer's family ridiculed after 'begging' for money...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/coronavirus/global/antivaxxers-family-slammed-for-begging-for-money/news-story/6cb5726f9c1a9d03158c92c238c36f57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of a Covid-19 conspiracy theorist who ultimately died of the virus has been ridiculed for “begging” for money and launching a fundraising page — with strangers accusing them of “stupidity” and urging potential donors not “to help pay for the funeral of someone who caused others to die”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Must Face Claim That Siri Violates Privacy, Judge Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-02/apple-must-face-claim-that-siri-violates-privacy-judge-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge allowed a lawsuit against Apple Inc. to proceed with a claim that its Siri voice assistant violates users’ privacy, but he dismissed part of the complaint under California’s Unfair Competition Law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving workplace spawns new jobs: Social scientist, remote work evangelist, digital anthropologist....</title>
      <link>https://metropolismag.com/viewpoints/think-lab-future-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metropolismag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ThinkLab report finds that if we adapt as we go, the workplace could become a practical extension of our present conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Digital Currencies to Be Tested in Experiment...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/central-bank-digital-currencies-tested-040000941.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Bank for International Settlements will test the use of central bank digital currencies with Australia, Malaysia, Singapore and South Africa in an experiment that could lead to a more efficient global payments platform.Codenamed “Project Dunbar,” the study aims to develop prototypes for a common platform that will enable international settlement in digital fiat currencies issued by central banks, BIS said in a release Thursday. The system would allow direct transactions in cen</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
