<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Doctor Investigates Throat Clearing, Stiffer Gait...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/582436-bidens-doctor-says-hes-fit-for-office-after-annual-physical</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s physician on Friday determined he was healthy and fit to execute the duties of the presidency following his annual physical the day before his 79th birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court rejects NYT bid to resume VERITAS coverage...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211119224008-iar3u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK TIMES-PROJECT VERITAS/ (PIX):Appeals court rejects New York Times bid to resume Project Veritas coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Probe Set to Slam Into Asteroid and Kill Self...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nasas-dart-mission-will-slam-into-an-asteroid-to-teach-us-how-to-save-earth-from-annihilation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DART is a $325 million suicide mission in space that could teach us how to save the world from annihilation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  After 20 Years of Failure, Kill TSA...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/19/after-20-years-of-failure-kill-the-tsa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On this day in 2001, in response to the terrorist attacks of September 11, the Transportation Security Administration (TSA) was created in a demonstration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to give homeless right to housing roils Sacramento...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-plan-to-give-homeless-people-the-right-to-housing-roils-sacramento/ar-AAQUdiK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father, son die within days of each other...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-ab9ac13c954a08754ed568f84d43ed05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VICTORY, N.Y. (AP) — A New York family, who all contracted COVID-19, has suffered the loss of a father and son to the virus within a few days of each other. Rick Martin, 57, of Victory, died on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to give homeless right to housing roils Sacramento...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/homeless-housing/story/2021-11-19/sacramentos-mayor-wants-a-right-to-housing-some-in-his-city-are-skeptical</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacramento Mayor Darrell Steinberg has introduced what he is calling a "Right to Housing."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police fire warning shots during Rotterdam protest...</title>
      <link>https://nltimes.nl/2021/11/19/police-fire-warning-shots-covid-measures-protest-rotterdam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nltimes.nl&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The police in Rotterdam fired multiple warning shots during riots on the Coolsingel, a main road in the center of the city. “There are injuries related to the gunshots fired,” police confirmed. It was not immediately clear how many people were injured in total. There were also reports that a journalist was attacked on the street. Rijnmond said the journalist was beaten and his camera was destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ANGRY' BIDEN URGES PEACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/biden-asked-about-rittenhouse-acquittal-says-jury-system-works-n1284262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president said he hadn't watched the trial and that, "I stand by what the jury has concluded."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC school will to segregate students...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/18/manhattan-school-to-sort-kids-by-race-during-social-justice-discussions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lower Manhattan Community School will conduct the exercises as part of its mission to “undo the legacy of racism and oppression in this country that impacts our school community.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justices could rule on Texas ban as soon as Monday...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-us-supreme-court-health-texas-2b7039e03a1cf0a162587c6ea215f224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court could rule as soon as Monday on Texas' ban on abortion after roughly six weeks. The justices are planning to issue at least one opinion Monday, the first of its new term, the court said on its website Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYLE ALL SMILES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4104150/kyle-rittenhouse-not-guilty-kenosha-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYLE Rittenhouse was pictured grinning as he left court on Friday after he was found not guilty of killing two. Rittenhouse was acquitted of all charges after pleading self-defense in the deadly Ke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ballad was originally 15 minutes long...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-features/adele-i-drink-wine-30-song-review-1260116/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 30 track is one of the best songs of her already-storied career, a gorgeous power ballad that sees a pop deity come down to Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos after Rittenhouse verdict as woman collapses on courthouse steps...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4104842/kyle-rittenhouse-verdict-kenosha-court-woman-collapses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHAOS at Kenosha court as woman reportedly collapsed on steps and hundreds of protesters rally after the Kyle Rittenhouse verdict. According to WFRV, an unidentified woman had a medical emergency o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army bars refusers from promotions, reenlistment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/19/politics/army-covid-vaccinations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With less than one month until the Army's deadline to vaccinate its active-duty force, the service will begin barring soldiers who refuse to be vaccinated against Covid-19 without an exemption from reenlistment, promotions, and other "favorable personnel actions."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ charges some who posed as pro-Trump Proud Boys...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/justice-department-charges-2-iranians-210552849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The duo made a fake video depicting a person hacking state voter websites and creating fake absentee ballots, capitalizing on Trump's rhetoric.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Hackers Going After US Critical Infrastructure...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/iranian-hackers-going-after-us-critical-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hacking group is targeting a broad range of organizations, taking advantage of vulnerabilities that have been patched but not yet updated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interior Secretary moves to rid USA of 'racially derogatory' place names...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/19/interior-secretary-haaland-moves-to-rid-us-of-racially-derogatory-place-names-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Interior Secretary Deb Haaland announced Friday that the federal government will establish a process to review and replace racially derogatory terms used in place names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA mulls nuke reactor on moon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-science-business-moon-idaho-ae35ae200a46bec0ca215bc88923181d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — If anyone has a good idea on how to put a nuclear fission power plant on the moon, the U.S. government wants to hear about it. NASA and the nation’s top federal nuclear research lab on Friday put out a request for proposals for a fission surface power system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research links virus in pregnancy with stillbirths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-lifestyle-health-centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention-09d66b3b147016b45bae8e405062d7d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pregnant women with COVID-19 face increased chances for stillbirths compared with uninfected women, and that risk spiked to four times higher after the delta variant emerged, new government data show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big tech critics flocking to ORACLE home on Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/19/tech-capitol-hill-townhouse-oracle-523014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers and lobbyists looking to check the power of Silicon Valley's biggest giants have flocked to the $2.8 million house that Oracle owns just blocks from the halls of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas calls on Justin Bieber to cancel show in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/hamas-calls-on-justin-bieber-to-cancel-show-in-israel-685384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was arrested for not wearing mask -- he died in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/security-guard-arrested-after-not-wearing-mask-on-bus-dies-in-santa-rita-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The story of what happened to Maurice Monk, a 45-year-old security guard who suffered from mental illness and who died in a cell on Monday, raises questions about the care he received while incarcerated and why he was in Santa Rita Jail in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White power movement turning on each other with spectacular bitterness in court...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/19/us/unite-the-right-trial-charlottesville-rally/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key federal defendant accused of conspiracy over the 2017 Unite the Right rally was forced this week to confront his own explicit calls for violence -- and who should do the actual fighting -- in the months before the deadly event unfolded in Charlottesville, Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  SITS FOR HOUR-LONG THERAPY SESSION WITH ZANE LOWE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1gtPULpjzuA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zane Lowe sits down with Adele to unpack her fourth studio album, ’30,’ exploring the inspirations behind each track and their impact on her life. Adele expl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PICTURES: Longest lunar eclipse in 600 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4100119/photos-of-lunar-eclipse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A STUNNING lunar eclipse occurred this morning and it could be viewed for over three hours in the US. It involved the Earth’s shadow covering about 97 per cent of the full Beaver Moon. Viewer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook moves 3 Senate races toward Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cook-political-report-senate-races-gop-3cd595f8-db50-4a53-b58d-2ba3de23475a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The moves reflect the increasingly bullish midterm environment for Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden transfers power to Kamala while gets colonoscopy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4102232/biden-colonoscopy-birthday-kamala-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden is set to undergo a colonoscopy today ahead of his 79th birthday and Kamala Harris will become acting president while he is under anesthetic. The president arrived at Walter Reed Hospital…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump writes picture book, son brags: Dad 'wrote all the captions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-book-coffee-table-29bcec81-74d3-4eef-975d-c529002bdf29.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It features 300+ official White House photographs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT INTENSIFIES: HOW MANY SHOTS WILL BE REQUIRED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-vaccines-boosters-fauci-america-c0f4e198-9a2f-42c4-ba74-3fa06ce1d811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some experts and officials are pushing for the definition of "fully vaccinated" to change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becomes first woman to hold presidential power...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-transfer-power-harris-colonoscopy-physical-3503f6b9-3f98-463a-97d3-d9b3e7480dfb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden will also receive his first annual physical as president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside world's first lockdown for unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/11/inside-the-austrian-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We explore the world's first lockdown for the unvaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado ICU Doctor: More Worried NOW Than BEFORE...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/11/18/covid-trajectory-fort-collins-surge-hospitals-icu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since the Delta variant has caused a surge of COVID-19 cases and hospitalizations in northern Colorado, medical providers in the packed halls of the ICU are sharing their stories with CBS4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord Among Jurors?</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/11/18/kyle-rittenhouse-jury-deliberations-irv-miller/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors in the Kyle Rittenhouse trial left the Kenosha County courthouse for the third night with no verdict late Thursday – and the deliberations seem to be taking longer than some thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60-foot waves exploded off Pacific Coast during bomb cyclone...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/60-foot-waves-exploded-off-the-pacific-coast-during-octobers-bomb-cyclone/article_123708be-1231-5c90-992d-ac2de04fc646.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The bomb cyclone and atmospheric river that pummeled Northern California in late October produced exceptionally heavy rain and high winds. But it also battered the California coast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roadrunner hitched 3,000-mile ride from Vegas to Maine. Bird experts trying to send back...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/A-roadrunner-hitched-a-nearly-3-000-mile-ride-16634451.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In less than an hour, 73-year-old Karen Silverman did what Wile E. Coyote has not been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why NASA Probe Set to Slam Into Asteroid and Kill Self...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nasas-dart-mission-will-slam-into-an-asteroid-to-teach-us-how-to-save-earth-from-annihilation?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DART is a $325 million suicide mission in space that could teach us how to save the world from annihilation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Death toll could soar by 300,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4101928/study-warns-of-300000-covid-deaths-in-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW study has revealed Europe could face “300,000 deaths and one million people in hospital” as Covid wreaks havoc across the continent this winter. The London School of Hygiene and T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch delay care for cancer, heart patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211119135227-ycl1s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NETHERLANDS:Facing new COVID wave, Dutch delay care for cancer, heart patients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet The Bonnie and Clyde of MAGA World...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/11/19/dustin-stockton-jen-lawrence-trump-profile-522823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a decade, Dustin Stockton and Jennifer Lawrence had surfed the wave of populist-right politics like few other people in America. Then came Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania GOP baffled by Dr. Oz Senate bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/19/pennsylvania-republicans-dr-oz-senate-bid-523023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP insiders are rattled by the unsettled primary field in one of the nation’s most important Senate races.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosters authorized for all adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-authorizes-pfizer-moderna-booster-adults-rcna5856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA authorized Pfizer and Moderna booster shots for all adults. A CDC advisory panel will take up the issue on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ire grows as DeSantis popularity with Republicans takes off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/19/politics/trump-desantis-relationship/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a matter of months, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has gone from being a shining example in Donald Trump's eyes of a MAGA leader molded in his image to an average politician who forgot his roots as he rose to Republican stardom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci office flooded with attacks over beagle experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Fauci-s-office-flooded-with-attacks-over-beagle-16634352.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Anthony Fauci was swamped by so many angry messages and threats that in late...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockdown fears rattle investors, spark dash for safe-havens...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/global-markets/europe-lockdown-fears-rattle-investors-spark-dash-for-safe-havens-idUSKBN2I4068</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European stocks retreated from record highs, while government bond yields, oil prices and the euro tumbled on Friday as the specter of a fresh COVID-linked lockdown in Germany and other parts of Europe cast a fresh shadow over the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron used to be indestructible. Now, his health is biggest concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/lebron-james-used-to-be-indestructible-now-his-health-is-the-lakers-e2-80-99-biggest-concern/ar-AAQU2lB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megachurch founder forced girls and young women into sex, telling them it was 'God's will'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/filipino-megachurch-founder-forced-girls-and-young-women-into-sex-telling-them-it-was-e2-80-98god-e2-80-99s-will-e2-80-99-feds-say/ar-AAQTT9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA worker alleges sex harassment rampant in suit. Now other women stepping forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/A-Tesla-factory-worker-alleges-sexual-harassment-16634382.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - Jessica Barraza was only months into her job at Tesla's factory when she...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary opposition leader vows to restore western alliances...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-religion-russia-china-elections-48d6759386cb29344f7925b2eca593bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HODMEZOVASARHELY, Hungary (AP) — Hungary's opposition leader wants to restore his country's frayed ties with the West — and also has a message for American fans of right-wing Prime Minister Viktor Orban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists mystified, wary, as Africa avoids COVID disaster...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-pandemics-united-nations-fcf28a83c9352a67e50aa2172eb01a2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARARE, Zimbabwe (AP) — At a busy market in a poor township outside Harare this week, Nyasha Ndou kept his mask in his pocket, as hundreds of other people, mostly unmasked, jostled to buy and sell fruit and vegetables displayed on wooden tables and plastic sheets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway tightens entry rules, urges dropping handshake...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-denmark-norway-2343d26b5e7475b489b8d68be8d4039b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Norwegian officials said Friday the country is introducing stricter controls at border crossings, requiring everyone to register before entering the country, in a bid to tackle the rise in COVID cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacist prison guards work with impunity in FL?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-prisons-florida-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-60b96681445509d89e6c0497405497d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In June, three Florida prison guards who boasted of being white supremacists beat, pepper sprayed and used a stun gun on an inmate who screamed “I can’t breathe!” at a prison near the Alabama border, according to a fellow inmate who reported it to the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look at intimate details AMAZON knows about us...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211119112546-ny6lf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AMAZON.COM/PRIVACY-SIDEBAR (PIX, TV):A look at the intimate details Amazon knows about us</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court bars NYT from publishing VERITAS memos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/court-bars-new-york-times-from-publishing-project-veritas-memos-in-move-called-e2-80-98unconstitutional-e2-80-99/ar-AAQSGeu </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saying grace: How moment of thanks, religious or not, adds meaning to meals...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Saying-grace-How-a-moment-of-thanks-religious-16632304.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brett Levanto and his family had never said grace before meals, not regularly, anyway....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Forcing Out Soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2021/11/exclusive-army-force-out-soldiers-who-refuse-covid-vaccine/186954/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New policy bars unvaccinated soldiers from re-enlistment, promotions as Oklahoma governor says National Guard need not obey Biden's vax mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Diet-related illness increases with availability of red meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/diet-related-illness-increases-with-availability-of-red-meat-study-01637276708 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware Putin amid US-China rivalry, Hillary Clinton warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.asiaone.com/world/beware-putin-amid-us-china-rivalry-hillary-clinton-warns-bloomberg-forum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiaone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the United States' rivalry with China, Washington and its Western allies must remain wary of Russian President Vladimir Putin and his use of dubious "non-state actors" to sharpen his global projection of power, former US Secretary of State Hillary Clinton has said. Speaking via video link on the final day of the Bloomberg New Economy Forum in Singapore, Clinton...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest lunar eclipse in 580 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/beaver-moon-lunar-eclipse-photos-november-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the longest partial lunar eclipse in 580 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zemmour draws comparisons to Trump as he upends French presidential election...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/c3-a9ric-zemmour-draws-comparisons-to-trump-as-he-upends-french-presidential-election/ar-AAQTx8d </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy late night speech punctuates two party's disdain for each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mccarthy-e2-80-99s-late-night-speech-punctuates-week-where-the-two-party-e2-80-99s-disdain-for-each-other-was-on-full-display/ar-AAQT0db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Tells Trump He Needs to Leave Past Behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/rupert-murdoch-tells-trump-he-needs-to-leave-the-past-behind/ar-AAQPEyk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHIFT: Florida Republicans Overtake Democrats in Registered Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/florida-republicans-overtake-democrats-in-registered-voters/ar-AAQStxc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE NATION, APPLE, Travis Scott sued for $2 billion over 'Astroworld' disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/live-nation-apple-travis-scott-sued-for-242-billion-over-astroworld-disaster/ar-AAQRYrj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euro winter of discontent: Now Germany locks down unvaccinated!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10218895/French-protest-against-Austrias-new-Covid-apartheid-fearing-rule-spread-Europe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large crowds waving flags gathered outside the Austrian Embassy in Paris in protest at Vienna's lockdown for the unvaccinated, with Italy and Greece considering similar restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS: THIRD day of deliberations in Rittenhouse case with no verdict...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kyle-rittenhouse-wisconsin-shootings-kenosha-ac4ff9ba75f00884ce6cd5e5932d5543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (AP) — The jury at Kyle Rittenhouse’s murder trial deliberated for a third full day without reaching a verdict Thursday, while the judge banned MSNBC from the courthouse after a freelancer for the network was accused of following the jurors in their bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House moves toward OK of sweeping social, climate bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-joe-biden-business-lifestyle-environment-a518d86dfb69ab2a56ac507746a8d810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A divided House moved toward passage Thursday of Democrats' expansive social and environment bill  as new cost estimates from Congress' top fiscal analyst suggested that moderate lawmakers' spending and deficit worries would be calmed, moving President Joe Biden closer to a badly needed victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure on Fed rising...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-economy-prices-inflation-jerome-powell-583029ed34f028d4950fd5b0d896388f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell surely expected to have some breathing room after taking the first step this month to dial back the Fed’s emergency aid for the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The vaccine tore her family apart. Could a death bring them back together?</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/the-vaccine-tore-her-family-apart-could-a-death-bring-them-back-together/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Thanksgiving nearing, infections high or rising in many parts of the U.S. and vaccines now widely available to children, family breaches over COVID immunization status are reaching new levels of rancor and intensity. Here's the Haughts' story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Charlottesville trial, jurors learn to decode secret slang of white supremacists...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/In-Charlottesville-trial-jurors-learn-to-decode-16632986.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. - The jury in a federal courtroom listened as a longtime researcher...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL: BIDEN APPROVAL DROPS TO 36%</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/poll-release?releaseid=3827</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
