<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>No flights or internet during Bali's sacred Day of Silence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bali-shuts-down-day-silence-051247640.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesia's holiday island Bali fell quiet Thursday for the annual "Day of Silence" festival, halting flights, internet and closing tourist attractions to allow time for meditation and introspection. Known locally as Nyepi, Hindus on the island are expected to stay at home for 24 hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROVE:  The Primary From Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-democratic-primary-from-hell-11551916920?mod=searchresults&amp;page=2&amp;pos=7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New rules, endless candidates and a front-loaded schedule. Pass the popcorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg Turns Attention to Private Communications...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-plans-new-emphasis-on-private-communications-11551899847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is making a major bet that the future of social media will be in private messaging and small group chats, not the public sharing of photos and messages that it pioneered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pleading the Fifth?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/3-things-to-watch-trump-kids-associates-eye-pleading-the-fifth-as-dems-bore-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like many issues, where President Trump stands on pleading the Fifth is inconsistent. His stance appears linked to how it might help him or hurt an enemy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA teams with ALIBABA for massive China expansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nba-alibaba/nba-to-offer-content-across-all-alibaba-platforms-in-expanded-deal-idUSKCN1QO046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Basketball Association will offer fans in China original programmin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems fear targeting Trump family could backfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/06/trump-children-democrats-investigations-1207640</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They worry zeroing in on Ivanka, Don Jr. and Eric would be politically perilous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Government Tracking Journalists Through Secret Database...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/investigations/Source-Leaked-Documents-Show-the-US-Government-Tracking-Journalists-and-Advocates-Through-a-Secret-Database-506783231.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The documents detail an intelligence-gathering effort by the United States and Mexican authorities, targeting more than 50 people including journalists, an attorney, and immigration advocates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Gut-wrenching' day as Ohio GM assembly plant prepares to close...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/gut-wrenching-day-ohio-gm-assembly-plant-prepares-close-n980136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last Chevrolet Cruze built at GM's plant near Youngstown is expected to come off the assembly line Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAMPED</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Not-my-fault-Trump-struggles-to-defend-his-13668725.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump proclaimed in a freewheeling speech to a conference of conservatives last weekend that "America is winning again." But his administration has been on a pronounced losing streak over the past week. Trump is losing ground on top priorities to curb illegal immigration, cut the trade deficit and blunt North Korea's nuclear threat - setbacks that complicate his planned reelection message as a can-do president who is making historic progress. Late last week, Trump flew home empty-handed from a summit with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un in Hanoi, Vietnam - and, within days, new satellite images appeared to show the North was secretly rebuilding a rocket launching site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal immigration on pace to triple 2017 levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/06/three-times-the-illegal-immigration-of-2017-levels-at-current-rate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigration this year is on pace to more than triple the levels of just two years ago, new projections reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town Proposes Rule Giving Dog Owners Jail Time For Nonstop Barking...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/03/05/new-jersey-dog-owners-jail-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dog owners who break the new rules could face fines ranging between $100 and $1,000, but owners could also receive a sentence of community service or even prison time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Candidates Stumbling Over Themselves On Campaign Trail...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democratic-candidates-literally-bumping-trail-031009998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2020 primary is packed but candidates insist it will be cordial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Reveals She Was Raped While in Air Force...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190306220653-lrzh6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CONGRESS/MCSALLY (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-U.S. Senator McSally, an Air Force veteran, says she was raped by a superior officer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Posts Record Trade Deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/december-2018-trade-data-from-u-s-commerce-department-11551877494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. trade deficit in goods reached a record in 2018, defying President Trump’s efforts to narrow the gap, as imports jumped and some exports got hammered by retaliation against U.S. tariffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of millionaires were C students...</title>
      <link>https://www.theladders.com/career-advice/these-are-the-earliest-signs-of-a-future-millionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theladders.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Author Tom Corley continues his exploration of all the little under-observed qualities that separate millionaires from everyone else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS REVOLT AGAINST PELOSI...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/06/ilhan-omar-israel-democrats-1206740</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers clashed behind closed doors, with some complaining that Speaker Nancy Pelosi and her leadership team had failed to handle the escalating political crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tense Epstein hearing airs sex claims against Dershowitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/06/alex-acosta-jeffrey-epstein-plea-deal-1206753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acosta was stung by a judge’s ruling last month that he and other prosecutors violated federal law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro shocks with Brazil 'golden shower' tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/brazils-president-jair-bolsonaro-posts-sexually-explicit-golden-showers-video-on-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNER BROS. CEO being investigated for sex misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/i-need-be-careful-texts-reveal-warner-bros-ceo-promoted-actress-apparent-sexual-relationship-1192660</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of leaked text messages between Kevin Tsujihara, actress Charlotte Kirk and partners Brett Ratner and James Packer show the powerful executive, under pressure, said repeatedly he would push for auditions as accusations of "extortion" and a proposed settlement agreement followed. WarnerMedia says it will investigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Fed: Growth to slow 'considerably'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190306-us-growth-slow-considerably-2019-ny-fed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US growth to slow 'considerably' in 2019: NY Fed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court Grants Aborted Baby Legal Rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/03/judge-grants-unborn-baby-legal-rights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An aborted baby for the first time in the United States has been recognized to have legal rights. An Alabama man suing a clinic for providing an abortion to a woman he says was pregnant with his baby petitioned a probate judge to allow him to represent the unborn child’s estate, reported WHNT-TV in Huntsville, […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS REVOLT AGAINST PELOSI</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Democratic-divide-over-Omar-s-remarks-tests-13668736.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats find themselves in one of the trickiest battles on Capitol Hill, trying to prove their unity in the fight against President Donald Trump and on core issues they campaigned on last year. They had a remarkably effective first two months in the majority, defying Trump on his demand for a border wall and clearly winning the leftover budget battle from 2018. They passed a significant bill that would require expanded background checks on gun purchases. And they are poised to approve an expansive bill that would revamp ethics and electoral laws. But those early wins are threatened by the growing controversy about how House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah legalizing sex outside of marriage...</title>
      <link>https://fox13now.com/2019/03/06/fornication-will-no-longer-be-illegal-in-utah/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox13now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY -- The Utah State Legislature is making sex outside of marriage legal. In a bill cleaning up Utah's criminal code, lawmakers repealed the misdemeanor crime of fornication. The House passed Senate Bill 43 on a 41-32 vote. It previously passed the Utah State Senate and now goes to Governor Gary Herbert for his signature or veto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS REVOLT AGAINST PELOSI</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-democrats-erupt-in-protests-over-indirect-sanction-of-rep-omar-for-alleged-anti-semitism/ar-BBUrXKN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: I'LL BLOCK 'FAKE NEWS' FROM HOLDING 2020 DEBATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-blasts-dnc-for-barring-fox-news-from-debates-then-ill-do-the-same-with-the-fake-news-networks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SPOTLIGHT RISK'</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/432947-harris-attention-surrounding-omar-puts-her-at-risk-of-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris (D-Calif.) defended Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAMALA: PUTTING SPOTLIGHT ON OMAR DANGEROUS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/bernie-sander-ihlan-omar-antisemitism-legitimate-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JEOPARDY!' Host Trebek Reveals Stage 4 Cancer Diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/jeopardy-host-alex-trebek-has-stage-4-pancreatic-cancer-51218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beloved "Jeopardy!" host Alex Trebek has been diagnosed with stage 4 pancreatic cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges against ex-Rep. Schock to be dropped...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-ex-congressman-aaron-schock-guilty-20190306-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a surprise move for a high-profile public corruption case, federal prosecutors in Chicago have agreed to drop all charges against former U.S. Rep. Aaron Schock if he pays back money he owes to the Internal Revenue Service and his campaign fund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems won't let FOXNEWS host debate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/432879-dems-wont-let-fox-news-host-primary-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Committee (DNC) said Wednesday it would not permit Fox News to host a presidential primary debate, citing an explosive story this week alleging deep ties between the conservative network and President Trump’s inner circle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops use social livestreaming to crack down on speeders...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox13news.com/news/local-news/lakeland-police-use-facebook-live-while-cracking-down-on-speeders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox13news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lakeland Police are cracking down on speeders with a new twist: by using Facebook Live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 300-mph supercar...</title>
      <link>https://www.roadandtrack.com/car-shows/geneva-auto-show/a26617787/koenigsegg-jesko-geneva-motor-show-photos-info-specs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.roadandtrack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It also has a nine-speed gearbox with seven clutches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gardener suspected of planting bombs to kill foes days before he died...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/german-gardener-suspected-of-planting-explosives/a-47798087</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police believe a gardener from a city in western Germany planted booby traps intended for his foes in the days before his own death. One explosive device already killed a man, and authorities fear there could be more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama complains about leaders who beat their chest...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6776169/Obama-complains-leaders-beat-chest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former US President Barack Obama told a crowd in Canada on Tuesday that much of what is trotted out as leadership today is just old-style beating your chest and talking loud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museums keep exhibits on display...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf5ea921dfd54e288574fab904676e97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Megastar Michael Jackson's musical legacy has been getting critically reappraised after a new documentary rekindled allegations of child sexual abuse, but at least two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phenomenon makes NC Outer Banks appear surrounded by boiling water...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/latest-news/article227171464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire diamond trader dies during penis enlargement surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6777961/Billionaire-diamond-trader-65-dies-penis-enlargement-surgery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ehud Arye Laniado, a billionaire diamond trader, 65, reportedly suffered a heart attack during the operation in Paris. A friend of the Israeli's said he was 'always focused on his appearance'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitism Rebuke Put Off Amid Growing Discord...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-06/anti-semitism-rebuke-threatens-rift-among-house-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Santa Anita Suspends Racing After 21st Horse Dies...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/03/05/santa-anita-race-track-suspension/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after the death of the 21st horse at Santa Anita since late December, track officials reportedly announced Tuesday an indefinite suspension of racing at the famed facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. McSally, ex-Air Force pilot, says officer raped her...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/arizona/2019/03/06/martha-mcsally-reveals-she-raped-superior-officer-air-force/3082201002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Martha McSally revealed during a congressional hearing Wednesday that she was raped by a superior officer while she was in the Air Force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>390 FAMILY DOLLAR stores closing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/197d0aca696f403ca1c18f697ec89806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Dollar Tree Inc. is closing up to 390 Family Dollar stores this year and rebranding about 200 others under the Dollar Tree name. The company also slashed the value of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protections for gray wolves to be lifted...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comc&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carnival float features puppets of grinning Jews, rat, money bags...</title>
      <link>https://www.jta.org/2019/03/04/global/belgian-carnaval-party-features-puppets-of-grinning-jew-with-a-rat-money-bags</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jta.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A protest against "rising prices" contains “typical, anti-Semitic caricatures from 1939.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE giving pregnancy tests to all girls over nine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6778273/Kirstjen-Nielsen-says-recycling-rings-let-illegals-reuse-children-jump-border-repeatedly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'At ICE, when we have families with children, we have to give every girl a pregnancy test over 10. This is not a safe journey,' Kirstjen Neilsen told the House Homeland Security Committee on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen gives docs on 4th day of testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/06/politics/michael-cohen-testimony-congress/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen on Wednesday provided the House Intelligence Committee with new documents showing edits to the false written statement he delivered to Congress in 2017 about the Trump Organization's pursuit of the Trump Tower Moscow project into the 2016 campaign season, according to multiple sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK reputation sinking fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-login-28425848-9e0a-4ba0-9311-0da70a1276c3.html?chunk=0#story0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ina Fried, our expert on tech, illuminates the news shaping Silicon Valley and tech products. Weekday mornings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier who took machine gun round to head has helmet to prove it...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2019/03/05/soldier-who-took-a-machine-gun-round-to-the-head-now-has-his-helmet-to-prove-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since this incident the Army has begun fielding an even better helmet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland considers exhumations at pogrom site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9a9bdfb84494a88b5bdde19d2b389ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — The Polish government is reconsidering whether to exhume human remains at a World War II-era site where Jews were burned alive by Polish neighbors, though the country's chief...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physical wallet dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2019/03/06/can-ditch-my-wallet-smart-wallet-my-phone/3032297002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You grab your keys, smartphone and your wallet when you leave the house. It may not be such a disaster to leave the wallet and keys behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American journalist detained in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/american-journalist-based-in-caracas-detained-by-government-officials-amid-venezuela-unrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American reporter based in Caracas, who earlier this week covered opposition leader Juan Guaido's "triumphant" return to  Venezuela, has been detained by government officials after an early morning raid Wednesday, reports said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Cancels Report on Civilian Deaths in Drone Strikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-06/trump-cancels-u-s-report-on-civilian-deaths-in-drone-strikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur tracks make fresh impression at Valley Forge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f6f6f1fda6a44d9ebce3047bc50b10f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VALLEY FORGE, Pa. (AP) — The national park on the site where George Washington and the struggling Continental Army endured a tough winter during the American Revolution boasts a new feature that's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German ambassador ordered to leave...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7f93b0a4b6bd43ad89db35ba2575e282</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — The Venezuelan government on Wednesday gave the German ambassador 48 hours to leave the country after he expressed support for opposition leader Juan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX Delivery Robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbaltv.com/article/man-who-invented-segway-teams-with-fedex-to-build-delivery-robot/26691223</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbaltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The robot is battery-powered and can travel 10 miles an hour, and can carry up to 100 pounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans question LeBron's heart after another embarrassing loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/sports/2019/03/fans-question-lebron-james-heart-after-another-embarrassing-loss.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lakers' loss to the Clippers all but assures LeBron James won't be in the postseason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200 Cases of Mumps in Texas Detention Centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/03/04/200-cases-of-mumps-confirmed-in-texas-migrant-detention-centers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas health officials report that nearly 200 people contracted mumps in migrant detention facilities located across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As pigs are delivered to slaughterhouse, activists offer water and comfort to the doomed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/as-pigs-are-delivered-to-the-slaughterhouse-activists-offer-water/article_11090b32-4f40-56ce-bd54-d162c4c64b80.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Maya Benperlas stood in the middle of busy Vernon Avenue on a chilly Sunday night as a big rig hauling pigs slowed to a halt just outside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Japanese Worship Buddhist Robot at Ancient Shrine...</title>
      <link>https://thediplomat.com/2019/03/an-ancient-japanese-shrine-debuts-a-buddhist-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thediplomat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high-tech twist hopes to offer Buddhist wisdom that’s easily understood by younger generations in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL BEATDOWN:  6 WORKERS ATTACK MAN...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/03/05/watch-6-taco-bell-employees-beat-up-man-and-his-girlfriend-outside-center-city-location/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reese says he decided to release the video after reaching out to corporate Taco Bell, but the only response he got was an offer for a $20 gift card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRENNAN:  MUELLER COULD MOVE ON FRIDAY</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/03/05/brennan_predicts_mueller_report_more_indictments_on_friday_i_dont_have_inside_knowledge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CIA Director John Brennan said that, "not knowing," he would not be surprised if indictments produced by special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation were delivered this Friday. In an interview Tuesday night with MSNBC's Lawrence O'Donnell, Brennan said if a Trump family member is indicted that would signal the end of Mueller's investigation because Trump would probably fire him. "I wouldn't be surprised if for example this week on Friday, not knowing anything about it, but Friday is the day the grand jury indictments come down and also this Friday is better than next Friday because next Friday is the 15th of March, which is the Ides of March," Brennan said. "And I don't think Robert Mueller will want to have that dramatic flair of the Ides of March when he is going to be delivering what I think are going to be are his indictments, the final indictments as well the report." "I do think also if anybody from the Trump family, extended family is going to be indicted, it would be the final act of Mueller's investigation because Bob Muller and his team knows if he were to do something, indicting a Trump family member or if he were to go forward with indictment on criminal conspiracy involving U.S. persons, that would be that would basically be the deathknell of the special counsel's office because I don't believe Donald Trump would allow Bob Mueller to continue in the aftermath of those types of actions," Brennan said on MSNBC's 'The Last Word.' LAWRENCE O'DONNELL, MSNBC HOST 'LAST WORD': Are you one who's willing to, at this stage of the game, venture a guess about where Robert Mueller is and isn't in this process and how close he is to filing a report? And beyond that, what would you would expect from such a report? JOHN BRENNAN, FMR. CIA DIRECTOR: I think Robert Mueller wants to be able to conclude his work and turn over the investigative threads to the Southern District of New York, the Eastern District of Virginia, and other jurisdictions as appropriate as we're coming up to two years. So I think he does want to conclude that. I wouldn't be surprised if for example this week on Friday, not knowing anything about it, but Friday is the day the grand jury indictments come down and also this Friday is better than next Friday because next Friday is the 15th of March, which is the Ides of March. And I don't think Robert Mueller will want to have that dramatic flair of the Ides of March when he is going to be delivering what I think are going to be are his indictments, the final indictments as well the report he gives to the Attorney General. O'DONNELL: What makes you believe that he has more indictments?  BRENNAN: Because he hasn't addressed the issues related to criminal conspiracy as well as individuals -- O'DONNELL: A criminal conspiracy involving the Russians?  BRENNAN: Yes. I think it was very -- O'DONNELL: That's an area you know something about. That was developing while you were still on the job.  BRENNAN: Well, it was in terms of looking at what was going on with the Russians and whether or not U.S. persons were actively collaborating, colluding, cooperating and involved in a conspiracy with them or not but also if there is going to be any member of the Trump family -- O'DONNELL: Did you see enough at that stage to believe that there would now, that that would result in indictments once investigated? BRENNAN: I thought at the time there was going to be individuals who were going to have issues with the Department of Justice. Yes. And I think we've already seen a number of individuals who have been indicted, either have plead guilty or have been convicted now.  So again, I don't have any inside knowledge. I'm not talking with anybody in the special counsel's office. O'DONNELL: Yes, you do. You have the inside knowledge of what began it all. BRENNAN: Not about the status of the investigation now but I do think also if anybody from the Trump family, extended family is going to be indicted, it would be the final act of Mueller's investigation because Bob Muller and his team knows if he were to do something, indicting a Trump family member or if he were to go forward with indictment on criminal conspiracy involving U.S. persons, that would be that would basically be the deathknell of the special counsel's office because I don't believe Donald Trump would allow Bob Mueller to continue in the aftermath of those types of actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Trump works to maintain illusions of progress, as his main promises go unfulfilled...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-trump-claims-progress-for-promises-unfulfilled-20190305-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump insists he's made progress on his stalled or stymied promises, including a border wall, trade deals and North Korea's denuclearization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese, Tarantino Movies Going to Cannes Festival?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cannes-film-festival-2019-lineup-50-titles-could-make-cut-1191927</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the 72nd Cannes International Film Festival just two months away, The Hollywood Reporter takes an exhaustive look at the titles that could bow on the Croisette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family devastated after losing 10 relatives in tornado...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/914d4c99851f41308ed7e2bd07ba8694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEAUREGARD, Ala. (AP) — Cousins Cordarrly Jones and Demetria Jones have a hard time counting all the relatives they lost to a monster tornado that wiped out a rural community in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cord-Cutting Accelerates; Doubles Last Year...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/nearly-3m-pay-tv-subscribers-cut-service-in-2018-double-2017-rate-study-1202570400/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pace of cord-cutting accelerated in 2018, with the largest pay-TV providers shedding about 2.9 million video subscribers, nearly double the 1.5 million subscriber losses in 2017, according to t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Einstein 'puzzle' solved as missing page emerges...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/einstein-puzzle-solved-missing-page-emerges-trove-145841171.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Albert Einstein "puzzle" has been solved thanks to a missing manuscript page emerging in a trove of his writings newly acquired by Jerusalem's Hebrew University, officials announced Wednesday. The handwritten page, part of an appendix to a 1930 paper on the Nobel winner's efforts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka Calls on Businesses to Reshape Training Efforts...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ivanka-trump-calls-on-businesses-to-reshape-training-efforts-11551881026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employers must enhance the skills of workers for the economy to continue its robust growth, said Ivanka Trump, ahead of a meeting Wednesday with executives, educators and governors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privilege lecture tells students white people 'dangerous' if don't see race...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/white-privilege-lecture-tells-students-white-people-dangerous-if-they-dont-see-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This person doesn’t understand culture. This person is not self-aware.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cries, screams...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6777629/R-Kellys-claims-brainwashed-girlfriends-PARENTS-handed-unhinged-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kelly, whose real name is Robert, shouted, screamed and at times spoke directly to the camera while being interviewed by Gayle King for CBS News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris to Tokyo: Where Super Rich Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/lifestyle/from-paris-london-to-tokyo-this-is-where-the-world-s-super-rich-live-119030600140_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.business-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business opportunities, lifestyle desires, hospitals and transportation infrastructure are all factors that draw the super-rich to splash out on homes in large cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stray mongrel beats pedigrees to become elite sniffer dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/06/stray-mongrel-beats-pedigrees-become-elite-indian-sniffer-dog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 18 months after being rescued from stone-throwing children, a street-dwelling mongrel has emerged as India's top dog in the country's elite bomb- and drug-sniffing squad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson songs banned from radio stations around the world...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/music/michael-jackson-songs-banned-from-radio-stations-around-the-world-2457781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio stations across the world have dropped Michael Jackson songs from their playlists in wake of 'Leaving Neverland' documentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil President Posts Sexually Explicit Video to Denounce Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/brazils-president-jair-bolsonaro-posts-sexually-explicit-golden-showers-video-on-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protein shake before bed for BIGGER muscles?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6774069/Want-bigger-muscles-Drink-protein-shake-bed-Late-night-intake-increases-gains.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Maastricht University in the Netherlands found the extra consumption of calories won't make you fat - even though it's followed by hours of inactivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames parents for 'selling' daughters to him...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/03/06/r-kelly-claims-parents-sold-daughters-to-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “I Believe I Can Fly” singer flew off the handle in his 80-minute sit-down with “CBS This Morning” co-host Gayle King.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHOLE FOODS cuts worker hours after AMAZON introduces minimum wage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/mar/06/whole-foods-amazon-cuts-minimum-wage-workers-hours-changes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An email shared with the Guardian by a Whole Foods employee cites the shift cuts as a ‘direct result of guidance from our regional team’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleanse spirit, meditate, stargaze...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/bali/articles/nyepi-why-bali-is-going-silent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No flights or internet during Bali's sacred Day of Silence...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/bendbulletin/article/f5309ba059b04b35b628bd2acf2c0755/no-flights-or-internet-during-balis-sacred-day-silence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENPASAR, Indonesia (AP) — Bali's airport will close for 24 hours, the internet will be turned off and streets emptied as the predominantly Hindu island in Indonesia observes its New Year with an annual day of silence."Nyepi" begins at 6 a.m. Thursday, clearing beaches and all public spaces of people except for special patrols to ensure silence is observed. For the second year, phone companies will turn off the mobile internet on the island, home to more than 4 million people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen 4th day of testimony could touch on Russia, finances...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/991f1295ab4d436f99e11b20fd1c433f/cohen-returns-capitol-hill-4th-day-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's former lawyer is returning to Capitol Hill for a fourth day of testimony as Democrats pursue a flurry of investigations into Trump's White House, businesses and presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgian mayor defends float featuring Jews with money and rat...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/belgian-mayor-defends-carnival-float-featuring-jews-with-money-and-a-rat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite widespread condemnation, Aalst Mayor Christoph D’Haese argues display 'should be allowed' and that 'carnival participants had no sinister intentions'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Time for Chinese miracle': Beijing's new English language propaganda push...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/06/time-for-the-chinese-miracle-beijings-new-english-language-propaganda-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaign including confusing rap song and stilted video explainer coincides with the annual Two Sessions political conference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 pulses of lightning off SoCal coast in 5 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-socal-lightning-20190305-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A band of thunderstorms that stretch from southern Kern County past the Channel Islands was producing a dramatic lightning show Tuesday night in the Southern California sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitism Rebuke Threatens Rift Among Dems...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anti-semitism-rebuke-threatens-rift-090000290.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota freshman’s name doesn’t appear in the resolution, which could go to the House floor as soon as Thursday, but it denounces anti-Semitism by describing tropes similar to some of those she has invoked. Omar has apologized for some of her controversial remarks and defended others. The fact</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
