<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>1 million cases in CA -- in 1 week...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/california-surpasses-7-million-covid-cases-with-1-million-recorded-in-1-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has recorded more than 7 million coronavirus cases, after its fastest accumulation of reported infections in the history of the pandemic. The unprecedented count, recorded in Califo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens to drive big rigs to ease supply chain shortage...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/teens-drive-big-rigs-semi-trucks/11483898/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Currently, truckers who cross state lines must be at least 21 years old, but an apprenticeship program to ease supply chain backlogs would drop that age to 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts raise fresh fears over 'stalking' APPLE AirTags...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4484085/warning-iphone-airtag-stalker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPERTS warn that Apple AirTags are being used as a stalking tool after one victim was ‘trailed home’ by one. A police report emerged in Providence late last week detailing a victim who…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO chief says pandemic 'nowhere near over'...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/covid-19-across-world/covid-pandemic-nowhere-near-over-new-variants-likely-to-emerge-who-chief/articleshow/88980527.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India News: NEW DELHI: The Covid-19 pandemic is far from over, the World Health Organization chief said on Tuesday while cautioning against the narrative that the.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W. BUSH PREDICTED IT ALL?</title>
      <link>https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1283304/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen A. Smith Opens Up on Scary Battle With Covid: 'Didn't Know if I Was Gonna Make it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/stephen-a-smith-details-frightening-battle-with-covid-didnt-know-if-i-was-gonna-make-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one month after testing positive for Covid, Stephen A. Smith returned to First Take and revealed the frightening details of his battle with the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris looks to recapture lost beauty after criticism...</title>
      <link>https://news.in-24.com/news/497598.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.in-24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Editor Sues NY POST for 'Years of Sex-Based Harassment and Abuse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ex-editor-michelle-gotthelf-sues-new-york-post-for-years-of-sex-based-harassment-and-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ousted digital editor claims the Post’s former longtime boss sexually propositioned her and later ordered her to scrub a story accusing Donald Trump of rape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual Omicron warning sign in eyes...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/unusual-omicron-warning-sign-eyes-25975762 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Omicron continues to be the dominant coronavirus variant, various unusual symptoms of the virus are being reported around the world. Here’s one Omicron symptom affecting the eyes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli vaccine chief: Vax passports 'no longer relevant'...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/israeli-vaccine-chief-we-have-made-mistakes/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Cyrille Cohen is head of Immunology at Bar Ilan University and a member of the advisory committee for vaccines for the Israeli Government. In a wide-ranging and forthright interview, the Professor tells Freddie Sayers: The Green Pass / vaccine passport concept is no longer relevant in the Omicron era and should be phased out [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETBLUE pilot stunned as 'shape-shifting UFO' appears beside plane over TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/jetblue-pilot-stunned-shape-shifting-25977561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The JetBlue pilot said the mysterious white object stayed for five minutes and disappeared but when it re-appeared, it merged with another UFO in front of them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks fall sharply as rates rise... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/17/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The major averages fell sharply Tuesday after Goldman Sachs reported disappointing earnings and as government bond yields hit Covid-era highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Cost of Pork Rises, People Turning to Crocodile Meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkp338/crocodile-meat-thailand</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s high in protein, low in fat, and traders say it tastes just like chicken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of AI Fighter Pilots...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2022/01/24/the-rise-of-ai-fighter-pilots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence is being taught to fly warplanes. Can the technology be trusted?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fissures at Supreme Court suggest justices dysfunctional family...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/18/1073428376/supreme-court-justices-arent-scorpions-but-not-happy-campers-either</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anybody who regularly watches Supreme Court arguments is used to seeing testy moments. But you don't have to be a keen observer these days to see that something out of the ordinary is happening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge turns staff scheduling at CA hospital into frustrating numbers game...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/like-tetris-covid-surge-turns-staff-scheduling-at-california-hospital-into-a-frustrating-numbers-game/ar-AASTMiz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto raises $7M in first weeks of bid for TX gov...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/congress-beto-orourke-texas-campaign-finance-campaigns-d1c2e31cda877f2307721c6e93c096fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Democrat Beto O'Rourke said Tuesday that his campaign for Texas governor raised $7.2 million in the first six weeks of a race that could wind up as one of the nation's most expensive in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT buying ACTIVISION 'to enter metaverse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4487336/microsoft-buying-activision-billions-deal-call-of-duty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MICROSOFT is buying video game publisher Activision for a staggering $68.7billion. Activision is famous for publishing the Call of Duty franchise. It’s also behind World of War Craft and Diab…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police accused of using spyware on domestic opponents of Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israeli-police-accused-of-using-pegasus-spyware-on-domestic-opponents-of-netanyahu/ar-AASTpb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate candidate from Louisiana smokes pot in campaign ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/us-senate-candidate-from-louisiana-smokes-marijuana-in-campaign-ad/ar-AASTQWo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGAVILLE: Trump Plans to Build 2,300 Luxury Homes at His Miami Resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/donald-trump-is-planning-to-build-luxury-homes-at-miami-resort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump Is Planning to Build Luxury Homes at Miami Resort</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Thins Out Embassy in Ukraine, Possible Clue to Putin's Next Move...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/17/russia-thins-out-its-embassy-in-ukraine-a-possible-clue-to-putins-next-move/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine — The week before intensive diplomatic meetings began over the buildup of Russian troops on the Ukrainian border,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under-fire Boris Johnson denies lying over lockdown parties...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-boris-johnson-europe-london-7c26aef9171abe54f31cadbb40150e7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson on Tuesday denied misleading Parliament about lockdown-breaching parties, as senior government ministers said he would have to resign if he was proven to have lied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope's right-hand man positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.arabnews.com/node/2006896/world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arabnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY: The Vatican’s top diplomat and adviser to Pope Francis, Cardinal Pietro Parolin, has tested positive for Covid, a spokesman for the Holy See said Tuesday. The 67-year-old cardinal, who as secretary of state is the Vatican’s number two after the pope, was currently in isolation, exhibiting only “mild symptoms,” said Vatican spokesman Matteo Bruni. Venezuelan archbishop, Edgar Pena Parra, the Vatican’s deputy secretary of state, also tested positive, but he was asymptomatic, Bruni said. Both men had been vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris says 'nobody told me' lockdown party was against rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/boris-johnson-says-nobody-told-me-no-10-lockdown-garden-party-was-against-the-rules-12519115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson has said "nobody told me" the Number 10 garden party during lockdown was "against the rules".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gluten NOT To Blame For IBS? Lesser-Known Dietary Element Eyed As Culprit...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/gluten-not-behind-ibs-fodmaps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Swedish study finds that excluding gluten from the diets of individuals suffering from Irritable Bowel Syndrome (IBS) may not be as important as previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Psychedelic Trips Helping People Heal From Trauma...</title>
      <link>https://www.brainhackernews.com/how-psychedelic-trips-are-helping-people-heal-from-trauma/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.brainhackernews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As psychedelic use for therapeutic treatment increases in popularity, individuals are finding themselves turning to psychedelics when all other options have been exhausted. Particularly with conditions such as Post Traumatic Stress Disorder, the painful flashbacks and images can be resistant to some of the most common treatments. The powerful practice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Hits Vatican...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-pope-francis-health-vatican-city-europe-74c130deb6f13824fbbc2a0a693a1fd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The Vatican secretary of state and his deputy have both tested positive for the coronavirus , Vatican officials said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis proposes special police agency to monitor elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-governor-proposes-special-police-agency-to-monitor-elections/ar-AASTzbS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's youth turn left...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/youth-politics-polling-democrats-d8e7b368-15ca-48c7-8c27-29021b09670d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Generational replacement will not be kind to Trump’s Republican Party."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Faces Twin Mutation Threat as Cases Rise Before Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/beijing-faces-twin-variant-threat-as-cases-rise-before-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing Faces Twin Variant Threat as Cases Rise Before Olympics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Not 'Woke' for Businesses to Think Beyond Profit, BLACKROCK Chief Says...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/18/its-not-woke-for-businesses-to-think-beyond-profit-blackrock-chief-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurence D. Fink, the founder and chief executive of the investment giant BlackRock, has become one of the most influential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong to kill 2,000 hamsters over animal-to-human transmission...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/top-stories/hong-kong-to-kill-2-000-hamsters-because-of-suspected-animal-to-human-covid-transmission/ar-AASTjVY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected Lions Prompt Variant Warning in S Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/news/world/covid19-infected-lions-prompt-variant-warning-in-south-africa-11642500634310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lions and pumas at a zoo in Pretoria got severe Covid-19 from asymptomatic zoo handlers, raising concerns that new variants could emerge from animal reservoirs of the disease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: 10 housing market records broken in '21...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/10-housing-market-records-broken-in-2021-16784047.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The word "unprecedented" may have been a bit overused during the months since the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China orders overseas mail disinfection...</title>
      <link>https://www.bangkokpost.com/world/2249431/china-orders-overseas-mail-disinfection-over-omicron-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bangkokpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING: China's postal service has ordered workers to disinfect international deliveries and urged the public to reduce orders from overseas after authorities claimed mail could be the source of recent coronavirus outbreaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distrust in political, media, business leaders sweeps globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/distrust-in-political-media-and-business-leaders-sweeps-the-globe-f02f7cf0-9385-4067-abff-92c6b6392d02.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government leaders and journalists are considered the least trustworthy societal leaders, per a new survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major sponsor fires warning shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10411681/Djokovic-sponsor-Lacoste-contact-tennis-star-review-events-Australia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Novak Djokovic's major apparel sponsor has sent the tennis champion a foreboding message saying they wish to speak with him following his deportation from Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia suffers its worst day of deaths since pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australia-suffers-deadliest-day-pandemic-011555138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia on Tuesday suffered its deadliest day of the pandemic as a fast-moving Omicron outbreak continued to push up hospitalisation rates to record levels, even as daily infections eased slightly. Australia is dealing with its worst COVID-19 outbreak, fuelled by the Omicron variant of the coronavirus that has put more people in hospitals and intensive care than at any time during the pandemic. A total of 74 deaths were registered by late morning between New South Wales, Victoria and Queensland, Australia's three most populous states, exceeding the previous national high of 57 last Thursday, official data showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Crypto.com Suspends Withdrawals After 'Unauthorized Activity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2022-01-17/crypto-com-suspends-withdrawals-unauthorized-activity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto.com said it stopped all deposits and withdrawals while it investigates 'unauthorized activity' on some accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia suffers its worst day of deaths since pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10412587/Australia-suffers-worst-day-deaths-Covid-74-lives-lost.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia has suffered its worst day for Covid deaths since the start of pandemic with 74 people losing their lives so far, smashing the September 2020 record of 58 during Victoria's deadly second wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London plans 'pay per mile' charges to force drivers onto public transport...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10412367/Sadiq-Khan-plots-hit-motorists-London-pay-mile-charges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The capital's Labour mayor (pictured) wants road pricing to force those who drive petrol or diesel cars to switch to public transport, walking, cycling or electric vehicles 'where necessary'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Airlines warn of 'calamity' if 5G deployed near airports...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-airlines-warn-calamity-5g-233418874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief executives of America's largest airlines warned of a "catastrophic disruption" to travel and shipping operations if telecommunication firms roll out their 5G technology as planned Wednesday without limiting the technology near US airports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland has entered a fifth wave of COVID...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220117172909-0pa0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/POLAND (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Poland has entered a fifth wave of COVID, says minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronauts blood destroyed in space; Cells damaged...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4482978/astronauts-space-anemia-mystery-red-blood-cell-destruction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE causes the human body to destroy its own red blood cells and scientists don’t know why. The strange phenomenon is called space anemia and new research suggests it plagues astronauts eve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING IN THE CASH: Adele to earn $700,000 A NIGHT from Vegas residency...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4483471/adele-500k-las-vegas-residency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADELE will earn £500,000 a show from Friday — making her one of the highest-paid female stars in the history of Las Vegas residencies. Tickets for Weekends With Adele at Caesars Palace’s Colosseum …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCLA researchers cure HIV in 40% of mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-692579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic Athletes Told to Leave Phones at Home to Dodge Spying...</title>
      <link>https://au.finance.yahoo.com/news/olympic-athletes-advised-leave-phones-220000587.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Beyond Omicron and gold medal tallies, athletes arriving in China’s capital for the Winter Games next month may have one more thing to worry about: is it safe to access the internet?Most Read from BloombergDeadly Strikes on UAE Upset Efforts to Ease Gulf FrictionsOne of the World’s Wealthiest Oil Exporters Is Becoming UnlivableFourth Pfizer Dose Is Insufficient to Ward Off Omicron, Israeli Trial SuggestsDjokovic Loses Shot at Tennis History as Australia Deports StarChina Cuts Inte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci warns 'end' not near: 'High probability' of another variant...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10411817/Fauci-warns-Omicron-not-end-Covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Anthony Fauci, the U.S.'s top infectious disease expert, warns that the Omicron variant may not be the last of the Covid pandemic and that a new strain could eventually emerge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK sending weapons to defend Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-60033012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defence secretary says he is sending short-range anti-tank missiles amid Russian invasion fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Dying Japanese Town Obsessed With Aliens...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxdxx5/japan-aliens-iino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The town is home to a striking mountain that residents believe attracts flying saucers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New VR gaming vest 'could be used for SEX'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4480045/hi-tech-sex-vest-vr-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW virtual reality vest that lets you feel multiple sensations could be used by long-distance lovers. That’s according to sex tech experts who think the OWO Game vest could be used for mor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Italian musicians, unvaccinated means locked out of public life...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/For-two-Italian-musicians-being-unvaccinated-16782841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OSIGO, Italy - After many rounds of rules targeting the unvaccinated, the chamber...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beat it: Michael Jackson Impersonator Wins Thriller Vegas Street Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/weird/beat-it-michael-jackson-impersonator-wins-thriller-of-a-street-fight-in-vegas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michael Jackson impersonator got the better of a man in Las Vegas during a fight that was as absurd as the puns which are being written about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police charge flight attendants at center of Hong Kong outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220117-police-charge-cathay-flight-attendants-at-centre-of-hong-kong-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong police arrested and charged Monday two Cathay Pacific flight attendants for allegedly contravening Covid regulations, after the emergence of the Omicron variant in the territory was traced…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA weighs DOUBLING taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/california-proposal-double-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California lawmakers unveiled a new bill at the beginning of the year that would establish a single-payer health care system – an ambitious plan that would be funded by nearly doubling the state's already-high taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK freezes BBC funding for two years...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-freezes-bbc-funding-two-193851424.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK government came under fire on Monday for freezing the BBC licence fee, with critics accusing it of a politically motivated attack to save the prime minister's job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA sees highest death rate in 10 months...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/l-a-county-sees-highest-covid-death-rate-in-10-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County saw an average of 40 coronavirus deaths a day over the past week, the highest such rate in nearly 10 months, a sign that the prolific Omicron variant may be deadlier than many in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi threw chair at suspect to end 10-hour hostage ordeal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/17/texas-rabbi-credits-security-training-for-hostage-survival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rabbi Charlie Cytron-Walker said his Congregation Beth Israel has “participated in multiple security courses,” including with local police and the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish leaders call FBI comments on Texas hostages 'insulting'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/17/jewish-leaders-call-fbi-comments-on-texas-hostages-insulting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jewish leaders ripped the FBI for saying the terrorist who took hostages at a Texas synagogue didn’t make demands that were “specifically related to the Jewish community,” reports said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thefts from trains spike in LA: 'Spiraling crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/spiraling-crisis-thefts-from-cargo-trains-have-spiked-in-l-a-county-company-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rail thefts have spiked in Los Angeles County, with thieves climbing aboard cargo trains, breaking into containers and stealing packages, railroad company Union Pacific warned Sunday. Union Pacific…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii to require travelers have boosters...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/hawaii-require-travelers-covid-booster-shot-fully-vaccinated/story?id=82307999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii to require visitors to the state receive a COVID-19 vaccine booster if they want to skip quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic risk factor found for smell, taste loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/genetic-risk-factor-found-covid-19-smell-taste-loss-researchers-say-rcna11996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are piecing together why some people lose their sense of smell after contracting Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Miami Beach Hotel, and Its History, Might Be Torn Down...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/17/a-grand-miami-beach-hotel-and-its-history-might-be-torn-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH — The baby-faced Beatles spent nine sun-kissed days in Miami Beach in 1964, basking in the warm winter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Netanyahu agrees to 'moral turpitude' in potential plea deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/reports-netanyahu-agrees-to-moral-turpitude-in-potential-plea-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA WARRIORS Owner: Nobody Cares About Uyghurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2022/01/17/owner_of_the_golden_state_warriors_chamath_palihapitiya_nobody_cares_about_whats_happening_to_the_uyghurs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chamath Palihapitiya, the CEO of "Social Capital" and owner of the Golden State Warriors basketball team, told the "All-In" podcast that "nobody cares" about the ethnic cleansing of Uyghur Muslims in East Turkestan by the Chinese Communist Party.  "If you're asking me if I care about a segment of a class of people in another country, not until we can take care of ourselves will I prioritize them over us," he said.  Social Capital's website states: "Our mission is to advance humanity by solving the world's hardest problems. We partner with companies at every stage of their business, for as long as it takes." "It's a nice thing that you care, but nobody else cares." "I'm telling you a hard, ugly truth. Of all the things I care about, it is below my line," Palihapitiya said. "I care about the fact that our economy could turn on a line if China invades Taiwan. I care about that. I care about climate change. I care about America's crippling and decrepit healthcare infrastructure. But if you're asking me if I care about a segment of a class of people in another country, not until we can take care of ourselves will I prioritize them over us." "I'm sorry if that's a hard truth to hear, but every time I say I care about the Uyghurs, I m really just lying." Hat tip:  Billionaire @chamath "nobody cares about what's happening to the Uyghurs" Palihapitiya https://t.co/S3hZ584UoO pic.twitter.com/mlh2sBhGd9-- Timothy Pereira (@TimoPG) January 15, 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Were Authorities So Evasive About Gunman's Motive?</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/why-were-authorities-so-evasive-about-the-synagogue-gunmans-motive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why were President Biden and the FBI so reluctant to say that the synagogue gunman was motivated by antisemitism and jihadism?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joss Whedon Denies Misconduct Claims, Says Gal Gadot Misunderstood...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/joss-whedon-denies-misconduct-claims-says-gal-gadot-misunderstood-him-english-is-not-her-first-language/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Joss Whedon has broken his silence on the allegations of misconduct launched against him last year, directly responding to Justice League's Gal Gadot and Ray Fisher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico president says he's beaten Covid for 2nd time...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220117-mexico-president-says-he-s-beaten-covid-for-second-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said Monday that he had recovered from a second bout of Covid-19, as he resumed his public activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic now banned from French Open?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/sportsnews/article-10410441/Novak-Djokovic-faces-banned-French-Open-May.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French Open is the next Slam in the tennis calendar taking place in May and Djokovic was expected to participate without complication - but the new Covid Pass has changed that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic depletes collection plates at churches nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-churches-financial-difficulty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're surviving. … But we have felt the hurt," said one pastor in Nashville, Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel trial, world's first, finds 4th dose 'not good enough'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-trial-worlds-first-finds-4th-dose-not-good-enough-against-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expert at Sheba Medical Center says jab raises COVID antibody levels, but there are ‘still a lot of infections’ among those who received it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics tickets will not be sold to general public due to Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/17/sport/winter-olympics-china-tickets-covid-19-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tickets for the upcoming Winter Olympic and Paralympic Games in Beijing will not be sold to the general public in response to Covid-19 but will instead be distributed by authorities, the Beijing Winter Olympics Organizing Committee announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop grabs female officer by throat after she pulls him off suspect...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/17/florida-cop-grabs-female-officer-by-the-throat-after-she-pulled-him-off-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to footage, Christopher Pullease whipped around, grabbed hold of the officer’s neck and shoved her against another patrol car after trying to pepper spray a suspect.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
