<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fixates on vaccine -- real or not -- as key to reelection...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-fixates-on-the-promise-of-a-vaccine-real-15545751.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump is so fixated on finding a vaccine for the novel coronavirus that in meetings about the U.S. pandemic response, little else captures his attention, according to administration officials.  Trump has pressed health officials to speed up the vaccine timeline and urged them to deliver one by the end of the year. He has peppered them with questions about the development status and mass-distribution plans. And, in recent days, he has told some advisers and aides that a vaccine may arrive by Nov. 1, which just happens to be two days before the presidential election.  Trump's desire to deliver a vaccine - or at least convince the public that one is very near - by the time voters decide whether to elect him to a second term is in part a campaign gambit to improve his standing with an electorate that overwhelmingly disapproves of his management of the pandemic.  "We remain on track to deliver a vaccine before the end of the year and maybe even before November 1," Trump told reporters at a Friday news conference. "We think we can probably have it some time during the month of October."  Trump has repeatedly offered similar promises, adding to the pressure scientists and officials at the Food and Drug Administration and the National Institutes of Health feel to develop, test and authorize a coronavirus vaccine on what some of the president's aides refer to as "Trump time."  Several Trump aides said one key to the president winning reelection is having a vaccine or demonstrating rapid progress toward one, as well as a robust economic turnaround, over the next two months.  Democratic strategists, too, said a vaccine announcement could play in Trump's favor, but they cautioned that it is unlikely to significantly change the contours of the race.  "If...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Osama bin Laden Sending Coded Messages in Porn?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/was-osama-bin-laden-sending-coded-messages-in-porn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new National Geographic special “Bin Laden’s Hard Drive” analyzes the porn collection found in the slain terrorist’s compound—and presents a curious theory about the XXX stash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Sierra fire traps people at popular reservoir...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Fast-moving-fire-in-California-s-Sierra-National-15545901.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brush fire in the Sierra National Forest exploded Saturday, consuming more than 36,000 acres, threatening local communities and trapping 150 near a popular reservoir. The fast-moving Creek fire cut off evacuation routes to Mammoth Pool Reservoir, according the Madera County sheriff's office. All of the people were reported safe but 10 of them suffered some type of injury, the sheriff's ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the workplace 'spiritual consultants'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thought-capitalism-couldnt-worse-meet-102321604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employers have figured out how to exploit society’s crisis of meaning – by turning workplaces into sites of cult-like religious devotion Do you feel lost? Like your life has been drained of meaning or purpose? During your work day, do you wander from task to task in a daze, just waiting to be released</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cacophony of chaos'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cacophony-chaos-why-us-election-060016736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent polls gave conflicting signals in race complicated by crises of public health, economic recession and racial injusticeIt was just like old times. Donald Trump stood at a presidential lectern, encouraging a rambunctious crowd of supporters – few of whom wore face masks or physically distanced –</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Police Make Sweeping Arrests as Protests Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/hong-kong-police-make-sweeping-arrests-as-protests-return/ar-BB18KGm2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Trip Ended With Art Loaded on Air Force One...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-ended-2018-france-trip-having-art-loaded-on-air-force-one/ar-BB18L58T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists can't explain lack of coronavirus outbreaks in Africa...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/04/scientists-cant-explain-puzzling-lack-of-coronavirus-outbreaks-in-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The novel coronavirus has infected more than 26.35 million people, with just four countries accounting for over 15 million cases. They are America, Brazil, India, and Russia — the same four that ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax Race Pits Spy vs. Spy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/05/race-for-coronavirus-vaccine-pits-spy-against-spy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Chinese intelligence hackers were intent on stealing coronavirus vaccine data, so they looked for what they believed would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea may be prepping submarine-launched ballistic missile test...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/north-korea-may-be-prepping-submarine-launched-ballistic-missile-test-n1239420</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A sea-launched missile test would definitely cross all of President Trump’s red lines because it would involve a major ballistic missile," Dr. Victor Cha said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DERBY DAY: Armed militia, Black Lives Matter protesters collide in Louisville...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/state/kentucky/article245518430.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed guards provided for threatened lesbian couple...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-54009586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their love story made headlines as they fought to get protection from their own families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange to fight US extradition bid in UK court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c246fe423998bf9d1bbf4797f6db4837</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange is set to fight for his freedom in a British court after a decade of legal drama, as he challenges American authorities’ attempt to extradite him on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dodge fire bombs as Portland protesters mark 100 straight days...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/6/portland-protests-mark-100-straight-days-police-do/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people gathered for rallies and marches against police violence and racial injustice Saturday night in Portland, Oregon, as often violent nightly demonstrations that have happened for 100 days since George Floyd was killed showed no signs of ceasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several knifed in Birmingham, UK; Cops declare major incident...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12595407/birmingham-stabbing-major-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE man was killed and seven people hurt with the killer on the run after a string of stabbings unfolded in Birmingham city centre overnight. Cops are today hunting for the person – believed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For first time since Great Depression, majority of adults under 30 living with parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2020/09/04/a-majority-of-young-adults-in-the-u-s-live-with-their-parents-for-the-first-time-since-the-great-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The share of 18- to 29-year-olds living with their parents has become a majority since U.S. coronavirus cases began spreading early this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two strangers and a terrifying story about ketamine in policing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/31/us/ketamine-use-in-police-stops/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men in Colorado were cuffed on the ground. Both were injected with tranquilizers against their will in police stops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy NYC woman busted in BLM rampage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/05/wealthy-nyc-woman-busted-in-blm-rampage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20-year-old Upper East Sider is the daughter of an architect and child psychiatrist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-India standoff risks unintentional war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d27ec36d89d5b8011ebaaeef2983809f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SRINAGAR, India (AP) — As a monthslong military standoff between India and China along their disputed mountain border protracts, experts warn that the nuclear-armed countries — which already have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass evacuation as Japan braces for typhoon...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-54046150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200,000 people are ordered to shelter from the second storm to hit the region in a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISHES DIRT ON DONALD... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8702221/Trump-said-Obama-got-Harvard-Law-f-ing-affirmative-action-Cohen-says-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen's memoir, Disloyal, hits bookshelves Tuesday - despite his still serving out a federal prison sentence for tax evasion, lying to Congress and campaign finance violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considered suicide as way to 'escape the unrelenting insanity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/05/politics/michael-cohen-book-trump-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Donald Trump ever sought the Oval Office, he was preoccupied by its occupant President Barack Obama, publicly questioning his birthplace and privately describing him as "a Manchurian candidate" who obtained his Ivy League degrees only by way of affirmative action, according to a new book by Trump's former attorney, Michael Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California grid operator warns of rotating power outages in record heat wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200906022155-95z56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WEATHER/POWER:California grid operator warns of rotating power outages in record heat wave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France now Europe's hotspot with highest ever daily cases figure...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1426073/france-europe-covid-hotspot-icu-two-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE has become Europe’s new coronavirus hotspot as it recorded its highest ever number of daily cases The country’s count hit a new high with nearly 9,000 yesterday – almost do…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS MAGA:  Multiple boats sink during Trump Boat Parade on Lake Travis...</title>
      <link>https://cbsaustin.com/news/local/multiple-boats-in-distress-sinking-at-trump-boat-parade-on-lake-travis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbsaustin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parade for President Donald Trump gets dicey when multiple boats sink on Lake Travis. According to first responders, nobody was injured. At around 2:50 p. m. the TCSO confirmed via tweet that they had responded to multiple calls made about boats being in distress at the parade. They also confirmed that several of those boats sank on the lake. As of Saturday night, the Travis County Sheriff&amp;lsquo;s office said they were still sorting out just how many boats went under.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spends hours in box filled with ice cubes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6839bc681e86b773f26ba1c17fb43d58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELK, Austria (AP) — An Austrian man beat his own record for the longest full body contact with ice cubes on Saturday. Josef Koeberl managed to stay 2 hours, 30 minutes and 57 seconds inside...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan raises rhetoric in Greece standoff in Mediterranean...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/61226ebfea4cb7ddcf9c23b5fbd94b84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Saturday warned Greece to enter talks over disputed eastern Mediterranean territorial claims or face the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen memoir casts him as star witness against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2b171cabf1801526a76d4534e808a99d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Michael Cohen's tell-all memoir makes the case that President Donald Trump is “guilty of the same crimes” that landed his former fixer in federal prison, offering a blow-by-blow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK blocks end-of-life broadcasts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/16880246e8bbdc5ceb98ed57b87a88ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LE PECQ, France (AP) — Facebook on Saturday blocked live broadcasts from a chronically ill bed-ridden man who appealed to French President Emmanuel Macron for a medically-assisted death and who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran blasts 'heartless and evil' US for killing thousands with coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/iran-brands-heartless-evil-thousands-22634200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani has hit out at the USA over sanctions that have been in place since 2018. The political leader has argument the global health crisis should have seen sanctions reduced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for placing 1171 calls to 911...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/egg-roll-call-915027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 4--A Tennessee man called 911 more than 1100 times over the past six weeks, a prolific misuse of the emergency dispatch system that included the suspect asking a police operator “if they wa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple boats in distress, sinking at Trump Boat Parade on Lake Travis... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://cbsaustin.com/news/local/multiple-boats-in-distress-sinking-at-trump-boat-parade-on-lake-travis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbsaustin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple 911 calls have been made regarding boats being in distress, some sinking at the &amp;lsquo;Trump Boat Parade&amp;rsquo; scheduled for Saturday afternoon on Lake Travis, according to the Travis County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office. TCSO confirmed with CBS Austin that multiple boats have been sinking and are in distress. The sheriff's office says calls have been made about boats along the entire route of the parade, some of the locations include: Paradise Cove, Emerald Point and West Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Reporters Defend Colleague After Trump Calls for Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2020/09/05/fox-news-journalists-defend-colleague-targeted-by-president-trump/#263dcfdf2a84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My sources are not anonymous to me and I doubt they are anonymous to the president.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNAL CONFUSION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/05/media/the-atlantic-trump-military-fox-news/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Fox News has worked to undermine and discredit the work of other news organizations that have reported damning details about President Trump and his administration. But on Friday, something unusual happened: The network turned a skeptical eye toward reporting from its own correspondent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirby, LaBeouf Grieve Over Loss of Newborn in 'PIECES OF A WOMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/pieces-of-a-woman-film-review-venice-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: He has yet to find magic potion to get ahead in race...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-has-yet-to-find-magic-potion-to-get-ahead-15545477.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential election is now eight weeks away, and the structure of the contest is little changed from where it has been for some time. President Donald Trump is struggling and at times floundering. The question is whether he has the skills to turn around his candidacy in hopes of replicating his 2016 surprise victory.  At the traditional Labor Day kickoff to the fall campaign, the race remains former vice president Joe Biden's to lose - which of course could still happen. Trump has tried many things over the past months in an effort to avoid becoming a one-term president. So far, nothing has proved to be the magic potion the president seems to believe is out there.  Trump has claimed Biden is mentally challenged. He has gone after Biden's son Hunter as corrupt. The president has accused Biden of being a radical leftist, a socialist. He says the former vice president is weak. He says his challenger is soft on China. He has said Biden supports violent protesters and doesn't support the police. Oh, he's also said Biden's 1994 crime bill was too tough on crime (and by implication, therefore, on the side of the police).  He is now preaching law and order, seizing on months of nightly protests in Portland, Ore., which often have turned violent, along with the protests and violence that followed the police shooting of Jacob Blake in Kenosha, Wis. He claims the nation's cities are ablaze and that a Biden presidency would destroy the suburbs. The rhetoric aimed at suburban voters is grounded in racism.  It is premature to say the law and order message isn't working, though there's been minimal movement in the polls since the conventions ended. What is left in the Trump tool kit if this message fails to do what Trump hopes it will do?  Trump's mistakes, record and history plague his candidacy. He paints his record in glorious...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer culture skewered in film at Venice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d7ab5511afd1787133056db3ff6a36b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE (AP) — Coronavirus lockdowns have kept most U.S. filmmakers and actors away from the Venice Film Festival, but Gia Coppola and Maya Hawke have brought a bit of today’s America to the Lido...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unions threaten work stoppages amid calls for racial justice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/02da00cb921ec61a69d8a30c9ff56244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ahead of Labor Day, unions representing millions across several working-class sectors are threatening to authorize work stoppages in support of the Black Lives Matter movement amid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Reporters Defend Colleague After Trump Calls for Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/fox-news-reporters-leap-to-defend-jennifer-griffin-from-trumps-demand-she-be-fired-for-reporting-he-trashed-vets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News reporters leapt to the defense of their colleague Jennifer Griffin after President Donald Trump demanded her firing after she confirmed the key elements of a raft of stories in which Trump denigrated military veterans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DERBY DAY SHOWDOWN: Militia gather at Churchill Downs ahead of protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8701095/Armed-Trump-supporters-gather-near-Churchill-Downs-ahead-Kentucky-Derby-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavily armed pro-Trump activists and far-right militia members have gathered near Churchill Downs in Louisville vowing to protect the city ahead of a day of Black Lives Matter protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting in person Nov. 3? Expect drive-thrus, sports arenas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8f347fec097280234fdef8589def9a44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Voting will look a little different this November. States are turning to stadiums, drive-thrus and possibly even movie theaters as safe options for in-person polling places...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
