<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BIG LOSSES</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-taxes/trump-tax-returns-from-1985-to-1994-show-1-billion-in-losses-ny-times-idUSKCN1SD2R4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump's businesses lost a total of more than $1 billi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Catalan leader running for office via SKYPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Fugitive-Catalan-leader-wanted-for-rebellion-is-13825574.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS - Carles Puigdemont once tried to lead Catalonia to independence from Spain. Now his dominion is a house in the suburbs of Brussels.  He fled charges of rebellion after his fall 2017 attempt to split his prosperous province from the rest of the country. And he is adapting to an odd new life where he can travel just about anywhere he wants - except the rolling hills of his native land.  Puigdemont on Monday scored a rare victory against the Spanish state, winning the right to run for European Parliament on May 26 after an election board initially barred the way. The case rose all the way to Spain's Supreme Court.  As long as he seeks to avoid arrest by Spanish police, it will have to be a campaign by Skype and Facetime. He will dial in to rallies in Catalonia from the pink brick building in Waterloo that he and his supporters have dubbed "the House of the Republic."  Meanwhile, some of his rivals and former compatriots will be running from behind bars in Spain, where they are on trial for rebellion, disobedience and misuse of public funds.  Puigdemont defends his self-imposed exile as strategic.  "We decided to live here in order to continue fighting," Puigdemont said in an interview. "If all of us were in jail, the narrative, the version of the Catalan crisis could be very different."  He said it was just a coincidence that his new home and headquarters is located in Waterloo, the site of Napoleon's final defeat. (He cheerfully notes that Napoleon's defeat was the Duke of Wellington's triumph.)  The Waterloo house "is a part of Catalonia," Puigdemont said, looking more tired than he did when he stirred crowds in Barcelona and across his region during the ill-fated independence attempt.  The walls are covered with Catalan art. The shelves are filled with books in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Privilege?  White House instructs McGahn not to comply with congressional subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/white-house-instruct-counsel-comply-congressional-subpoena/story?id=62873987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Jerry Nadler sounding off after former White House counsel Donald McGahn was told not to comply with House Democrats' subpoena for Mueller probe documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT GETS TRUMP TAX DOCS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/5-takeaways-from-10-years-of-trump-tax-figures/ar-AAB2BDR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy Hospital Ship Deployed to Aid Refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/05/07/navy-hospital-ship-comfort-deploy-aid-venezuelan-refugees.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy hospital ship Comfort will deploy next month to the Caribbean and Central and South America to provide assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Burglar enters home, pets pup, washes dishes...</title>
      <link>https://klewtv.com/news/offbeat/deputies-say-ohio-burglary-suspect-pet-victims-dog-washed-dishes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;klewtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vinton County Sheriff's Office said a woman is facing a burglary charge after she entered a home, pet the victim's dog and washed the dishes. Cheyenne Ewing is charged with burglary, according to the sheriff's office. Deputies said they received a call about a burglary about 9 a. m. Monday in Hamden. The victim said the suspect entered the home and sat on the couch to pet the family dog. The victim said the suspect then washed the dishes and left the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Censors Musical Short -- About Chinese Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/culture-desk/cbs-censors-the-good-fight-for-a-musical-short-about-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The segment is clear about one of the motives for American self-censorship: China is too big of a market for media corporations to ignore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive backlash against Seattle woman raped by homeless man...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/seattle-elites-homeless-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle elites show little sympathy for a woman raped by a homeless man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools to serve cold food to students who owe lunch money...</title>
      <link>https://www.providencejournal.com/news/20190506/warwick-schools-to-serve-cold-sandwiches-to-students-whose-families-owe-lunch-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARWICK — City schools warned parents Monday that they will serve a simple sandwich to children whose lunch money is in arrears, until the balance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frenchman Arrives In Caribbean After Crossing Atlantic In Big Barrel...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/adventure/outdoors/a27396168/frenchman-crosses-atlantic-ocean-in-barrel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because sometimes adventure beckons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activist faces jail in Poland for posters of Virgin Mary, Jesus with rainbow halos...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/07/world/poland-lgbt-flag-rainbow-halo-black-madonna-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish police say Elżbieta Podlesna put up posters of the revered Black Madonna that showed the Virgin Mary and Jesus with rainbows from the LGBT flag as the halos. Now she could face two years in prison for offending religious feelings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fatigue? DISNEY Announces 3 New 'STAR WARS' Films...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/entertainment/2019/05/disney-announces-release-dates-for-new-star-wars-avatar-and-marvel-movies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next "Star Wars" movies after December's "The Rise of Skywalker" will arrive in theaters on 2022, 2024, 2026. Whatever they are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese-style surveillance being exported to West...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2019/may/07/chinese-style-surveillance-exported-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese model is now being exported – and the results could be terrifying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd roars as woman tells Joe 'hug, kiss me anytime!'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/woman-tells-biden-rally-you-can-hug-kiss-me-anytime-n1002986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former VP has been hit with stories from several women who have come forward recently to say he touched them in ways that made them uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,000 'gifts' to voters legal?</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2019/05/07/election-2020-andrew-yang-universal-basic-income-payments-freedom-dividend-iowa-caucuses-president/1120575001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential hopeful Andrew Yang's campaign admitted the error, after the Register began inquiring about it. His campaign plans to amend his financial reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift fails to dethrone Lil Nas X for No.1 spot...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/music/2019/05/lil-nas-x-holds-off-taylor-swift-no-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the arrival of a new single from pop superstar Taylor Swift, "Old Town Road" rapper Lil Nas X has managed to hold on to his No. 1 spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic' mushroom decriminalization vote in Mile High City...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8aaa48465b1d42f38014433f61a879df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Voters on Tuesday were deciding whether to make Denver the first U.S. city to decriminalize psilocybin — the psychoactive substance in "magic mushrooms" — and add a new chapter to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn deemed public health crisis by AZ politicians...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/porn-deemed-public-health-crisis-arizona-politicians/story?id=62874408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arizona State Senate voted Monday to declare pornography a public health crisis, but beyond stating such on their resolution, no further action will be taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers who backed uprising face jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190507-venezuela-prosecute-lawmakers-who-backed-failed-uprising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela to prosecute lawmakers who backed failed uprising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great-grandmother with CBD oil arrested at DISNEYWORLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/travel/grandmother-cbd-arrested-disney-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney World may be the most magical place on Earth, but it turned into a legal nightmare for a great-grandmother with arthritis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran moving ballistic missiles by boat, USA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/07/politics/us-iran-transporting-missiles/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intelligence showing that Iran is likely moving short-range ballistic missiles aboard boats in the Persian Gulf was one of the critical reasons the US decided to move an aircraft carrier strike group and B-52 bombers into the region, according to several US officials with direct knowledge of the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Send migrants to Gitmo...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/immigration/442459-trump-should-send-migrants-to-guantanamo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deterring these migrants from coming requires a different approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star seeks Ramadan fasting advice for playoffs...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/26693616/kanter-texts-olajuwon-ramadan-advice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trail Blazers big man Enes Kanter, with advice from Hall of Famer Hakeem Olajuwon, will fast during Ramadan, meaning no water, food or medication during the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Crashes Lawn Mower Into Cop Car: 'F*** It, I'm Drunk, Take Me To Jail'...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/drunk-florida-man-crashes-lawn-mower-police-car/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police officers have to worry about people driving under the influence or boating under the influence, but now, they'll have to look out for those lawn mowing under the influence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: 'Electability' Argument How Dems Lose Elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/05/joe-biden-electability-argument-is-how-democrats-lose-elections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Democrats play it safe and “fall in line,” the results are devastating—as Dukakis, Gore, and Kerry made plain. If Biden wins the nomination next year, it will be because Democrats went with their heads, not their bleeding hearts. But Hillary Clinton’s 2008 campaign is a cautionary tale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union Plans Picket Of Vegas Fundraiser... </title>
      <link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/union-plans-picket-of-joe-biden-fundraiser-hosted-by-kaiser-board-member_n_5cd1c051e4b04e275d510425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Union of Healthcare Workers is battling the health care provider over mental health staffing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz condemns mini skirts with concentration camp photos...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/442526-auschwitz-condemns-redbubble-for-selling-pillows-mini-skirts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Auschwitz Memorial and Museum in Poland on Tuesday condemned Redbubble, an online marketplace for independent artists, for allowing products including throw pillows and mini skirts featuring images of the Nazi concentration and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Dog Thwarts Abduction Of Baby...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/family-dog-credited-thwarting-baby-abduction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio family believes their pet dog may have prevented the abduction of their infant son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash still king: San Fran to ban credit-only stores...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e4e95476e4e74756b3973ed23fa3b00e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco is about to require brick-and-mortar retailers to take cash as payment, joining Philadelphia and New Jersey in banning a growing paperless practice that critics...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Chicago police sergeant charged in attack outside gay bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-former-chicago-cop-bar-attack-20190507-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Chicago police sergeant once accused of having sexual contact with teenage boys has been charged with a vicious attack at a gay club on the North Side last year that left two men with serious injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer apologizes for 'worst national anthem rendition ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article230112979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentuck Derby winner out of Preakness in Triple Crown debacle...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/07/country-house-out-of-preakness-stakes-in-triple-crown-debacle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There will be no Triple Crown winner this year. Controversial Kentucky Derby winner Country House will not be running in the May 18 Preakness Stakes after developing a cough, trainer Bill Mott told…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnancy deaths up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4907da5c58c84a708a548c4ea18fc5c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More U.S. women are dying from pregnancy-related causes, and more than half of those deaths are preventable, government health officials said in a report Tuesday. Although these deaths are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley coming for your house...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Silicon-Valley-Is-Coming-for-Your-House-13824737.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In today's on-demand digital world, buying and selling a home remains stubbornly, painfully analog. Most sales still begin with a real estate agent (and a 6% commission). Most still end in an office, with the two sides signing page after page of legalese.  Silicon Valley wants to change that. Tech companies have begun to nibble away at the edges of the residential real estate industry, offering virtual open houses, digital closings and other services. Now they are coming straight for the real estate transaction itself through "instant buying," in which companies buy homes, perform some light maintenance and put them back on the market.  Established companies like Zillow and venture-backed upstarts like Opendoor and Offerpad have raised billions of dollars on the promise that they can use sophisticated algorithms to predict the value of individual homes. They contend that those predictions, combined with old-fashioned economies of scale, will allow them to be far more efficient than traditional home flippers.  The companies and their backers say they are doing what tech is best at: bringing efficiency and convenience to a process not known for either. Silicon Valley has already upended the way we hail a cab and order takeout, they argue. Why not improve a transaction that even well-educated professionals find intimidating?  "You should be able to sell a home within a handful of clicks," said Eric Wu, Opendoor's chief executive.  But houses are not taxicabs. A bad Uber ride might set a user back $20 and make her late for a meeting. A house is the largest asset for most Americans and the most expensive purchase they will ever make.  At best, skeptics see instant buying, also known as "iBuying," as an overhyped, capital-intensive business whose explosive growth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine commandos ran military gear theft ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2019/05/06/north-carolina-raider-theft-rings-marines-stole-tactical-gear-vehicle-parts-flashbang-grenades-and-pawned-off-some-of-the-loot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than $300,000 worth of government property was stolen by one group of four Marines in 2017 alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe measles outbreak infects 34,000...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/07/europe-measles-outbreak-infects-34000-travel-advisory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 34,000 Europeans were infected with the measles during the first two months of 2019, most of whom are in Ukraine but who inhabit 42 countries in all. In a new report, the World Health Org…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This anchor doesn't exist, didn't say that...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/deep-fake-videos-intelligence-agencies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video of a seemingly real news anchor, reading a patently false script saying things like the &amp;quot;subways always run on time&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;New York City pizza is definitely not as good as Chicago&amp;quot; gives a whole new meaning to the term fake news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rallies with union members in Vegas... </title>
      <link>https://www.lasvegasnow.com/news/local-news/joe-biden-to-campaign-in-southern-nevada/1982386054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lasvegasnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden will make his first campaign stop in the Las Vegas valley since announcing his 2020 bid for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowfall on Way in Denver...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/05/07/denver-weather-may-7-snow-fog-thunder-lightning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service has issued a dense fog advisory for the Denver metro area Tuesday morning. As the day progresses the weather conditions will only get more dramatic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro Caught Dancing During Military Uprising...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/05/07/venezuela-nicolas-maduro-danced-on-tv-during-military-uprising/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan socialist dictator Nicolás Maduro responded to last week's call for a military uprising by appearing on television and dancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Make America calm again...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/839841/trumps-presidency-puts-america-state-perpetual-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The endless drama in Washington is exhausting â€” and bad for Americans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals attack, seeking to blunt momentum...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442378-liberals-attack-biden-seeking-to-blunt-his-momentum </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives are taking shots at Joe Biden, seeking to blunt the former vice president’s rise in polls by arguing he is too conservative to be the party's presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple die of bubonic plague after dining on raw marmot...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/couple-die-in-mongolia-of-bubonic-plague-after-eating-raw-marmot-135154552.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists were left stranded for days after a quarantine was introduced following the deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  Russia case NOT closed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48dd7f423f40473a9562fca769104fcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on Congress and the special counsel's Russia report (all times local): 11:50 a.m. The White House is instructing former counsel Don McGahn not to comply...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete claims more experience than Trump, Pence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/buttigieg-claims-more-experience-trump-pence-would-bring-very-different-n1002731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 37-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, spoke with NBC News' Craig Melvin while campaigning in South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starr Comes For 'Whiny' Mueller!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/ken-starr-comes-for-robert-mueller-committed-an-unforgivable-sin-with-whiny-leaked-letter-to-ag-barr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With rare exception, special counsel Robert Mueller has emerged from the past two years unscathed -- seemingly immune to cable news criticism. But on Monday, one man who previously ran a high-profile independent investigation of a president came after him with a blistering take. Appearing on The Story, Ken Starr -- the man who led the investigation into former President Bill Clinton in the late '90s -- shredded Mueller for his letter to Attorney General William Barr, which took the AG to task for his four-page Mueller Report summary. "His letter, that was then leaked on the very eve of Bill Barr's testimony, was essentially, I believe, an unfair, whiny complaint," Starr told Fox's Martha MacCallum. "Whiny" was just the beginning of Starr's blistering critique. The former independent counsel went on to refer to the leaked letter as an "unforgivable sin" against Barr. "Here comes Bob Mueller with this letter which is then leaked. That is, to me, the unforgivable sin," Starr said. "He,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET WAITS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/07/us-stock-market-us-china-trade-tensions-remain-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Tuesday after a top U.S. trade official indicated that higher tariffs on Chinese goods are coming later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company LOSES 58 cents per ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/uber-ipo-uber-losing-an-average-of-58-cents-per-ride-and-says-its-ready-to-go-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The profitless company could be valued at up to $90 billion by Wall Street, or roughly twice the market cap of Ford</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  57% of Dems Believe Trump Guilty of Treason...</title>
      <link>https://scottrasmussen.com/57-of-democrats-believe-president-trump-guilty-of-treason/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scottrasmussen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-seven percent (57%) of Democrats believe that, in his relations with the Russian government, President Trump is guilty of treason. A ScottRasmussen.com national survey found that just 14% of those in Nancy Pelosi's party disagree while 29% are not sure.Republicans reject the notion that the president is guilty of treason by an 82% to 7% margin. Among Independent voters, 30% believe he has committed treason while 44% disagree and 25% are not sure (see full crosstab results).Among all voters, 33% believe the president is guilty of treason while 45% disagree.ScottRasmussen.com releases new public opinion data every day relating to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politician Wants To Ban ALL Bags...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/05/07/new-jersey-politician-wants-to-ban-all-bags-paper-or-plastic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Garden State's plan to ban all grocery store bags could have negative consequences for consumer convenience and the environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sorcerer' promised to help people find love. Instead, orchestrated 'witchcraft extortion scheme'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-sorcerer-promised-to-help-people-find-love-13825060.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The love ritual began with candles, alcohol, vegetables and photographs, all carefully arranged. Then clients were told to send photos and videos of themselves reciting graphic statements and performing sex acts to a Paraguayan business specializing in witchcraft to finish the magic spell aimed at finding a soul mate.  That's when a self-described sorcerer started another familiar rite: extortion.  Ariel Boiteux, an Argentine national who masterminded an international scheme that entangled an estimated 200 victims in at least 12 countries, threatened to post the photos and videos of the intimate acts unless his clients paid "large sums of money," according to authorities, sometimes demanding six-figure payoffs. Boiteux, 31, and associates with his company, Amarres Inmediatos, even posted some explicit content to websites, Facebook and Instagram and forced clients to pay to take down the posts.  But as the alleged warlock of witchcraft extortion learned this week, there were no tricks in his bag of distorted magic that could get him out prison.  The U.S. attorney's office for the Southern District of California announced Monday that Boiteux was sentenced to two years in federal prison for the crime of foreign transmission of an extortionate threat. He pleaded guilty in December after being extradited from Paraguay to San Diego last July, the Los Angeles Times reported.  "This was a despicable scheme that preyed upon people who put their trust in a phony," U.S. Attorney Robert Brewer Jr. said in a news release on Monday. "This defendant used the vulnerability of the lovelorn to humiliate and extort them, and for that he will pay a price."  Authorities in Paraguay said that the estimated 200 victims hailed from the United States, Paraguay, Argentina, Bolivia, Chile, the Dominican Republic, Guatemala, Italy, Mexico, Peru,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Comey in trouble and knows it...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/442278-james-comey-is-in-trouble-and-he-knows-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three internal investigations likely will fully expose Comey’s mishandling of the FBI and legal processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier trampled to death by elephant during mission to protect wildlife from poachers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9019837/brit-soldier-trampled-death-elephant-malawi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRITISH soldier has been trampled to death by an elephant while on anti-poaching duty in Malawi, it emerged today. Guardsman Mathew Talbot, 23, died on Sunday morning during a mission to stop the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rebel priest: 'Gay people in church not going away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/07/rebel-priest-gay-church-campaign-same-sex-marriage </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rev Andrew Foreshew-Cain says his same-sex marriage cost him his ministry. Now he is launching a campaign for the rights of LGBTQ Christians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana man's DNA oldest found on continent, testing company says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/05/06/blackfeet-man-dna-deemed-oldest-americas-cri-genetics/1121352001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DNA testing company calls Darrell "Dustry" Crawford's test results "like finding bigfoot."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War brewing over lithium mining at edge of Death Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-death-valley-lithium-mine-california-environment-20190507-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A request to drill for lithium near Death Valley National Park has alarmed environmentalists, who say mining the metal is unacceptable, even if it is an essential ingredient in the production of zero-emission electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When comes to power in workplace, 30 the new 50...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90338362/when-it-comes-to-power-in-the-workplace-30-is-the-new-50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. labor force is aging, yet nearly 40% of Americans now report to a younger boss. Here’s how to navigate the generational power dynamics of the contemporary workplace, writes Modern Elder’s Chip Conley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit's LED streetlights going dark after few years...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/detroit-city/2019/05/07/detroits-led-streetlights-going-dark-after-few-years/3650465002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;20,000 lights â€˜prematurely dimming, burning outâ€™ a few years after being installed; lawsuit targets Calif. manufacturer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcists gather in Rome to trade tips on fighting Satan...</title>
      <link>https://www.perthnow.com.au/technology/science/exorcism-goes-mainstream-combined-churches-assemble-in-rome-to-learn-best-practice-eviction-of-demons-ng-d97c59cfe2d1bac0fc53432d0f3e2776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.perthnow.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic, Lutheran and Protestant priests have put aside their differences and flocked to Rome in a bid to learn ‘best practice’ techniques for expelling demons from their flocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are we watching John Bolton's last stand?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Are-we-watching-John-Bolton-s-last-stand-13824655.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is John Bolton about to get the Iran war he's always wanted, or is he on the verge of losing his job?  Over the past several days, President Trump's national security adviser has made comments and issued statements about Iran and Venezuela that are usually reserved for the run-up to military campaigns.  Yet Bolton's boss doesn't seem to be playing along.  On Sunday, the White House released a statement, attributed to Bolton, that the United States is deploying the USS Abraham Lincoln aircraft carrier strike group to the Persian Gulf. The aim: "to send a clear and unmistakable message to the Iranian regime that any attack on United States interests or on those of our allies will be met with unrelenting force." The message added: "The United States is not seeking war with the Iranian regime, but we are fully prepared to respond to any attack, whether by proxy, the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps, or regular Iranian forces."  A U.S. official said the deployment was in response to "clear indications" of a "possible attack" by Iran or its proxies.  Although Tehran announced on Monday that it would restart some of its suspended nuclear activities to mark the year anniversary of the U.S. departure from its commitments, for its part, the Iranian regime isn't taking Bolton's bait yet.  Last month, the United States designated the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps as a terrorist organization; Tehran predictably responded by branding all U.S. forces in the Middle East as terrorists in turn. Aside from their rhetoric, however, the Iranians have made no other visible moves to ratchet up tensions between the two countries.  Meanwhile, in recent weeks Iran's foreign minister, Mohammad Javad Zarif, has been signaling his government's desire to negotiate a new nuclear deal with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT TV pounds gavel again as all-trial channel reborn...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/956616a8a9d94c24abe9c466a926f883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Court TV is ending its long recess. The channel for legal junkies that thrived during the trial-crazy 1990s comes back from the dead after more than a decade Wednesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norwegian Health Minister: Let People Smoke, Drink, Eat Red Meat...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/europe/201905071074774940-norway-health-minister/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway's newly appointed Health Minister Sylvi Listhaug, no stranger to controversy, has once again stirred the public by claiming that she wants to avoid becoming the "moral police" and instead intends to let fellow Norwegians indulge in bad habits as they please.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pardons ex-soldier convicted of killing Iraqi prisoner...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/michael-behenna-pardon-donald-trump-iraq-war-al-qaeda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has pardoned a former Army lieutenant who was convicted in 2009 of killing an Iraqi prisoner suspected of being a member of Al Qaeda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOOKS:  Chinese spies acquired NSA hacking tools...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/442415-chinese-spies-stole-nsa-tools-used-them-to-attack-us-allies-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leading cybersecurity firm found evidence Chinese intelligence operatives repurposed National Security Agency hacking technology in 2016 to attack American allies and private firms in Europe and Asia,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TAKES 32-POINT LEAD OVER BERNIE!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/what-americas-thinking/442310-joe-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden has a 32-point lead in the Democratic presidential race in a Hill-HarrisX poll released Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEOFF WITH CHINA</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-plays-hardball-china-ahead-key-talks-145934061--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump on Monday effectively ended a six-month trade truce with China, with top US officials accusing Beijing of backtracking ahead of a key round of negotiations this week. Tariffs on $200 billion in Chinese merchandise will more than double to 25 percent at 12:01 am (0401 GMT) Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravers get hypothermia at snow-hit French techno festival...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ravers-hypothermia-snow-hit-french-techno-festival-154045672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guéret (France) (AFP) - Around 30 people were treated for hypothermia at an outdoor techno music festival in France after unexpected snowfall left many ravers sheltering under survival blankets distributed by the Red Cross. Around 10,000 people attended the unauthorised Teknival 2019 festival in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backers 'failed to follow through'... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/backers-failed-abortive-uprising-guaido-tells-afp-211010888.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido said Monday that backers who had pledged support for his abortive uprising last week had "failed to follow through" to dislodge President Nicolas Maduro. The 35-year-old National Assembly chief has branded Maduro a usurper over his controversial re-election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUMULTY:  PRESIDENT IS TROLLING US AGAIN, STOP FALLING FOR IT!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Trump-is-trolling-us-again-so-stop-falling-for-it-13823344.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has a superpower. With just a few taps to the screen of his iPhone, he can transform his staunchest adversaries into . . . Donald Trump.  No one loves a good conspiracy theory as much as the man in the Oval Office. Indeed, that is how he launched his political career. He was the chief propagator for a shameful lie that the nation's first blackpresident was not born in this country.  He continues to gin up new ones. But in addition to using them to stir his own base, Trump has become highly effective at fomenting preposterous scenarios that send his opposition into a conspiratorial frenzy.  The latest example came over the weekend, when Trump retweeted an obvious, if lame, joke by one of his most devoted sycophants.  "After the best week ever for @realDonaldTrump - no obstruction, no collusion, NYT admits @BarackObama did spy on his campaign, &amp; the economy is soaring," Jerry Falwell Jr., the president of Liberty University, wrote. "I now support reparations - Trump should have 2 yrs added to his 1st term as pay back for time stolen by this corrupt failed coup."  Reparations - get it? Falwell was sucking up to the president, distorting the results of special counsel Robert Mueller's report on Trump's possibly illegal effort to obstruct the investigation of Russian interference in the 2016 election, and making a racially insensitive reference to redressing the abomination of slavery. It was a three-fer, in less than 240 characters.  Trump himself continued the trolling with a tweet that read: "they have stolen two years of my (our) Presidency (Collusion Delusion) that we will never be able to get back."  Traditional and social media took the bait, as Trump surely knew they would.  Out of that tweet came a torrent of speculation about the extralegal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  TRUMP APPROVAL HITS HIGH; TOPS OBAMA AT SAME TIME IN PRESIDENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/gallup-trump-approval-rating-ticks-up-to-new-high-of-46-percent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Gallup poll shows Donald Trump’s presidential job-approval rating hitting a new high of 46 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops to Florida woman: 'Do you have anything else?' She pulled a gator from her pants...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article230091664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/tiger-woods-gives-moving-speech-at-medal-of-freedom-ceremony-youve-seen-the-good-and-the-bad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professional golfer Tiger Woods gave a humbled speech on Monday as he received the Presidential Medal of Freedom at the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Guaido's popularity in Venezuela begins to dwindle, what's next for opposition?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/sns-tns-bc-venezuela-guaido-20190506-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUCUTA, Colombia Since he first stood on a stage Jan. 23 and announced he was seizing the presidency from Nicolas Maduro, Juan Guaido, the 35-year-old head of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: First thing I'd do is repeal those tax cuts!</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/biden-first-thing-i-d-do-repeal-those-trump-tax-cuts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s promise to repeal the tax cuts is a promise to raise taxes&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Democrat presidential candidate Joe Biden threatened to raise taxes during a speech in Colombia, South Carolina this Saturday.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;“First thing I’d do is repeal those Trump tax cuts,” said Biden.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;[Click here for video]&amp;#13;&amp;#13;A repeal of the Tax Cuts and Jobs Act would impose a large tax increase on the American people. Thanks to the tax cuts, a typical family of four earning the median family income of $73,000 saw a tax cut of over $2,000– a 58% reduction in federal taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian PM egged while campaigning...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-05-07/scott-morrison-egged-on-federal-election-campaign-trail/11087174?pfmredir=sm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Prime Minister is egged by a female protester while meeting with delegates from the Country Women's Association in Albury, on the NSW-Victorian border — the woman who attacked him is in custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAGA STRIPS THROUGH FOUR OUTFITS... </title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/lady-gaga-met-gala-photos-video-outfits-strip-red-carpet-1203206552/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga busted into the 2019 Met Gala with an extravagant Brandon Maxwell outfit–well, outfits. Like a Russian nesting doll, Gaga took off one layer after another. The Oscar-winning singer-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  More Than 100 CNN Workers Take Voluntary Buyouts...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/cnn-layoffs-warnermedia-restructuring-att-1202608354/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN is the latest division of AT&amp;T’s WarnerMedia to feel the effects of company-wide restructuring, with voluntary buyouts being taken by more than 100 seasoned workers at the cable new n…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
