<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Most Epic Fails of Decade, From MOVIEPASS to 'MEGYN KELLY TODAY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/10-most-epic-fails-in-hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even Netflix didn't get out of the 2010s unscathed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION: Japanese News Agency Reports NKorea Missile Test In Error...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/476880-north-korea-fires-missile-japan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan’s broadcaster NHK reported a missile launch from North Korea, stating the projectile was estimated to have fallen some 2,000 km off Hokkaido's coast. The news, however, was retracted shortly afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW RECORDS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-market-set-to-rise-in-post-christmas-climb-2019-12-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks opened higher Thursday in light trading, with investor attention still squarely on trade deal progress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At each end of Pacific, skepticism over China farm purchases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ebf7a2646dda9371fe2762a5a3f1804f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — President Donald Trump likes to joke that America's farmers have a nice problem on their hands: They're going to need bigger tractors to keep up with surging Chinese demand for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Garages aren't even cheap anymore:' Bay Area exodus drives lowest growth rate in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/12/26/garages-arent-even-cheap-anymore-bay-area-exodus-drives-lowest-growth-rate-in-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid exodus of fed-up residents, the net growth has come largely from babies born here, and  they don’t take up a lot of space yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facts are misremembered to fit personal biases, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dispatch.com/news/20191225/facts-are-misremembered-to-fit-personal-biases-ohio-state-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study by Ohio State researchers found that people tend to misremember information to match commonly-held beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone's Steamboat Geyser breaks eruption record, stuns scientists...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2019/12/24/steamboat-geyser-yellowstone-park-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’re headed to Yellowstone National Park in Wyoming, there’s a good chance that visiting the park’s iconic geysers will be near the top of your to-do list. In 2019, tourists …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrier to Trump Wall: Landowners in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-barrier-to-trumps-border-wall-landowners-in-texas/ar-BBYm5rv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raids and conscription: Russian authorities crack down on Kremlin critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Raids-and-conscription-Russian-authorities-crack-14932111.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - In Russian authorities' latest crackdown this week on Kremlin critics, opposition leader Alexei Navalny's Anti-Corruption Foundation office was raided Thursday, just days after one of his top aides was suddenly conscripted and sent to a desolate base in the Arctic.  Navalny, who was barred from running in Russia's 2018 presidential election, said on Twitter that he was dragged out of the office by force before eventually being allowed to return. In the moments before his brief detention, Navalny live-streamed the raid as police used power tools to saw through the door.  "The picked the day not by chance - I was supposed to go on the air," Navalny said on Twitter, referring to his YouTube channel.  There have been multiple raids on Navalny's office this year, and he wrote on Instagram that the official reason for this one was related to his group's refusal to take down a 2017 YouTube documentary that investigated alleged corruption involving Prime Minister Dmitry Medvedev. A criminal case was opened against Ivan Zhdanov, director of the Anti-Corruption Foundation, as a result, and Thursday's search was apparently part of the investigation of that case, Navalny said.  Navalny says he will not take down the video, which has more than 32 million views.  Navalny is Russia's most prominent and most vocal critic of President Vladimir Putin, which has made him and his allies targets of the Kremlin's methods for keeping dissenting voices at bay. The European Court of Human Rights ruled last year that the multiple arrests of Navalny - there were seven from 2012 to 2014 alone - violated his rights and appeared to be part of a broader effort "to bring the opposition under control."  The raid on his office comes less than a week after Ruslan Shaveddinov, a 23-year-old project manager for Navalny's anti-corruption group, was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial Finds Scant Precedent in History...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-senate-impeachment-trial-finds-090000682.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bill Clinton’s impeachment two decades ago set the modern template for President Donald Trump’s upcoming trial in the Senate. But the process may be even more contentious this time given sharper tribal divisions in Washington.Clinton’s four-week proceeding in 1999 riveted the nation. Thirteen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too big to fail? Tech's decade of scale and impunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/dec/26/too-big-to-fail-techs-decade-of-scale-and-impunity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big tech behaves as though power absolves them of responsibility. Have we learned nothing since the financial crash?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS: IT COULD BE BERNIE</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/26/can-bernie-sanders-win-2020-election-president-089636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His resiliency in the primary has caught the attention of the party establishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Central American surge, Mexicans join asylum line at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-12-26/seeing-a-central-american-surge-mexicans-join-the-asylum-line-at-the-u-s-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a long, steady decline in overall Mexican immigration following its peak in 2000, the number of Mexican asylum seekers arriving at the southwestern border has been steadily rising in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: LARGE, NON-GOVT DRONES FLYING GRID PATTERN OVER COLORADO...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/large-non-government-drones-flying-in-mysterious-grid-pattern-over-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody knows who's flying them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rally far outpacing past presidents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/26/trumps-stock-market-rally-is-far-outpacing-past-us-presidents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 has returned more than 50% since Trump was elected, more than double the average market return of presidents three years into their term, according to Bespoke Investment Group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Kevin Spacey accuser and ex of Norwegian princess kills self...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/12/25/ari-behn-norwegian-princess-ex-and-kevin-spacey-accuser-dead-at-47/?_ga=2.129877706.714084198.1577358933-753093207.1577358933</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In December 2017, Behn came forward to accuse Spacey, 60, of groping him under a table at a Nobel Peace Prize concert in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Caffeine may offset holiday weight gain...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/health/caffeine-may-offset-holiday-weight-gain-study-says/5785117/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found that drinking four cups of coffee daily could reduce weight gain from a diet high in fat and sugar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump on quest for foreign wins -- and drama -- in election year...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-quest-foreign-wins-drama-election-045911063.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has shattered norms and niceties on the world stage in his nearly three years in office. Entering an election year, Trump is unlikely to slow down as he seeks what has largely eluded him -- a headline-grabbing victory. Trump closes 2019 with a stain as the third president in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' eclipse wows across Asia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ring-fire-eclipse-wows-across-asia-061506563.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers from Saudi Arabia and Oman to India and Singapore were treated to a rare "ring of fire" solar eclipse Thursday. While these types of eclipses occur every year or two, they are only visible from a narrow band of Earth each time and it can be decades before the same pattern is repeated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, Russia, Iran to hold joint naval drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-russia-iran-hold-joint-naval-drills-093455381.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China, Russia and Iran will hold joint naval drills starting Friday in the Gulf of Oman, Beijing and Tehran said, at a time of heightened tensions since the US withdrew from a landmark nuclear deal with Tehran. Set to take place from December 27 to 30, the military exercises aim to "deepen exchange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Babies-for-sale' scheme shocks Armenia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/babies-sale-scheme-shocks-armenia-034352226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syuzan Patvakanyan has been searching for her daughter ever since doctors in post-Soviet Armenia forced her to give her up as a baby nearly two decades ago. Now 35, she shared her story with AFP as the authorities this month detained the country's chief obstetrician-gynaecologist, the head of an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's baby mayor, face of anti-abortion movement...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/americas-baby-mayor-face-anti-abortion-movement-022305392.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whitehall (United States) (AFP) - "The mayor's breakfast is ready," Chad McMillan sings out from the living room of his Texas ranch. Charlie McMillan is no ordinary city official -- he's only seven months old and a new face of the anti-abortion movement in America. A twist on US President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Algeria to Hong Kong, year of anti-establishment rage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/algeria-hong-kong-anti-establishment-rage-042753397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angry citizens have swelled the streets of cities across the globe this year, pushing back against a disparate range of policies but often expressing a common grievance -- the establishment's failure to heed their demands for a more equitable future. While street protests are nothing new, experts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid hotshot passers, old men Brady and Brees roll on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/284b1651efd7a44e7f2c373d83043fb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between them, Tom Brady and Drew Brees have played 38 pro football seasons, 39 if you count 2008 when the New England star wrecked his knee in Week 1. Both probably should be long retired and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli lawmaker aims to oust Netanyahu in Likud primary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24f06ab3d3c1eb62eb532c5be73ff89c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel’s governing Likud party was holding a primary vote on Thursday in the first serious internal challenge to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in his more than a decade in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles DA considers charging Harvey Weinstein as investigation expands...</title>
      <link>https://www.omaha.com/news/national/los-angeles-da-considers-charging-harvey-weinstein-as-investigation-expands/article_5cc6e3dc-8aa0-59a0-9ed1-55191ee32223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — More than two years after the Los Angeles and Beverly Hills police departments launched sexual assault investigations into Harvey Weinstein, the Los Angeles County district attorney’s office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top adviser to Syria's president warns of 'operations' against US troops guarding oil fields...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/u-s-has-no-right-syrian-oil-adviser-president-assad-n1106846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bouthaina Shaaban was referring to President Donald Trump’s declaration earlier this year that the U.S. would “keep” Syrian oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  For Trump Organization, Office Skyscrapers Make Up for Lagging Hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-trying-times-for-presidents-business-it-turns-out-less-trump-is-more/ar-BBYkY2A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GOOD NEWS FILE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Appeal to the 'Reasonable Republican Dad' Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/joe-bidens-appeal-to-the-reasonable-republican-dad-vote/ar-BBYkY7i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis-related psychosis, addiction, ER visits: For young users, marijuana can be dangerous game...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/marijuana-addiction-adolescents-psychosis-abuse-vaping-penn-state-20191223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While it was once doubted as an addictive substance, treatment professionals now say they are seeing more adolescents and young adults with cannabis use disorder. Often starting in their early teens, many graduate to daily use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LET IT BE:  Phil Spector pictured sporting goatee, bald head, hearing aids in latest mugshot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7826387/Phil-Spector-79-pictured-sporting-goatee-bald-head-hearing-aids-latest-mugshot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 79-year-old fallen music legend, main in 2019, was sentenced to 19-years to life in 2009. He was convicted over the 2003 death of Lana Clarkson. His previous looks are pictured inset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85-year-old woman charged with murder, assault in double shooting...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/85-year-old-woman-charged-with-murder-assault-in-double-shooting-at-federal-way-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEDERAL WAY, Wash. - An 85-year-old woman has been charged with first degree murder and assault in the double shooting of her roommates earlier this month. Beverly Jenne is now being held on $1 million bail and will be booked into jail when she is released form a Tacoma hospital, prosecutors said. Police report that dispatchers received a 911 call from a woman in her 30s around 1 a. m. on Dec. 19 saying she had been shot in her home in the 2000 block of SW 306th Lane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports of patients' deaths linked to heart devices lurk below radar...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/reports-of-patients-deaths-linked-to-heart-devices-lurk-below-radar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because of a little-known federal exemption program, death data about heart devices sits in inaccessible FDA files that can take up to two years for the public to see under open-records laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Doctor Will See You Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-doctor-will-see-you-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advances in neural networks and other techniques promise to transform health care while raising profound questions about our bodies and society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subway graffiti making resurgence in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/25/subway-graffiti-is-making-a-resurgence-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graffiti is on the express track back into New York’s subway landscape, MTA data obtained by The Post shows. After holding at around 200 markings in stations and on trains per year in the fir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Anti-Putin activist 'forcibly drafted' and sent to Arctic base...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anti-putin-activist-forcibly-drafted-sent-arctic-144303947.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny said Wednesday that one of his allies had been forcibly conscripted and sent to serve at a remote Arctic base, in a move his supporters said amounted to kidnapping. Ruslan Shaveddinov, a project manager at Navalny's anti-corruption foundation, went missing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norwegian Princess' ex-husband takes his own life...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/5104224/norweigan-princess-ex-husband-takes-his-own-life-leaving-behind-couples-three-young-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCESS Martha Louise of Norway’s ex-hubby has taken his own life. Tragic Ari Behn’s death left the palace stunned and family and friends grief-stricken as member of the royal family p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divorce lawyers brace for busy January...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/as-lawyers-brace-for-a-surge-in-divorce-cases-in-january-new-research-highlights-the-financial-benefits-of-splitting-up-2019-12-24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In states with ‘no fault’ divorces, couples are 8% more likely to both work full-time outside the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to conduct naval drills with China, Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2019/12/25/iran-to-conduct-naval-drills-with-china-and-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drills are slated to start Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Loaded UPS Truck Found Abandoned, Unlocked On Xmas Eve...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/12/25/ups-truck-natomas-abandoned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While UPS trucks are known for making deliveries, one box truck with the signature logo was parked overnight on Sierra Point Drive in a Natomas business park fully loaded and unlocked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 quakes in less than 24 hours hit California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article238708288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI RUSHED OFF STAGE OVER ROCKET FEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/rocket-alert-sirens-blare-in-southern-israel-1.8319031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas strip club under fire after donating tents to homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7826391/Las-Vegas-strip-club-comes-fire-donating-tents-clubs-logo-homeless.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mother - who wished to remain anonymous - complained that the tents from Deja Vu Showgirls were 'immoral' and 'disgusting,' adding that she was 'taken back' when she saw some tents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US ambassador recalled after dispute with Zambian govt over gay rights, corruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/25/politics/daniel-foote-zambia-ambassador/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an extraordinary move, the State Department is pulling the US ambassador to Zambia after the president there objected to his harsh criticism of the government's record on corruption and gay rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final solar eclipse of the decade will create a 'ring of fire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/final-annular-solar-eclipse-decade-ring-of-fire-how-to-watch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annular solar eclipse will be a Christmas spectacular.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fragile Notre Dame might not be saved...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48fee6c01627bca5f212c0f2e35d81cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The rector of Notre Dame Cathedral says the Paris landmark is still so fragile that there's a “50% chance” the structure might not be saved, because scaffolding installed before this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETANYAHU: Putin said if I were not PM, Israel and Russia would be at war...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/netanyahu-putin-said-that-if-i-were-not-pm-israel-and-russia-would-be-at-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In interview ahead of Likud primary, PM refuses to answer questions on whether he will seek immunity from prosecution or what he’ll do if High Court rules he can’t form government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First contact with aliens more and more likely...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/will-we-find-aliens-in-the-next-decade-its-not-as-crazy-as-you-might-think</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First contact looks more and more likely. But if we’re going to find extraterrestrial life in the 2020s, we might need to switch up exactly where, and how, we’re looking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists warn AI control of nukes could lead to 'terminator-style' war...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/International/Nuke-scientists-warn-AI-control-could-lead-to-Terminator-style-nuke-war-612123</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world may be inching closer to an apocalyptic nuclear war could be possible as control over nuclear weapons is yielded to artificial intelligence (AI).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican senator 'disturbed' by McConnell's White House coordination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/25/politics/lisa-murkowski-senate-impeachment-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Sen. Lisa Murkowski of Alaska said she is "disturbed" by coordination between Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell and the White House over the upcoming Senate impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Calls for Exemplifying Teachings of Christ...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-celebrates-christmas-by-calling-for-americans-to-unify-and-exemplify-the-teachings-of-christ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"While the challenges that face our country are great, the bonds that unite us as Americans are much stronger."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Warmth On Christmas In Chicago? </title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/12/25/chicago-weather-christmas-day-record-breaking-temperatures-possible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicagoans could see a record-breaking Christmas Day as temperatures rise.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
