<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Dutch girls who seduced Nazis -- and lured them to deaths...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/14/meet-the-dutch-girls-who-seduced-nazis-and-lured-them-to-their-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When she came across a Nazi killing an infant by repeatedly swinging its tiny body against a brick wall, Truus Oversteegen didn’t flinch. The freckle-faced teenager, who was just three months shy o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Jones Says 'Fired' From Show For 'Wrong Message For Black America'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/orlando-jones-fired-american-gods-racism-gabrielle-union-fremantle-starz-neil-gaiman-1202809444/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tumultuous run of American Gods looks to have taken another turn, with Orlando Jones declaring he has been fired from the Starz series for having “the wrong message for black America.” In a vid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid adversity and missteps, Biden resilience has been one theme of '19...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Amid-adversity-and-missteps-Joe-Biden-s-14906746.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of the year, former vice president Joe Biden has often been described in negative terms. It has been said he is not as sharp as he should be or once was; that he is well liked but can't excite the base of the new Democratic Party; that his agenda is little more than "return to normalcy" and that his fundraising problems belie bigger weaknesses.  All of that is well and good, but he nears the end of 2019 also as a candidate who has absorbed more criticism than just about everyone else in the Democratic field combined, and he has survived the attacks reasonably well. He remains atop the national polls, his support among African Americans has proved durable through the year, and while his numbers have slipped in Iowa and New Hampshire, he is nonetheless in the battle in those two early-voting states.  The story of Biden for most of the year has been written as a glass-half-empty narrative. What about the opposite way of viewing where he stands? I recently asked a Democrat who has been involved in several presidential races this question: What if Biden were to win the Iowa caucuses? His answer: "He could run the table."  This Democrat was not predicting it; nor was he ruling it out. But if Iowa falls into Biden's column, it would instantly change the way everyone looks at the 2020 field and the potential outcomes.  This has happened before. In December 2003, then-Sen. John Kerry, D-Mass., the perceived early front-runner, was in all kinds of trouble. He was running behind in Iowa and New Hampshire and was down in the polls nationally. His campaign had been through a staff shake-up that left supporters lacking in confidence. He seemed to be floundering.  Even some of Kerry's closest advisers were saying privately, just weeks before Iowa, that Howard Dean was the likeliest person to win that state and to become the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops refused service at California STARBUCKS...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/society/riverside-county-deputies-allegedly-refused-service-at-starbucks/5754060/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is apologizing after two uniformed Riverside County deputies were allegedly refused service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is trap being set for president in Senate trial?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/474242-is-a-trap-being-set-for-trump-in-the-senate-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House may be seriously underestimating the resentment against the president by a number of Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scramble to rack up accomplishments gives conservatives heartburn...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/474550-trump-scramble-to-rack-up-accomplishments-gives-conservatives-heartburn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s race to rack up accomplishments heading into an election year is giving conservatives heartburn, with some worried he is striking deals that include giveaways to Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans Consider 'Living Off Grid' To Keep Data Safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/digital-deception-9-in-10-americans-have-been-victimized-by-an-online-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey finds that 90% of Americans have been a victim of an online scam, fraud, data breach, identity theft, or social media hacking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RICHARD JEWELL' could mark one of worst openings of Clint Eastwood career...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-jumanji-next-level-nabs-47m-thursday-previews-1262508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Richard Jewell' could mark one of worst nationwide openings of Clint Eastwood's directing career and the lowest in two decades. 'Black Christmas' is also getting scrooged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover deepest point on land...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/14/us/deepest-point-on-land-scntrnd-/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study shows that the deepest point on land is under the Denman Glacier in East Antarctica. Glaciologists at the University of California, Irvine, were mapping the area only to find that the trough under the glacier went far deeper than they had imagined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5G 'can spy on you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/5g-can-spy-you-critic-21083745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vocal 5G critic who makes Youtube videos describing the technology as "weapons" has claimed it can be misused to listen and watch people in their own homes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN climate talks unraveling, face failure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-climate-talks-unraveling-face-failure-110423955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UN climate summit in Madrid risked collapsing Saturday after all-night negotiations between countries left them more divided than ever over on how to fight global warming and pay for its ravages. Diplomats from rich nations, emerging giants and the world's poorest countries -- each for their own</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas mayhem feared as French transport strike continues...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/christmas-mayhem-feared-french-transport-strike-continues-143133316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France reeled under a crippling public transport strike for a 10th day Saturday aimed at forcing the government to scrap a pension revamp, as fears grew of travel mayhem during Christmas. Train traffic was severely disrupted with only one out four high speed long-distance trains and three of 10 regional</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reparations Mark New Front for Colleges Tied to Slavery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f390bd047c87a71d372e38ffbf477ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The promise of reparations to atone for historical ties to slavery has opened new territory in a reckoning at U.S. colleges, which until now have responded with monuments,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Was One of Mexico's Deadliest Assassins. Then He Turned on Cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/he-was-one-of-mexicos-deadliest-assassins-then-he-turned-on-his-cartel/ar-AAK7nnX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PATRIOTS Season of Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://postofasia.com/the-patriots-season-of-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;postofasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots are 10-3. They at present maintain the No. 2 seed within the A.F.C. In all chance — a 76 p.c probability, in accordance with The New York Occasions’s playoff simulator — they are going to earn a first-round bye for the 10th consecutive postseason. And but an uneasy feeling has settled …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea conducts another test at long-range rocket site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a65ce1c9102331e8e0036be11cb4d872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Saturday that it successfully performed another “crucial test” at its long-range rocket launch site that will further strengthen its nuclear deterrent....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST ACTOR?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791443/Harvey-Weinstein-MeToo-monster-looked-bit-broken-man.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOM LEONARD: Shirt collar askew, ill-fitting suit and grey face a picture of misery and forbearance, Harvey Weinstein shuffled into a Manhattan court this week hunched over a walking frame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's not fair!' </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7791387/Trump-whines-impeachment-says-unjust.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It's not fair that I'm being Impeached when I've done absolutely nothing wrong! The Radical Left, Do Nothing Democrats have become the Party of Hate. They are so bad for our Country!' Trump tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church investigated over claims pastors pushed members into 'selling their blood to raise funds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7790197/Charity-Commission-investigates-Spac-Nation-Church-Bling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charity Commission has opened an inquiry into SPAC Nation after allegations emerged that pastors had told worshipppers to take out loans and even sell their blood to raise money.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
