<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Feds Claim Airport Facial Recognition 'Not Surveillance Program'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/05/cbps-airport-facial-recognition-not-surveillance-program/157373/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the public grows wary of facial recognition, the head of CBP’s biometric entry and exit initiative says the agency is using the tech responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamers Earning $15,000 an Hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/top-gamers-earning-up-15000-an-hour-1214953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new lawsuit reveals the high stakes in gaming as brands like Coca-Cola and Bud Light push the hourly income of popular streamers as high as five figures: "It's become something nobody predicted."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 11 Employers Prosecuted for Hiring Illegal Aliens in Last Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/06/02/feds-only-11-employers-prosecuted-for-hiring-illegal-aliens-in-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only 11 employers and no businesses were prosecuted for hiring illegal aliens over American citizens for U.S. jobs last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia requires TINDER to provide data on its users...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/103dc01ce19e48fd89cd32e083ca1e50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Dating app Tinder is now required to provide user data to Russian intelligence agencies, the country's communications regulator said Monday. The app was included on a new list...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://www.pravdareport.com/world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pravdareport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAFRICA: Prominent white farmer killed following land grab dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesouthafrican.com/news/stellenbosch-farm-murder-stefan-smit-killed-following-land-grabs-dispute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesouthafrican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After expressing concerns about land grabs on his property earlier this year, Stefan Smit has fell victim to a farm murder on his Stellenbosch estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonds 'on fire' as flight to safety rumbles on...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-markets/bonds-on-fire-as-flight-to-safety-rumbles-on-idUSKCN1T402Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stampede to safety sent benchmark government bond yields tumbling on Monday, h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAB HACK COULD HIT MILLIONS; MEDICAL INFO EXPOSED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Quest-Diagnostics-12-Million-People-Data-Breach-510754611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quest Diagnostics, one of the biggest blood testing providers in the country, warned Monday that nearly 12 million of its customers may have had personal, financial and medical information breached due to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania homage to Diana...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-7098355/Melania-Trump-pays-tribute-D-Day-veterans-military-themed-650-Burberry-blouse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The First Lady, 49, plumped for a classic combination of a navy knee-length skirt and matching blazer as she stepped off Air Force One at Stansted Airport this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing Index Dips to Lowest Level in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-manufacturing-index-dips-lowest-134500487.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“May saw U.S. manufacturers endure the toughest month in nearly 10 years, with the headline PMI down to its lowest since the height of the global financial crisis,” said Chris Williamson, economist at IHS Markit. Survey respondents stated that weak client demand drove the drop in new orders for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's record offers cautions for battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/02/europe-google-fines-1496124</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The EU has levied multibillion-dollar fines against the search giant but has struggled to change its behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor tried to set up threesome with underage girls...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2019/05/31/kentucky-elevate-pastor-sought-sex-threesome-minors-police-say/1297598001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobby J. Blackburn, pastor of Elevate Church in Prestonsburg, Kentucky, was arrested May 29, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few political allies, history of complaints...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/02/doj-will-move-faster-vs-google-than-it-did-with-microsoft-experts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft's battle with the Justice Department dragged on for almost a decade. If the DOJ investigates Google, expect things to move more quickly, according to two antitrust lawyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYAL WELCOME</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/97064142e675468ea48090be89e2ab44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — President Donald Trump met with Queen Elizabeth II Monday during a three-day visit to Britain meant to strengthen ties between the two nations, although the trip was immediately at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Ai-Da: Robot artist giving real painters run for their money...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/meet-ai-da-robot-artist-174804279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Auguste Rodin spent the best part of four decades working on his epic sculpture The Gates of Hell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise and fall of Kevin Spacey...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/rise-fall-kevin-spacey-timeline-sexual-assault-allegations/story?id=63420983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than three decades, the award-winning actor could seemingly do no wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to improve life? Learn to say no...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/jun/02/want-to-improve-your-life-just-say-no</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are used to saying yes to please others but it can be harmful not to be more assertive. And imagine what you can do with all that free time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris launches campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-launches-campaign-to-become-next-british-pm/ar-AACjZ7r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet split in two...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-us-china-internet-split-20190603-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing-based correspondent Alice Su and L.A.-based columnist Frank Shyong discuss living and working between Chinese and non-Chinese online spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of quakes hit SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-earthquakes-southern-california-20190602-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 small quakes have hit the Riverside County this weekend, including one measuring magnitude 3.3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second round of deadly Israeli strikes hit Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190603-syria-israel-second-deadly-strikes-hit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel launched a second round of strikes against Syria in 24 hours on Sunday, state media reported, as US President Donald Trump called on Russia and Iran to “stop bombing the hell” out of the war-torn country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA food sampling finds contamination by 'forever chemicals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e9c5fa42a1244de48e3edea7a1bb14eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Food and Drug Administration's first broad testing of food for a worrisome class of nonstick, stain-resistant industrial compounds found substantial levels in some grocery...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia orders TINDER to turn over data to intelligence agencies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/briefingroom-blogroll/446582-russia-orders-tinder-to-turn-over-data-to-intelligence-agencies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Russian oversight policy requires Tinder to provide intelligence agencies with user data,  The Associated Press reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's longest flight to be even less comfortable than expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/australianz/worlds-longest-flight-to-be-even-less-comfortable-than-expected</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY (BLOOMBERG) - Proposed flights half way around the globe are set to be even less comfortable than expected. That is, if the marathon 20-hour non-stop services from Sydney to London get off the ground at all.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLE fruit trucks burned in Honduras as protests spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-honduras-protests/dole-fruit-trucks-burned-in-honduras-as-protests-spread-idUSKCN1T40IQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters burned and looted some 30 shipping containers marked with the logo of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factories Feel Pain as Wall St Sees Recession Risk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/asia-factories-feel-trade-war-020553337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global manufacturing took another knock last month from trade tensions, adding to concerns that the world economy is weakening. The latest signs of factory weakness -- in countries including South Korea, Germany and Japan -- underscore the growing threat to the world economy posed by the escalating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Govt Test Internet Kill Switch?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-06-02/did-government-just-test-internet-kill-switch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hits back at London mayor on arrival in UK...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-hits-back-london-mayor-arrival-uk-091924143.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump lashed out at London Mayor Sadiq Khan on Monday as he arrived for a three-day state visit to Britain, reviving a long-running enmity between the two. On landing, he sent out a pair of tweets calling Khan a "stone cold loser" for criticising his red carpet treatment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires having 'young blood' transfusions in bid to live forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9194101/from-young-blood-transfusions-to-apocalypse-insurance-weird-ways-billionaires-are-trying-to-live-forever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT’S simply not enough for billionaires to have everything they’ve ever wanted – they need eternity to enjoy it, too. At least a dozen of the world’s richest men have ploughed mil…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FRESH LOOK TO MEET QUEEN</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9207550/donald-trump-new-haircut-uk-visit-meet-queen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has showed off a slick new hairdo as he prepares to meet the Queen during his first official state visit to the UK. The US President’s new look, no doubt achieved with copious amounts …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARD TIME:  California's jails are so bad some inmates beg to go to prison instead...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/california-s-jails-are-so-bad-some-inmates-beg-to/article_f7903d65-f147-5593-b8a9-8519370d5a31.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Ever since he stole his first car at age 10, Cody Garland has spent much of his life behind bars. Now 35, he has served time at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craddock was violent with co-workers before Virginia Beach rampage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/02/dewayne-craddock-had-been-getting-violent-with-co-workers-before-virginia-beach-shooting-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman who shot dead 12 people at a Virginia Beach municipal building had been facing disciplinary action for a violent fight at work, according to a report. DeWayne Craddock, 40, was still emp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On eve of UK visit, Trump denies 'nasty' Meghan Markle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eve-uk-visit-trump-denies-taped-remark-nasty-162350215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump denied on Sunday that he had called Meghan Markle "nasty" just days before heading to Britain to be hosted, and lavishly feted, by other members of the royal family. Trump's tweet Sunday came a day before his three-day state visit is to begin with a pomp-filled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass shootings transform how America talks, prays, prepares...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/73d3cdd6ee5643449bab86c3fe301ce8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Pardeep Singh Kaleka has surveyed the landscape of an America scarred by mass shootings. Seven years ago, a white supremacist invaded a Sikh temple in Wisconsin and killed six...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More turning to 'La Bestia'...</title>
      <link>http://www.hastingstribune.com/despite-perils-more-u-s--bound-migrants-are-turning/article_fa8bbb08-4321-5f01-add7-1579ea41bab1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARRIAGA, Mexico — They gathered at dawn in this railyard in southern Mexico, contemplating their next move: catching a ride on the roof of La Bestia (the Beast) — the</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
