<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>White House freezes Ukraine military package that includes lethal weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/18/white-house-ukraine-military-lethal-weapons-495169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials prepped $100 million worth of arms as Russia massed troops on the border, then pulled the plug as the Biden-Putin summit approached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Hopes for J&amp;J Fizzle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/high-hopes-for-johnson-johnson-s-covid-vaccine-have-fizzled-in-the-u-s/ar-AALaPHq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correction: June 18, 2021 This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: An earlier version of this article incorrectly stated what portion of the doses Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson promised to the U.S. government by the end of June had been delivered. It is less than half, not a quarter. WASHINGTON — When Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson’s single-dose coronavirus vaccine was authorized for emergency use in late February, ​it was seen as a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viral infections in Israel are surging...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/covid-19-might-be-over-but-viral-infections-in-israel-are-surging-671354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children and adults around the country are getting sick as it usually happens in the winter, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas pushes land swap to balance growth, conservation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/las-vegas-science-government-and-politics-business-environment-and-nature-aa4483c2d05775fc922592b0e85ddbec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARSON CITY, Nev. (AP) — Record-breaking heat and historic drought in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND:  Mayor uses million$ in virus funds to fight racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3109928/chicago-mayor-lori-lightfoot-racism-public-health-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO Mayor Lori Lightfoot has declared racism a public health crisis – and will give $10million in Covid money to fight it. The Democrat said on Thursday: “At almost every single point in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Intermittent Fasting NOT Effective Weight Loss Plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/intermittent-fasting-nothing-special/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say a fasting diet may actually make it harder to maintain muscle mass and physical activity levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion returns to catwalks as DIOR takes over Athens ancient stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2021/jun/18/fashion-returns-to-catwalks-as-dior-takes-over-athens-ancient-stadium</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maison’s Cruise collection at Panathenaic stadium includes pieces inspired by contemporary Greece</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  ONE AMERICA NEWS is face of Arizona election audit  --  its reporter is also helping pay for it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/one-america-news-is-the-face-of-the-arizona-election-audit-its-reporter-is-also-helping-pay-for-it/ar-AALbOAR?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The right-wing channel’s Christina Bobb is simultaneously covering, promoting and fundraising for the Republican-led review of 2020 election results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90% of NFTs Will Be Worthless, COINBASE Founder Warns...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/06/coinbase-cofounder-warn-nfts-worthless-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You could say the same thing about early internet companies in the late ’90s.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Woke' university doctors call for new laws to protect animals -- from hate speech!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3105534/hate-speech-law-for-animals/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW laws are being proposed by two university doctors to protect animals — from hate speech. A barmy research paper suggests anti-animal language should be banned. It says “speciesist” hate speech …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zookeeper mauled to death by tiger after electric fence switched off...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3104115/zookeeper-mauled-to-death-by-siberian-tiger/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BELOVED zookeeper was mauled to death by a Siberian tiger after an electric fence was turned off at a predator park in South Africa. David Solomon, 52, was bitten several times and had his neck s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT03/refresh/AL032021_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/151141_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan and Mexico have earthquake early-warning systems. How does United States compare?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/japan-and-mexico-have-earthquake-early-warning-systems-how-does-californias-compare/ar-AAKYjrM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan has a sophisticated system to alert its residents, and Mexico City has ubiquitous sirens. Is California's early warning system ready?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Refusing to Open U.S. Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/trudeau-resists-business-pressure-to-open-us-border-for-summer/ar-AALbTpd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Non-essential travel between the U.S. and Canada will be banned for another month despite mounting pressure from businesses to ease Covid-19 travel restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man survives dramatic assassination attempt on streets of NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/video-man-escapes-assassination-attempt-in-brooklyn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING VIDEO: Men in two vehicles attempted to carry out what appears to be a coordinated assassination attempt on the streets of Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Gulf Coast braces for Tropical Storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/gulf-coast-braces-for-tropical-storm-claudette-rain/964923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters say Tropical Storm Claudette is likely to develop, and it is rated a 1 on the AccuWeather RealImpact Scale due to projected flooding rainfall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  AMERICANS SHARPLY DIVIDED ON POST-PANDEMIC LIFE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-lifestyle-coronavirus-pandemic-health-ddfd165dd67e9ec79d4850a1d80734e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — Many Americans are relaxing precautions taken during the COVID-19 pandemic and resuming everyday activities, even as some worry that coronavirus-related restrictions were hastily lifted, a new poll shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUNETEENTH, 2021</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/black-americans-laud-juneteenth-holiday-but-more-work-ahead-0f88c732156486bf648041813f60c7e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Black Americans rejoiced after President Joe Biden made Juneteenth a federal holiday, but some said that, while they appreciated the recognition at a time of racial reckoning in America, more is needed to change policies that disadvantage too many of their brethren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORST DROUGHT IN 1,200 YEARS?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jun/18/us-heatwave-west-climate-crisis-drought</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers had long forewarned of this crisis and now they’re seeing their studies and models become real life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can AI predict how sick you'll get?</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/can-artificial-intelligence-predict-how-sick-youll-get-from-covid-19-scientists-think-so/article_6f2b81df-ab45-5012-839e-b674313e1049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — A team of San Diego scientists is harnessing artificial intelligence to understand why COVID-19 symptoms can vary dramatically from one person to the next — information that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans with ASTRA jab won't get into Springsteen show...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/18/springsteen-on-broadway-to-deny-guests-with-astrazeneca-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Springsteen on Broadway” has a lengthy Q&amp;A page detailing the vaccination protocols in place — including a mandate that all guests must be fully vaccinated with an FDA-approved sho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine experts having second thoughts about rushing to inoculate kids...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vaccine-experts-having-second-thoughts-100022396.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing contingent of medical experts is questioning the conventional wisdom that healthy children should get COVID-19 shots as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Streaming Platforms Crashing Before Popular Finales?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/hbo-max-mare-of-easttown-disney-plus-wandavision-showtime-logan-paul-floyd-mayweather-streaming-outages-1234969382/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you were on Twitter on the night of May 30, also known as the Mare of Easttown finale night, you may have believed that HBO Max failed at its one job. Dozens and dozens of viewers who were anxio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight Housing Market Uncoils With Sellers Ready To Cash Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.fa-mag.com/news/tight-u-s--housing-market-uncoils-with-sellers-ready-to-cash-out-62690.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fa-mag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the housing market is still a long way from normal, with inventory still down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong newspaper prints 500,000 copies in face of crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/559120-hong-kong-newspaper-prints-500000-copies-in-face-of-chinese-crackdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong newspaper Apple Daily printed 500,000 copies on Friday, five times more than usual, a day after Chinese authorities arrested five editors and executives for allegedly conspiring with foreign governments to endanger national security, acc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON Militia of Ex-Cops, Soldiers Training 'Patriots' for Revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avnxn/qanon-militia-of-ex-cops-and-soldiers-is-training-patriots-for-revolution</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 1st Amendment Praetorians, founded by a QAnon believer, are providing free security for “patriotic and religious events across the country.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side of Fitness Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/06/apple-physical-hot-vax-summer/619249/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Apple+ series 'Physical' is a reminder that making people hate their body is a thriving pillar of American commerce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daredevil dies attempting record-setting motorcycle jump...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/daredevil-dies-while-attempting-record-setting-motorcycle-jump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tragic incident unfolded at the Moses Lake Airshow. Alex Harvill was attempting to fly over 350 feet and break the Guinness World Record for longest distance jumped from a ramp on a motorcycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They All F*cking Hate Me!' Trump Ranted About 'The Blacks' After George Floyd Response...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/they-all-fcking-hate-me-trump-ranted-about-the-blacks-after-his-response-to-george-floyd-unrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then-President Donald Trump regretted not taking a harder line against protesters in the wake of the late George Floyd’s death, lamenting that “the Blacks” hated him and would never vote for him anyway. According to Wall Street Journal reporter Mike Bender’s upcoming book “Frankly, We Did Win This Election: The Inside Story of How Trump […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone Network Encryption Deliberately Weakened?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avnan/bombshell-report-finds-phone-network-encryption-was-deliberately-weakened</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new paper shows that two old encryption algorithms still used in mobile networks can be exploited to spy on phones' internet traffic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF Americans Fear They'll Never Fully Recover From Pandemic Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/half-americans-will-never-recover-pandemic-stress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average American feels they would need 10 days completely alone in their ideal location to completely de-stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE searches for new measure of skin tones to curb bias in products...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/sustainable-business/exclusive-google-searches-new-measure-skin-tones-curb-bias-products-2021-06-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet Inc's (GOOGL.O) Google told Reuters this week it is developing an alternative to the industry standard method for classifying skin tones, which a growing chorus of technology researchers and dermatologists says is inadequate for assessing whether products are biased against people of color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thirty TESLA crashes linked to assisted driving system under investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jun/18/thirty-tesla-crashes-linked-to-assisted-driving-system-under-investigation-in-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Auto regulators have opened probes into crashes involving 10 deaths where the company’s Autopilot system was in use</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'Biden Republicans' Took Over Suburbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/06/18/biden-republican-voters-oakland-county-michigan-suburbs-494983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican collapse in Michigan’s Oakland County, once a stronghold, was a long time coming. Is losing these suburbs a warning light for Trumpism?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car thefts highest in decade as prices surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/18/with-car-prices-surging-yours-is-a-prime-target-for-thieves-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has helped fuel the biggest jump in auto thefts in more than a decade, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6-3 bench? It's actually 3-3-3...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/18/politics/roberts-kavanaugh-barrett-supreme-court/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts, along with Justices Amy Coney Barrett and Brett Kavanaugh, demonstrated their collective power at America's highest court on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Gaetz investigation ramps up, feds mount sweeping probe into FL political scene...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/gaetz-investigation-ramps-feds-mount-sweeping-probe-central/story?id=78321551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal probe into sex trafficking allegations involving GOP Rep. Matt Gaetz has engulfed the tight-knit Central Florida political scene, sources tell ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School probes use of markers to ID unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.seacoastonline.com/story/news/education/2021/06/16/hand-markings-at-prom-unvaccinated-nh-school-probe-call-for-calm-not-who-we-are/5295729001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seacoastonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students were marked with Sharpie to designate COVID vaccine status at Exeter High's prom. “Not a good look” in hindsight, SAU 16 Superintendent says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear goes on rampage; Storms military base, airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/bear-goes-on-rampage-in-japan-storms-military-base-airport/ar-AALarmM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bear injured four people, and caused schools to close and flights to be canceled, before it was eventually shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin blames 'nihilism' as Moscow sees record infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210618095328-gczn1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RUSSIA-CASES (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Kremlin blames 'nihilism' as Moscow sees record COVID-19 infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There's no water,' says farm manager forced to leave fields fallow...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210618084953-8venz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DROUGHT/CALIFORNIA-FARMER (TV, PIX):'There's no water,' says California farm manager forced to leave fields fallow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam introduces nationwide code of conduct for social media...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210618040727-kltxd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Social media users are encouraged to promote the beauty of Vietnam's scenery, people and culture, and spread good stories about good people," reads the code</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hydroelectric plant expected to shut down first time in 50 years!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/17/us/california-drought-oroville-power/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Water in a key California reservoir will fall so low this summer that its hydroelectric power plant will be forced to shut down for the first time, officials said Thursday, straining the state's already-taxed electric grid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Athletes Get Ready to Score Some Serious Cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-18/college-athletes-get-ready-to-score-some-serious-cash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six states will allow student players to profit from the use of their likeness starting on July 1—and the NCAA isn’t pleased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Money: Autocrats Use London to Strike Foes Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/18/the-power-of-money-how-autocrats-use-london-to-strike-foes-worldwide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Olena Tyshchenko, a lawyer based in Britain, was facing years in a crowded Russian prison cell, when a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/nm60344372/executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.8 Mag Earthquake Rattles Indiana, Felt In Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/06/17/indiana-earthquake-bloomingdale-felt-chicago-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 3.8 earthquake was reported Thursday afternoon in western Indiana, with some people more than 150 miles away reporting they felt the tremor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It used to feel that life hung in balance during US-Russia summits. No longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/jun/17/us-russia-summit-china-biden-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of China puts any decisions made at Biden’s meeting with Putin into perspective, says Guardian columnist Martin Kettle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE INCREASES TO DROP MASK MANDATE ON PLANES...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/06/17/senators-running-out-of-patience-on-mask-mandate-for-travelers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican senators expressed mounting impatience with the federal mask mandate for travelers as restrictions are lifted elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTORIA'S SECRET ditches supermodels and replaces them with 'diverse high-achievers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3101328/victorias-secret-megan-rapinoe-priyanka-chopra-catwalk-angels-models/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VICTORIA’S Secret has announced it is ditching its “Angels” supermodels to redefine sexy with “diverse high-achievers” like Megan Rapinoe. The lingerie brand announced…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook claims GOOGLE Android system littered with bad, dangerous software...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3102068/android-worse-dangerous-iphone-apple-boss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE boss Tim Cook has made a subtle dig at Google, claiming that the firm’s Android operating system is littered with dodgy software. In an interview yesterday, the 60-year-old said that An…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines pressure for less restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/fully-vaccinated-people-uk-could-be-allowed-travel-amber-list-countries-the-2021-06-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain is considering easing travel rules for double vaccinated people, a move that would placate airlines which have launched legal action against the government's curbs on trips abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega-heatwave peaking in West, breaking records and intensifying drought, fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/mega-heat-wave-is-peaking-in-the-west-breaking-records-and-intensifying-drought-fires/ar-AAL9n9s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change has made the situation worse, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic City to use sirens to start nightly curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/atlantic-city-to-use-sirens-mark-10-pm-juvenile-curfew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sirens soon will sound each night in Atlantic City at 10 p.m., marking the arrival of a juvenile curfew prohibiting those under 18 from being on the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Juneteenth, Federal Employees Now Get 44 Paid Days Off Each Year!</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamandrzejewski/2021/06/17/with-juneteenth-federal-employees-now-get-44-paid-days-off-on-average/?sh=2acdecf83477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This makes 44 paid days off for the average federal employee annually, which is nearly nine full weeks of paid-time off each year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK infections climb to highest since Feb...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/uk-coronavirus-infections-4-month-high-34d7d30b-8120-409a-ba96-e4999623ef93.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delta variant continues to spread across the U.K. and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-2 DECISION</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-spares-obamacare-gop-challenge-n1271140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of Trump's three appointees, Brett Kavanaugh and Amy Coney Barrett, joined the majority opinion, while the third, Neil Gorsuch, dissented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Secretly Harboring Top China Official?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/rumors-of-u-s-secretly-harboring-top-china-official-swirl/ar-AAL9Tb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese-language anti-communist media and Twitter are abuzz this week with rumors that a vice minister of State Security, Dong Jingwei defected in mid-February, flying from Hong Kong to the United States with his daughter, Dong Yang. Dong Jingwei supposedly gave the U.S. information about the Wuhan Institute of Virology that changed the stance of the Biden Administration concerning the origins of the COVID-19 pandemic. Dong is, or was, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing launches astronauts to new space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-launches-first-astronauts-to-its-new-space-station-as-race-with-us-heats-up/ar-AAL8h0w </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES KEEP OBAMACARE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/17/obamacare-survives-after-supreme-court-rejects-latest-republican-challenge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court ruled against Texas and other Republican-led states seeking to strike down the Affordable Care Act in its latest high court test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garcia could be first cigarette-smoking winner since '65...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/17/kathryn-garcia-could-be-first-cigarette-smoking-nyc-mayor-since-65/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Sanitation Commissioner and mayoral candidate Kathryn Garcia could be City Hall’s first smoker-in-residence since Mayor Robert Wagner left office in 1965.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEARS Eyeing Move Out Of Chicago?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/bears-eyeing-possible-move-out-of-downtown-chicago-to-suburb-that-sits-35-miles-away-from-soldier-field/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bears could be leaving Soldier Field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Gaza after Hamas fires incendiary balloons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/west-bank-israel-middle-east-health-3619c2694df63cc92bdec9cce2e69493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel launched airstrikes on the Gaza Strip late Thursday for a second time since a shaky cease-fire ended last month's 11-day war. The strikes came after activists mobilized by Gaza's militant Hamas rulers launched incendiary balloons into Israel for a third straight day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis gun-waving couple plead guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/st-louis-gun-waving-couple-plead-guilty-to-misdemeanor-charges/article_5b02e25b-0034-58a3-8181-f0a724ffa323.html#tracking-source=home-top-story-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark McCloskey on Thursday pleaded guilty to fourth-degree assault. Patricia McCloskey pleaded to second-degree harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists still puzzling over deaths of DC birds...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2021/06/scientists-still-puzzling-over-deaths-of-birds-in-dc-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ornithologist at the Smithsonian said that experts are still trying to figure out what’s behind a “mortality event” that’s been plaguing birds in the D.C. area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  MSNBC WON'T RECOGNIZE NEW UNION...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/559028-msnbc-says-it-wont-voluntarily-recognize-new-union-effort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 200-plus MSNBC workers are forming a union, but the network, known for its progressive politics, said it won’t recognize the effort until a majority of workers vote in a secret ballot election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops resign en masse from Portland crowd control unit...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/crime/2021/06/officers-sergeants-with-portlands-rapid-response-team-resign-from-the-specialized-crowd-control-unit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers who serve on the Portland Police Bureau’s specialized crowd control unit, known as the Rapid Response Team, voted to resign from the team during a meeting Wednesday night, a police lieutenant and the mayor's office confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOUND:  New fossils of largest land mammals ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/new-fossils-giant-rhinos-largest-land-mammals-ever-are-found-china-rcna1213</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fossils from two giant rhinos dating back about 22 million years have been unearthed in China, according to a study published Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Campaign Trail With Andrew Giuliani...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/andrew-giuliani-new-york-governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Son of Rudy is working out his father issues on the road to Albany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian ships once believed to be headed toward Venezuela change course...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/17/iran-ships-venezuela-495013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People familiar with the matter believe diplomatic efforts may have made a difference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform could soon track troops' body signals -- and tell if sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/06/17/your-uniform-could-soon-track-your-bodys-signals-and-tell-you-if-youre-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who collected hospital's bodies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wasnt-just-anyone-collected-bodies-120029485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man collecting the Loma Linda hospital's COVID victims was all but invisible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race-Based Bailouts In Stimulus Face Legal Setbacks...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/courts/race-based-bailouts-in-covid-stimulus-bill-face-legal-setbacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative legal groups are challenging the racially driven repayment programs Democrats included in their $1.9 trillion coronavirus relief act.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
