<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD:  Progressives are the modern Puritans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/spare-me-the-purity-racket/ar-AAEWOe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clown starts violent brawl on cruise ship as passengers use plates for weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-clown-violent-brawl-cruise-18785703</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Families feared for their lives as chaos erupted on the P&amp;O Britannia cruise following a boozy patriotic party where large amounts of alcohol were consumed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:  47% WANT IMPEACHMENT!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/buried-bombshell-fox-news-poll-shows-only-45-percent-of-americans-oppose-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Democrats inch slightly closer to impeaching President Donald Trump, a new Fox News poll shows that Americans who impose impeachment are distinctly in the minority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak unstoppable as victims refuse treatment fearing govt 'behind disease'...	</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/794395/ebola-outbreak-unstoppable-victims-refuse-treatment-government-conspiracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXELROD:  If Trump loses, this will be why...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/455010-david-axelrod-slams-trump-attacks-on-cummings-baltimore-if-he-loses-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN political commentator and Democratic strategist David Axelrod slammed President Trump's attack on Rep. Elijah Cummings (D-Md.), arguing the president's "stream of ugly, divisive bombast" could threaten his reelection chances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN anchor chokes up on air...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/27/cnn-anchor-victor-blackwell-chokes-up-on-air-after-trump-rips-infested-baltimore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN anchor Victor Blackwell got choked up on air Saturday after President Trump ripped Rep. Elijah Cummings and the city, calling it “a disgusting, rat and rodent infested mess.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/outrage-trump-brands-mostly-black-baltimore-infested-mess-172645866.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump&amp;#39;s outburst came in a series of sharply worded tweets aimed at Democratic Representative Elijah Cummings -- a high-profile critic of Trump&amp;#39;s administration whose district covers much of Baltimore. &amp;quot;No human being would want to live there,&amp;quot; he said -- in an attack ostensibly provoked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 hopefuls take aim...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/27/democratic-candidates-take-aim-at-donald-trump-ove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump drew the ire of potential 2020 rivals Saturday for ranting on Twitter about Baltimore and Rep. Elijah Cummings, Maryland Democrat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama shares op-ed criticizing President Trump's 'poisoning of our democracy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Barack-Obama-shares-op-ed-criticizing-President-14190447.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama, who doesn't often comment on current politics, seemed to endorse on Saturday an op-ed written by 148 African Americans who served in his administration that called out President Donald Trump for recent comments degrading four congresswomen of color.  "I've always been proud of what this team accomplished during my administration. But more than what we did, I'm proud of how they're continuing to fight for an America that's better," Obama tweeted with a link to the op-ed published Friday evening in The Washington Post.  Under the headline, "We are African Americans, we are patriots, and we refuse to sit idly by," the former Obama administration officials vowed to stand up against the "racism, sexism, homophobia and xenophobia . . . wielded by the president and any elected official complicit in the poisoning of our democracy."  "There is truly nothing more un-American than calling on fellow citizens to leave our country - by citing their immigrant roots, or ancestry, or their unwillingness to sit in quiet obedience while democracy is being undermined," they wrote.  After Trump tweeted that four minority lawmakers should "go back" to the places they were from and a crowd of Trump supporters chanted "Send her back!" at the mention of Rep. Ilhan Omar, R-Minn., a Somali refugee who became a U.S. citizen in 2000, at a campaign rally, most Democrats became indignant.  Even former first lady Michelle Obama, who also shies away from Trump-era outrage, made known her disdain for Trump's comments.  "What truly makes our country great is its diversity," Michelle Obama tweeted, an apparent reference to Trump's campaign slogan. "I've seen that beauty in so many ways over the years. Whether we are born here or seek refuge here, there's a place for us all. We...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor slams 'unacceptable' comments...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/455019-baltimore-mayor-slams-unacceptable-trump-comments-on-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore Mayor Bernard "Jack" Young (D) blasted President Trump's comments about his city and Rep. Elijah Cummings (D-Md.) on Saturday, calling the president a "disappointment to the people of Baltimore."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racial tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d49bd171f9b4245b3d24e62a77ad35f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President tells black lawmaker to clean up 'disgusting' district...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190727165259-hatmv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/CUMMINGS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Trump tells black lawmaker to clean up 'disgusting, rat and rodent infested' district</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside San Fran's high stakes underground dice scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/local/article/San-Francisco-underground-dice-scene-exposed-14188244.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're considering playing bar dice for the first time, bartender John Mattiassi of Shanghai Kelly's has some advice: don't start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RODENT INFESTED MESS'</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/politics/bs-md-pol-cummings-trump-20190727-chty2yovtvfzfcjkeaui7wm5zi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump took to Twitter on Saturday morning to demand an investigation into Maryland’s 7th congressional district in a series of tweets criticizing U.S. Rep. Elijah Cummings of Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: BALTIMORE 'FAR WORSE' THAN BORDER</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/454995-trump-slams-cummings-as-a-brutal-bully-claims-baltimore-district-far</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump slammed House Oversight Committee Chairman Elijah Cummings (D-Md.) on Twitter early Saturday as a “brutal bully,” claiming the longtime congressman's Baltimore district is “far worse” and "more dangerous"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL star blames fertility treatment for failing substance abuse test...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/27/golden-tate-suspended-as-giants-receiver-hell-worsens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The situation is going from bad to worse to almost disastrous for the Giants and what now must be considered an ill-fated wide receiver situation. Golden Tate, their free agent acquisition brought …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, Guatemala sign agreement to restrict asylum cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/23f6b9a087e841188c5484cd5cf04f3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sale of Manson murder house stirs LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jul/27/los-angeles-charles-manson-family-labianca-house-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghost Adventures’ Zak Bagans is buying the $1.98m house with ‘very, very strong energy’ where Charles Manson’s followers killed Leno and Rosemary LaBianca in 1969</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pork prices rise as sweltering summer leads to skinny pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/jul/27/pork-prices-farming-economics-business-pigs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farmers say they have more slender summer herd to sell after overweight and numerous pigs in spring led to lowest prices in a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if we're no longer afraid of Ebola?</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/07/25/what-if-no-longer-afraid-ebola/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Historically, Ebola epidemics have been major news. The latest one has not been‚ and I worry that I might know the reason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police fire tear gas, rubber bullets in Hong Kong clash over banned march...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-extradition-protests/police-fire-tear-gas-rubber-bullets-in-hong-kong-clash-over-banned-march-idUSKCN1UM040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police fired tear gas and rubber bullets while protesters hurled rocks during cl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelical Megachurch Sued for $1+ Million in Child Sex Abuse Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-evangelical-megachurch-is-sued-for-more-than-dollar1-million-in-child-sexual-abuse-case/ar-AAEUYCB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordic sizzles...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190727-nordic-countries-sizzle-european-heatwave-moves-north</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nordic countries sizzle as European heatwave moves north</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US lawmaker 'concerned' over reported sightings by Navy pilots...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/rep-walker-tells-tucker-carlson-hes-concerned-over-reports-of-ufo-sightings-by-navy-pilots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Mark Walker, R-N.C., told Fox News Friday that he is "concerned" about recent reports by U.S. Navy pilots of encounters with unidentified aircraft that some have speculated could be otherworldly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger 'dressed as clown' cruise ship sparks brawl...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/passenger-dressed-as-clown-sparks-brawl-on-po-cruise-ship-11771670</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six people, including three men and three women, were assaulted and injuries included significant bruising and cuts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest hundreds at Moscow election protest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dfcfbfe2381c4d5394df2cfa407dff7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa's booming cities face severe toilet crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c225ff70420846489892ea206ecca6d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New prosthetic hand allows users to feel again...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/07/27/scientists-have-developed-bionic-hand-can-help-users-feel-again/1827828001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have developed a prosthetic hand that will allowÂ patients to have the sense of touch again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antiques Road Show: Real State of Military...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/07/real-state-us-military/594754/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wars of the future may depend not so much on the kinds of things you can put on parade, but on new technologies that reimagine warfare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 dead tigers found in car...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190726-seven-dead-tigers-found-car-vietnam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven dead tigers found in car in Vietnam</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden looks 'frail,' Obama's former doctor says...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/obamas-former-doctor-thinks-biden-looks-frail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doctor who served former President Obama for more than 20 years before his presidency said this week he thought former Vice President Joe Biden "looked frail" during the first Democratic debate in Miami, when he was attacked by Sen. Kamala Harris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite calls to start over, US health system covers 90%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4770e9dfbede42999dbe48b03476d3b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should Rich Be Allowed to Buy the Best Genes?</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2019-7-27/should-the-rich-be-allowed-to-buy-the-best-genes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Walter Isaacson - QUEbec CityBiology is the new tech. I'm at a conference in Quebec City on CRISPR, the molecular tool designed to edit genes, and it has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDakota to require 'In God We Trust' signs at public schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/south-dakota-will-require-in-god-we-trust-signs-in-all-public-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When students return to public schools in the state this fall, they'll see a new message on display: "In God We Trust"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump uncorks French wine threat in digital tax retaliation...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/trump-uncorks-french-wine-threat-digital-tax-retaliation-200823687--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump vowed "substantial" retaliation against France on Friday for a tax targeting US tech giants, threatening to slap tariffs on French wine and blasting President Emmanuel Macron's "foolishness."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
