<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS cancels all international flights until March next year...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8520077/Forget-overseas-holiday-Qantas-pulls-international-flights-MARCH-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's national carrier has removed international inventory until March 28, 2021. Flights to New Zealand are now unavailable until further notice due to the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida governor DeSantis heckled... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8519311/People-dying-doing-Florida-governor-heckled-press-conference.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ron DeSantis, the Republican governor of Florida, was heckled by activist Thomas Kennedy on Monday afternoon in Miami. 'More than 4,000 people have died, and you are doing nothing!'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FOXNEWS Tucker to Take Vacation Amid Staffer Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fa409bc29a3dd7b8ff933c2e375287f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fox News' Tucker Carlson said Monday that his former writer who posted racist comments online was wrong but criticized “ghouls now beating their chests in triumph” after his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says Prosecutors Were 'Sadistic, Arrogant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/07/13/roger_stone_talks_commutation_muellers_dirty_cops_prosecutors_were_sadistic_arrogant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone appeared on Sean Hannity's FOX News program for his first interview following President Trump's decision to commute his sentence. Stone talked about how his faith guided him and his take on the probe led by then-special counsel Robert Mueller. Transcript, via FOX News below. "Well, this is the most horrible experience you can have because I see immediately why 99 percent of the people who choose to plead not guilty and go to trial lose, when you're up against the horrific and deep-pocketed resources of the federal government and these really sadistic, arrogant, politically motivated prosecutors," Stone said. "And I had a biased judge. I had a stacked jury. I had a corrupt jury forewoman. As my friend Tucker Carlson said, my trial was over before it started. And now when you go through something like this, Sean, you find out who your real friends are and who the people are who really never were your friends. You had been a tremendous friend. You have done a great job of keeping people informed." SEAN HANNITY, FOX NEWS HOST: As we told you, President Trump announced Friday he was commuting the sentence of Roger Stone. Just days before, Stone was set to start a three-plus-year prison sentence stemming from Robert Mueller's Russian witch hunt.  Remember, Stone was convicted of process crimes relating to 2017, and statements he made to House lawmakers. In other words, lying before Congress. Huh. Adam Schiff presiding, the biggest liar in Congress.  Now, neither the Schiff show nor Robert Mueller produced one bit of evidence that Stone was working with anybody colluding with Russia. And, by the way, as a White House press secretary explained, quote: these charges were the product of recklessness born of frustration and malice.  Joining us now, Roger Stone, first TV interview and his attorney, David Schoen.  I would like to say to you, Roger, well, I'm glad you had your sentence commuted and you are not headed to prison this week. There's a part of me that is also very angry and very concerned for the country based on the entire handling of your matter.  Why don't I just let you say it in your own words what this has been like for you?  ROGER STONE, FORMER TRUMP CAMPAIGN AIDE: Well, this is the most horrible experience you can have because I see immediately why 99 percent of the people who choose to plead not guilty and go to trial lose, when you're up against the horrific and deep-pocketed resources of the federal government and these really sadistic, arrogant, politically motivated prosecutors.  And I had a biased judge. I had a stacked jury. I had a corrupt jury forewoman. As my friend Tucker Carlson said, my trial was over before it started.  And now when you go through something like this, Sean, you find out who your real friends are and who the people are who really never were your friends. You had been a tremendous friend. You have done a great job of keeping people informed.  But I have to really single out your FOX News colleague, Tucker Carlson. He took up the cudgels early. He stayed on this case with every twist and turn, wasn't afraid to take on the judge, laid out the jury question, encouraged me when I got discouraged.  He's a man of incredible loyalty and he's a great friend. He may be the best friend a man can have. So my hats off to him.  And also Congressman Matt Gaetz from Florida who I hope to live long enough to see in the White House. He was a great friend who never gave up and tried to make sure everybody understood the injustice that I had been through.  But so many others, Bernie Kerik, the former New York police commissioner, and Charlie Kirk, Reverend Franklin Graham, Pastors Mark Burns and Darrell Scott, you know, Randy Coggins, dynamic young evangelist from Florida, the entire Flynn family, General Mike Flynn, a man who is still being persecuted.  My hats off to all of them because they helped me and my wife and my family through the scariest, most difficult process you can imagine.  But above all, I must tell you, Sean, based on advice from you and Reverend Graham and the two pastors I mentioned, I really want to thank God because I was literally hours away from being sent to a COVID-infested prison in violation of current Bureau of Prisons and DOJ policies, in violation of every precedent in the country where people going to jail or in jail were asking for compassionate release, and in every case, it was granted.  I am 67 years old. I've had a lifelong problem of respiratory problems. I was facing what I really believed was a near-death sentence.  So you --  HANNITY: Let me --  STONE: -- particularly Tucker, Matt Gaetz and everybody I named, my heart goes out to you. I'm deeply, deeply grateful.  But more than anything else, I am grateful for God because as you told me, if I would -- if I would rededicate my life to Christ, if I would be reborn --  HANNITY: My first e-mail to you, I remember writing it.  (CROSSTALK)  STONE: -- I can remember it like it was yesterday. And your advice was as solid as can be. You said, God will never desert you. He will never abandon you. He will protect you if you -- if you confess your sins and you walk in his way. And I have done my very best to do that.  HANNITY: Let me go through and I want you to tell people, because this -- there's this whole system of justice where, you can use Sammy "The Bull" Gravano as the biggest case in point, he commits 19 murders and he's given a get-out-of-jail-free card and a witness protection program because he flipped on John Gotti.  All right, put that aside for a second. In your case, did Mueller and his team offer anything of value, your freedom for example, I would argue is of great value, if you would say certain things they wanted you to say whether they were true or not?  STONE: Well, in the beginning of the case, Sean, I don't think that was their intention. But as they got closer and closer to having to issue the Mueller Report and they realized that they had no Russian collusion because there was no Russian collusion, it was a hoax -- on July 24th, Jeannie Rhee, who was heading my prosecution within the Mueller team, that's extraordinary in itself because she previously represented Hillary Clinton and the Clinton Foundation in the illegal e-mail server case, and the missing e-mail case.  So, she had a clear bias. She was a maximum donor to both of Hillary's presidential campaigns. By the way, she has all the charm of a North Korean prison guard.  She made it very clear to one of my lawyers after a hearing, she asked to see them privately, that if I would re-remember certain phone conversations I had with candidate Trump, if I would come clean, if I would confess, that they -- that they might be willing to, you know, recommend leniency to the judge. Perhaps I wouldn't even serve any jail time.  And I didn't have to think about it very long. I said absolutely not. There was no circumstance under which I would bear false witness against the president. I was -- I was just not willing to lie.  Now, in the last two days when I said that, people said you see Stone had the goods on Trump and he traded his silence for -- for commutation. That is patently false. I never said that. I never implied that.  What I said has been consistent, that I would not lie against my friend of 40 years so they could use it for impeachment. They wanted me to be the ham in their ham sandwich because they knew the Mueller Report, particularly on Russia, was a dud. It was a goose egg. They had nothing.  And they were hoping that I would re-characterize my phone calls. I think these phone calls that were plea-bargain-induced claims by Michael Cohen and Rick Gates for which they could never find any corroboration, and I simply refused to do it.  HANNITY: Let me go to you, David Schoen, and I'll ask you both the same question simultaneously.  Roger, I think I've known you well enough over the years. You're a fighter. Your instincts are going to be, OK, now, I'm going to go back and I'm -- maybe if you go back and you appeal this and you open up this case again, I would -- I would argue right now, you're home free.  And I think that I saw nothing but corruption in that courtroom by that judge and that jury they not giving you another trial.  David, I would say that if you go forward with that, you're now putting Roger's life back in jeopardy again. And I don't know --  DAVID SCHOEN, CRIMINAL DEFENSE LAWYER: You're right --  HANNITY: I don't have any faith in that system. I don't have any faith in that judge. I don't have any faith with that jury.  Nobody on this case do I believe is honorable here.  SCHOEN: Yes, I think you're right. You raise a very interesting question and a perplexing one. We have to sit down and make a decision as to whether to go forward with the appeal, knowing that a win in this case and there should be a win, classic Fifth and Sixth Amendment violations, would go right back to the same judge in a courtroom of injustice.  Let me just say this to you, this commutation is a great tribute to President Trump for three reasons. He sends the message that the Mueller team was rotten to the core from its inception. And Mr. Mueller picked Andrew Weissmann as his --  (CROSSTALK)  HANNITY: I've been saying that for over three years, David. Screaming it.  SCHOEN: Well, you're right. You don't pick -- an investigation that involves the president of the United States requires integrity. You don't pick -- and Andrew Weissmann was the most ethically bankrupt prosecutor I've ever come across. I represent two men right now, Mr. Orena and Mr. Sessa, who were wrongfully convicted with him.  You talked about making deals with witnesses. He lied about those deals. He was mentioned specifically by a judge for his misconduct. So, that's one thing. The Mueller team was rotten to the core, filled with partisans.  Number two, an unfair trial. The president recognized that. The judge denied the entire defense theory.  Mr. Stone wasn't allowed to mention on social media or make a defense theory that in any way challenge the integrity of the Mueller team. Unprecedented.  And, thirdly, the president saved a life here because the judge's decision on denying a surrender extension when COVID was in the prisons and with these health conditions goes against all authority in the country on this issue as to the Court of Appeals.  HANNITY: You know, I'm listening to your attorney and I've known David a long time, Roger. I've known you a long time. And you're a character. Everyone knows you're a character.  But that's not about you as a character. I would want a fair and impartial jury for everybody. I wouldn't want any Democrat or liberal to have 29 guys in tactical gear over a process crime. I wouldn't want a gag order on any American that should have a right to speak out in their own defense. I wouldn't want a jury foreperson that's prejudiced or a judge that went along with this crap.  My question to you is, we've seen this now with Papadopoulos. We've now seen this with Paul Manafort. We saw it with General Flynn. We've seen it with you.  I'll be honest, Roger. I believe in our Constitution. I believe in our rule of law. I think I read a lot about equal justice and application of our laws. I don't see any of this in any of these cases.  I see a travesty of injustice. You've been a part of it. I don't know. I'm losing faith in the system, Roger.  STONE: Well, you -- it's -- you have a good reason to.  I mean, you examine the D.C. Circuit Court of Appeals, where I had to file a last-minute emergency appeal of Judge Jackson's rule sending me to jail. She ignored all the legal precedents in that. She ignored my health conditions. She ignored the conditions at the prison at that time. And she ignored the current policies of DOJ and the BOP.  Now, you would have thought that that would been reversed in the appeals court. But they ruled for her 3-0. I'm afraid. I -- this is a fixed system.  Above all, though, I guess I would have to say the most important thing here is the courageousness of the president's act. I know there were many, many, many people who told him, in an election year, don't do this. Let Roger Stone wait maybe for a pardon after the election.  Sean, I don't think I would have lived that long, not with my asthmatic condition, not with now 60 COVID-19 cases in that prison. So, I have deep, deep affection for Donald Trump, because I have known him 40 years.  He's a man of great justice and fairness. He's a man of enormous courage. I knew he would take some shots for this. But I think most people, most fair-minded people, understand he saved my life. And, at least on paper, he gave me a chance to fight for vindication.  Now, I'm not a fool. I'm going to be -- I'm going to be guided by the advice of my lawyers. As I understand it, if I -- my conviction is overturned by the appeals court, I would be back in front of Judge Jackson.  Judge Jackson issued an incredible ruling that said that I could not raise misconduct by the special counsel, the FBI, the DOJ, or any member of Congress, Adam Schiff.  So, I mean, if that were in place in General Flynn's case, we still wouldn't know how he was railroaded. We still wouldn't know about the political motivations behind taking him down.  So, I have got to become convinced I can get a fair second trial, because I certainly didn't get a fair first trial.  HANNITY: You had a gag order, and you weren't allowed to even put on your defense. You wanted to put on a defense. They denied you that right.  Then, of course, we have the whole jury foreperson. This is on top of the raid, predawn raid.  By the way, I am sure you probably called CNN, Roger, and said that.  Here is -- I do not believe you can get any fair trial in that courtroom or that system. I don't know. I think that probably every fiber of your being would want to be to fight to get the acquittal you believe you should get.  But I don't know if I would give you that advice, because I don't think there's anybody in that courtroom that is fair, Roger.  STONE: Well, and, as you point out, Comey, Clapper, Brennan, McCabe, Strzok --  HANNITY: Strzok, Page.  STONE: -- Page, Rosenstein, Mueller himself, Hillary, they all lied under oath.  But they lied about material things, consequential things. Therefore, they had an intent and a motive to lie. I was charged with making misstatements that were innocuous.  And if you look at it very carefully, it's very clear what happened here. And that is that Aaron Zelinsky, the corrupt prosecutor, the dirtiest of Mueller's dirty cops, other than Weissmann, shared the fruits of the surveillance into me with Adam Schiff, so that he could fashion gotcha questions, most of them of no consequence.  And then after the setup, in which I appeared voluntarily before the House Intelligence Committee, Schiff, in violation of House rules, shared the classified testimony with Mr. Zelinsky, so Mr. Weissmann could fashion a very contorted and contrived indictment.  Yet, today, you have Mueller and Schiff and Rosenstein back to saying, Stone was in cahoots with Russian intelligence.  This is nonsense. They are all the way back to the Russia, Russia, Russia lie. They know it's false, but they keep --  (CROSSTALK)  HANNITY: Was there ever any evidence of that, Roger? There was not.  Was there any evidence ever --  STONE: No.  HANNITY: -- given of any contact with any Russian intelligence that you --  (CROSSTALK)  STONE: Here's what there was.  There -- there was -- there was evidence that I had a Twitter direct message exchange with Guccifer 0.2 (sic), a persona. But if you look at when that happened, it happened long after WikiLeaks had published all their material.  HANNITY: Right.  STONE: And if you look at the actual content of the exchange, it's benign. There is no collusion. There's no collaboration.  And, thirdly, we don't even know that Guccifer 2.0 is a Russian agent. Just because John Brennan says something's true -- he said the Steele dossier was real, too.  So, just because they assert something doesn't mean it's true. I could have proved at trial, using forensic evidence and expert testimony from fellows like Bill Binney, former SNA (sic) counterintelligence expert, and Ray McGovern, that no one hacked the DNC, that there was no online hack of the DNC, that the information, based on the download times --  HANNITY: Right.  STONE: -- was downloaded to a portable disk and taken out the back door.  But I wasn't allowed to present that defense, because Judge Jackson would not allow it.  HANNITY: Roger, I want to believe in our system of justice.  And, in a way, it worked, I guess, in the end with the president's commutation. But what happened to you, what happened to Papadopoulos, what happened to General Flynn, what happened to Manafort, what happened to the president of the United States, what happened to Carter Page, we are going to lose this country if this happens again.  It's the biggest abuse of power, corruption scandal in our history.  Glad you're free tonight, Roger. We wish you Godspeed.  And, David, think you for the great work you do as his attorney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FOXNEWS Tucker to Take Vacation Amid Staffer Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/tucker-carlson-vacation-fox-news-blake-neff-1234705595/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson, one of Fox News Channel’s most-watched hosts, said he would take a pre-planned vacation as his primetime program comes under intense scrutiny. Carlson announced his plans Monday  in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge demands information on commutation...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/13/judge-demands-information-on-roger-stones-commutation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice on Monday released President Trump’s commutation order for his longtime pal Roger Stone, commuted Stone’s 40-month prison sentence on Friday evening, just days before he w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police levy thousands of fines as Indians chafe at mask... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/police-levy-thousands-fines-indians-chafe-mask-rules-044444368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian police are having a field day handing out fines to people who do not wear a mask during the coronavirus pandemic. New Delhi shared-ride driver Munish Tiwari said he had received two tickets for 500-rupee ($6.50) fines since taxis got back on the road a month ago, which had wiped out a day'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as sailors infected with virus after 35 days at sea... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mystery-argentine-sailors-infected-virus-35-days-sea-035702418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Argentina is trying to solve a medical mystery after 57 sailors were infected with the coronavirus after 35 days at sea, despite the entire crew testing negative before leaving port. The Echizen Maru fishing trawler returned to port after some of its crew began exhibiting symptoms typical of COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro fed up with quarantine, to take new virus test... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-fed-quarantine-virus-test-012124265.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro, who has been in quarantine nearly a week after testing positive for the new coronavirus, announced Monday he plans to take another test as he "can't stand" being in isolation. Since the beginning of the crisis, the far-right president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Shuts Down All Offices...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/los-angeles-near-red-theat-level-coronavirus-hospitalizations-la-county-stats-1202984844/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti said Monday that the city’s COVID-19 threat meter is “on the border of going to red,” the highest level, which would mean a complete shutdown in L.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI COVID CAPITAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article244190287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refrigerated trucks requested in AZ, TX as morgues reach capacity...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/refrigerated-trucks-requested-in-arizona-texas-as-morgues-reach-capacity-amid-covid-19-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With COVID-19 cases surging in many states across the U.S., Texas and Arizona have requested refrigerated trucks in several counties that have nearly reached their morgue capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She had ex-British military as security at hideout...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/crime/2020/07/13/epstein-associate-ghislaine-maxwell-had-ex-british-military-as-security-at-n-h-estate-prosecutors-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the FBI moved on Maxwell at her estate, agents had to break down the door and found her hiding in a room in the interior of the home, according to a new court filing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM star was 'kidnapped' by FBI and now faces money laundering trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1132416/instagram-star-hushpuppi-kidnapped-by-fbi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INSTAGRAM star Ramon Olorunwa Abbas, who went by the name Hushpuppi, was “kidnapped” by the FBI to face a US money laundering trial, according to a claim from his lawyer. Abbas, a 37-ye…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferno on San Diego Navy ship rages into second day...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/military/story/2020-07-13/inferno-on-san-diego-navy-ship-rages-into-second-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smoke and fire smell spreads throughout San Diego area as crews battle flames by air, sea and land</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov't to Expand License Plate Reading Program Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/analytics-data/2020/07/customs-expand-license-plate-reading-program-nationwide/166841/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Federal Spending and Deficit Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-spending-and-deficit-set-records-through-june</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set records for both the amount of money it spent and the deficit it ran in the first nine months of fiscal 2020 (October through June), according to data released today in the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  HIGH HEAT BLAST FOR MOST OF USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/dc-nears-record-hot-streak-as-dozens-of-records-fall-around-us/776334</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immunity may be gone in months...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/507043-virus-immunity-in-recovered-patients-may-be-gone-in-months-researchers-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who have recovered from COVID-19 may lose their immunity to the virus within months, according to research released this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chance of big San Andreas earthquake increasing, study suggests...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chance-big-san-andreas-earthquake-160033233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New odds mean a large quake on the Garlock fault is much more likely and the chance of a large quake on the San Andreas has also increased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men's Rights Activist Shot Dead at California Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mens-rights-activist-marc-angelucci-shot-dead-at-his-california-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawyer was featured in the documentary “The Red Pill.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adulthood interrupted: Millions of Gen Zers move back to parents' homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/living-in-sf/article/Gen-Zers-COVID-moving-home-depression-15399559.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Generation Z is tough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong DISNEYLAND Closes After Spike in Infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/health/hong-kong-disneyland-closes-after-spike-in-regions-coronavirus-infections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The park will shut its gates again on July 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine production to start by end of summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/13/drugmakers-will-start-coronavirus-vaccine-production-by-end-of-summer-trump-health-officials-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Reveals New Face Shield To Protect Players...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/nfl-oakley-reveal-new-face-shield-to-protect-players-from-the-coronavirus-in-2020-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL unveiled a face shield on helmets to help stop the spread of COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Group Brutally Beats Orthdox Man In Broad Dalight, Yell Anti-Semitic Slurs...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/12/police-looking-for-3-men-suspected-of-yelling-anti-semitic-slurs-beating-orthodox-jewish-man-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said the victim was walking home when two unidentified men approached him, started yelling anti-Semitic slurs, pushed him to the ground and punched him repeatedly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  No Charges Against Man Who Put NYPD Officer In Headlock...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/12/nypd-headlock-police-benevolent-association-pat-lynch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cellphone video has surfaced showing an NYPD officer being put in a headlock by a man he was attempting to arrest in the Bronx.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stops, Searches by Minneapolis Cops Plummet...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/number-of-minneapolis-police-stops-searches-plummets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The embattled Minneapolis Police Department has mostly ceased stopping and searching residents of the city, as resources are stretched thin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colo. Town Sets Record High &amp; Record Low -- On Same Day!</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/07/11/same-day-record-high-low-alamosa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same thing happened three days in a row in late August 2002.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Shut Down Order Includes All Offices In 'Non-Critical' Sectors...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/los-angeles-county-coronavirus-officials-say-state-stay-at-home-order-includes-offices-in-l-a-1202984528/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, California Governor Gavin Newsom, citing rising coronavirus numbers, ordered indoor operations for restaurants, movie theaters, wineries, zoos, fitness centers, places of worship, indoor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Eye On Karen Bass for VP...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/07/karen-bass-joe-biden-running-mate/613975/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California representative’s low-key manner and progressive credentials could strengthen Biden’s campaign when he needs it most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jet makes emergency landing after passenger's threat to 'kill everybody'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1132041/alaska-airlines-passenger-kill-everybody-jesus-black-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ALASKA Airlines flight had to make an emergency landing on Saturday night after he allegedly threatened to “kill everybody … unless you accept Jesus was a Black man.” Flight 422 from Seatt…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge throws out Georgia's anti-abortion law...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/federal-judge-throws-out-georgia-anti-abortion-law/WKIkpZp5AUFvP6o43T99FK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Monday struck down Georgia’s anti-abortion law approved by the General Asse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters carrying caribou heart rush Senator's stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/politics/2020/07/12/protesters-carrying-a-caribou-heart-rush-stage-at-dan-sullivan-campaign-event-in-anchorage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five protesters said Sullivan is 'heartless' about Alaska Native issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MORE THAN 100% OVERVALUED'</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/07/tesla-stock-surge-wall-street-analysis-elon-musk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The days of Tesla’s virtually unchallenged dominance may be numbered,” a top analyst warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigated by AMERICAN AIRLINES... </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1131866/ted-cruz-no-mask-american-airlines-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SENATOR Ted Cruz was seen flying without a mask aboard an American Airlines flight — and the airline says they’re investigated what happened. Cruz, a Republican from Texas, was aboard a comme…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches, gyms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2020/07/13/newsom-orders-statewide-shutdown-of-california-indoor-businesses-1300309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hardest hit counties of California will see the toughest constraints, Newsom said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz refuses to wear mask on plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article244188877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California closing indoor restaurants, movie theaters, bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/13/california-to-close-indoor-restaurants-movie-theaters-and-bars-statewide-as-coronavirus-cases-rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom ordered Monday all counties in the state to close indoor operations for a handful of businesses, including restaurants, bars, movie theaters and museums, as Covid-19 cases continue to climb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pub landlord installs electric fence to force social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-cornwall-53389977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonny McFadden says the fence is to remind people about social distancing when they are drinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgruntled AMAZON employee drives car into warehouse doors...</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/news/disgruntled-amazon-employee-drives-car-into-doors-at-warehouse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THORNTON, Colo. (KDVR) — After having a disagreement with his manager, 33-year-old Steven Cohen got into his vehicle and backed into entrance doors at the Amazon warehouse in Thornton around …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside GOOGLE Schmidt's exclusive and secret Montana retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/7/13/21318008/eric-schmidt-yellowstone-club-conference-google</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weekend getaways like these aren’t uncommon. But they are drawing more and more scrutiny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle-aged Americans less healthy than English peers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/13/health/us-uk-health-comparison-scli-intl-gbr/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Middle-aged people in the United States are in worse health than those living in England, and the disparities are larger for low income individuals, according to a new study. This gap could point to why Covid-19 has had a more devastating impact on low income Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Students Won't Return To Classroom In Fall...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/13/lausd-students-wont-return-to-classrooms-in-the-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fall semester will begin Aug. 18. However, it will begin online only, with no students returning to in-person classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent comet sightings are signs of Apocalypse, preacher warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1130902/comet-neowise-asteroid-signs-of-apocalypse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NUTTY preacher has claimed that recent sightings of a bright comet in the night sky suggest the apocalypse is upon us. US crackpot Paul Begley told his 300,000 YouTube subscribers that comet Neow…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight makes emergency landing after passenger threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8517857/Alaska-Airlines-flight-makes-emergency-landing-Seattle-passenger-threatens-kill-everyone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alaska Airlines Flight 422 returned to Seattle-Tacoma Airport in Washington after the 'belligerent' passenger yelled 'die in the name of Jesus' on Saturday's flight to Chicago, Illinois.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German study finds no evidence coronavirus spreads in schools...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/german-study-finds-no-evidence-164704005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schools do not play a major role in spreading the coronavirus, according to the results of a German study released on Monday. The study, the largest carried out on schoolchildren and teachers in Germany, found traces of the virus in fewer than 1 per cent of teachers and children. Scientists from Dresden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As ballots pile up in mail, potential 'nightmare' looms on Election Night...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/ballots-pile-mail-potential-nightmare-looms-election-night/story?id=71719232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential chaos "could make Florida in 2000 look like a garden party."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Era of Free News for FACEBOOKGOOGLE May Soon Be Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/the-era-of-free-news-for-facebook-and-google-may-soon-be-over/ar-BB16FWBE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of England Debating Digital Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bank-of-england-debating-digital-currency-creation-bailey-says/ar-BB16GiiA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus Coming for Rural America...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/coronavirus-is-coming-for-rural-america/ar-BB16GbjY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK HIGHER THAN GOOGLE</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-stock-is-now-pricier-than-shares-of-googles-alphabet-2020-07-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc. undefined shares on Monday rose more than 14%, headed for a record high and trading above shares of Google's parent Alphabet Inc....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27% of tests are positive in Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/arizona-coronavirus-cases-worst-in-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another looming situation facing Arizona is the opening of schools set for next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why Fauci should quit...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/925144/why-fauci-should-quit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would resigning from his government post allow him to do more for public health?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morocco reimposes Tangiers lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/morocco-reimposes-tangiers-lockdown-virus-spike-131326245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Morocco on Monday announced a return to lockdown measures in the northern port city of Tangiers to smother a new outbreak of the novel coronavirus, weeks after easing nationwide restrictions. The city of about a million inhabitants was locked down from Monday at noon local time, with public transport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masks, gloves polluting Europe's rivers ...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-masks-gloves-polluting-europes-rivers-151905813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe's major rivers are littered with surgical masks and medical gloves discarded by people protecting themselves against coronavirus, scientists have reported. The rubbish adds to plastic pollution already clogging the continent's major waterways, research organisation Tara Ocean Foundation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saved Roger thanks Jesus! </title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/nation/religion/believe-it-or-not-roger-stone-finds-jesus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Those who want to scoff, scoff,' the hardball operative, Trump confidante answers skeptics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families of Italy's virus dead seek  justice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df2353ff65f1f7a91abae0e322e7eeec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — It started out as way for grief-struck families to mourn their coronavirus dead online: a Facebook group where relatives who were denied a funeral because of Italy’s stringent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  57 injured in fire aboard ship at Naval Base San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c5e84874680cebcaa2ecd7dfdcc785b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — Firefighters were still battling a blaze Monday on a Navy combat ship that injured at least 57 people and sent smoke billowing over San Diego. The fire began Sunday morning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100 million in hole over taxes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/220e3a6210461a09243568144e70b7b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Johnny Depp accused Amber Heard of hitting him with a “haymaker” punch during an altercation near the end of their volatile marriage, as the star wrapped up testimony in his libel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Rich Call For Covid Tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2020/jul/13/super-rich-call-for-higher-taxes-on-wealthy-to-pay-for-covid-19-recovery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Group of 83 wealthy individuals demands ‘immediate, substantial and permanent’ higher taxes ‘on people like us’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEN X BUST:  DEPP TESTIFIES HE LOST $650 MILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/uk-news/1128782/johnny-depp-amber-heard-champagne-lost-millions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHNNY Depp allegedly grabbed Amber Heard by the hair and chucked a magnum of champagne at her when he discovered he lost $650million. The Hollywood star, 57, is accused of attacking Heard, 34, whe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 In 10 Adults More Tired Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-sleep-coronavirus-more-tired-than-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new survey, six in 10 Americans say their sleep routine during quarantine leaves them feeling more exhausted than usual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DEFIANT AS DEATHS PILE UP</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-promotes-tweet-claiming-cdc-media-democrats-and-doctors-are-all-lying-about-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump started the new work week by retweeting a supporter of his who claims "Everyone is lying" about the coronavirus' seriousness in order to keep the U.S. economy dow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Search Upgrades Make It Harder for Sites to Win Traffic...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2020/07/13/business/tech/google-search-upgrades-make-harder-websites-win-traffic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some web publishers that have historically relied on the internet giant to send users to their sites, the subtle tweaks have siphoned off vital traffic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  BIDEN +5 IN TEXAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/public-health/2020/07/12/joe-biden-builds-lead-over-donald-trump-in-reliably-red-texas-as-voters-sour-on-handling-of-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN — Former Vice President Joe Biden has built a five-point lead over President Donald Trump in Texas as unease over Trump’s handling of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDSKINS Officially Retire Name... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/13/washington-redskins-officially-retire-name-and-logo-after-sponsor-backlash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington's NFL team announced it will no longer be called the team's name it previoulsy held since 1932.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS GET COCKY:  REPEAT OF 2016?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/925170/democrats-are-getting-really-confident-thats-making-biden-pelosi-nervous</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At this point in the 2020 presidential campaign, you would rather be presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden than President Trump. Biden has a lead of 9 percentage points in the polling averages by RealClearPolitics and The Washington Post, and 9.4 points as measured by FiveThirtyEight. He leads Trump, 'in some cases outside the margin of error, in recent polls in the battleground states of Arizona, Florida, Michigan, North Carolina, Pennsylvania, and Wisconsin,' the Post reports. Democratic congressional candidates are also crushing their GOP rivals in online donations, Politico reports, setting off alarm bells among Washington Republicans. In fact, 'Trump's management of this summer's crises has triggered what Democrats detect as a tectonic shift in the political landscape, with party leaders suddenly bullish about not only taking back the White House but also wresting control of the Senate, as well as expanding their House majority,' the Post reports. Former Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe (D) predicted 'there's a tsunami coming.' Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-N.Y.) said 'we're feeling very good' about taking back the Senate. Not everyone thinks this level of confidence is helpful. Ignore the polls. Weâ€™ve got work to do: https://t.co/GCxsKwFY4h https://t.co/fnJezEaAg5 â€” Joe Biden (@JoeBiden) July 12, 2020 House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) told the Post that Democrats have 'one advantage' over 2016: 'People are vigilant, they are attuned, they are concerned.' Trump and his allies will try to suppress Democratic votes, she warned. 'I say: 'Own the ground. Don't give one grain of sand. Get everybody out.'' Longtime GOP strategist Mike Murphy, who opposes Trump, similarly said he would warn Democrats: 'Caution! Elections are very dynamic!' 'Trump and his advisers insist that their campaign's internal data show the race as more competitive,' the Post reports, 'and that he can gain momentum in the weeks ahead with a disciplined message and a brutal, sustained assault on Biden's character, ideology, and mental acuity.' Things can absolutely change, but over the past month at least, 'Bidenâ€™s lead over Trump has been both incredibly stable and unusually large,' Geoffrey Skelley notes at FiveThirtyEight, and he 'is verging on a landslide. Thatâ€™s not a word we use lightly.' Certainly, 'the president is in a very, very deep hole, and I'm not quite sure how he gets out of it,' said Amy Walter, national editor of the nonpartisan Cook Political Report. And 'instead of just a slight drag, the president is tying anchors around the ankles of Republican candidates.' Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO:  Coronavirus crisis may get 'worse and worse and worse'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200713135549-k1b00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO (PIX, TV):Coronavirus crisis may get "worse and worse and worse", warns WHO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Mary Statue Set On Fire Outside Church...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/07/12/blessed-vigin-mary-statue-set-on-fire-saint-peters-parish-church-dorchester/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating after a Blessed Virgin Mary statue was set on fire outside of a Dorchester church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customers, Employees Boycott WHOLE FOODS Over BLM Mask Ban...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/07/11/whole-foods-cambridge-black-lives-matter-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than two weeks, employees have walked off the job after being reprimanded for wearing their Black Lives Matter face masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BRAVE NEW WORLD' Arrives in Future It Predicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/13/arts/television/brave-new-world-peacock.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday, Peacock premieres an adaptation of Aldous Huxley’s 1932 science fiction novel. The world the book anticipated — designer drugs, casual sex, near-instant gratification — is already here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Stewart's new auto racing league to give fans alternative to NASCAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Tony-Stewart-s-new-auto-racing-league-to-give-15404212.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his NASCAR career winding down in October 2016, Tony Stewart described his plans for retirement.  "People ask, 'What are you're going to do next year?' and I say, 'Whatever I want.' It's the first time in 20 years I'm not going to be on NASCAR's schedule," he said. "You look at all the stuff I've got going on."  Since then, Stewart has tended to his NASCAR team, Stewart-Haas Racing, and continued to race on smaller dirt tracks across the country. But on Monday, his retirement shifted into a different gear, so to speak, with the news that he's starting a new auto racing circuit alongside fellow NASCAR Hall of Famer Ray Evernham, agent Sandy Montag and former NASCAR chief operating officer George Pyne.  The new venture, as reported by Sports Business Journal's John Ourand, will be called Superstar Racing Experience (or SRX) and will consist of six short-track races starting next summer, with all of the races televised live on Saturday nights by CBS. Unlike NASCAR, the SRX races will be designed to maintain viewer interest in part by fitting into a two-hour window, with two 45-minute heats and no pit stops.  "That's enough time to showcase the personalities in a way that's fun and appealing and exciting," Pyne told Ourand. "Having close, competitive racing, you're going to get 20 or 30 lead changes in a race."  There will be only 12 drivers per race, and they will drive identical cars designed by Evernham with identical equipment. Plus, each driver will be randomly paired with a crew chief for each race.  The races will take place at smaller tracks in what Ourand describes as "the American heartland," and the cars will be designed to race over a number of surfaces and styles - dirt, paved ovals, road courses, etc. - to further differentiate the product from NASCAR....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros directs $220 million toward efforts to achieve racial equality...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/507010-george-soros-directs-220-million-toward-efforts-to-achieve-racial-equality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open Society Foundations, the philanthropic organization founded by billionaire George Soros, is investing $220 million in emerging organizations and leaders building power in Black communities across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1-Year-Old Boy Shot To Death Outside Brooklyn Playground...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/13/1-year-old-boy-shot-to-death-outside-brooklyn-playground/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said the child was sitting in a stroller with a group of people having a barbecue when gunfire erupted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK NOW 5TH RICHEST PERSON ON EARTH!</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/tsla-explodes-higher-again-musk-now-5th-richest-man-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multitasking, technology causing more to become forgetful...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/information-overload-multitasking-technology-americans-forgetful/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's happened to everyone, you're busy with so many things you end up forgetting it's your friend's birthday. It may sound like a simple slip-up, but more Americans are saying their jam-packed schedules are making them more forgetful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA SHARES SURGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/13/tesla-jumps-11percent-on-sp-500-inclusion-speculation---now-the-10th-biggest-us-stock-by-market-value.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla's valuation has ballooned this year as shares continue their record climb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Comic Book Industry's Sexual Misconduct Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/warren-ellis-cameron-stewart-and-the-storm-of-sexual-misconduct-allegations-roiling-the-comic-book-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm of allegations against writers including Warren Ellis and Jason Latour is not a sign that the comics industry is broken. It’s a sign it’s running precisely as designed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strapped workers wait for delayed unemployment payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Workers-are-pushed-to-the-brink-as-they-continue-15403810.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexis Herdez has been filing for unemployment every week since April, shortly after she was laid off on her first day of work at a bridal clothing store.  But more than two months later, the 23-year-old in Lexington, Ky., has yet to receive any payment.  She and her husband have been struggling to pay rent and make their monthly car payment.  The automated phone system for the state's unemployment system takes her to a queue for a callback that has yet to come. Visits to state offices have been fruitless. While Herdez was finally able to get an appointment with someone at the unemployment agency to look at her case, it's not until August, she said.  The pandemic's toll on workers who have been furloughed or laid off like Herdez is measured in numbers that splash across headlines: 1.4 million new weekly unemployment claims and 18 million people are already receiving continuous unemployment insurance. Tens of thousands of workers at Levi's, Wells Fargo and United Airlines learned this past week they could be furloughed or laid off in coming months, sending those workers to seek jobless benefits as well.  Four months into the worst recession since the Great Depression, tens of thousands of workers like Herdez across the country have filed for jobless claims but have yet to receive payments. Many are now in dire financial straits.  "We've been only able to make half payments on everything," Herdez said in an interview. "We bought a large amount of groceries and have been taking things out of the freezer, but as the weeks go by, it's hard to figure out whether to pay bills or whether we have enough food to last the week."  The issue has spilled back into public view in recent weeks, as thousands of frustrated workers awaiting payments have camped out, sometimes overnight, in front of unemployment offices in states like...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why she may be granted bail at arraignment...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/13/will-ghislaine-maxwell-get-bail-at-her-arraignment-tomorrow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell will learn whether she’ll have to stay in jail pending her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's $3 trillion virus rescue inflates market bubbles...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/federal-reserves-3-trillion-virus-101225812.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. central bank has pledged unlimited financial asset purchases to sustain market liquidity, increasing its balance sheet from $4.2 trillion in February to $7 trillion today. While the vast majority of these purchases have been limited to U.S. Treasuries and mortgage-backed securities, the Fed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Mueller prosecutor writing book on investigation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b26df8ed548de1cf827dda6d2dbacf7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A top prosecutor for special counsel Robert Mueller has a book coming out this fall about the two-year investigation into the alleged ties between Russia and the 2016 campaign of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look out, Mars: Here we come with fleet of spacecraft...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4302ec5c515d37f53636b8ef60869991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Mars is about to be invaded by planet Earth — big time. Three countries — the United States, China and the United Arab Emirates — are sending unmanned spacecraft...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly elephant virus could jump to humans, experts warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12105753/deadly-elephant-virus-jump-humans-experts-warn-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS are investigating the disease that is killing hundreds of African elephants as it could transfer to humans. The new mysterious virus has killed up to 400 elephants in the Okavango Delta,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Taxes Meet Hedge Fund Riches in Manhattan D.A. Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-taxes-meet-hedge-fund-riches-in-manhattan-d-a-bid/ar-BB16Fy0t?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Sessions Comeback Bid Tests Trump Grip on Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jeff-sessions-comeback-bid-tests-trumps-grip-on-gop-voters/ar-BB16FsA7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman infects 71 people after 60-second elevator trip...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/woman-infects-71-people-coronavirus-22344755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details of the case have emerged in a new study released by the US Centres for Disease Control (CDC) which analysed the impact a single traveller with no symptoms can have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Search Upgrades Make It Harder for Sites to Win Traffic...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/how-google-search-changes-make-it-more-expensive-to-win-traffi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Rich Call For Covid Tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/global-super-rich-call-for-wealthy-to-face-coronavirus-tax-01594630205?refsec=afp-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 80 millionaires on Monday urged governments around the world to tax the super-wealthy much more to help fund the global recovery from the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 Reinvades States That Already Beat It Back Once...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/coronavirus/covid-19-reinvades-u-s-states-that-already-beat-it-back-once</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first states to endure the coronavirus this spring hoped the worst would be behind them. Instead, the virus is coming back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLIVER STONE: Hollywood has gone mad; Too fragile, sensitive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/07/13/magazine/oliver-stone-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Academy changes its mind every five, 10, two months about what it’s trying to keep up with. … I’ve never seen it quite mad like this.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scans Reveal Heart Damage in Over Half Patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/scans-reveal-heart-damage-over-half-covid-19-patients-study-1517293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kelly Preston, actress and Travolta wife, dies at 57...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kelly-preston-john-travolta-wife-actress-died-57-breast-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She lost a two-year battle with breast cancer, Travolta said in a tribute post on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Employees Say Racism Endures Behind Camera...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/13/espn-employees-say-racism-endures-behind-the-camera/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nationwide conversation over systemic racism and equality has prompted a series of discussions and forums at ESPN, where Black</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
