<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Klain had perfect résumé. His first year showed limits of experience...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Ron-Klain-had-the-perfect-resume-His-first-16802545.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As Joe Biden closed in on the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination, top...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirCar that transforms from vehicle into plane certified to fly...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10427811/AirCar-transform-road-vehicle-plane-certified-fly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AirCar was awarded its new status after completing more than 200 take-offs and landings during 70 hours of rigorous flight testing to European Aviation Safety Agency (EASA) standards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump New Social Platform to Reportedly Use Big Tech AI Censor...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/trumps-new-social-media-platform-to-reportedly-use-big-tech-ai-censor-we-want-to-be-very-family-friendly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRUTH Social, the new platform being developed by former President Donald Trump, will use artificial intelligence censors to purge content which is deemed NSFW.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans probe NBC over Beijing Olympics coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republican-investigation-nbc-beijing-olympics-d747928c-587a-41a8-91f7-777bc0a42f03.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The human rights abuses committed by the CCP have been the subject of intense scrutiny ahead of the Winter Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon was deplatformed. Obscure mogul keeps him on air...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2022/01/24/steve-bannon-war-room-real-americas-voice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘War Room’ is at the center of a new network monetizing what some employees saw as ‘Trump propaganda.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal peril for Prince Andrew puts focus on who will pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Legal-peril-for-Prince-Andrew-puts-focus-on-who-16802240.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles, royal honorifics and any illusion...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pig-Human Heart Transplant's Secret Weapon? Cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/neoscope/pig-human-heart-transplant-cocaine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To keep the gene-hacked pig heart beating during the historic operation earlier this month, surgeons used a drug cocktail that includes cocaine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Killed Emotional Support Ferrets...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/animals/arrest-in-ferret-slaughter-784930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANUARY 24--A Minnesota man charged with killing his roommate’s emotional support ferrets told police that he shot the caged animals with a BB gun because they “smell like shit” and claimed that one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk rocket set to crash into Moon after 7 years of chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4536277/elon-musk-rocket-crash-into-moon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FOUR-TONNE chunk of a SpaceX rocket is on a collision course with the Moon, according to online space junk trackers. The out-of-control booster was launched from Florida in February 2015 as part …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Eating More Guacamole, Spinach Dip Helps Prevent Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/magnesium-foods-fight-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other healthy foods high in magnesium includes lentils, almonds, cashews, tofu, seeds, oily fish, and dark chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to take reproduction in space seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/reproduction-sex-in-space-research-0f20f3a2-d8d1-46a6-bb97-f0f94f28d20b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that more science is needed on how humans and other mammals can reproduce in space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Armageddon elections to come...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/591114-the-armageddon-elections-to-come</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republicans’ strategy is clear: Oppose Biden on everything and highlight their cultural differences with the Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St white knuckle zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-stocks-suffer-sharp-losses-after-pandemic-s-worst-week/ar-AAT5uQv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategists Predict Trouble After Massive U-Turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/-head-fake-and-fed-put-potential-what-strategists-are-saying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday’s U.S. market action was wilder than most in its history, with the S&amp;P 500 falling about 4% before ending slightly higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalio Says USA in Decline; Warns of Election Risk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dalio-says-u-divisions-pose-021552945.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bridgewater Associates founder Ray Dalio said there’s a “reasonable chance” neither major U.S. political party will accept the results of the 2024 election.Most Read from BloombergStocks Storm Back From 4% Rout to Close Higher: Markets WrapU.S. Futures Fall, Stocks Are Mixed on Fed, Russia: Markets WrapBiden Has ‘Great Meeting’ With European Leaders: Ukraine UpdateHong Kong Billionaire Loses Half Her Fortune on China ProbeChina’s ‘Little Giants’ Are Its Latest Weapon in the U.S. T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Beijing Games, hugs discouraged but condoms available...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220125112915-uy22a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLYMPICS-2022/CONDOMS (PIX):Olympics-At Beijing Games, hugs discouraged but condoms available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's high-tech warplanes pose 'big new threat' to Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/china-s-high-tech-warplanes-pose-big-new-threat-to-taiwan/ar-AAT7m9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's deployment of J-16D jets into Taiwan's air defence zone this week marked the first sighting of the new high-tech warplanes, Taipei confirmed Tuesday, their electronic-jamming equipment posing a fresh threat to the island. Among the 13 observed on Monday were two J-16D jets, which the ministry confirmed Tuesday to AFP was the first time the high-tech warplanes had been seen in action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY state supreme court judge strikes down mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/24/us/new-york-state-mask-mandate-ruling/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A state supreme court judge struck down New York state's mask mandate Monday, ruling that the governor and NY State Department of Health did not have the authority to enact such a mandate without approval from the State Legislature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX meets outrage in Egypt with risque comedy-drama...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netflix-meets-outrage-egypt-risque-064453928.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix's first Arabic film production was always set to be a big event, but within days of its release, public opinion in Egypt was so inflamed that critics called for a ban on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Can't Get Heart Transplant Because Not Vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2022/01/24/covid-19-vaccine-heart-transplant-boston-brigham-womens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DJ Ferguson was set to receive a heart transplant, but because he has not got the COVID-19 vaccination, he is no longer eligible according to hospital policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police investigating...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boris-johnson-health-europe-london-cressida-dick-2d3448922de13c926c2c86a6193cd4a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — London police said Tuesday they were investigating Downing Street lockdown parties in 2020 to determine if U.K. government officials violated coronavirus restrictions, putting further pressure on Prime Minister Boris Johnson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow could burst Xi's Olympic dream with war in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/putin-would-burst-xis-olympic-dream-with-a-war-in-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last thing Mr Xi needs is for Mr Putin to overshadow China's big moment by triggering a global security crisis. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy fighter jet crashes during carrier landing in South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/navy-fighter-jet-crashes-carrier-landing-south-china/story?id=82447562</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy has confirmed that a U.S. Navy F-35 fighter jet was lost at sea while landing aboard the carrier USS Carl Vinson as it operates in the South China Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed may try to calm frazzled nerves...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-jerome-powell-may-try-to-calm-the-markets-frazzled-nerves-11643051800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can Powell calm the market's nerves? Here's a look at that and what other things economists and investors will be watching for when the Fed concludes the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10437625/Boris-faces-killer-blow-MPs-expect-party-revelations-calls-grow-PM-quit-now.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another huge blow to Boris Johnson's authority, ITV claims he attended a gathering organised by his wife Carrie in the Cabinet Room in No10 on June 19, 2020, to celebrate turning 56.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Heir's Sundance Docu Flounders In Attacks On Iger, Capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/01/abigail-disney-review-sundance-american-dream-other-fairy-tales-1234919114/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Iger is barely out the door at the Walt Disney Company and already a film from a scion of the founding family has  come along to give the well compensated ex-CEO a kick in the ass. However, bes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adele cancelled Vegas residency over swimming pool stunt?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/17428122/adele-cancel-las-vegas-residency-swimming-pool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POP superstar Adele cancelled her Las Vegas residency after launching into a furious rant at a swimming pool stunt planned for the big-money shows. The Brit was supposed to stand in the middle of o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin discusses 'strategic partnership' with Cuban leader amid fears of military threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/americas/2022-01-24/putin-cuba-strategic-partnership-4402280.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following recent threats of a potential military deployment to Cuba earlier this month, Russia’s President Vladimir Putin discussed the “strategic partnership” and further coordination of “actions in the international arena” with Cuban leader Miguel Díaz-Canel in a call disclosed Monday by the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears Send Chills to Battered Bitcoin Faithful...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/business/companies-markets/crypto-winter-fears-send-chills-to-battered-bitcoin-faithful</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chilling term refers to a sharp slump, followed by a drop-off in trading and months of market doldrums - a phenomenon that memorably befell the crypto market in 2018. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mayor pledges to rid city of gun violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/york-mayor-pledges-rid-city-001945331.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City Mayor Eric Adams vowed Monday to rid the city of guns, including by deploying plainclothes police on the streets, after a spate of violence in recent days claimed the life of a young officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volusia remains world shark bite capital as Florida attacks up in 2021...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/volusia-remains-world-shark-bite-215400054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Florida is once again the shark bite capital of the world as numbers jumped globally after three years of declines, according to the annual update from the International Shark Attack File. The group released its annual report this month and found 73 documented attacks last year, a stark contrast from 2020′s total of 52. Numbers don’t appear to be jumping the shark. Rather, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She told Mexico's president she feared for her life. Then she was killed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/she-told-mexicos-president-she-082845611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lourdes Maldonado López was shot to death Sunday night in Tijuana, becoming the second journalist killed there in less than a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Has Never Plunged 10% This Fast to Start a Year...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/market-never-plunged-10-fast-173607529.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The stock market has never been down this much 16 trading days into a year. Most Read from BloombergStocks Storm Back From 4% Rout to Close Higher: Markets WrapBiden Has ‘Great Meeting’ With European Leaders: Ukraine UpdateChina’s ‘Little Giants’ Are Its Latest Weapon in the U.S. Tech WarHong Kong Billionaire Loses Half Her Fortune on China ProbeUAE Says New Attack Repelled as Yemen’s Houthis Vow MoreThe S&amp;P 500 has dropped 11% -- heading toward what would count as a correction --</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They had covid-19 once. Then, they got it again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/they-had-covid-19-once-then-they-got-it-again/ar-AAT65AV?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW version of omicron doesn't appear to be more dangerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/there-e2-80-99s-a-new-version-of-omicron-e2-80-94-but-so-far-it-doesn-e2-80-99t-appear-to-be-more-dangerous/ar-AAT6dn3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street plunges through 'white knuckle' zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-stocks-suffer-sharp-losses-after-pandemic-s-worst-week/ar-AAT5uQv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo shells out for media makeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mike-pompeo-shells-out-for-media-makeover-8eae9986-94c1-471a-9715-4104702b315d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former secretary of State has been honing his media skills amid speculation about a possible presidential run, records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin Fights To Stop Lawsuit Over Fatal Film Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/01/alec-baldwin-lawsuit-rust-producers-dismiss-fatal-shooting-mamie-mitchell-gloria-allred-1234919067/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two months after the script supervisor on Rust filed a lawsuit against Alec Baldwin and other producers for the actor’s fatal shooting of cinematographer Halyna Hutchinson on the New Mexi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bars and gyms are bustling as Americans learn to live with covid...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2022/01/24/national-business/bars-and-gyms-are-bustling-as-americans-learn-to-live-with-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is how many expect the pandemic to peter out: COVID-19 remains, but becomes milder, and bit by bit, people don't let it rule their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN HOT MIC: 'Stupid Son of a B*tch' Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/what-a-stupid-son-of-a-btch-biden-caught-on-hot-mic-appearing-to-slam-peter-doocy-of-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden called Fox News reporter Peter Doocy a "stupid son of a b*tch" on Monday after a photo op at the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan refugee convicted of assaulting girl, 3, at QUANTICO...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/afghan-refugee-convicted-assaulting-girl-quantico-82447258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal jury has convicted an Afghan refugee housed at Quantico Marine Corps Base after he fled the country with a sexual assault</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police examine backgrounds, socials of lawmakers' contacts...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/24/capitol-police-social-media-00000948</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu rejects plea deal that would ban him from politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/netanyahu-rejects-plea-deal-corruption-charges-4a00dab5-d772-4dae-93d2-aec0a5e8771d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu faces multiple corruption charges but wants to stay in politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOM: Teachers 'secretly manipulated daughter into believing she was trans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10428993/Mother-teachers-manipulated-child-change-gender-identity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California mother Jessica Konen is suing a California school district, claiming that two teachers secretly manipulated her 11-year-old daughter into believing she was a transgender boy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA judges greenlight special grand jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/atlanta-news/breaking-fulton-judges-greenlight-special-grand-jury-for-trump-probe/DEBK3IQKLZHLBO6EYBGDXAHAU4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A panel of Fulton County judges on Monday cleared the way for a special grand jury to be used as part of District Attorney Fani Willis’ investigation of former President Donald Trump and his efforts to overturn Georgia’s 2020 election results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People losing their marbles as old pastime rises again...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/culture/article/people-are-literally-losing-their-marbles-as-an-old-past-time-rises-again-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clues on social media are leading tens of thousands of marble hunters to coveted glass spheres in Northern California and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC anchor urges liberals to 'pick up weapon, get involved' in 'war' for democracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/msnbc-tiffany-cross-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC host Tiffany Cross urged fellow progressives to "pick up a weapon and get involved" in the "war" for the survival of the country on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saturn's ice moon could be 'stealth' ocean world hospitable to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/24/world/saturn-moon-mimas-ocean-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturn's innermost moon Mimas, which resembles the Death Star from Star Wars thanks to a giant crater, may be a "stealth" ocean world, containing a hidden ocean beneath a thick shell of ice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe thinking new team...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2022/01/24/could-tom-brady-be-thinking-about-joining-a-new-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the nonchalance many have expressed regarding the possibility that Tom Brady will retire in lieu of playing next season, Brady has said — on multiple occasions — that he’ll play through 2022 and then decide whether to continue. Thus, as much as some would like to ignore it, something has changed. Dramatically.What is it, [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC Quietly Censors Own Archives...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2022/01/the-bbc-quietly-censors-its-own-archives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of public view, the state-owned broadcaster has been altering old episodes of its shows to make them ‘suitable’ for modern listeners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA expected to sharply restrict use of monoclonal antibodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fda-expected-to-sharply-restrict-use-of-two-monoclonal-antibodies-spurring-a-halt-in-federal-shipments-of-the-covid-19-treatments/ar-AAT5OyM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS:  FRONT LINES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/21/europe/gallery/ukraine-russia-fadek/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 500 yards away from Russian-backed separatists, a group of Ukrainian soldiers waits for a fight it's sure is coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomy's Most Dazzling Era About to Begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/astronomy-s-most-dazzling-era-is-about-to-begin/ar-AAT5ShN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope seen once omicron wave increases global immunity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-pandemics-covid-19-pandemic-7180f2efe35290ceaa09efc0ddb3d633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World health officials are offering hope that the ebbing of the omicron wave could give way to a new, more manageable phase of the COVID-19 pandemic, even as they warn of difficult weeks ahead and the possibility of another, more dangerous variant arising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Prebiotics -- Reduce Anxiety?</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/gos-prebiotics-anxiety-gut-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Introducing a prebiotic called galacto-oligosaccharides (GOS) into the gut microbiome has a positive effect on gut health and greater emotional wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FIGHT CLUB' Gets Very Different Ending in Mandarin...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k7wgea/fight-club-alternate-ending-china-censorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone tried very hard to please Chinese movie censors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPERBUBBLE, SUPERBURST</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/newsletters/sourcecode/when-the-superbubble-bursts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your five-minute guide to what's happening in tech this Monday, from what happens when the superbubble bursts to a very busy week for earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WHITE KNUCKLE' ZONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/wall-street-slides-into-white-knuckle-zone-as-s-p-500-hits-correction/ar-AAT5uQv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines who can't shave due to razor bumps
 won't be punished
...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2022/01/24/corps-stops-punishing-marines-who-cant-shave-due-to-razor-bumps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No shave? No problem. The Corps eases regulations for Marines diagnosed with painful skin condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: DON'T PANIC!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnbcs-jim-cramer-preaches-calm-as-market-craters-we-must-not-panic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CNBC guru said it might feel good to get out, but what happens if you can't get back in?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECONOMY SLOWS SHARPLY DURING OMICRON</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-economy-hits-the-brakes-in-january-during-omicron-wave-markit-surveys-show-11643035960</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy dropped down to a slower gear in January amid a record outbreak of coronavirus cases that intensified labor and supply shortages, according...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clapton claims jabbed under 'hypnosis'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/24/eric-clapton-people-vaccinated-against-covid-under-hypnosis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 76-year-old musician went on the Real Music Observer YouTube channel to discuss how his life has changed since reluctantly taking Astra Zeneca’s therapy in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris birthday bash -- during lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2022-01-24/boris-johnson-had-birthday-bash-during-lockdown-itv-news-understands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ITV News has learned that the prime minister's wife, Carrie Johnson, organised a surprise birthday party for him on 19 June when social gatherings were banned. | ITV National News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Abortion Movement's Victory Generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-anti-abortion-movement-s-victory-generation/ar-AAT5I00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia deploys HUNDREDS of military trains packed with troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/hundreds-trains-packed-russian-troops-26036065</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mirror has learned as many as 30 train loads of Moscow’s troops have entered Belarus in the past week - with a staggering 200 scheduled for the next few days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Fecal Transplants Can Stop GI Infections By Growing Healthy Gut Bacteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/fecal-transplants-c-diff-infections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transplantation of healthy feces into patients with C. difficile promotes the growth of healthy gut bacteria and eases the symptoms of infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY SHOCK SUNDANCE MOVIE FEATURES CANNIBALISM...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/22/sundance-disney-focuses-its-searchlight-on-horror-cannibalism-with-charmer-who-cuts-up-dates-and-eats-em</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom and Aaron symbols of fading era...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/what-to-know-from-the-nfl-playoffs-a-big-weekend-gives-way-to-some-big-decisions/ar-AAT5wGl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump losing to Trumpism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-is-losing-to-trumpism/ar-AAT5FfS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab monkey on the run after truck crash sparks fears it was 'infected'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/lab-monkey-run-after-truck-26035365</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A monkey was on the run after a transport truck containing around 100 lab test macaques crashed and allowed four to escape in the US, sparking fears it was carrying a disease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why we'll all end up eating bugs...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/why-well-end-up-eating-bugs/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The golden age of capitalism will emasculate us all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK trumpets massive new supercomputer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/meta-facebook-owner-wants-build-165916252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meta says it wants to build the most powerful artificial intelligence supercomputer in the world. The Facebook owner has already designed and built what it calls the AI Research SuperCluster, or RSC, which it says is among the fastest AI supercomputers in the world. It hopes to top that league by mid-2022, it said, in what would be a major step towards increasing its artificial intelligence capabilities.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
