<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DRIVING THROUGH HELL</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8653015/Dashcam-captures-terrifying-drive-California-wildfires-killed-six.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horrifying footage (left) shows cars driving through the raging flames of the Hennessey Fire in Napa County Friday, as California continues to be at the peril of 560 fires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bush Comeback Tactics From 1988 Echo in Race...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/22/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-trump-how-bush-mounted-a-comeback-in-1988/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George H.W. Bush was in trouble. It was July 1988 and Michael Dukakis, the Democratic candidate for president, was on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two of Larry King's children have died in the past three weeks...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/08/21/larry-kings-son-and-daughter-pass-away-within-weeks-of-each-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King’s son Andy passed suddenly a couple of weeks ago, and his daughter Chaia died Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:   Will not know election results 'for weeks, months, maybe never'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-warns-election-vote-count-201019233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump warned Friday that the results of the  November 3 presidential election could take weeks or months to determine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans set to make the case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/republicans-case-trump-democrats-endorse-170709843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican Party is to make its case next week for four more years of President Donald Trump after his Democratic opponent Joe Biden wrapped up his party&amp;#39;s convention with a vow to end what he called a &amp;quot;chapter of American darkness.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SEND IN THE NATIONAL GUARD'</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200822004209-em3s2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRE/ (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-California governor calls wildfires 'deadly moment,' urges residents to flee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Total anarchy, madness and chaos'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200821204831-03ekh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/CONVENTION (UPDATE 2, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 2-Battered by Democrats, Trump fires back against 'total anarchy, madness and chaos'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mounting deaths reveal an outsize toll on people of color...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a8e3244c77bcaf31efc826bbbe4a9d19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 215,000 more people than usual died in the U.S. during the first seven months of 2020, suggesting that the number of lives lost to the coronavirus is significantly higher than the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC TOPS...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/articles/democratic-national-convention-television-ratings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PECKER OUT AT NATIONAL ENQUIRER...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/national-enquirer-chief-david-pecker-out-after-ami-merger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tabloid king has been dethroned as the financially troubled American Media Inc. merges with a company that markets face masks and vitamin supplements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO chief believes covid pandemic could last another 2 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1350542/coronavirus-pandemic-another-two-years-who/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE CORONAVIRUS pandemic could last for another TWO YEARS, according to a World Health Organisation chief. Speaking on Friday director general Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus compared the virus to the 1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALWELL IN LIMBO AT LIBERTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/21/falwell-decision-liberty-university-400136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement came two weeks after Falwell was placed on leave from the prominent Christian university.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA WILDFIRES SOME OF LARGEST IN STATE HISTORY</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-fires-spread-fouling-air-204929058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thick smoke blanketed large areas of central and northern California on Friday as more people fled some of the biggest fires in the state&amp;#39;s history which have raged largely uncontrolled through the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24.6 MILLION WATCH BIDEN SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200821211532-2p53t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/TV RATINGS (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Democratic convention closing night draws event's biggest TV audience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK to challenge U.S. order...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-tiktok-trump-exclusive/exclusive-tiktok-to-challenge-u-s-order-banning-transactions-with-the-video-app-idUSKBN25H2QG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TikTok is preparing to mount a legal challenge as early as Monday to President Donald Trump's executive order prohibiting transactions with the popular short video app and its Chinese parent ByteDance, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors suggest more charges could be coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article245138570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases tied to Sturgis motorcycle rally cross state lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/21/us/sturgis-motorcyle-rally-sd-covid-nebraska-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases linked to the Sturgis motorcycle rally in South Dakota last week have now reached across state lines to Nebraska, public health officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT plans cloud contract push with foreign govts after $10 billion JEDI win...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/21/microsoft-plans-cloud-push-with-foreign-governments-after-jedi-win.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft hopes to keep widening its cloud infrastructure business by meeting public-sector needs abroad while maintaining a tight collaboration with the Trump Administration, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PECKER OUT: Embattled NATIONAL ENQUIRER CEO to depart...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/media_ink/status/1296913670421778436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Army Green Beret charged with Russian espionage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/aug/21/peter-rafael-dzibinski-debbins-ex-army-green-beret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors have charged a former Army Green Beret living in northern Virginia with espionage activity with Russia dating back as far as 1996.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Clinton Gave State Dept. Job to Ghislaine Maxwell's Nephew...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/hillary-clinton-gave-state-department-job-to-epstein-madam-ghislaine-maxwells-nephew-says-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OK! Magazine first reported on the ties, days after pictures surfaced of an Epstein victim giving a neck massage to former President Bill Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC CEO sent APPLE 2 am declaration of war...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/epic-s-ceo-sent-apple-a-2-a-m-declaration-of-war-over-fortnite-epic-will-no-longer-adhere-to-apple-s-payment-processing-restrictions/ar-BB18f38I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight Over Kennedy Dynasty Splinters Dems...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/pelosi-says-she-endorsed-kennedy-because-she-was-upset-by-assault-on-kennedy-family-legacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) said on Thursday that her startling endorsement of Rep. Joe Kennedy&amp;#8217;s (D-MA) primary campaign against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs Replaced as El Salvador's Most Prolific Killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/n7w5k8/coronavirus-has-replaced-gangs-as-el-salvadors-most-prolific-killer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country’s funeral workers were losing business - but then COVID hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Your Best Friend Gives Birth to Your Babies -- All 4 of Them...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2020/08/her-best-friend-was-her-surrogateand-had-quadruplets/615511/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“My kids know they’re a product of me and their dad, but that Debbie was our oven … They love her even more knowing the sacrifice she made.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Western states burning...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/21/us/wildfire-stats-california-colorado/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major wildfires are burning in California and other Western states. More than 20 major fires are burning in the Golden State, fueled by high temperatures. But states from the Northwest into the Rockies are also experiencing devastating wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highest TV ratings of week: 21.8 million...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/513135-biden-draws-highest-tv-ratings-of-week-for-democratic-convention-but-down-from</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ratings mark a 21 percent drop from Hillary Clinton's speech at the convention in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funeral for Robert Trump at White House -- something not done since 1936...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/trump-hold-funeral-brother-at-white-house-a-rare-event-2020-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time the deceased body of a private citizen was brought to the White House was in 1936.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's top critic permitted to leave Russia after suspected poisoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/putin-top-critic-allowed-to-leave-russia-after-suspected-poisoning-2020-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Numerous critics and opponents of Putin have been poisoned. Alexei Navalny's team believe he's the latest victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon: Use of surveillance planes in protests legal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4e3b87f50be81b25b3060eff7c61a253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The use of National Guard reconnaissance planes in four U.S. cities to monitor the widespread protests earlier this year didn't violate rules against the military collecting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistani minister threatens India with nukes in 'bloody last war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12464219/pakistani-minister-threatens-india-nuclear-attack-only-muslims-survive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PAKISTANI minister has threatened India with a nuclear attack in “the bloody last war” and says only Muslims will survive. Sheikh Rashid made the threat of nuclear war, claiming that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayoral candidate stages fake kidnapping for sympathy votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article245135460.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX and AMAZON Risking Monumental Consequences With So Many Satellites!</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/08/space-traffic-crowded-spacex-amazon-satellite-mission/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are thousands of dead and active satellites floating in Earth’s orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planter-like urinals Amsterdam's answer to 'wild peeing'...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/amsterdam-sustainable-urinal-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Amsterdam is going green in an attempt to combat an age-old problem -- public urination. The local council has installed eight hemp-filled, sustainable urinals in the city's "wild peeing" hotspots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels now using explosive-packed drones in new brand of warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12465886/mexico-drug-cartels-jalisco-nueva-generacion-explosive-warfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MEXICAN drug cartel is using drones loaded with explosives to attack its rivals. The Jalisco Nueva Generacion Cartel (JNGC) – one of the most violent and dangerous of the criminal gangs tea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate America choking on debt... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/corporate-america-choking-debt-imperiling-100000755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- After tapping the bond market at a record-shattering pace in recent months, Corporate America is more indebted today than ever before.And while much of that fresh cash -- more than $1.6 trillion in total -- helped scores of companies stay afloat during the pandemic lockdown, it now threatens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Successful Virtual Convention To Be New Normal?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/joe-biden-democratic-convention-review-night-4-donald-trump-coronavirus-kamala-harris-dnc-1203019492/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Family, and family, and family.” That was the motto of the video that introduced Joe Biden on the final night of the virtual Democratic National Convention, and showed just how the COV…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC After Party 'Totally Deranged'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/hollywoods-dnc-after-party-was-totally-deranged</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official “DNC After Party” featured Zooey Deschanel, Aubrey Plaza, a set of party rules, and Diplo DJing in front of a green screen. It was totally bonkers...but harmless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA officials blast 'callous' bystanders who filmed attack on trans YOUTUBE star and her friends... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/L-A-officials-blast-callous-bystanders-who-15504532.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed with a crowbar, a man in a black tank top approached Joslyn Allen on Hollywood Boulevard in Los Angeles just after 2 a.m. on Monday, spewing hateful slurs. "He literally grabs my hand and pulls me," Allen, who is a transgender woman, told KABC. "He's like 'We're going to find your friends because I'm going to beat y'all up.' "  Allen got away. But the man soon found her friends, Jaslene Busanet and Eden Estrada, who has a large following on YouTube as Eden the Doll. He hurled hate speech at the women, who are also transgender, and hit Busanet over the head with a bottle, knocking her to the ground, according to police.  All the while, a crowd of onlookers stood by, watching and recording the repeated verbal and physical assaults, with many yelling their own transphobic insults at the women.  The Los Angeles Police Department said on Thursday that they had found the man responsible for the crime, which inspired dozens to march in support of the victims and led city officials this week to slam the bystanders for failing to help the women.  Police arrested 29-year-old Carlton Callway on robbery and assault charges, calling Callway's actions a hate crime. Authorities said in a news conference Thursday that the suspect bragged about the assault on social media. Police also identified two other men allegedly involved in the incident, charging Willie Walker, 42, with extortion. Police are still searching for a third suspect, Davion Williams, 22, who is wanted for assault.  In a news conference on Thursday, deputy chief Justin Eisenberg called the witnesses to the scene "callous" and Los Angeles City Councilman Mitch O'Farrell said he was outraged by the footage.  "When I saw the video, like anyone who has seen it who believes in human decency, to see this level of violence celebrated gleefully, so much so that the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARVILLE:  I thought this was a perfect day...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/james-carville-relishes-perfect-day-for-democrats-began-with-arrest-of-trump-wh-strategist-steve-bannon-ended-with-joe-bidens-widely-praised-dnc-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Carville relishes 'perfect day' for Democrats: began with arrest of former Trump advisor Steve Bannon, ended with Joe Biden's widely praised DNC speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS RAVES:  'Enormously effective,' 'A home run'...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/fox-news-drudge-praise-biden-dnc-speech-despite-trump-2020-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After having echoed President Donald Trump's attack lines that Joe Biden is in cognitive decline, Fox News widely praised Biden at a crucial moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's squalid jails get even worse as covid spreads ...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-squalid-jails-even-worse-143558374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Squalid, overcrowded and prone to deadly riots, Brazil&amp;#39;s prisons now face a new problem as COVID-19 spreads inside them, pushing already precarious health services to the brink and increasing inmates&amp;#39; isolation from their families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLFIRES RAGE ON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2b421d9c899fec0c07a35060f4b00ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA CRUZ, Calif. (AP) — Sky-darkening wildfires that took at least five lives and forced thousands of people from their homes blazed throughout California on Friday as firefighting resources...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BARN BURNER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e8c1f414f046aa77fe37fea90e01f6c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Joe Biden accepted the Democratic presidential nomination with a vow to be a unifying “ally of the light” who would move an America in crisis past the chaos of President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy with stutter gave gripping convention speech...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/30951d24b0dab8b9ced01704d8ee9f2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Even in a week filled with emotional endorsements of Joe Biden, Brayden Harrington's stands out. The 13-year-old boy sat in his home, speaking to a cellphone camera and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Reviews for Hyped 'TENET' Range from 'Magnificent' to 'Huh?'</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/08/21/reviews-for-christopher-nolans-hyped-postponed-tenet-will-come-at-noon-with-words-like-jigsaw-puzzle-magnificent-and-huh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Tenet” is not an easy word to remember, or say. It sounds like “tenant.” And no one knows what it means. But that’s the title of Christopher Nolan’s new movie s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selling something that disappeared: Optimism...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/932712/biden-selling-something-that-disappeared-from-american-politics-optimism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In accepting the Democratic Partys presidential nomination on Thursday night, former Vice President Joe Biden offered the country something that has been missing from our politics lately: optimism. Yes, Biden referred to the present era as a 'season of darkness,' and made a pointed, even angry critique of how President Donald Trump has handled the COVID-19 pandemic. But he also made the case that â€” in this deeply polarized moment â€” Americans can and will work together for the common good, and that great possibilities are still attainable. 'The defining feature of America, everything is possible,' he said, later adding: 'This is our moment to make hope and history rhyme.' Now, optimistic talk about America's possibilities has often been a staple of American political talk. Barack Obama famously rode to the White House on a wave of 'hope and change.' But even Obama seems to have lost some of his hope â€” on Wednesday night, he warned the nation of President Trump's threat to American democracy, and concluded his speech with a plaintive 'Stay safe.' Obama's dark mood seemed to match that of the electorate: Three quarters of Americans think the country is on the wrong track, including 63 percent of Republicans. Much of that negativity has surely been earned. But the dark outlook has probably been helped along by President Trump's divide-and-conquer approach to politics. To the extent that Trump offers optimism to America, it almost always centers on himself: 'I alone can fix it.' And that optimism, such as it is, is often misplaced. Think of all the times Trump has suggested the coronavirus will simply 'disappear.' Biden, meanwhile, seemed more realistic about the challenges facing the country. And he centered his optimism on Americans and their ability â€” even now â€” to unite with each other. 'America isn't just a collection of clashing interests of Red States or Blue States,' he said. 'We're so much bigger than that. We're so much better than that.' Optimism, once a familiar force in our politics, now feels strange. We're about to find out if Americans still buy a hopeful message. Joel Mathis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Republicans abandoning the states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/513058-republicans-are-abandoning-the-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For half a century, the Republican Party was the party of the states. No more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapidly expanding...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deadly-bay-area-fires-rage-141702128.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fires in Northern and Central California have killed at least five people, destroyed more than 500 structures and scorched hundreds of square miles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Trump praise, Pence decries QAnon 'conspiracy theory'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ccd0c2c21f5a320b9fec1a8bb70a8459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence is dismissing QAnon as a “conspiracy theory,” drawing a line of distinction between himself and President Donald Trump, who earlier this week suggested he appreciated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHC forecast predicts 2 hurricanes...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/latest-nws-forecast-predicts-hurricanes-gulf-mexico-time/story?id=72509719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storms will be named Laura and Marco and are expected to hit Gulf states on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Developing Breakthrough 'Breathalyzer' Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/coronavirus-breathalyzer-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This device will scan the air after patients exhale, just like current breathalyzers detect alcohol particles in a person's breath.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you get virus via secondhand smoke? Smell is warning sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Can-you-get-coronavirus-via-secondhand-smoke-The-15504536.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The primary way the novel coronavirus spreads, according to health experts, is through close contact with people who are infected. Being in proximity with someone who has the coronavirus exposes you to the respiratory droplets emitted when the person coughs, sneezes or even speaks.  What if you're close enough to smell someone's secondhand smoke, or pass through a cloud of smoke on your way into a store? Does that expose you to the coronavirus, if the smoker happens to be infected?  There is little evidence to suggest the smoke itself could be carrying the coronavirus, but researchers and physicians say that merely being able to smell someone's cigarette is a warning sign you're breathing air that was just in someone else's lungs.  William Ristenpart, a professor of chemical engineering at the University of California at Davis who researches how pathogens are transported, told The Washington Post that the smoke particles themselves are unlikely to be carrying a virus that could infect other people. This is partly because the heat from the cigarette would probably kill the virus, but also because "a large fraction of the smoke particulates go into your lungs, never hit anything, and then are exhaled," Ristenpart said.  But there is reason to be concerned about transmission if you get a whiff of someone's smoke - the respiratory particles that come along with it.  "If you smell somebody else's exhaled cigarette smoke, then you are inhaling air that was in that person's lungs," Ristenpart said. "This means you could also be inhaling their virus-laden respiratory particles, which are composed of respiratory mucosa rather than ash."  Research is still inconclusive on whether the coronavirus can be transmitted in airborne particles, but the hypothesis is gaining traction. While the main source of transmission is believed to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan converts another former church into mosque...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200821-turkey-s-erdogan-converts-another-former-church-into-mosque</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey's Erdogan converts another former church into mosque</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Penn meeting with El Chapo was nearly his demise...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/20/sean-penns-meeting-with-el-chapo-was-nearly-his-demise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Oct. 2, 2015, Sean Penn flew to Mexico for what could have been the most disastrous and even deadly night of his life. The actor had been invited to a sit-down with Joaquín Guzmán Loera, the dru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How unknown British actress played role in downfall of Hollywood moguls...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/unknown-british-actress-play-role-005806299.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ron Meyer, the former vice chairman of NBCUniversal, was the second mogul embroiled in a sex scandal with Charlotte Kirk to be toppled in less than two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists grow first functioning mini human heart...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-08-scientists-functioning-mini-human-heart.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan State University researchers have created for the first time a miniature human heart model in the laboratory, complete with all primary heart cell types and a functioning structure of chambers and vascular tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to testify in Senate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0807b23d98f127a99ceb40d759341bbf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing public backlash, Postmaster General Louis DeJoy is set to testify Friday about disruptions in mail delivery as a Senate committee digs into changes in postal operations...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
