<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Lil Peep Doc Tells Familiar Story -- but Doesn't Make Less Sad...</title>
      <link>https://www.theringer.com/movies/2019/11/13/20962535/lil-peep-documentary-everybodys-everything-gustav-ahr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theringer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Everybody’s Everything" is about a promising young musician whose fame only deepened his substance abuse—a tale we’ve seen before, but like his music, Gustav Ahr’s life is well worth remembering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable news showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-13/msnbc-and-fox-news-girding-to-prosecute-and-defend-president-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impeachment inquiry into President Trump has widened a massive divide, nowhere more evident than on cable TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept faces biggest crisis since McCarthy hysteria...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/State-Department-faces-its-biggest-crisis-since-14831022.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As diplomats prepared to testify publicly at House impeachment hearings, the president of the American Foreign Service Association recalled another perilous era in U.S. history.  That was Sen. Joseph McCarthy's reign of hysteria in the early 1950s about supposed communists in Hollywood and the federal government - especially the State Department.  "I think it's fair to say in the past 70 years, since the McCarthy period, this is the most fraught time and the most difficult time for our members," said Eric Rubin, the president of AFSA, the union representing Foreign Service officers.  During McCarthyism, the Republican from Wisconsin wildly alleged that the State Department was infested with communists and chaired hearings to root them out.  Now, House Democrats are calling on diplomats to help uncover the truth concerning accusations that President Trump invited a foreign government into domestic affairs for his personal political benefit.  This time, unlike in the McCarthy era, Foreign Service officers are not the accused. Video showing William B. Taylor Jr., George Kent and Marie Yovanovitch on Capitol Hill for their closed-door testimony in the Ukraine matter provided images of proud, dedicated federal employees caught up in a political drama they cannot escape.  Taylor and Kent will testify publicly Wednesday, and Yovanovitch on Friday, on Trump's plan to have Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky embarrass Trump's political rival, former vice president Joe Biden, by investigating his son's activities in Ukraine.  This has plunged the diplomats into a legal predicament between the Democratic-controlled House of Representatives and the Republican-controlled White House, and leaves the association in unmapped terrain.  "Our colleagues are finding themselves...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing running 500 concentration camps?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uighur-researchers-china-running-hundreds-more-camps-181157759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uighur activists said Tuesday they have documented nearly 500 camps and prisons run by China to detain members of the ethnic group, alleging that Beijing could be holding far more than the commonly cited figure of one million people. The East Turkistan National Awakening Movement, a Washington-based</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces limits of his power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f43d4e272994e9ca321714c3974eac3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For three years, Donald Trump has unapologetically defied the conventions of the American presidency. On Wednesday, he comes face to face with the limits of his power, confronting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski leaves movie premiere in Paris by side door following protests...</title>
      <link>https://uk.movies.yahoo.com/roman-polanski-leaves-movie-premiere-in-paris-by-side-door-following-protests-130334639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roman Polanski made a swift exit from a back door at the premiere of his new movie in Paris last night, following angry protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy dogs headed to Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/470179-therapy-dogs-slated-to-visit-capitol-hill-today</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cuddly canines are coming to the rescue of stressed-out Capitol Hill staffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Nears Defining Hour as Impeachment Goes Public...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-nears-defining-hour-case-104512848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Balance of Power newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Politics on Twitter and Facebook for more.Congressional Democrats have a tall order ahead.Their challenge, at the start of public impeachment hearings today against President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff on Hook to Make Case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-hearings-open-schiff-090000658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s attempts to pressure Ukraine will be scrutinized in a historic public forum Wednesday as the House opens impeachment hearings that will pit him against Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff, who is tasked with making the case to remove the president from office.Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venetian anger after historic flood devastates city...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/devastation-venice-exceptional-tide-095855792.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venetians woke Wednesday to devastating scenes after the highest tide in 50 years washed through the historic Italian city, beaching gondolas, trashing hotels and sending tourists fleeing through rapidly rising waters. "The city is on its knees," Venice's mayor Luigi Brugnaro said in an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURTAIN-UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/468e0bcb51e74822a1f8cc11627a1c0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The closed doors of the Trump impeachment investigation are swinging wide open. When the gavel strikes at the start of the House hearing on Wednesday morning, America and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong readies for more chaos as violence spreads citywide...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191113012941-iptni</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-PROTESTS/ (PIX, TV):Hong Kong readies for more chaos as violence spreads citywide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pneumonic plague in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/13/two-people-diagnosed-with-pneumonic-plague-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities working to contain outbreak of disease that is worse than bubonic plague</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House laughs off Anonymous book as old news...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/12/white-house-anonymous-book-069684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminally-ill scientist completes transformation into 'world's first cyborg'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/terminally-ill-scientist-completes-transformation-20871943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Peter Scott-Morgan, who suffers from a muscle wasting disease, says he has fully completed his transition into 'Peter 2.0'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Israel-Gaza escalation rages for second day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deadly-israel-gaza-escalation-rages-second-day-113541641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exchanges of fire triggered by Israel's targeted killing of a top militant in Gaza raged for a second day Wednesday and showed little sign of easing, with 22 Palestinians killed. Fresh rocket barrages were fired at Israel, which responded with strikes on what it said were Islamic Jihad militant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to use webcams to create live feed of border wall construction... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/white-house-to-use-webcams-to-create-live-feed-of-border-wall-construction/ar-BBWFlFx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate trial to last 6 WEEKS? </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7678773/Senate-2020-candidates-work-SIX-days-week-Trump-impeachment-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The six senators running for president may find themselves in a time crunch, with President Trump's impeachment trial running six hours a day, for six days a week for six to eight weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel urges EU to seize control of data from US tech titans...</title>
      <link>https://www.afr.com/world/europe/merkel-urges-eu-to-seize-control-of-data-from-us-tech-titans-20191113-p53a5v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The German chancellor said the EU should claim 'digital sovereignty' by developing its own platform to manage data and reduce its reliance on the US-based cloud services run by Amazon, Microsoft and Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aides counseling Trump not to fire Mulvaney...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Mulvaney-says-he-will-no-longer-seek-judge-s-14828841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump has been threatening for weeks to fire acting chief of staff Mick Mulvaney, but senior advisers have counseled him to hold off on such a drastic step amid a high-stakes impeachment probe, according to three people familiar with the discussions.  Trump has expressed particular anger over Mulvaney's performance in an Oct. 17 news conference in which Mulvaney stunned White House aides by saying military aid to Ukraine was withheld to pressure its government to launch investigations that could politically benefit Trump, two of the people said. Later, Mulvaney issued a statement saying the media had misconstrued his televised comments and that "there was absolutely no quid pro quo."  Senior advisers have cautioned Trump that removing Mulvaney at such a sensitive time could be perilous, the people said - both because Mulvaney played an integral role in the decision to freeze the aid, and because of the disruption that would be caused by replacing one of Trump's most senior aides.  "I don't think you'll see him going anywhere until after December," said one Trump adviser, who like others spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private conversations. "But the president was very unhappy with that press conference. That was a very bad day for the president."  White House officials declined to comment Tuesday.  Mulvaney had direct talks with Trump about the president's desire to withhold nearly $400 million in security aid to Ukraine, The Washington Post has reported. At the same time, Trump and other allies were pressuring Ukraine to open an investigation of Democratic rival Joe Biden and of theories about the country's role in the 2016 election, according to congressional testimony in the impeachment inquiry.  Trump's advisers have cited as a cautionary tale the example of national...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary says 'many, many, many people' urging her to run...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/12/hillary-clinton-presidential-run-2020-000325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Threats Increase...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2019/11/as-trump-attacks-death-threats-against-the-whistleblower-and-his-lawyers-increase/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Law enforcement is involved."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Teams invite  Kaepernick to workout...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28067012/teams-invited-colin-kaepernick-workout-saturday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL clubs have been informed that Colin Kaepernick will hold a workout Saturday, although the QB's reps had asked that it could take place on a Tuesday, when more team personnel could attend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Death penalty not fair sentence for jaywalking...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/12/goodwin-trickster-adam-schiff-conjuring-guilt-out-of-thin-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dictionary defines a conjurer as someone who “practices magic arts” and “performs feats of sleight of hand and illusion.” In plain English, people like Adam Schiff. The California Democrat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declares economic 'boom' underway... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/trump-declares-economic-boom-underway-cbo-sounds-slowdown-alarms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump says the economy is "stunning." But congressional analysts see signs of a slowdown - already underway. It will be a big 2020 factor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Puerto Rico's infrastructure failing as federal aid remains on hold...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/policy/report-puerto-ricos-infrastructure-failing-federal-aid-remains-holdrelief-stalls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineers group says hurricane-ravaged island needs up to $23 billion investment over 10 years. The federal government is holding back aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Blocks 'Suspicionless' Searches of Phones, Computers at Borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-privacy/u-s-judge-rules-suspicionless-searches-of-travelers-digital-devices-unconstitutional-idUSKBN1XM2O2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Tuesday ruled that U.S. border agents need "reasonable s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems' lead lawyer known for prosecuting mobsters, swindlers ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-impeachment-lawyer-cut-his-teeth-prosecuting-mobsters-wall-street-cheats/ar-BBWF2p4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists Pursue New Kind of Expose: Uncovering Their Salaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/money/journalists-pursue-new-kind-of-expose-uncovering-their-salaries/ar-BBWF0wC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Blast Trade Aid as Favoring Southern Farmers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/democrats-blast-trump-trade-aid-as-favoring-southern-farmers/ar-BBWECQf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Sued for Censoring Posts Naming Whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-sued-censoring-posts-naming-211503373.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc. was accused in a lawsuit of censorship by a user who says the company hasn’t explained to him why it deleted three of his posts that named “the alleged Ukraine whistle-blower” who kicked off the presidential impeachment inquiry.Connecticut law school student Cameron Atkinson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURTAIN-UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/77645ee9804c4056a9a6e42e64cb755a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The closed doors of the Trump impeachment investigation are swinging wide open. When the gavel strikes at the start of the House hearing Wednesday morning, America and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHIFF: Impeachable Offenses Include 'Bribery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/12/778380499/rep-adam-schiff-trumps-potentially-impeachable-offenses-include-bribery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Intelligence Committee chairman said bribery is a "breach of the public trust in a way where you're offering official acts for some personal or political reason, not in the nation's interest."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approving marijuana sales leads to increases in crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/lake-county-news-sun/opinion/ct-lns-talk-of-county-st-1115-20191111-o3qksl5l4bhbbij3rfld4dfi7m-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk of the County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC scrambles to find leaker...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/12/abc-scrambles-to-figure-out-identity-of-amy-robach-leaker-who-goes-by-ignotus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC bigwigs are going potty to find the identity of the leaker behind the Amy Robach tape — after the alleged source posted a letter online slamming the network under the name “Ignotus,&amp;#8221…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURTAIN-UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a74ed5bfddba4c93918ec3aa5349ceb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The public impeachment inquiry hearings set to begin Wednesday will pit a Democratic attorney who built his reputation as a federal mob and securities fraud prosecutor against a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows families of Sandy Hook shooting victims to sue gunmaker...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8755008e727a4a1b804cdf5cf03ab620</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court said Tuesday that a survivor and relatives of victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting can pursue their lawsuit against the maker of the rifle used...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball coach told kid to slide. Then he got sued...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/slide-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Considered Firing Intel Inspector General...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-has-considered-firing-intelligence-community-inspector-general/ar-BBWEW5B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-ASTROS pitcher: Team stole signs with camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28066522/ex-astros-pitcher-mike-fiers-team-stole-signs-camera</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Astros pitcher Mike Fiers told The Athletic that the team used a camera in center field to help steal signs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Meat' -- Made From Air!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/air-protein-launches-air-based-meat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No, this is not a joke. Air Protein is making air-based meat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff's top inquisitor is ex-MSNBC personality...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/10/04/adam-schiff-tapped-former-msnbc-contributor-to-question-key-ukraine-envoy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President rails on Fed, notes negative rates: 'Give me some of that money'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/12/trump-rails-on-fed-says-market-and-economy-would-be-doing-even-better-without-powell-mistakes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump complained that foreign countries have negative interest rates. "Give me some of that money. I want some of that money," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAVAGE: DECADES OF DARKNESS, EVEN IF TRUMP WINS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/11/11/exclusive-michael-savage-raw-and-unfiltered-on-trump-beethoven-and-the-future-of-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with Breitbart News, conservative radio legend Michael Savage tackles a wide variety of today’s political issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 25% of infections in Canada resistant to drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50383332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 25% infections in the country are resistant to drugs and the figure is rising, scientists warn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Christmas Comes Early' as ABC Turns Journalists Into Promoters...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2019/11/12/christmas-comes-early-abc-whores-out-news-division-disney-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next time you hear liberals in the media talk about undue influence of corporate entities or the dominance of powerful voices, think of Good Morning America on Tuesday. The “news” program devoted almost 17 minutes to shilling for the new Disney+ streaming service. Disney, of course, owns ABC and the journalists on the network sounded more like PR talking points come to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: TRUMP MUST GO</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/ann-coulter-gives-up-daca-kids-can-stay-trump-must-go/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Braces for Violent Night; Pounded By 200+ Rockets...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Explosions-at-house-of-Islamic-Jihads-Abu-al-Ata-Palestinian-report-607579</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IDF reinforced its troops and prepared for multiple possible situations. Shelters in Ashkelon were opened and school was canceled as a "severe security event." Ashdod is in a state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat-shaming: Passenger loses airline miles over fat pet swap...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cat-shaming-russian-loses-airline-miles-over-fat-155447186.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's Aeroflot on Tuesday stripped a passenger of his air miles after he boasted online of sneaking his overweight cat on board by switching him for a slimmer cat during check-in. Traveller Mikhail Galin wrote in a Facebook post last week that his cat Viktor was judged too fat to be taken into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Homeless man hurls bucket of hot diarrhea at woman near Hollywood Walk of Fame...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/12/homeless-man-hurls-bucket-of-diarrhea-at-woman-near-hollywood-walk-of-fame/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A homeless man dumped a bucket of “hot” diarrhea on a Los Angeles woman near the Hollywood Walk of Fame — an unprovoked attack that’s left her with PTSD,  she said this…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy TX Millennial Spending Fortune Trying To Live To 120...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/11/11/texan-spending-fortune-hours-trying-live-120-years-old/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ari Rastegar goes to bed in special clothing on a temperature-regulated bed. He also wears a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hospital Delays Plan To End Life Support For TX Infant...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/11/10/cook-childrens-hospital-delays-plan-to-end-life-support-for-tinslee-lewis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook Children's Hospital in Fort Worth has stopped plans to end life support for 9-month-old Tinslee Lewis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German intel agencies open new spy school in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bd54c90fd83f40bf9ee7f8c58300b8f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A room full of grey suits, strict instructions only to photograph the audience from behind and — of course — a medley of James Bond tunes to lighten the mood. Germany's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe Mandates Labels for Jewish Products...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/world/food-israeli-west-bank-settlements-must-carry-special-labels-european-court-rules-psagot-wine-1.493035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows families of Sandy Hook shooting victims to sue gunmaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/12/778487920/supreme-court-allows-sandy-hook-families-case-against-remington-to-proceed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gun-maker had appealed to the highest federal court after the Connecticut Supreme Court allowed the lawsuit over the 2012 school massacre in Newtown, Conn., to go forward in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In private speech, Bolton says some of Trump's policy decisions guided by personal interest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/private-speech-bolton-suggests-some-trump-s-foreign-policy-decisions-n1080651</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former national security director was especially critical of the president's handling of Turkey, according to multiple sources present for his remarks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Frenzy: TV Networks Blast With 96% Negative News...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/rich-noyes/2019/11/12/impeachment-frenzy-nets-aim-destroy-trump-96-negative-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the six weeks since the Democrats’ impeachment inquiry was announced, the liberal media have tried to help the cause by giving the effort wall-to-wall coverage, blasting the President with 96% negative coverage (even including criticism of his performance after the successful mission against ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi), even as they ignore how Trump’s policies have benefited the record-setting economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Kamala Harris slips to 1% in NH...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/quinnipiac-kamala-harris-polling-at-1-percent-in-new-hampshire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest Quinnipiac poll of New Hampshire shows Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden with a narrow lead in a close four-way race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican senator: All comes down to motive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/gop-senator-john-kennedy-quid-pro-quo-probably-impeachable-if-trump-motive-political/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindsey Graham agrees, except that he doesn’t think there was a quid pro quo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West to take stage at Joel Osteen Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.disrn.com/2019/11/12/kanye-west-to-take-stage-at-joel-osteens-lakewood-church-sunday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West is scheduled to take the stage at Joel Osteen's Lakewood Church this Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daytime TV Shocker: Entire 'DAYS OF OUR LIVES' Cast Fired...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/11/12/days-of-our-lives-cancelled-cast-fired-season-56/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sand appears to be leaking out of the hourglass. TVLine has learned exclusively that the producers of Days of Our Lives have released the entire cast from their contracts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITI Warns of  'War on Wall Street and Wealth' in 2020 Election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/citi-warns-war-wall-street-153355457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The road to the White House in 2020 may entail a war against Wall Street and wealth itself, as polling results encourage more candidates to cast a jaundiced eye toward the financial world, Citi warned in a note to clients.Some candidates are prioritizing greater accountability for big</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: USC Student Found Dead Off-Campus, Brings Semester Death Toll To 9...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/12/9th-usc-student-found-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The student was a 28-year-old man and LAPD now says no foul play is suspected, after the death was reportedly considered suspicious Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gervais Back As GOLDEN GLOBES Host...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/ricky-gervais-host-golden-globes-2020-nbc-hfpa-1202783565/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Ricky Gervais has been pressed into service once again and will host the 77th annual Golden Globes next year. While the Oscars and the Emmys went hostless this year, the Hollywood Foreig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO DAIRY:  Top milk company declares bankruptcy amid drop in demand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5eb1173f5e2b4994927bc921f5b49f0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dean Foods, America's biggest milk processor, filed for bankruptcy Tuesday amid a decades-long drop-off in U.S. milk consumption blamed on changing trends and a growing variety of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Election vendors are 'prime targets,' need oversight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4fe79d4ef9ff487f97f0bc3981cf7fd0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The private companies that make voting equipment and build and maintain voter registration databases lack any meaningful federal oversight despite the crucial role they play in U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican who helped lead Clinton impeachment:   'Troublesome'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/republican-congressman-helped-lead-clinton-impeachment-trump-ukraine/story?id=66914842 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asa Hutchinson, governor of Arkansas, called the call between President Trump and Ukraine's president "very troublesome" on "The Investigation" podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reckless driver told cops he was speeding home after 'cheating on wife'...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/cheating/cheating-florida-man-390568</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida Man pulled over Sunday night for driving recklessly told police that he “needed to get home in a hurry because he was cheating on his wife,” according to an arrest affidavit. Cops report th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Meditate To Make Fewer Mistakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hate-mistakes-meditation-may-make-you-less-error-prone-in-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who are clumsy or error-prone when completing a task may want to consider adding meditation to their daily routines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of 10 earthquakes shakes Southern California...</title>
      <link>https://www.modbee.com/news/california/article237275064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake video shows Boris Johnson back Jeremy Corbyn for PM...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/creepily-realistic-deepfake-video-shows-20866883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deepfake was made by London-based thinktank Future Advocacy to alert people to the danger of fake news and video while the UK is just a month away from a General Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic blast to plunge 200 million into deep freeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/200-million-americans-to-experience-harsh-record-challenging-cold-this-week/622611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Take Probe Public as Trump Roars Defiant...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-impeachment-probe-public-trump-090000085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Democrats this week are taking their effort to impeach Donald Trump into a risky new phase of public hearings that the president is eager to turn into a made-for-TV personal battle, echoing his successful White House run in 2016.The hearings on Wednesday and Friday feature three</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong bloodshed in dangerous new phase... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2b32e41e4314aaf9d58cf117f19581d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Police and protesters battled outside university campuses and several thousand demonstrators blocked roads as they took over a central business district at lunchtime on Tuesday in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden autobiography censored in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/12/edward-snowden-says-autobiography-permanent-record-censored-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sections on democracy and privacy appear to be missing in Chinese edition of Permanent Record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Don Jr. Landed Smack in Middle of Right-Wing Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-donald-trump-jr-landed-smack-in-the-middle-of-a-right-wing-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Jr. is the latest conservative celeb to be besieged by racist “groypers,” who style themselves after an obese cartoon frog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC RACING MOVIE AS REAL AS EVER GONNA GET...</title>
      <link>https://autoweek.com/article/car-life/new-ford-v-ferrari-movie-real-its-ever-gonna-get</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;autoweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can predict if you'll die soon -- but we've no idea how it works...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2222907-ai-can-predict-if-youll-die-soon-but-weve-no-idea-how-it-works/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence can predict a person’s chances of dying within a year by looking at heart test results, but doctors can't work out what patterns it’s picking up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small quakes strike near big faults along California-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-11-11/several-small-earthquakes-strike-el-centro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small earthquakes under El Centro, Calif., are important to closely monitor, especially since they occur close to major faults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'cult' quietly operating in NY for decades...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/11/inside-the-alleged-cult-that-has-been-quietly-operating-in-ny-for-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In December 1978, a bizarre theater company headed by an actress from the “Slaughterhouse-Five” film was run out of San Francisco. Members of Sharon Gans’ so-called Theater of All…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAIN ZAP: NEW HEADSET COULD HELP SLEEP BETTER...</title>
      <link>https://home.bt.com/news/uk-news/new-headset-could-help-people-enjoy-better-nights-sleep-11364410252667</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;home.bt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modius SLEEP was launched on Tuesday by Belfast-based company Neurovalens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A NATION COMING APART...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a3b7df66e50f488a841a31ce31124987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Atlantic magazine was founded in the years leading up to the Civil War, so it's worth noting when it produces a special new issue on the theme, "How to stop a Civil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Then and now: How Trump impeachment hearing is different...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2efee2cfbfb4b5dbe7ed347ae8c8068</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The public impeachment inquiry hearings this week usher in a rare and momentous occasion in American history as Congress debates whether to remove a president from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RON PAUL: Bubble Pop?</title>
      <link>http://ronpaulinstitute.org/archives/featured-articles/2019/november/11/is-the-mother-of-all-bubbles-about-to-pop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ronpaulinstitute.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
