<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Plane becomes laboratory...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/i-just-took-the-worlds-first-20-hour-flight-heres-what-it-did-to-me/ar-AAJ2cdg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insult-comic act danger zone... </title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/466617-trumps-insult-comic-act-enters-danger-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It can be electrifying. But it also can be a difficult, dangerous way to get attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss count votes in possible 'green wave'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/swiss-vote-possible-green-wave-election-022903850.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland was counting votes on Sunday in an election that could see unprecedented gains for parties demanding bold climate action and a possible slip for the anti-immigrant right-wing. In a country that recently held a funeral march for an iconic glacier that has nearly vanished due to melting, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tear gas and water cannon as crowds defy rally ban...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democracy-crowds-defy-hong-kong-police-activists-attacked-061123808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong police fired water cannon and tear gas on Sunday as crowds held an illegal march, with hardcore protesters throwing petrol bombs and trashing busineses, capping a week of anger after the recent stabbing and beating of two pro-democracy protesters. Authorities had forbidden the rally in Tsim</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING wants it to fly, but travelers fear 737 MAX...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boeing-wants-fly-travelers-fear-737-max-065650000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On September 12, Boeing started putting out 30-second videos in which employees tout its planes' safety, hoping to reassure travelers about the 737 MAX that's been grounded worldwide since two crashes that killed 346 people. "When the 737 MAX returns to service I will absolutely put my</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS completes longest non-stop New York-Sydney flight!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d6545469f97842e8b1c908397812a39d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY (AP) — Australia's Qantas on Sunday completed the first non-stop commercial flight from New York to Sydney, which was used to run a series of tests to assess the effects of ultra long-haul...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORAL WON'T HOST</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/333a646911a34ae2889ed4ae71e8111d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Responding to stinging criticism, President Donald Trump has abruptly reversed his plan to hold the next year's Group of Seven world leaders' meeting at his Doral golf resort in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian newspapers unite in protest against media restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-security-media/australian-newspapers-unite-in-protest-against-media-restrictions-idUSKBN1WZ0ED</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's biggest newspapers were expected to run front pages on Monday m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago's top cop caught sleeping in car after 'couple of drinks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/chicago-police-superintendent-sleeping-car-drinks-dinner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eddie Johnson, the superintendent of Chicago Police, has requested the department investigate him after he was caught sleeping in a car at a stop sign — which the city's mayor claims came after the top cop had "a couple of drinks with dinner."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let jihadists return home, French anti-terror magistrate urges...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/let-jihadists-return-home-french-anti-terror-magistrate-113902292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The refusal of the French government to take back Islamic State fighters from Syria could fuel a new jihadist recruitment drive in France, threatening public safety, a leading anti-terrorism investigator has told AFP. David De Pas, coordinator of France's 12 anti-terrorism examining magistrates,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor says she was fired in sex-for-grades scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/20/laura-jean-champagne-goodwin-college-says-she-was-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former professor at a college in Connecticut says in a lawsuit she was fired for refusing to disclose the name of a student who told her a male professor was offering better grades in exchange for sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Flags All Over for Senate Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationaljournal.com/s/682314?unlock=1EAZFXDRKO5HMK81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New polls and fundraising reports show key GOP senators in political trouble, giving Democrats a solid shot to win back control of the upper chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British soldier jailed for excessive nipple twisting...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2019/10/18/bad-case-of-bullying-british-soldier-jailed-for-excessive-nipple-twisting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The courts reportedly refused to invoke the ancient Mesopotamian Code of Hammurabi and the right to nipple-for-a-nipple retaliation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Mulvaney faced White House ouster threat before impeachment crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/20/politics/mulvaney-white-house-trump-impeachment-inquiry/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney faced internal efforts to oust him before House Democrats moved ahead with their impeachment inquiry against President Donald Trump, multiple sources tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Brady Claims NETFLIX 'Spa' Video Not Mocking Kraft: 'Would Never Do That'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/10/19/tom-brady-netflix-spa-robert-kraft-paul-rudd-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New England Patriots quarterback Tom Brady answered questions Saturday about a video clip that’s taking social media by storm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caught up in middle, US diplomats fight back...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e8d683da132d4250b0af220f56c38389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Three years of simmering frustration inside the State Department is boiling over on Capitol Hill as a parade of current and former diplomats testify to their concerns about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California housing cost drives out middle class...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/10/19/california-housing-crisis-residents-flee-san-francisco-because-costs/3985196002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former bohemian mecca, San Francisco nowÂ lays claim to the most expensive housing in the West, withÂ a median home price of $1.4 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother's stress during pregnancy may affect baby's sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/10/18/stressed-pregnant-women-less-likely-birth-boys-study/3986574002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Columbia University researchers found that stressed mothers are less likely to have male births, as well as an increase in some birth complications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But British govt still says leaving in 11 days...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eu-mulls-johnsons-reluctant-brexit-delay-request-051245011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A defiant British government doubled down Sunday, insisting it would leave the European Union in 11 days' time despite parliament forcing a reluctant prime minister to request another delay. In a day of high drama on Saturday, MPs in the House of Commons passed up the chance to decide on the revised</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour demands 2nd public vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ae28491c5164e38b8632a35c2666ffb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The Latest on Britain's impending departure from the European Union (all times local): 12:45 p.m. The prime minister of Finland, whose country holds the European Union's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Driving Scooters Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/10/can-self-driving-scooters-solve-sidewalk-clutter/600262/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies hope they’ll keep the sidewalks clear, but there’s plenty of reason for skepticism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human waste from homeless makes Miami streets unpleasant, unsanitary ...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/downtown-miami/article236262158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi, other US lawmakers arrive in Jordan for Syria talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/pelosi-other-us-lawmakers-arrive-in-jordan-for-meetings-on-syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and a bipartisan group of U.S. lawmakers announced late Saturday U.S. time that they had arrived in Jordan for meetings with King Abdullah II and other officials regarding the situation in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ERS first NFL team to rely on emotional support dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/19/us/49ers-zoe-emotional-support-dog-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco 49ers are on fire -- but it's their smallest teammate who's stealing the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'New Ohio?' Georgia Dems eye 2020 swing...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/the-new-ohio-georgia-dems-eye-2020-swing-from-rust-belt-sun-belt/LdzGHYfpzX3u6yuqfQbZUL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia Democrats say the state, with a more diverse population and tightening elections, holds more promise for the party than Midwestern states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense chief: US troops leaving Syria to go to Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a66bf441fdfb43ca80d200dcbfb5d09d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABOARD A U.S. MILITARY AIRCRAFT (AP) — Defense Secretary Mark Esper says that under current plans all U.S. troops leaving Syria will go to western Iraq and the military will continue to conduct...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-7 86'D</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-doral-miami-resort-no-longer-hosting-g-9edbb885-c809-4768-87c3-cce1db492eb5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He'd faced criticism from some Republican lawmakers over the move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-7 86'D</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/breaking-trump-announces-doral-resort-no-longer-host-site-for-g-7/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump says he will not hold the next G-7 Summit at a resort he owns, a move that drew immediate criticism last week when it was announced. ....Therefore, based on both Media &amp; Dem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Zuckerberg pushes back against Sanders's call to abolish billionaires... </title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/facebook-s-zuckerberg-pushes-back-against-bernie-sanders-s-call-to-abolish-billionaires-1.603775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worth more than $70 billion, Zuckerberg seemed to express concern in an interview on Fox News that eliminating billionaires in America would stifle competition between private and public actors in funding scientific research and philanthropy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> BALZ:  Dems wonder which of their candidates can beat him...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-Trump-reels-Democrats-wonder-which-of-their-14546913.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are moments in every presidential nomination contest when many strategists, donors and activists can more easily explain why each of the candidates can't win the nomination or the presidency rather than which ones can. That this feeling has begun to grip some Democrats at a time when things are going so badly for President Donald Trump, however, is not at all typical.  On paper, the field of candidates running for the Democratic nomination is everything the party's rank and file might hope for. It is big, offering more choices than ever. It is experienced, with candidates from every level of government and beyond. It includes more women and minorities than ever at a time when their voices are redefining the party. It is generationally and geographically diverse.  Yet, to date, there's been little that has given Democrats the confidence that their nomination process will produce a challenger strong enough, appealing enough and politically skilled enough to withstand what will be a brutal general election against a weakened and vulnerable president. Trump's campaign is already running a general election loaded with cash and with months of time to try to shape voters' perceptions of Democrats negatively before their nominee is even selected.  For Democrats, almost everything about the past week should be grounds for optimism about the shape of the political landscape. The litany of things that happened to or were done by the president in just a few days is beyond comprehension, starting with the case that Trump used the powers of his office to try to damage a political opponent that is at the heart of the impeachment inquiry in the House.  That case against the president appeared to gain strength, with closed-down testimony on Capitol Hill, and it was helped when acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enters key stretch in fragile state...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-s-season-of-weakness-President-who-prizes-14547356.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEASHINGTON - President Donald Trump, whose paramount concern long has been showing strength, has entered the most challenging stretch of his term, weakened on virtually every front and in danger of being forced from office as the impeachment inquiry intensifies.  Trump now finds himself mired in a season of weakness. Foreign leaders feel emboldened to reject his pleas or contradict him. Officials inside his administration are openly defying his wishes by participating in the impeachment probe. Federal courts have ruled against him. Republican lawmakers are criticizing him. He has lost control over major conservative media organs. And polling shows a growing share of Americans disapprove of his job performance and support his impeachment.  Many of Trump's Republican allies revolted over his decision to withdraw U.S. troops in Syria, which triggered a bloody Turkish invasion that killed Kurdish fighters and civilians.  Trump bragged about sending a "very powerful letter" warning Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan not to invade Syria. "Don't be a fool!" Trump wrote. But Turkish officials leaked word that their leader had thrown the letter in the trash, and Erdogan then took Trump to task for his "lack of respect."  "Are we so weak, and so inept diplomatically, that Turkey forced the hand of the United States of America? Turkey?" Sen. Mitt Romney of Utah, the Republican Party's 2012 presidential nominee, said in a speech Thursday denouncing Trump's Syria decision as "a bloodstain in the annals of American history."  Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) wrote an op-ed criticizing the pullout, a rare rebuke of Trump.  "America's wars will be 'endless' only if America refuses to win them," he wrote, referencing Trump's frequent argument that his critics want to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only two fellow candidates defend Tulsi Gabbard from Hillary accusations!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7592415/Tulsi-Gabbard-says-Hillary-Clinton-blood-hands-embodiment-corruption.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tulsi Gabbard hit back at Hillary Clinton on Friday, telling Fox News that the former Secretary of State has 'blood on her hands' because of her support for wars in Iraq and Libya.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE SENDS EU 3 LETTERS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7592073/Boris-Johnson-sends-THREE-letters-EU-one-urge-Brussels-NOT-grant-delay.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first was the letter demanded by the Benn Act, which asks the EU to delay Brexit beyond the October 31 deadline - but not signed by the PM - using the exact wording specified in the legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong activists wear Joker and Winnie-the-Pooh masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7590823/Hong-Kong-activists-wear-Joker-Winnie-Pooh-masks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro-democracy demonstrators in Hong Kong gathered along the city's subway lines in cartoon masks depicting characters like Winnie-the-Pooh and Guy Fawkes on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS tests passengers, pilots' brains on world's longest flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7586741/Longest-non-stop-flight-New-York-Sydney.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian airline Qantas is testing the longest, non-stop flight from New York City to Sydney that will take around 20 hours to complete and researchers will be on board to monitor passengers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol says women 'equally capable of crime' as men as it reveals most-wanted list...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/europol-says-women-equally-capable-161633519.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europol has revealed the names of Europe's most-wanted fugitives - and 18 of the 21 criminals on the list are women, warning they are “equally capable” of committing serious crimes as men. Called the "Crime has no gender" campaign, Europe's policing agency on Friday rolled out a new</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE APP IPHONE...</title>
      <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/official-drudge-report-free/id375614185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apps.apple.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‎Welcome to the all new version 6 of the one and only official app of the Drudge Report. Here's all you need to know to use the app to it's fullest: *** NOTIFICATIONS *** On first open, iOS will ask you to allow notifications. Tapping allow results in alerts being sent your phone whenever there is…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS FLASHBACK:  'Would rather be dead in a ditch'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/sep/05/boris-johnson-rather-be-dead-in-ditch-than-agree-brexit-extension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officer falls ill after standing in sun as Johnson delivered often rambling speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKY NEWS Brexit-Free Channel Offers Relief...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brexit-got-you-down-sky-news-brexit-free-channel-offers-relief/ar-AAJ1mxf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot judges 'will pass sentence with no human bias' in AI courts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/robot-judges-will-pass-sentence-20648849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasing use of AI in legal system points the way to an all-robot courtroom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeWork value plunges $29 billion  -- in 9 months!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/wework-value-8-billion-c65ba7d7-32d8-4748-a33f-c0c159d2fd84.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rescue plan also comes after the company slammed the brakes on its IPO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump cranks out executive orders after bashing Obama for doing same...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-obama-executive-orders-8bb2a175-b09a-42c8-8d71-2b0720759c3a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has relied on executive orders to tackle some of his biggest campaign promises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coppola backs Scorsese in row over MARVEL films...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coppola-backs-scorsese-row-over-marvel-films-173112180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Francis Ford Coppola jumped into a controversy over the Marvel superhero movies Saturday, not just backing fellow director Martin Scorsese's critique of the films but denouncing them as "despicable". Earlier this month Scorsese, director of classics such as "Taxi Driver" and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE BLOWOUT IN QUEENS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f646f91c070e405d93beb53e8a2047d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Storming past questions about his health, Bernie Sanders vowed that he's "more ready than ever" to fight for a political revolution — with a little help from new friends — at a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fonda returns to civil disobedience for 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49691207fb434fa392fd7443bf07f8a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Inspired by the climate activism of a Swedish teenager, Jane Fonda says she's returning to civil disobedience nearly a half-century after she was last arrested at a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eCI5D5hHWt0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shows Starting October 25 Limited Tickets https://jesusisking.imax.com/tickets #JesusIsKing #KanyeWest #IMAX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan vows to 'crush the heads' of Kurdish forces if no pullout...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/erdogan-vows-to-crush-the-heads-of-kurdish-forces-if-no-pullout-by-deadline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish president threatens Kurdish fighters if they don't withdraw from planned safe zone by Tuesday evening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Grow in Lebanon as Anger Explodes at Political Elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/middleeast/middleeast-top-stories/protests-grow-in-lebanon-as-anger-explodes-at-political-elite/ar-AAJ2160?li=BBJGzsi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Tarantino Won't Recut 'HOLLYWOOD' for China...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/quentin-tarantino-wont-recut-once-a-time-china-1248720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country's regulators pulled the film from the schedule a week before its release Oct. 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye Aims to Save Souls...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kanye-west-aims-save-souls-jesus-is-king-trailer-1248878 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concert film will be released exclusively in Imax theaters around the world on Oct. 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streisand Shares Photo of Pelosi Killing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/10/19/barbra-streisand-shares-photo-of-nancy-pelosi-killing-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Left-wing actor and Grammy-winning singer Barbra Streisand posted a photo to Twitter early Saturday depicting a bloodied President Donald Trump being impaled by the heel of a shoe with the word "Pelosi" emblazoned on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady visits massage parlor in NETFLIX cameo that will make Robert Kraft squirm...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/19/tom-brady-visits-massage-parlor-in-netflix-cameo-that-will-make-robert-kraft-squirm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady can throw shade, too. Fans are calling the QB a “legend” off the field for a Hollywood cameo that will hit particularly close to home for his boss, New England Patriots owner …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT DELAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/10169227/brexit-news-boris-johnson-saturday-vote-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson will write to the EU to ask for another Brexit delay TONIGHT after Tory rebel Sir Oliver Letwin trashed his chance to make history today. In a day of high-drama in the House of Common…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubting death: How our brains shield us from mortal truth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/oct/19/doubting-death-how-our-brains-shield-us-from-mortal-truth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brain seems to categorise death as something that only befalls other people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT TODAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/19/uk-lawmakers-back-a-change-to-brexit-vote-which-delays-full-approval-and-forces-deadline-extension.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House of Commons sat for a historic Saturday session and lawmakers were due to have a "meaningful vote" on Johnson's new deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIOTS STUN CHILE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chile-president-declares-state-emergency-violent-protests-070230347.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Chile's capital awoke Saturday to a ravaged city as burned-out buses, bikes and garbage littered the streets after a day of violent protests that prompted the government to declare a state of emergency and call out soldiers to maintain order for the first time in decades. The stunning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191019133903-wrh6q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 8-Johnson defiant after British parliament votes to force Brexit delay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unveils biggest ancient coffin find in century...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-archaeology-luxor-idUSKBN1WY0C5 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt on Saturday unveiled the details of 30 ancient wooden coffins with mummies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Water System Collapsing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/19/world/americas/venezuela-water.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To understand how far it has deteriorated, The New York Times ran tests and found dangerous levels of bacteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican House member 'thinking' about impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/54ebdce60d6c4075a3a9e8c7447fc1d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump gave an atta-boy to Republican Rep. Francis Rooney last year on the congressman's home turf in swing state Florida. "I love it when he defends me,"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confronted by impeachment, Trump adds to chaos...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49fd63d02be24f5daad0bba353edc738</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The impeachment investigation into President Donald Trump has thrust Washington into a political crisis. And Trump keeps adding to the chaos. In the four weeks since House...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
