<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to Be Covered by Global Tax Deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report-international/amazon-set-to-be-covered-by-global-tax-deal-despite-thin-margins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global policy makers are crafting their international tax plan to make sure Amazon.com Inc. is included, even though the U.S. company’s profit margin is below the 10% proposed threshold that would give other countries rights to collect revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big win for Merkel's party confounds pundits, pollsters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/the-strategic-vote-in-saxony-anhalt-big-win-for-merkel-cdu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor’s CDU romped home in state of Saxony-Anhalt despite polls suggesting close race with far right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Turning Water-Scarcity Crisis into Weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/06/china-is-turning-its-water-scarcity-crisis-into-a-weapon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antagonizing neighbors, imposing top-down solutions, and not actually solving the underlying problem — as China in other areas, so with water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise line reverses course on requiring jabs for passengers...</title>
      <link>https://local12.com/news/coronavirus/one-cruise-line-has-already-reversed-course-on-requiring-vaccinations-for-passengers-royal-caribbean-ron-desantis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;local12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (CNN/CNN Newsource/WKRC) - The cruise industry is getting ready to set sail once again but a political storm brewing on land &amp;ndash; one between Florida Governor Ron DeSantis and the Centers for Disease Control &amp;ndash; suggests it will be anything but smooth sailing. Right now, most cruise lines are advertising new summer sailings with vaccination requirements. But Royal Caribbean abruptly changed course on Friday. Only its ships departing from Seattle and the Bahamas on or before Aug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian neo-Nazis plotted to bomb NATO base...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/italian-neo-nazis-were-plotting-to-bomb-nato-base-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carabinieri raided the homes of 12 alleged members of an extremist group on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Steps up Efforts to Sow Discord Inside USA...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6071615/iran-disinformation-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian state actors are intensifying their disinformation campaign on social media to spread discord and anti-Semitic tropes inside the U.S., two U.S. intelligence officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabbed in park hours before announcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-stabbed-in-central-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was stabbed on the east side of Central Park late Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY MASK WARS MAY NEVER END...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-the-mask-culture-wars-may-never-end-163722944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masks have been divisive from the start, and even though the pandemic appears to be nearing its end in much of the United States, mask-related divisions remain as wide as ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREAT REOPENING SHOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/entertainment/new-york-city-pplans-a-central-park-mega-concert-to-celebrate-reopening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lineup hasn't been announced for the Aug. 21 event, but producer Clive Davis, who has worked with numerous big names, says he's aiming for eight "iconic" stars for the event, which will be televised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planned Parenthood loses lawsuit over Texas 'Sanctuary City for the Unborn'...</title>
      <link>https://thetexan.news/planned-parenthood-lawsuit-against-lubbock-abortion-ban-dismissed-by-u-s-district-judge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thetexan.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Plaintiffs admit that this Court cannot force the city to revoke or amend its ordinance," Judge Hendrix wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious video...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/07/suspicious-floyd-mayweather-logan-paul-video-emerges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exhibition boxing match between Logan Paul and Floyd Mayweather on Sunday night was a farce for many reasons – but a video clip from the fight suggests it may have gone as far as to be fixed. W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and O'Reilly to embark on MAGA Arena Tour... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/7/donald-trump-conduct-history-tour-his-presidency-t/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump announced Monday that he will go on a “history tour” to discuss his presidency for paying customers at arenas in Florida and Texas in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS HE WEARING A DIAPER?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3030920/americans-convinced-donald-trump-diaper-bulge-north-carolina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE were speculating online that former president Donald Trump was wearing a diaper after they spotted a bulge in his suit trousers during his speech to Republicans in North Carolina. Trump addr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHENEY: Republicans Voted Against Impeaching Out of Fear For Personal Safety...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/liz-cheney-gop-members-of-congress-told-her-they-voted-not-to-impeach-trump-due-to-personal-security-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Liz Cheney revealed to David Axelrod that multiple GOP members of Congress told her they did not vote to impeach Trump due to concerns about their safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Last Time He'll Step In Ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/boxing/news/floyd-mayweather-vs-logan-paul-fight-results-highlights-money-impresses-as-exhibition-goes-the-distance/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The retired pound-for-pound great wasn't able to finish his much larger opponent, but he was crisp throughout the eight-round affair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves Alzheimer's drug despite 'lack of evidence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fda-alzheimers-drug-biogen-2a729516-4c7e-46f1-8d1f-a3e716a7e13e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA ignored the advice of its independent expert panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at Mo'Nique After She Slams Black Women for Wearing 'Bonnets and Slippers' in Public...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/06/04/monique-unapologetic-for-comments-about-black-women-and-bonnets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mo'Nique says she's "unapologetic" for an Instagram post telling Black women to fix themselves up before they go out in public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico President's Grip on Congress Slips, Showing Limits of His Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/07/mexico-presidents-grip-on-congress-slips-showing-limits-of-his-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — Mexico’s leftist ruling coalition was on track to lose its absolute majority in Congress following midterm elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes won't hear challenge to male-only military draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/07/politics/supreme-court-military-draft/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Monday declined to hear a constitutional challenge to the male-only registration requirement for the draft filed by a group called the National Coalition for Men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels says attorney in contact with prosecutors investigating Trump Org...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/557110-stormy-daniels-my-attorney-is-in-contact-with-new-york-investigators-as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels says her lawyer has been in touch with prosecutors in New York City who are investigating former President Trump's company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticks on 'quest' for blood at CA beaches. Lyme disease rising risk?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ticks-quest-blood-californias-beaches-120016167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyme disease-carrying ticks usually found in woodlands and fields are spreading along California's beaches, carried by an unknown host.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative talk host once backed election recount. Now warning Republicans against it...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/conservative-talk-radio-host-once-130014093.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Broomhead, a talk radio host in Phoenix, used to support a local audit of the 2020 election. Now he's urging fellow Republicans to reconsider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jails emptied in pandemic. Should they stay that way?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-5f212e27598df815243ef90a7aea4dc5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn’t long after Matthew Reed shoplifted a $63 set of sheets from a Target in upstate New York that the coronavirus pandemic brought the world to a standstill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul v Mayweather ends in boos...</title>
      <link>hhttps://www.msn.com/en-gb/sport/boxing/logan-paul-v-floyd-mayweather-ends-in-boos-as-each-fighter-makes-millions/ar-AAKM7UX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans have 'untapped' ability to regenerate body parts, scientists claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9660023/Humans-untapped-ability-regenerate-body-parts-just-like-salamanders-scientists-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studying axolotls helped experts from MDI Biological Laboratory in Bar Harbor, Maine, to conclude humans have an 'untapped' ability to regenerate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON off hook AGAIN?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jun/06/global-g7-deal-may-let-amazon-off-hook-on-tax-say-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: communique from ministers suggests deal only applies to ‘profit exceeding a 10% margin’, which could rule out Amazon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan fury at Floyd fix...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/boxing/article-9659389/Furious-boxing-fans-claim-Logan-Pauls-exhibition-bout-against-Floyd-Mayweather-FIXED.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayweather dominated the contest at the Hard Rock Stadium in Miami but was surprisingly unable to stop Paul, with the rookie surviving the full eight rounds of their exhibition bout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 historic deal on global tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/05/g-7-nations-reach-historic-deal-on-global-tax-reform.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's most powerful economies have been at odds over taxation for some time. The goal is to make sure companies are paying taxes to the proper regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation of seabirds wiped out by drone. Now, scientists fear for future...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/generation-seabirds-wiped-drone-o-110013203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 3,000 elegant terns fled the Bolsa Chica Ecological Reserve after the May 12 crash, in the largest egg abandonment scientists who work there can recall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE to change ad practices in landmark antitrust deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607103602-q5x39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-GOOGLE/ANTITRUST (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Google to change global advertising practices in landmark antitrust deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-tax-reform-technology-government-and-politics-business-12736e0426f0898a1a3bc187e3c4dfc1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The Group of Seven wealthy democracies agreed Saturday to support a global minimum corporate tax of at least 15% to deter multinational companies from avoiding taxes by stashing profits in low-rate countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gluten-Free Generation: Children With Celiac Disease Doubles in 25 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gluten-free-children-celiac-disaese-doubled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with celiac disease produce antibodies to gluten, a protein found in wheat, barley and rye, ingredients which are commonly used to make a variety of tasty foods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital patient dies after security guard performs surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210607-hospital-patient-dies-after-security-guard-performs-surgery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospital patient dies after security guard performs surgery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president keeps Congress but loses shine in mid-term vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607061347-y28qh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-ELECTION/ (PIX, TV):Mexican president keeps Congress but loses shine in mid-term vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Turkish mafia boss dishes dirt, becomes YOUTUBE phenomenon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-middle-east-health-coronavirus-pandemic-6868c1563a1152712bd2b2191445da95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — From alleged drug trafficking and a murder cover-up to weapons transfers to Islamic militants, a convicted crime ringleader has been dishing the dirt on members of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s ruling party through a series of tell-all videos that have captivated the nation and turned him into an unlikely social media phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sedition Hunters' Turn Capitol Insurrection Into Ultimate Online Manhunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2021-capitol-riot-sedition-hunters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amateur sleuths have turned the Washington D.C. insurrection on Jan. 6 into the ultimate online manhunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul v Mayweather ends in boos...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jun/07/logan-paul-vs-floyd-mayweather-boxing-fight-result-earnings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight between one of the greatest boxers in history and one of the best YouTube personalities in his family ended in predictable fashion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-haulers report improvement after vaccination, surprising experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/many-long-haul-covid-19-patients-report-improvement-after-vaccination-surprising-experts/ar-AAKKWI4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Wendy French of northwest suburban Lake in the Hills used to run 10 miles a day several times a week before she caught COVID-19 in September, which left her fatigued and suffering from a variety of symptoms for months after the virus was supposedly gone. The previously healthy 45-year-old stopped running and even began dreading typical household chores such as doing laundry, because ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His lonely war in Room 533: How patient fought to keep his life from crumbling...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lonely-war-room-533-covid-120059820.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Perry, who by his own sheer grit built a middle-class life for his family in Compton, was waging battle on two fronts: Fighting against COVID-19, and trying desperately to hold on to everything he had worked for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is someone stalking you? Tiny trackers make it alarmingly easy...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2021/06/06/news/nation/tiny-trackers-make-it-alarmingly-easy-for-someone-to-stalk-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proliferation of tracking devices — particularly the type of popular gadgets being sold to help you find your belongings, such as your wallet, keys or luggage — have led to an increase in fears of stalking, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When missing people don't want to be found: 'I'd removed myself to push the world away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/jun/05/when-missing-people-dont-want-to-be-found-id-removed-myself-to-push-world-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happens if you decide to disappear – then find yourself plastered over the internet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX RATES FALL OFF</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccination-rates-fall-off-imperiling-biden-e2-80-99s-july-fourth-goal/ar-AAKLD5I?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ‘last mile’ of delivering coronavirus shots has become a marathon, with health officials showing up at stores, parks and factories to entice people who might not otherwise get immunized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nowadays, having fun needs to be taken seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/with-pandemic-problems-easing-having-real-fun-needs-to-be-taken-seriously/ar-AAKLfZd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoyment can be social or solitary, something new or old. “Fun is a counterweight to the burdens of life, such as work, school and parenting” in today’s world, one expert says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  APPLE's tightly controlled App Store is teeming with scams...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/apple-s-tightly-controlled-app-store-is-teeming-with-scams/ar-AAKL0TG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple claims its App Store is carefully curated so that only the best apps get through. The truth is, the App Store is littered with scams and "fleeceware," which uses fake user ratings to trick customers into paying for something they don't want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Businesses Raise Fears of Future Lockdowns as Cases Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-k-businesses-raise-fears-of-future-lockdowns-as-cases-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Businesses Raise Fears of Future Lockdowns as Cases Rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PANTS STEAL SHOW AT COMEBACK SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/06/06/donald-trump-pants-backwards-speech-fly-north-carolina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump traveled to North Carolina for a speech to Republicans, but the headline may be in his pants!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eilish tough time on charts...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/06/billie-eilishs-latest-single-lost-cause-is-an-actual-lost-cause-image-change-from-slacker-to-femme-fatale-may-be-cause</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billie Eilish, the teen phenom with 7 Grammy Awards from 2020, and more still this past year, is having a tough time on the charts right now. On Thursday she dropped her latest single, called &amp;#822…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We all said a little prayer, but we're good'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-da90ee6c8e2f6eccd7228faad7a137db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOINT BASE ANDREWS, Md. (AP) — A technical issue that involved “no major safety concerns” forced Vice President Kamala Harris' plane to return to Joint Base Andrews in Maryland about 30 minutes after she had left Sunday on a trip to Guatemala and Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grievances cloud Republican agenda...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-election-2020-campaign-2016-senate-elections-government-and-politics-861ce4d1c92c8026c5312a9ea922cf22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Republicans are fighting to seize control of Congress. Just don't ask what they'd do if they win. Look no further for evidence of the GOP's muddled governing agenda than battleground North Carolina, where party leaders packed into a convention hall Saturday night to cheer former President Donald Trump .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador looks to become world's first country to adopt crypto as legal tender...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-el-salvador-health-coronavirus-pandemic-technology-b1c08cae170aede89ea5cb41d97048cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador (AP) — El Salvador President Nayib Bukele announced in a recorded message played at a Bitcoin conference in Miami that next week he will send proposed legislation to the country's congress that would make the cryptocurrency legal tender in the Central American nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris in Air Force 2 scare...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3029035/air-force-two-kamala-harris-mexico-guatamala-trip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AIR Force Two was forced to return due to a “technical issue” just 30 minutes after Kamala Harris took off on Sunday for her first international trip as vice president. Harris is travel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First international trip cut short after 30 minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/vice-president-plane-return-guatemala-mexico-ab98ff30-cf79-44ac-bed4-524396dfed5c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m good, I’m good. We all said a little prayer, but we’re good,” Harris told reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin's opposition clouds future of Dem bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-voting-rights-bills-elections-government-and-politics-3eb2968199c9ceccd537c01c4cfdfb0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A key Democratic senator says he will not vote for the largest overhaul of U.S. election law in at least a generation, leaving no plausible path forward for legislation that his party and the White House have portrayed as crucial for protecting access to the ballot.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
