<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China releases first images taken by its Mars rover...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/19/asia/china-mars-rover-first-images-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has released the first images taken by its Mars rover, Zhurong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of 'third intifada'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/third-intifada-west-bank-protests-israel-3bc3d572-8633-476f-86af-1300a0b1c146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four Palestinians were killed on Tuesday and 15 since the clashes began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist Ocasio-Cortez's TESLA Parked Illegally Outside WHOLE FOODS...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/socialist-tesla-whole-foods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like most celebrities, Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D., N.Y.) doesn't always play by the rules. Sources inform the Washington Free Beacon that the socialist congresswoman's white Tesla was parked illegally outside the Whole Foods near her posh apartment complex in Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Oregon counties vote to explore joining Idaho...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/may/19/five-oregon-counties-vote-to-explore-joining-idaho/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five eastern Oregon counties voted Tuesday in support of considering becoming part of Idaho.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists show how LSD opens doors of perception...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/may/19/acid-test-scientists-show-how-lsd-opens-doors-of-perception</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study analysing brain scans of people finds psychedelic drug lowers barriers that constrain thoughts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightfoot only speaking to reporters of color...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/lightfoot-slams-overwhelming-whiteness-of-chicago-press-defends-only-speaking-to-reporters-of-color</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot, D., defended her controversial announcement to only give individual interviews to journalists of color Wednesday and blasted Chicago media institutions for their "overwhelming whiteness and maleness.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are young men so scared of sex?</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/topic/young-men-scared-sex-sexting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reality is that what young men really want these days is not action, but talk; not sex, but smut. This may be dismaying to oldies like me</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey business: Researchers find origins of Florida colony...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fl-state-wire-florida-environment-and-nature-1383d2be8f47e5597d86bffb16b10e4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANIA BEACH, Fla. (AP) — A colony of monkeys has lived for about 70 years in urban South Florida, near jets taking off from a nearby airport and fuel storage tanks. No one was quite sure where they came from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly dims skyline after 'mass collision' kills thousands of birds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/19/us/philadelphia-skyline-dimming-birds-collision/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly twenty buildings in Philadelphia are dimming their lights this spring after thousands of birds perished in the city's largest mass collision in recent history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brink of fertility crisis: Plummeting sperm counts caused by everyday products...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfaa.com/article/news/health/male-fertility-rate-sperm-count-falling/67-9f65ab4c-5e55-46d3-8aea-1843a227d848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfaa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 40-year-long study showed sperm counts have dropped by nearly half. Dr. Shanna Swan hypothesizes men will no longer produce sperm by 2045.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Country on Cusp of New Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-country-is-on-the-cusp-of-a-new-era/ar-BB1gUT5j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America is inching closer to a possibility it has never seen before: the indictment and trial of a former president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium on alert after rogue soldier threatens virus expert...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210519-belgium-on-alert-after-rogue-soldier-threatens-virus-expert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Belgium on alert after rogue soldier threatens virus expert</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Germany, Early Vax Shot Comes With Disapproving Looks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-germany-an-early-covid-vaccine-shot-comes-with-disapproving-looks/ar-BB1gTZS9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAMBURG, Germany — When a young woman showed up at Hamburg’s giant Covid vaccination site last week, the city officials who check whether people are eligible were skeptical. She was in her mid 20s; shots are being given mainly to those 60 and older. But she said she qualified for an exemption because she was caring for her infirm mother and produced a form to make her case. Without a signature from her mother, the form was invalid and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK SAYS NO...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/boris-johnson-holidays-abroad-eu-uk-mps-pmqs-international-travel-b935942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Visit EU if you’ve had two doses of vaccine’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of PPP Loans Went to Fake Farms in Absurd Places...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/ppp-farms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An online lending platform called Kabbage sent 378 pandemic loans worth $7 million to fake companies (mostly farms) with names like “Deely Nuts” and “Beefy King.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Perry stuns fans with slurred speech in 'FRIENDS' reunion promo...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/05/19/matthew-perry-slurs-speech-in-friends-reunion-promo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 51-year-old actor had an odd stare and a labored speech pattern in a video promoting the upcoming HBO Max special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS BANS MOST ABORTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/story/news/politics/state/2021/05/19/abbott-heartbeat-ban-abortion-law-signed/5128325001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Greg Abbott signed into law a ban on abortions once a fetal heartbeat is detected, which will effectively ban most abortions in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court delights conservatives with action on wish list...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-delights-conservatives-with-action-on-wish-list/ar-BB1gTvKo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court is offering hints of the kind of paradigm shift conservatives have long craved by adding major abortion and gun-rights cases to its docket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM AND BUST?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/crypto-craze-waited-for-everyone-to-get-in-before-coming-undone/ar-BB1gUFXS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like many things in markets, Bitcoin managed to maximize the pain. Its rise went on just long enough to pull in a bunch of otherwise sensible money. And then it made them pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany vows to crack down on antisemitism at protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/germany-vows-to-crack-down-on-antisemitism-at-israel-protests-668488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, Germany made it illegal to publicly destroy or damage the flag of a foreign state with which they have diplomatic relations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey's anti-Israel obsession reaches new heights...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/turkeys-anti-israel-obsession-reaches-new-heights-668494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the recent statements include a demand by Turkey to separate Jerusalem from Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're all screwed:' Kimmel rips network TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/jimmy-kimmel-abc-upfront-2021-1234955049/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy Kimmel roasted the post-pandemic broadcast television landscape at Disney’s annual upfront presentation Tuesday. The late night host delivered a searing stand-up routine during the comp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  Man's finger bitten off in latest NYC attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/police-probe-brutal-attack-on-west-side-as-a-hate-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attacker repeatedly punched his victim in the face and yelled, "Go back to your country," and then bit the man's fingers, severing a fingertip, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless brawl in subway...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/homeless-rumble-in-harlem-subway-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of homeless men got into a fight on a subway platform in what was described as a territory dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  SMASHED ALL PC TABOOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g9OCReTZRIo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(((█▬█ █ ▀█▀ subscribe, █▬█ █ ▀█▀ like &amp; comment)))) ⏺Music Channel - https://youtu.be/SjfkVEQ1gaAFOR PROMOTIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. NO COPYRIGHT INTENDED ------...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising sport to explode in Texas: Cricket...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfaa.com/article/sports/cricket-leagues-grow-north-texas-collin-county/287-921a25eb-cb51-47cf-ac20-9e9fca69ca03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfaa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Texas has three large recreational cricket leagues and a total of more than 300 teams. Games are played day and night, nearly every day of the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMIC GENIUS MOONEY DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/05/19/comedian-paul-mooney-dead-dies-79/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedic legend Paul Mooney dead at 79.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREER SPANNED DECADES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/2917232/paul-mooney-dead-sudden-heart-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PAUL Mooney has died at the age of 79 after he suffered a sudden heart attack, a publicist for the comic confirmed to The Sun. The actor, known as the Godfather of Comedy, was at home in Oakland, C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollster Luntz claimed was impartial -- but paid by Cruz!</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/05/19/gop-pollster-frank-luntz-claimed-to-be-impartial--but-was-paid-by-ted-cruz-during-2018-texas-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson has blasted GOP pollster (and Kevin McCarthy pal) as a "fraud." Turns out he may have a point</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No sign of Israel-Gaza ceasefire as fighting rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/ceasefire-still-elusive-israel-gaza-conflict-2021-05-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Joe Biden pushed Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Wednesday to reduce tensions in the Gaza conflict on the path to a ceasefire, a White House spokeswoman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE HEAT ON THE DON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/new-york-ag-s-offic-opens-criminal-probe-trump-organization-n1267887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether the former president's business had inflated the value of its assets for the purposes of tax breaks and loans has reportedly been the key issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Zucker poised for comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/media/ts-warnermedia-discovery-deal-jeff-zucker-poised-comeback-rcna967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Zucker appeared headed for the exit. Now, sources say he is in prime position to take on a larger role at a unified WarnerMedia and Discovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Gitmo prisoners approved for release...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/three-guantanamo-prisoners-approved-for-release/ar-BB1gSnjn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three of the 40 prisoners still at the Guantanamo Bay US military prison have been approved for release, a lawyer for one said Tuesday, the first such approvals under the administration of President Joe Biden. The three included Pakistani Saifullah Paracha, who at 73 is the oldest of those still held, nearly two decades after the United States detained hundreds of suspects in the wake of the September 11, 2001 attacks. The others approved for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiring troubles prompt employers to eye automation, machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hiring-troubles-prompt-some-employers-to-eye-automation-and-machines/ar-BB1gTERH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From warehouses to oil fields, artificial intelligence, robots and advanced software are leaving a mark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE PLANS TO ACTIVATE MAGA RALLIES FOR BATTLE!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-plans-to-resume-his-trademark-rallies-in-june/ar-BB1gI6wO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The often-raucous events were a staple of Trump’s campaigns in 2016 and 2020 and during his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second-Largest Country in World Running Out of Land...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/the-second-largest-country-in-the-world-is-running-out-of-land/ar-BB1gS4Tr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian dream of a house with a yard is becoming unaffordable as real estate prices surge and space to build runs short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chip Crisis Danger Zone; Record Wait Times...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/chip-crisis-in-danger-zone-as-wait-times-reach-new-record/ar-BB1gSPRz?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortages in the semiconductor industry, which have already slammed automakers and consumer electronics companies, are getting even worse, complicating the global economy’s recovery from the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK-FUELED BITCOIN RALLY COLLAPSES...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-plunges-to-38000-as-elon-musk-fueled-rally-collapses/ar-BB1gTobc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crypto bubble that inflated Bitcoin’s value past $1 trillion and added billions to nonsense digital tokens overnight is bursting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: HORROR SEQUEL SOMETHING TO SCREAM ABOUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/entertainment/movies/a-quiet-place-part-ii-review-e2-80-93-emily-blunt-horror-is-something-to-scream-about/ar-BB1gSOaY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;T he first Quiet Place movie emitted the most piercing silent scream imaginable. This sequel from writer-director John Krasinski may not quite have all its focus and intimate horror, while the borrowings from Alien, Jurassic Park and Jaws are admittedly more obvious this time around. But it’s a really effective and engrossing followup, with an absolutely sensational “prelude” sequence at the top of the movie, a barnstorming shocker equal to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mysterious mass' found on NC coast. What is blob baffling experts?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article251517373.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Short on answers, wildlife experts asked the public to weigh in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON Shaman Attorney Defends Rioters as 'Short Bus People'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/qanon-shaman-attorney-defends-his-client-and-alleged-capitol-rioters-as-short-bus-people-in-wild-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Missouri-based lawyer representing Jacob Chansley (AKA the "QAnon Shaman") has offered a highly...um...unorthodox defense of his client.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He bragged at dentist's office about attending Capitol riot. Patient turned him in...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/He-bragged-at-the-dentist-s-office-about-16186966.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than a week after the failed insurrection at the U.S. Capitol, a patient at a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Drinking ANY alcohol harmful to brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9595095/Drinking-alcohol-harmful-brain-study-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's 'no safe dose of alcohol for the brain', according to a team of scientists from the University of Oxford.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riots break out at holy sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9592101/Riots-break-Jerusalems-holy-sites-Israeli-troops-fire-tear-gas-Palestinians.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tear gas was fired at demonstrators at Damascus Gate, around half a mile from Temple Mount where clashes last Monday at Al-Aqsa Mosque provoked a barrage of missiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York AG's office opens criminal probe into Trump Org...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/18/politics/new-york-attorney-general-trump-organization-criminal-probe/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Attorney General Letitia James is joining the Manhattan district attorney's office in a criminal investigation of the Trump Organization, James' office said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA, COINBASE PLUNGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/19/tesla-coinbase-lead-drop-in-crypto-related-stocks-as-bitcoin-plunges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency related stocks led by Tesla and Coinbase fell Wednesday as bitcoin dropped to new session lows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel backing rival to Musk brain implant company...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/19/peter-thiel-is-backing-a-rival-to-elon-musks-neuralink-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palantir co-founder and venture capitalist Peter Thiel has invested in a company that's putting computer chips into people's heads in a bid to improve them in some way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homebuyers applying for ever bigger mortgages as prices soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/19/homebuyers-are-applying-for-ever-bigger-mortgages-as-home-prices-soar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky-high home prices mean demand for ever bigger mortgages, but those prices may also be causing a pullback in homebuying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13-year-olds can now trade stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/marketing-children-consumers-media-trading-b5452fde-0858-4f67-937f-b34e12946d4c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kids are a lucrative market given how much younger they are developing online habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to Monitor Military Personnel Social Media...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/05/17/military-pentagon-extremism-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The military has previously balked at surveilling service members for extremist political views due to First Amendment protections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask mountain sets new recycling challenge...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-05-pandemic-mask-mountain-recycling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in Australia want to transform single-use COVID masks into road material. In the United States, the protective gear is recycled into benches. And in France, they are reborn as floor carpets for cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Fourth Stimulus In Works?</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/18/stimulus-check-update-fourth-relief-payment-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the latest round of stimulus checks already distributed to most eligible Americans, many wonder if additional aid is coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Madman, racist, sexist pig': Book details Obama thoughts on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/madman-racist-sexist-pig-book-144221663.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic ex-president was candid in remarks to donors and advisers, according to Battle for the Soul by Edward-Isaac Dovere President Barack Obama greets President-elect Donald Trump at his inauguration on 20 January 2017. Photograph: Carlos Barría/Reuters For much of Donald Trump’s presidency, Barack Obama largely abided by the convention that former presidents do not publicly criticize or attack their successors. Obama jettisoned any such caution during the 2020 election that put his own vice-president, Joe Biden, in the White House. But behind the scenes, with donors and advisers, Obama was reportedly much more candid. According to a new book, Obama called Trump a “madman”, a “racist, sexist pig”, “that fucking lunatic” and a “corrupt motherfucker”. The remarks are reported in Battle for the Soul: Inside the Democrats’ Campaigns to Defeat Donald Trump by Edward-Isaac Dovere, a staff writer at the Atlantic, which will be published next week. The Guardian obtained a copy. Extracts of Dovere’s candid reporting have been published elsewhere – including a passage in which the now first lady, Jill Biden, is quoted as saying now Vice-President Kamala Harris should “go fuck herself” after a memorable debate-stage attack on Joe Biden early in the primary. The reported remarks by Obama about Trump seem likely to prompt an angry reaction from the 45th president. Trump still has huge power over the Republican party. But he is in increasing political and legal jeopardyfrom a prospective 9/11-style commission into the 6 January Capitol attack and multiple investigations into his financial affairs. Trump’s loathing for Obama is well-known and oft-expressed, beginning with his championing of the racist birther conspiracy which said Obama was not qualified to be president. Obama’s feelings are well-known, but have rarely been reported in such blunt detail. Dovere reports that Obama first preferred the prospect of Trump as president to Ted Cruz, because Trump was nowhere near as clever as the hard-right Texas senator, the runner-up in the Republican primary in 2016. But from 2017, as reality swiftly set in, Obama reacted like many in the US and around the world. “He’s a madman,” Dovere reports Obama telling “big donors looking to squeeze a reaction out of him in exchange for the big checks they were writing to his foundation”. “More often: ‘I didn’t think it would be this bad.’ Sometimes: ‘I didn’t think we’d have a racist, sexist pig.’ Depending on the outrage of the day … a passing ‘that fucking lunatic’ with a shake of his head.” Obama’s strongest remark, Dovere reports, was prompted by reports that Trump was speaking to foreign leaders – including Vladimir Putin, amid the investigation of Russian election interference and links between Trump and Moscow – without any aides on the call. “‘That corrupt motherfucker,’ he remarked.” Like Lucky: How Joe Biden Barely Won the Presidency, by Jonathan Allen and Amie Parnes, Dovere also reports extensively on a relationship between Obama and Biden that was not as smooth as might have been thought given their eight years in power together. Like Allen and Parnes, Dovere reports Obama’s vocal doubts, shared by much of the Democratic establishment, that Biden was too old and perhaps past his best. Dovere also reports perhaps Biden’s key campaign insight, that Democrats including campaign rivals and he and Obama when in power were not sufficiently focused on the working- and middle-class voters who gave Trump his victory over Hillary Clinton in 2016. In an interview, Biden describes the size of the challenge he found after succeeding in his third attempt to be president, close to his 78th birthday and in the middle of a global pandemic. “I remember someone saying, ‘Joe, now you caught the car.’ I said, ‘No, I think I got the bus.’ I’m the dog that caught the bus.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face recognition, fake identities, digital surveillance: Post office covert ops...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facial-recognition-fake-identities-and-digital-surveillance-tools-inside-the-post-offices-covert-internet-operations-program-214234762.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The post office’s law enforcement arm has faced intense scrutiny in recent weeks over its Internet Covert Operations Program, which tracks social media posts of Americans and shares that information with other law enforcement agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Investigate Possible Jewish Hate Crime Attack At BEVERLY GROVE Restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/19/police-investigate-possible-jewish-hate-crime-attack-at-beverly-grove-restaurant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Witnesses said a mob of pro-Palestinians attacked a group of Jewish men who were dining at the restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob Violence Fueled by Groups on WHATSAPP...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/19/mob-violence-against-palestinians-in-israel-is-fueled-by-groups-on-whatsapp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Wednesday, a message appeared in a new WhatsApp channel called “Death to the Arabs.” The message urged Israelis to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Motorist Driving TESLA 82 MPH -- While Asleep...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/05/18/tesla-sleeping-driver-wisconsin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He claims he was awake, but police say a Palatine man was asleep at the wheel while driving his Tesla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers weighing which emergency orders should become law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ri-state-wire-laws-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-health-ccb2f3fb61df371c155ca3fd2609276f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — More than a year after COVID-19 upended Beacon Hill, Massachusetts lawmakers are scrambling to adjust to a post-pandemic world — and to decide what lessons learned from the past year should be enshrined in state law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India sets record for daily virus deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-coronavirus-pandemic-health-ce604ee88062c459e0a3bd9f1e1ed686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — India on Wednesday reported more coronavirus deaths in a single day than any other country at any time during the pandemic, while infections continued to spread through vast rural areas with weak health systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student's arrest for racist post sparks free speech debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fairfield-connecticut-high-school-racist-post-36ab75190a03be2ccd4dddbda1544ff8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arrest of a Connecticut high school student accused of posting racist comments about a Black classmate on social media is being supported by civil rights advocates, but free speech groups are calling it an unusual move by police that raises First Amendment issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA-Russia showdown looms as top diplomats meet in Iceland...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-donald-trump-iceland-europe-middle-east-aeeed7773fc80941862fa2acf6bb4335</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REYKJAVIK, Iceland (AP) — Top diplomats from the United States and Russia are set to square off this week in Iceland for their first face-to-face encounter that comes as ties between the nations have deteriorated sharply in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrictions reimposed across Asia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-business-health-9e9e237d169e251ec4c00774104938f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Taxi drivers are starved for customers, weddings are suddenly canceled, schools are closed, and restaurant service is restricted across much of Asia as the coronavirus makes a resurgence in countries where it had seemed to be well under control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA chief says increase in unruly passengers should concern all...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/faa-chief-concerned-uptick-unruly-passengers/story?id=77745303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) is continuing its crackdown on disruptive passengers as the agency continues to see more incidents than years prior.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
