<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Generation H(elpless)? Many Millennials Can't Change Light Bulb...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/generation-helpless-many-millennials-cant-change-a-light-bulb-by-themselves-survey-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey of 2,000 young adults and millennials finds that most still need assistance with the simplest of tasks -- like changing a light bulb!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER TUESDAY HERALDS EPIC DEM CLASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/03/super-tuesday-2020-democratic-primary-battle-119360</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Bernie’s revolutionary zeal pit against Biden’s calls for restoration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After shift to right, Supreme Court to hear major abortion case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/after-shift-right-under-trump-supreme-court-hear-major-abortion-n1147461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outcome is uncertain following the president's nominees Gorsuch and Kavanaugh joining the bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Bloomberg waste $500 million?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Did-Mike-Bloomberg-waste-500-million-running-for-15101124.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the craps table of this campaign, there's a $500 million chip sitting on "Super Tuesday." The bettor's name is mike - small "m," according to the visual design of his campaign, like he's your modest neighbor from the split-level down the block instead of a titan of media and finance with estates in Bermuda and Southampton.  That's Bloomberg. Mayor of New York from 2002 to 2013. Democrat, then Republican, then independent, then Democrat. Purveyor of fancy data terminals. Ninth-richest person in the world. A few months ago Bloomberg saw a moribund field of candidates and thought he could vault his way to the nomination through a delegate grab on Super Tuesday.  So now it's mike, responsible presidential candidate, asking for the car keys as the nation stumbles around.  Is he trying to save the party, or accidentally sabotaging it? Is "mike" just a proxy for Bloomberg as he tries to buy the presidency?  "My first answer to that all the time is: What's the right price to save democracy from Donald Trump?" said Tim O'Brien, a senior adviser to mike, at a Bloomberg house party in McLean, Virginia, Thursday night. There, Northern Virginians sipped Chianti and canned Perrier and whispered about Joe Biden as if he were an uncle in hospice care (this was 48 hours before his defibrillation in South Carolina). They shuddered at the thought of Bernie Sanders, democratic socialist, for his perceived radicalism and dismissed Elizabeth Warren, capitalist reformer, for her vendetta against mike.  What's a democracy worth? A year ago, before mike arrived on the scene, Bloomberg pledged a half billion to vanquishing Trump. In Virginia, over the past three years, he spent $3.5 million to help flip the statehouse to Democrats, whose gun-control advocates now speak of him with reverence. So far this year, Bloomberg has spent $50 million to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anyone but Trump': The evangelicals who plan to vote Democrat...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200303-anyone-but-trump-the-texas-evangelicals-who-plan-to-vote-democrat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is home to one of the largest evangelical populations in the country, most of which traditionally votes Republican. But some current and former members of the evangelical community have turned…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00cc158976f9c23e424df524a3487c6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The latest on the Democratic presidential primary and Super Tuesday (all times local): 8 a.m. A super PAC supporting Joe Biden‘s presidential bid is running a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary Could Show Just How Blue Texas Turning...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/03/02/810401130/super-tuesday-could-show-just-how-blue-texas-is-turning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Texas Democrats, the state's Super Tuesday primary could help define the shape of a party that's on the rise after more than two decades of being shut out of power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Children Having Nightmares Over 'Climate Change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/children-climate-change-sleep-nightmares-eco-anxiety-greta-thunberg-a9371191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans continue to vote with their feet towards low-tax states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/485497-how-tax-rates-affect-congressional-apportionment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before we know it, the 2020 census will be in the books and states will know their fates for congressional reapportionment and the electoral college map</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin critic Navalny says bank accounts frozen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kremlin-critic-navalny-says-bank-accounts-frozen-115221373.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's main opposition leader Alexei Navalny said Tuesday that authorities had frozen all of his bank accounts and those of his family, including his elderly parents. The 43-year-old anti-corruption blogger, who has emerged as President Vladimir Putin's most prominent critic, accused the Russian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile capital rocked by violent anti-govt rallies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chile-capital-rocked-violent-anti-government-rallies-103847153.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santiago (AFP) - Chile's capital has been rocked by its worst anti-government violence in weeks after stone-throwing protesters clashed with police in running battles across the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek army, police dig in along Turkey border after migrant clashes...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200303093733-0z09i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/GREECE (PIX, TV):Greek army, police dig in along Turkey border after migrant clashes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs or drones? Time-lapse video at Outer Banks finds mysterious 'red trails' in sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/article240802356.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster: Tornadoes shred 40 buildings around Nashville...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/795688aab981d4e8220042c20e095b55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — At least two tornadoes touched down early Tuesday in central Tennessee, including one that ripped across downtown Nashville and caused about 40 buildings to collapse around...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smiley responds to six PBS employees' accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Smiley-responds-to-six-PBS-employees-accounts-15099830.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - One by one, the voices of six female employees of former PBS talk show host Tavis Smiley sounded in a District of Columbia courtroom, each woman describing incidents in which they claim Smiley requested sex or told a lewd joke while at work.  Some of the women said that they felt pressured to comply with those requests and that they faced retaliation - even losing their jobs - if they didn't. Others described comments or jokes by Smiley that they said made them uncomfortable in the workplace.  During three weeks of trial, Smiley listened to the women's accounts, played in court by video deposition. When he took the witness stand he admitted that he'd had intimate relationships with two of the women. But he said several of the accounts were false and insisted he never acted with retribution and never intended to offend.  "I'm a black man struggling to make it in America. I have laughed at all of this so-called power. I struggled to raise money to keep my show on the air. I never had such power," Smiley, 55, testified. "I have influence, but I don't have power."  The accusations - and Smiley's responses - were detailed as Smiley and PBS squared off in court, with each side arguing that the other was in breach of contract when the network stopped airing his show in 2017 amid the sexual harassment allegations. On Monday, attorneys for PBS and Smiley gave their closing arguments before the jury began deliberations.  For 14 years, PBS distributed Smiley's late-night talk show to 238 stations nationwide, about 72% of its network.  PBS is suing Smiley for about $1.7 million the network says Smiley owes in money it had provided for a season that never aired. Smiley, who says the network terminated his contract without proof of the allegations, is countersuing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials clash over passenger tracking...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Major-airlines-U-S-officials-clash-over-15099881.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - U.S. officials are pressuring airline executives to turn over the email addresses and phone numbers of international passengers as the Trump administration tries to track who may have been exposed to the coronavirus, according to five people briefed on the situation.  Government officials have said they need the data so they can warn local authorities about who might have been exposed to the virus. But the airline industry has balked, saying the federal government should instead share information it already collects between different agencies and come up with a system for obtaining the rest.  The impasse has dragged on for weeks despite concerns about the growing number of people with coronavirus in the United States. It has become a top issue of the Trump administration's virus task force and U.S. lawmakers. Airline executives are slated to meet Wednesday with Vice President Mike Pence.  The airline industry has pushed Congress to intervene, with some lobbyists asking lawmakers to insert a provision in an emergency spending package that would effectively absolve the airlines of having to track some of the data.  The failure to resolve the issue could complicate the government's efforts to contain the outbreak's spread. United Airlines, Delta Air Lines, and American Airlines deferred questions to Airlines for America, a lobbying group that represents the airline industry. Airlines for America said collecting the data shouldn't be the airlines' job since the government already has much of it in existing databases. They also said it would take up to a year for the airlines to set up the tracking system.  Even though both sides have been fighting over the data for weeks, the battle has taken on new urgency in recent days.  The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is asking airlines to collect and - when...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMY, PETE ENDORSE JOE...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democrats-embrace-Biden-as-Sanders-hopes-for-big-15100191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parade of establishment Democrats began coalescing around Joe Biden on Monday, an attempt to bolster the former vice president and stall Sen. Bernie Sanders' ascent as voters in 14 states prepared to cast ballots Tuesday, the most consequential day of the presidential nominating contest.  On a day with cascading developments that rapidly recast the presidential race, Sen. Amy Klobuchar, D-Minn., dropped out and made plans to join Biden at his rally in Dallas on Monday night. In a visual symbol of Biden's attempts to consolidate the moderates in the party, former South Bend, Indiana, mayor Pete Buttigieg - who dropped out Sunday night, and who had an intensely cold relationship with Klobuchar - also scrambled to get to Dallas and endorse Biden.  It was the second straight day that moderates, previously paralyzed over whom to endorse, rushed to join Biden's campaign. Harry Reid, a former Senate majority leader from Nevada, endorsed Biden along with other Democrats including Susan Rice, the former national security adviser to President Barack Obama; political activist and actress Alyssa Milano; Victoria Reggie Kennedy, the widow of Sen. Edward Kennedy, D-Mass.; and Sen. Tammy Duckworth, D-Ill.  There are still looming questions about Biden - his propensity for gaffes, the moments when he searches for words or, on Monday, his struggle to come up with well-worn phrases in the Declaration of Independence before shouting, "You know . . . the thing!" - but his campaign has found unmistakable new momentum it is hoping to carry into the elections Tuesday.  Not everyone was playing to his benefit, however. Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., and former New York mayor Mike Bloomberg both vowed Monday to stay in the race.  "I'm in it to win it," Bloomberg said. He has poured hundreds of millions of dollars into the primary...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF 23 YEAR RUN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/02/business/media/chris-matthews-resigns-steps-down-msnbc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Matthews’s show, “Hardball,” has been on the air since 1997.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHRIS MATTHEWS QUITS MSNBC 'HARDBALL'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/chris-matthews-announces-retirement-mutually-parts-ways-msnbc-n1147536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthews was due to retire in the near future with the events of the past week playing a factor in the timing of the move, an MSNBC spokesperson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'OUT OF TOUCH'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-chris-matthews-msnbc-veteran-retires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Matthews resigned from MSNBC Monday night after more than two decades at the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUSHED?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/chris-matthews-departure-msnbc-hardball-1203521543/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Matthews is abruptly stepping down from MSNBC’s “Hardball” amid scrutiny of recent on-air remarks as well as speculation about behind-the-scenes behavior. The veteran anchor and politic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE BLOWOUT OR DELEGATE SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/a-sanders-blowout-or-a-delegate-split-california-to-shape-outcome-of-2020-primary-race/ar-BB10ECxt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Museum of American Jewish History files for bankruptcy protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philadelphia-jewish-museum-bankruptcy-debt-20200302.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In papers filed with U.S. Bankruptcy Court in Philadelphia, the museum said that it owed a little more than $30 million to bondholders and about $1 million to unsecured creditors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What can govt force people to do in name of containing? </title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/coronavirus/sns-what-can-government-force-people-to-do-name-containing-coronavirus-20200302-zwhxf6uclzdcpelyzoyripiqdm-photogallery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q&amp;A: What can the government force people to do in the name of containing the coronavirus?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEGALA: Trump will 'dump Pence' for Haley...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/485562-cnns-begala-trump-will-dump-pence-for-haley-on-day-of-democratic-nominees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime CNN political analyst Paul Begala predicted on Monday that President Trump is "gonna dump [Vice President] Mike Pence in favor of former South Carolina Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMY, PETE ENDORSE JOE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/485510-buttigieg-set-to-endorse-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg is set to endorse former Vice President Joe Biden in the Democratic presidential race one day after ending his own bid, according to a source close to the Biden campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan says MILLIONS of refugees will be released...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/erdogan-warns-europe-share-migrant-burden-113820883.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan warned on Monday that "millions" of migrants would soon head for Europe, drawing accusations from EU leaders that he is trying to pressure them into backing his incursions into Syria. Turkey gave the green light to refugees and migrants on Friday to leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top central banks primed to act on coronavirus risk...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200302233859-nyn23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Cancels Show Hours After Star Timothy Hutton Accused of Rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/almost-family-canceled-fox-one-season-timothy-hutton-brittany-snow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Timothy Hutton and Brittany Snow-led drama concluded Feb. 22</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen to Set Record Straight in Surprise Autobiography...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/03/02/woody-allen-will-set-the-record-straight-in-surprise-autobiography-coming-april-7th-called-apropos-of-nothing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprise! The rumored Woody Allen autobiography is here. The 400 page “Apropos of Nothing” will be released by Grand Central Books on April 7th.  There had been rumblings for a while th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff: Graphic Kobe Bryant crash photos must be deleted...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article240816571.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI BACK FROM BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200302231027-vu74f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Netanyahu ahead in Israeli election, but still seeking governing majority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Extortion Attempts'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/timothy-hutton-rape-allegation-denied-1983-1202872687/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Timothy Hutton is vigorously denying claims that he raped a teenager back in 1983 and he may be filing a defamation lawsuit soon against his accuser and the publication that detailed her allegation…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stimulus Hopes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9dca8cb640916fb8d10b37f81e2980d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average soared nearly 1,300 points, or 5%, Monday as stocks roared back from a seven-day rout on hopes that central banks will take action to shield the global economy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSED:  Biden botches Declaration of Independence: 'You know the thing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/2/joe-biden-botches-declaration-of-independence-you-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President hopeful Joseph R. Biden made social media headlines on Monday for all the wrong reasons after botching the Declaration of Independence in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka Completes Political Evolution: 'Proud Trump Republican'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ivanka-trump-completes-a-political-evolution-im-a-proud-trump-republican/ar-BB10Eayb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wozniak claims he may have been 'patient zero'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8067135/Apple-founder-Steve-Wozniak-claims-coronavirus-patient-zero.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wozniak's bizarre claim that he and his wife may have both been 'patient zero' for coronavirus in the U.S. turned out to be a false alarm after his wife confirmed actually has a sinus infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Rich Are Preparing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-03-02/can-we-get-a-vaccine-early-how-the-rich-prepare-for-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids may be secret carriers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/02/ex-cdc-head-tom-frieden-says-kids-may-be-secret-coronavirus-carriers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-director of the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Monday that the deadly coronavirus may be “impossible” to contain — and that kids may be secret carriers of the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI BACK FROM BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/netanyahu-back-from-brink-with-dazzling-election-win-now-two-court-battles-loom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Likud leader utterly out-campaigned Blue and White head Gantz, reasserting his 'King Bibi' credentials. Will he prove as successful in the legal battles that lie ahead?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Strong Gas Odor Causes Evacuations Across Philly...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/03/02/strong-gas-odor-from-pes-refinery-tank-being-cleaned-permeates-center-city-causes-multiple-buildings-to-be-evacuated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple buildings in Center City, including CBS3, were evacuated due to reports of a strong gas odor on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban end truce as Afghan violence resumes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taliban-end-partial-truce-afghan-violence-resumes-153659616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban called an abrupt end to a partial truce on Monday, just two days after signing a deal with the United States that was meant to bring peace at last to Afghanistan. In the southern province of Kandahar, considered the Taliban's heartland, fighting broke out in at least in two districts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches Change Practices For Mass...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/03/01/local-churches-change-practices-for-mass-as-precautions-amid-coronavirus-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 120 parishes in the Diocese of Joliet are under a precautionary directive indefinitely amid the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More testing sheds light on how virus is spreading...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7c5091a8f80e8adc2d79d1047880272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — An increase in testing for the coronavirus began shedding light Monday on how the illness has spread in the United States, including among nursing home residents in one Washington...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Detect Largest Explosion In Universe Since Big Bang!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/astronomers-detect-largest-explosion-in-universe-since-big-bang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers in Perth, Australia have detected the largest explosion ever found in the universe since the Big Bang, a new study reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT POLLS: Netanyahu's bloc wins majority... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections/Benjamin-Netanyahus-Right-bloc-wins-majority-exit-polls-619513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is expected that after the third election in one year, this time the prime minister will succeed in forming a government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Wall Street activists set sights on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/3/1/21160375/jack-dorsey-twitter-elliott-management-paul-singer-ceo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Activist investor" Elliott Management has targeted Dorsey, who runs Twitter and Square at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DA's husband accused of pulling gun on Black Lives Matters...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/los-angeles-district-attorney-s-husband-allegedly-pulled-gun-black-n1146976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jackie Lacey, L.A. County's first black district attorney, has been the target of regular protests over the office's handling of high-profile cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabid Cow at Texas Rodeo May Have Infected Attendees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-rabid-cow-at-a-texas-rodeo-may-have-infected-attendees-officials-warn/ar-BB10Ddi8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem establishment falls in line. Harry Reid endorses Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-03-02/joe-biden-endorsements-harry-reid-klobuchar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Democratic presidential rival Amy Klobuchar will back Biden. Former Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid also endorses the former vice president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa readies as cases confirmed on continent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/439fe91fdadce80450d87a70940462ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAKAR, Senegal (AP) — Across Africa, steps are being taken to prepare for — and to reduce the effects of — the spread of the new coronavirus. Testing laboratories are being supplied, quarantine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bye-bye handshakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.newindianexpress.com/world/2020/mar/02/bye-bye-handshakes-how-coronavirus-is-changing-global-habits-2111190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newindianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All around the world people are changing their daily habits at work, at home and in worship to reduce the risk of contracting the coronavirus and prevent it from spreading any further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC TESTS FAILED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8065613/New-York-doctor-warns-coronavirus-cases-surge-thousands-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Matt McCarthy, who is a staff physician at the New York-Presbyterian Hospital in Manhattan, claimed he doesn't have the tools to care for patients because of the lack of coronavirus tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITE OR FIGHT?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/01/super-tuesday-polls-bernie-biden-bloomberg-118459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanders is poised to rebound from a distant second-place finish in South Carolina, according to surveys released over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA prepping for emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/fema-prepping-possible-coronavirus-emergency-declaration-n1147016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To me this is another indication that the president and the White House are finally aware of the gravity of the situation," said former FEMA official Michael Coen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Restricts Travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnn-severely-restricts-international-travel-over-coronavirus-outbreak-globally-in-new-memo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new WarnerMedia memo to news and sports employees by chairman Jeff Zucker told employees to "limit all forms of travel as much as possible," that intercontinental trips must be personally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus may have spread undetected for 6 weeks in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/health/2020/03/01/coronavirus-may-have-spread-undetected-for-weeks-in-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This strongly suggests that there has been cryptic transmission in Washington State for the past 6 weeks."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says it's safe to hold rallies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/485460-trump-says-its-safe-to-hold-rallies-amid-coronavirus-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said Monday that he believed it was safe to continue holding campaign rallies across the country during the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury as Kanye West hymn service pushes out transgender show...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fury-kanye-west-hymn-pushes-transgender-show-155456467.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US rapper Kanye West was at the centre of a storm Monday after a Paris show by an acclaimed transgender performer was cancelled at the last minute to make way for one of his religious services. The mercurial singer took over the Bouffes du Nord theatre in the French capital for one of his famous "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bond Movie Release Delayed?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/james-bond-open-letter-calls-no-time-die-delay-coronavirus-1282047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Writers for the biggest 007 blog have urged Eon, MGM and Universal to postpone the release until summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chained-up  monkey forced to lift weights and do sit-ups for tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkey-forced-lift-weights-sit-21614745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poor monkey was walked around with a chain on its neck as it performed for the enjoyment of tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMLO Approval Falls in Polls on Mexico Rampant Violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amlo-approval-falls-two-polls-153521697.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador’s backing took a hit in two national opinion polls as respondents raise concerns about unchecked violence in the country.Lopez Obrador’s approval rate fell to 59% in February from 68% in December, according to a Reforma newspaper poll published</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS SET FOR SUPER TUESDAY DRAMA!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be14026452cb8d39de828ac25ff041cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SELMA, Ala. (AP) — An emboldened Joe Biden is trying to cast himself as the clear moderate alternative to progressive Bernie Sanders as the Democrats' shrinking presidential field races toward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis vote in 3rd election in year focused on Netanyahu... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1465b297a02795783f5d8927b7058c72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israelis were voting Monday in an unprecedented third election in less than a year to decide whether longtime Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu stays in power despite his upcoming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is world's tallest mammal at risk from 'silent extinction'?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/africa/namibia/articles/giraffes-hoanib-valley-silent-extinction-safari/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos $165M Home and Why New Moguls Love Old Hollywood Estates...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/jeff-bezos-165m-home-why-new-moguls-love-old-hollywood-estates-1281092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon chief bought the Jack Warner property from David Geffen, showing the enduring appeal of mansions built by entertainment pioneers: "People appreciate owning a piece of history."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US manufacturing slows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/02/februarys-ism-manufacturing-index-is-50point1-vs-an-expected-50point8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manufacturing activity in the U.S. grew at a slower-than-expected pace last month as the coronavirus outbreak dampened sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks attempt rebound...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/01/awaiting-us-stock-futures-open-at-6-pm-after-wall-streets-worst-week-since-2008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks opened higher as Wall Street tried to rebound from its worst week since the financial crisis amid fears of the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS investigating defect in tests...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/485426-hhs-investigating-defect-in-coronavirus-tests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services on Sunday said it is probing a manufacturing problem in the first testing kits for coronavirus that led several states to request emergency approval for state-specific tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will decide fate of Obamacare -- again...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/supreme-court-decide-fate-obama-health-care-law-69334934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court has agreed to decide a lawsuit that threatens the Obama-era health care law, but the decision is not likely until after the 2020 election</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
