<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ginkgo Supplement Was Ginkgo-Free, Watchdog Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ginkgo-supplement-was-ginkgo-free-u-s-watchdog-finds-1542239276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two dietary supplements promoted as improving memory using Ginkgo biloba contained either none of the ingredient or a lower amount than advertised, a federal watchdog said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>68% of Americans quit or taken break from socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/bailey-richardson-decided-to-quit-instagram-this-year-she-also-helped-create-the-social-media-app-1947551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the evening of Sept. 26, Bailey Richardson logged in to Instagram for the last time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO MORE GAVEL?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/pelosi-faces-daunting-challenge-in-speakers-bid-as-democratic-foes-stand-firm/2018/11/14/29c1e018-e83a-11e8-a939-9469f1166f9d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an electoral year marked by a record number of women joining the House, incoming female Democrats may help decide Nancy Pelosi’s fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump lawyers, CNN square off in federal court in Jim Acosta case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/media/cnn-trump-lawsuit-hearing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first hearing in CNN and Jim Acosta's federal lawsuit against President Trump and several top White House aides ended with the judge saying that he would rule on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell Says Fed Deserves Credit for Economic Growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/powell-credits-fed-policy-for-the-us-economy-being-in-a-good-place.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell expressed confidence in U.S. economic strength Wednesday and said markets will have to get used to the idea that the central bank could raise rates at any time starting in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Sees Uptick In Travelers Packing Turkeys Into Bags...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/13/tsa-expecting-record-setting-crowds-during-thanksgiving-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines and the TSA are not just expecting big crowds, but record setting crowds during this year's Thanksgiving travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI ON THE BRINK?	</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pelosi-challenges-unhappy-dems-block-her-bid-speaker-175012347--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As a steadfast Rep. Nancy Pelosi all but dared potential rivals for the gavel to come forward, a group of restive House Democrats vowed Wednesday to produce enough votes to block her from becoming the House's new speaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earliest Houston snowfall ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/local/snow-vember-the-earliest-houston-snowfall-ever-just-happened/285-614153347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your eyes didn't deceive you -- it snowed in Houston today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-breathing premature baby revived by police officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/11/14/non-breathing-premature-born-boy-revived-by-oakland-police-officer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oakland police officer is being credited with saving the life of an infant boy, who he revived when the child stopped breathing after being born prematurely inside a car Tuesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant sues AMERICAN AIRLINES, says she was dragged down aisle mid-flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/american-airlines-flight-attendant-suing-scarf-assault-drag-down-aisle-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American Airlines flight attendant is suing the Fort Worth, Texas-based airline over a 2016 altercation with another crew member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE wants virtual assistant in every room of house...</title>
      <link>http://www.weny.com/story/39479577/google-wants-its-virtual-assistant-in-every-room-of-your-house </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Heather Kelly, CNN Business</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold San Antonio 'shatters' 102-year-old record...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/weather/article/Icy-San-Antonio-weather-shatters-102-year-old-13391345.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Antonio reached a low of 23 degrees at the International Airport this morning, which ties for the fourth coldest November low temperature on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK TURNS BEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/apple-bellwether-for-technology-stocks-falls-into-a-bear-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple dipped into a bear market on Wednesday as shares added to a 20 percent decline from recent all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 Buses with 900 More Near Border... </title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/14/22-buses-with-900-caravan-migrants-nears-u-s-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 900 Central Americans in 22 buses arrived in the northern border state of Sonora, escorted by state and federal police on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast, South brace for winter storm...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2018-11-14-winter-storm-avery-snow-ice-east-midwest-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With cold air in place, a wintry mess is moving in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flake vows to oppose judges unless Mueller protection bill gets vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/28c5f8d772fd4b3097e152c025336fd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Republican Sen. Jeff Flake said Wednesday that he won't vote to confirm judicial nominees unless GOP leaders hold a vote on legislation to protect special counsel Robert Mueller from being fired. Flake of Arizona and Democratic Sen. Chris Coons of Delaware went to the Senate floor on Wednesday and tried to bring the legislation up for a vote. But Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell objected. McConnell has said that the legislation is unnecessary because he believes Mueller won't be fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE downgraded, more iPhone estimates cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/apple-gets-downgraded-more-iphone-estimates-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guggenheim downgraded Apple to neutral from buy and removed its prior $245 price target. UBS cut its 12-month price target on Apple to $225 from $240 and lowered iPhone unit sales estimates for the current quarter to 73.5 million from 75 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DENIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/michael-avenatti-denies-alleged-domestic-violence-ive-never-been-physically-abusive-in-my-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVENATTI ARRESTED FOR DOMESTIC VIOLENCE...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2018/11/14/official-michael-avenatti-in-los-angeles-police-custody-on-domestic-violence-allegation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Avenatti, who skyrocketed to fame as a critic of President Donald Trump and the lawyer for porn actress Stormy Daniels, was released on bail after being arrested Wednesday and booked on a felony domestic violence charge, Los Angeles police said. The victim in the case had visible injuries, according to Officer Tony Im, a police spokesman. But Avenatti slammed the allegation as "completely bogus" in a statement released by his law firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She hit me first!'</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/11/14/michael-avenatti-arrested-domestic-violence-stormy-daniels-attorney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Avenatti was arrested for felony domestic violence against a woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crypto civil war' slams bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/bkcm-brian-kelly-crypto-civil-war-slams-bitcoin-but-not-for-long.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin had been coasting in recent months on fairly low volatility until "things exploded," says the cryptocurrency fund manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic bishops leave conference without acting on abuse reforms...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/news/catholic-bishops-baltimore-sex-abuse-cardinal-theodore-mccarrick-20181114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the prospect of leaving their most closely watched gathering in years with no consensus response to the sex abuse crisis that has gripped their church since summer, the nation's Catholic bishops pushed Wednesday for something – anything – they might approve to show they were taking the problem seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURDER ON CRUISE SHIP SAILING IN CARIBBEAN?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/cruises/2018/11/14/princess-cruises-woman-dies-fall-ship-royal-princess/2001881002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American woman aboard a Princess Cruises ship died Tuesday in what authorities are treating as a possible murder case, according to several news outlets in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBC votes no confidence in DNC Perez...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/14/congressional-black-caucus-tom-perez-991270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cedric Richmond said members “felt that the DNC pitted them against their constituents.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Thanksgiving nears, mystery of drug-resistant Salmonella in turkey persists...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/as-thanksgiving-nears-regulators-food-processors-grapple-with-ongoing-salmonella-threat-in-turkey/500506282/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota has reported 17 cases, the most of any state. With Thanksgiving a week away, federal officials aren't telling consumers to stop eating turkey, but they are stressing the importance of proper handling and cooking techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock-Market Supercomputer to Launch With Glitches...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stock-market-supercomputer-to-launch-with-glitches-1542236446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A data warehouse created to track all U.S. stock market orders is expected to launch on Thursday with limited functionality because the contractor in charge of it hasn’t been able to make it reliably searchable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Dems 'Dog Whistle' Tactics Against Clyburn...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article221666375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after Rep. Jim Clyburn, D-South Carolina, accused detractors of using racially-motivated “dog whistle” tactics to undermine his bid to be House majority whip, Rep. Steny Hoyer, D-Maryland, came to his defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi battle for Speakership votes...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-congress-pelosi-speaker-20181114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi is whipping votes to try to regain the gavel as House speaker. More than a dozen Democrats have come out against her, and the result remains uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Filing confirms investigation will extend into next year...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mueller-isnt-done-former-trump-campaign-aide-gates-222015853.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Robert Mueller isn't done with former Trump campaign aide Rick Gates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafty crook fished $400K  out of PO boxes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/crafty-crook-fished-400k-in-checks-out-of-postal-boxes-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queens is a great spot to go fishing — for checks, that is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putino MILITARY CHURCH to bolster patriotism, spirituality...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1045323/russia-news-military-church-vladimir-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has unveiled plans to build a military church as Moscow seeks to reinforce the value of “patriotism, love, and devotion to our Motherland” into troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service loss TRIPLES as package deliveries rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-postal-service-results/u-s-postal-service-loss-triples-even-as-package-deliveries-rise-idUSKCN1NJ2HS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Postal Service lost almost $4 billion in 2018 even as package deliverie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'War on Terror' price tag to top $6,000,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2018/11/14/price-tag-of-the-war-on-terror-will-top-6-trillion-soon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The figure is several times higher than official Pentagon reports on war spending because it includes VA benefits and other related expenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guidance overhaul on college sex assault gives new rights to accused...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-betsy-devos-college-sexual-assaults-20181114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education Secretary Betsy DeVos is set to release a sweeping overhaul of how colleges and universities must handle allegations of sexual assault and harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. says defendant in political fundraiser hacking case has diplomatic immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/u-s-says-defendant-elliott-broidy-hacking-case-has-diplomatic-n935456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-diplomat accused of helping steal and distribute GOP fundraiser Elliot Broidy's emails is entitled to immunity, the U.S. government tells NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER loses $1 Billion, bookings slow...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uber-posts-1-billion-loss-210213496.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber Technologies Inc said on Wednesday that growth in bookings for its ride-hailing and delivery services rose 6 percent in the latest quarter, the third quarter in a row that growth has remained in the single digits after double-digit growth for all of last year. As a private company, Uber is not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorite crater bigger than Paris found under Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/meteorite-crater-meteor-greenland-ice-sheet-hiawatha-glacier-scientists-a8633826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 contenders say Republicans 'stealing' Georgia race...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/2020-democratic-contenders-georgia-gop-stealing-governors-race-abrams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two potential 2020 Democratic White House contenders are accusing Georgia Republicans of stealing the governor's race from Democrat Stacey Abrams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delay, Deny and Deflect: Inside FACEBOOK's Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/14/technology/facebook-data-russia-election-racism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian meddling, data sharing, hate speech — the social network faced one scandal after another. This is how Mark Zuckerberg and Sheryl Sandberg responded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES tool warns if articles quote too many men...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/nov/14/financial-times-tool-warns-if-articles-quote-too-many-men</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paper develops bot in attempt to force writers to look to include more expert women in pieces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER NYC cab driver deep in debt kills self...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/another-nyc-cab-driver-deep-in-debt-kills-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another debt-burdened New York City cabbie has committed suicide — the eighth for-hire driver to kill himself in the past year, Taxi and Limousine Commission officials confirmed on Wednesday.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsa paying $10,000 just to move there...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-us-city-is-paying-people-more-than-10000-just-to-move-there-2018-11-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The package for newcomers to this Oklahoma city includes a free membership at a co-working space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Staggering' raccoons acting rabid just drunk, cops say...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/article221652130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two raccoons in Milton, West Virginia, appear to have gotten drunk on crab apples, the Police Department said. One of the creatures is named Dallas. People thought they had rabies, but they’re not rabid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH:  44 dogs in freezers, 130 more living in squalor...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/pets-animals/44-dogs-found-in-freezers-130-more-living-in-filth-in-nj-home/4688017/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey State Police have arrested a 65-year-old woman after they say dozens of dogs were found dead in freezers and more than 100 more living in filth inside her home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Looters Arrested For Stealing Motor Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article221651485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Butte County Sheriff’s Office has reported six arrests this week relating to incidents in areas under mandatory evacuation orders due to the Camp Fire, with suspected crimes ranging from drug possession to looting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ:  Mueller Probes Possible Witness Intimidation by Roger Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mueller-probes-possible-witness-intimidation-by-roger-stone-1542222284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Mueller’s office is exploring whether longtime Trump adviser Roger Stone tried to intimidate and discredit a witness who is contradicting Mr. Stone’s version of events about his contacts with WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Calls Acosta 'Bad For Country'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/14/trump-cnn-lawsuit-bad-for-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We’ll see how the court rules'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Biden, Bernie lead early primary states...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/democrats-not-ready-hillary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Likely Democratic voters in primary states are not eager for a third White House run by Hillary Clinton, according to a new poll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Super-Earth' discovered orbiting Sun's nearest star...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/super-earth-discovered-orbiting-suns-nearest-star-180125151.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "super-Earth" has been discovered orbiting the closest single star to our Sun, scientists said Wednesday in a breakthrough that could shine a light on Earth's nearest planetary neighbours. Astronomers studied Barnard's Star, a red dwarf just six light years away -- practically in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neanderthal life not especially risky, skull analysis shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/neanderthal-life-not-especially-risky-skull-analysis-shows-180255654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Life as a Neanderthal was no picnic, but a new analysis says it was no more dangerous than what our own species faced in ancient times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Best US Airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-best-of-the-biggest-u-s-airports-1542204004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first WSJ U.S. airport rankings uses 15 metrics to decide which of the 20 largest airports treat travelers better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Claims Fires Are Retribution, Vows More...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-group-claims-california-wildfires-are-retribution-vows-you-will-see-more-fires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terror group has previously suggested both wildland and commercial or residential arson as an attack tactic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Collect Record Taxes in October...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/feds-collect-record-taxes-october-still-run-100b-deficit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Paul Ryan, Sept. 6, 2018. (Getty Images/Mark Wilson)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious purple glow lights up night sky in Eastern Wash...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/mysterious-purple-glow-lights-up-eastern-wash-night-sky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINLEY, Wash. - It looked like something out of The X-Files - a pink and purple glow filled the night sky near the Tri-Cities in Eastern Washington. Was it caused by a UFO? Or emissions from the Hanford nuclear facility? Or a top-secret military experiment? â€œWe thought maybe the bar that's out there was having some kind of party,â€� said local resident Alisha Dickenson. Purple lights illuminated the sky Sunday night, but it wasn't from a party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARAVAN JUMPS BORDER FENCE; NO TROOPS...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/2018/11/13/video-shows-group-climbing-on-border-fence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People on the Mexican side of the border could be seen climbing the fence near Friendship Park Tuesday afternoon after part of the Central American migrant caravan arrived in Tijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY'S BREXIT D-DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/13/theresa-may-can-no-longer-delay-her-bunfight-with-tory-brexiters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May hopes to secure support for the ‘product’, but tougher challenges await</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN WHO COULD BE CHIEF</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/13/nick-ayers-replace-john-kelly-987654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Ayers, Pence’s chief of staff, was initially seen as a potential Kelly successor this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beekeeper therapist uses venom to heal patients...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181113201908-97opo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EGYPT-HEALTH/BEES (TV, PIX):Beekeeper therapist uses venom to heal his patients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How GOOGLEAMAZON Got Away with Not Being Regulated...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/book-excerpt-curse-of-bigness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet companies used to grow big and die—fast. But now a few of them are huge and entrenched, because regulators didn't foresee their dominance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Evacuation fatigue'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/13/california-wildfires-evacuation-fatigue-paradise-camp-danger </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How  World's First Male Supermodel Escaped Abusive Doomsday Cult...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-the-worlds-first-male-supermodel-escaped-an-abusive-doomsday-cult</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hoyt Richards was dubbed the “world’s first male supermodel,” pulling in a minimum of $15,000 a day. But little did the world know that he was deeply involved in a terrifying cult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Police Escort 400 from Migrant Caravan to U.S. Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/13/watch-mexican-police-escort-400-from-migrant-caravan-to-u-s-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A caravan of nearly 400 migrants in eight buses arrived in Sonora, escorted by state and federal police on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study: Men with beards more attractive...</title>
      <link>https://fox8.com/2018/11/14/study-men-with-beards-are-more-attractive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study shows men who have full beards are more attractive than men who are clean-shaven. The study was published in the Journal of Evolutionary Biology. Researched asked more than 8,500 women to rate men on their attractiveness as a long-term romantic partner, Yahoo News reported. Here's how the facial hair rated:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000+ Troops Converge...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/11/13/1000-troops-converge-on-border-awaiting-migrant-caravan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 troops are on the U.S. Mexico border preparing for the possible arrival of a migrant caravan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parties barrel toward clash over border wall... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/13/government-shut-down-congress-mueller-border-wall-trump-988159</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the two sides can't come to terms on special counsel Mueller and the border wall, part of the government will shut down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great for ratings!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/11/13/donald-trump-jim-acosta-222463</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fakest news in town is that the president is mad at a preening TV reporter who’s great for ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O:  Yes, I'm black...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-michelle-obama-united-center-chicago-20181113-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long before former first lady Michelle Obama was to take the stage at United Center on Tuesday night to kick off her much-anticipated book tour, the crowds had gathered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX BACKS CNN IN ACOSTA LAWSUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fox-news-cnn-lawsuit-trump-jim-acosta-press-pass-81bc6dd3-4590-4f66-9197-6d1ff92676b6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We do support a free press, access and open exchanges for the American people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: ISIS Suggested Arson and Devastation of California...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-details-devastation-california-wildfires-caliphate-newsletter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terror group has encouraged followers to try arson as a terror tactic, yet has not taken credit for starting any of the blazes still under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>250+ CASES...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/officials-investigating-252-cases-polio-illness-afm/story?id=59163987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are now investigating 252 cases of possible acute flaccid myelitis (AFM) including 90 confirmed cases in 27 states, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>878,000 MILLIONAIRES ADDED IN YEAR </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/america-first-878-000-millionaires-added-in-last-12-months-trump-effect-relentless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The booming U.S. economy, jump started by the 2017 GOP tax cut, has created 878,000 more millionaires in just the last 12 months, according to an international wealth report from Credit Suisse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE:  Number of US citizens seeking asylum in Canada reaches record high...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/14/us-citizens-seeking-asylum-canada-increases-immigration-refugees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans, Haitians and Nigerians were the largest groups seeking asylum, spurred by fears they would be deported by the Trump administration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIN!!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/return-of-moisture-to-aid-firefighting-efforts-in-californias-wildfire-disaster-next-week/70006616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA's secret 'truth serum' to bust terror plots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7736660/cia-truth-serum-drug-al-qaeda-911-suspects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE CIA contemplated giving Al-Qaeda terror suspects a “truth serum” to force them into revealing information about potential attacks, in the wake of 9/11. Newly declassified documents show interro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne's husband launches new anti-Trump group...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6389209/Kellyanne-Conways-husband-founds-new-group-anti-Trump-conservative-lawyers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missing from the mission statement of 'Checks and balances' is any mention of Conway's wife, who helmed Trump's White House campaign and is now one of his most trusted advisers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob That Stalked Tucker Carlson Back On TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/14/smash-racism-dc-back-twitter-tucker-carlson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how they got around their suspension</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfire death toll 48; Search for missing continues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2144d7d18c2144d09ce31eec69515441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — A message board at a shelter for the many people who fled California's deadliest wildfire is filled with photos of the missing, as well as pleas for any information about relatives and friends. "I hope you are okay," reads one hand written note on the board filled with white and yellow sheets of notebook paper. Another had a picture of a missing man: "If seen, please have him call." Authorities on Tuesday reported six more fatalities from the Northern California blaze, bringing the total number of dead so far to 48. They haven't disclosed the total number still missing, but earlier in the week that figure was more than 200.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polluting air more than 100 miles away...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/california-wildfires-fouling-air-100-miles/story?id=59162108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two massive California wildfires are creating bad air more than 100 miles away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal prosecutors reviewing altered election docs tied to Florida Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/florida/story/2018/11/13/federal-prosecutors-reviewing-altered-election-documents-tied-to-florida-democrats-695299</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Department of State says the concerns can be tied to the Florida Democratic Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Lesbian Love Triangle 'FAVOURITE' Builds OSCAR Buzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/favourite-blows-up-metoo-gender-politics-love-triangle-1160665</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This ain't your mother's costume drama as Olivia Colman, Emma Stone and Rachel Weisz preside over a royal spectacle of cunning ladies and dandied-up men with a lot to say about Trump-era power struggles: "We're disgusting and gorgeous and powerful and weak and filthy and brilliant."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7735163/theresa-may-brexit-deal-cabinet-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May today faced down hostile MPs as she fights for her political life amidst fallout from her Brexit deal. The PM is holding a crunch Cabinet showdown this afternoon where she will set out …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate contrarian uncovers scientific error, upends major ocean warming study...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/environment/sd-me-climate-study-error-20181113-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists with UC San Diego’s Scripps Institution of Oceanography and Princeton University recently walked back a claim made last month that oceans had been heating up dramatically faster than the international scientific community previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP subpoenaed by DOJ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/snap-subpoenaed-by-justice-department-over-its-ipo-disclosures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Justice Department and Securities and Exchange Commission have subpoenaed Snap for information about its March 2017 initial public offering, the social media app maker told Reuters on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E discloses 'electric incident' just before wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/pge-plunges-20percent-after-disclosing-an-electric-incident-just-before-fire.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PG&amp;E fell 20 percent after the company said that if its equipment is responsible for the "Camp Fire," the cost of the damage would exceed its insurance coverage and harm its financial health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Boom Comes Up Against Law of Gravity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/residential-real-estate-boom-comes-up-against-the-law-of-gravity#gs.A9UVH18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real Estate Fights the Law of Gravity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited food coming, but will shoppers buy?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/584754eadd0a43a1ab5bf93af54845af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The next generation of biotech food is headed for the grocery aisles, and first up may be salad dressings or granola bars made with soybean oil genetically tweaked to be good for your heart. By early next year, the first foods from plants or animals that had their DNA "edited" are expected to begin selling. It's a different technology than today's controversial "genetically modified" foods, more like faster breeding that promises to boost nutrition, spur crop growth, and make farm animals hardier and fruits and vegetables last longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns 'to gossip is to kill'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/064ffe09bc6e4fa9bf5a6c73692a9fe7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis is denouncing gossip as a form of "terrorism" and is warning the faithful against telling lies. Francis explored the Catholic commandment against "bearing false witness" during his Wednesday general audience. He warned the faithful in a chilly St. Peter's Square that "We all live by communicating, and we are continuously on the edge between truth and lies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Morale Takes Tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-morale-takes-a-tumble-along-with-stock-price-1542200400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An internal survey found just 52% of employees were optimistic about Facebook’s future, down from 84% the year earlier. The darkening mood comes amid a dropping share price, leadership turmoil and disclosures of privacy violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan migrants reach Tijuana, start climbing the border fence...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/caravan-migrants-reach-tijuana-start-climbing-the-border-fence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first wave of migrants from the Central American caravan began climbing border fences on Tuesday after arriving at the U.S. border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China builds artificial sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/china-built-artificial-sun-its-13588517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's artificial sun is designed to help develop cheap and clean energy on earth using nuclear fusion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Never Nancy': Dems ramp up efforts to sideline...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/nancy-democrats-ramp-efforts-sideline-pelosi-offering-alternative/story?id=59180391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A band of House Democrats determined to oppose House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi's speaker bid are planning to release a signed letter as soon as this week indicating that they have gathered enough support to deny her the 218 votes needed to win the gavel on the House floor in January, a move they...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazes on two fronts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/paradise-lost-california-fires-rage-155925886.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of firefighters battled blazes in northern and southern California on Tuesday as body recovery teams searched the remains of houses and charred cars for victims of the deadliest wildfire in the history of the US state. Most of the fatalities have been caused by the so-called "Camp Fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who battled flames to save his corner...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-battled-flames-save-corner-paradise-023856218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paradise (United States) (AFP) - By all accounts, retired carpenter Brad Weldon should have evacuated his home in Paradise as the flames approached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech stars see shares dim in eyes of investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181114-tech-stars-see-shares-dim-eyes-investors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Robocop' patrols summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/robocop-patrol-singapore-summit-094319844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi-tech Singapore has deployed an autonomous robot with a swivelling camera for a head and flashing lights to patrol a summit venue -- arresting the attention of amused passers-by who stopped to snap selfies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tech factory conditions fuel suicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/china-tech-factory-conditions-fuel-suicides-study-10929938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost city built by Trojan War captives found...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-lost-ancient-city-built-by-Trojan-War-captives-13390072.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mention the Trojan War and what may first come to mind is the oft-told tale of Helen, wife of Sparta's King Menelaus and possessor of a divinely bestowed beauty, falling in love with Paris of Troy. Their supposed affair and her subsequent abduction from Sparta sparked a 10-year Greek siege of Troy that would shape Greek civilization for centuries to come - at least according to Greek mythology. Now fast-forward about three millennia. For the past several years, archaeologist Elena Korka has been focused on a far less romantic but more concrete legacy of the Trojan War: A lost city named Tenea, reportedly settled by war prisoners brought over from Troy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida voting machines overheat, forcing another recount...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/floridas-palm-beach-county-voting-machines-overheat-forcing-another-recount-of-about-175k-early-votes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida’s Palm Beach County recount was delayed Tuesday night after its voting machines overheated, forcing it to restart the recount of about 175, 000 early votes, according to Susan Bucher, supervisor of Elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP to Pick Another Cheney to Help Party Find Winning Message...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/gop-to-pick-another-cheney-to-help-party-find-a-winning-message#gs.QddzCkY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP to Pick Another Cheney to Help Party Find a Winning Message</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel defense minister resigns over Gaza cease-fire; 'Surrendering to terror'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46207094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avigdor Lieberman denounced the cabinet's decision to accept a ceasefire as "surrendering to terror".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal justice reform faces a make-or-break moment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/416558-criminal-justice-reform-faces-a-make-or-break-moment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long-stalled criminal justice reform effort is facing a make-or-break moment: winning over President Trump’s support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink's husband threatens looters: 'Will be shot on site'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2018/11/13/pinks-husband-carey-hart-threatens-california-wildfire-looters-shot-site/1996302002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carey Hart posted a picture to Instagram Tuesday of a dozen gun-wielding men standing in front of a sign that reads,Â "Looters will be shot on site."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five days of fury...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ie/news/world/five-days-of-fury-inside-trump%E2%80%99s-paris-temper-election-woes-and-staff-upheaval/ar-BBPGZml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems eye Senate seat in Republican-led Mississippi...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2867f89dc1d347cdaab422902a320a55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — National Democrats are focusing on Mississippi's U.S. Senate runoff, a year after winning a longshot contest in another Deep South state dominated by Republicans. Democrat Doug Jones defeated Roy Moore in Alabama last December after Moore was hit by accusations of sexual misconduct. Now in Mississippi, Mike Espy is challenging Republican Sen. Cindy Hyde-Smith. She faces sharp criticism for a video that surfaced Sunday of her praising a supporter at a Nov. 2 campaign event in Tupelo by saying: "If he invited me to a public hanging, I'd be on the front row."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro Bashes President Again: 'Down With This Motherf*cker!'</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/scene/news/robert-de-niro-bashes-trump-again-down-with-this-motherf-er-1203027278/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert De Niro may have been the target of the Donald Trump-supporting pipe bomb mailer, but that isn’t stopping the Oscar winner from trashing the president. Just two days after playing Robert Mue…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC, CBS fighting for ratings dominance...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/nbc-cbs-fighting-television-ratings-dominance-59174251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Score one week for NBC in what's becoming an intriguing battle with CBS for dominance in the television ratings this season. NBC's victory in the most recent measurements provided by the Nielsen company means it has won bragging rights for three weeks so far this fall, with CBS also winning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES: Trump, stung by midterms and nervous about Mueller, retreats from traditional duties...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-trump-absent-20181113-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump, brooding over midterm losses and the Mueller probe, has cancelled a number of events that presidents normally attend, including a visit to Arlington National Cemetery. Behind the scenes, he has lashed out at aides, from low level press assistants to senior officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Virgin bride' sold to highest bidder on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7733272/virgin-bride-for-sale-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SICK family sold their 17-year-old daughter “virgin bride” on Facebook to the highest bidder for 500 cows, three cars and £7,500 in a “barbaric slave market”. The teen was married to businessman …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's most secretive lab: Bullets that never miss, weaponized insects, superhumans...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7726956/darpa-tech-us-government/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BULLETS that never miss, super soldiers with extreme strength and robot warriors capable of rising up against humans may sound like the stuff of science fiction… but the truth is that they have all…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clyburn claims critics using race to oppose leadership bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article221603770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Jim Clyburn, D-South Carolina, is accusing his detractors of launching a “dog whistle” whisper campaign to undermine his candidacy for House majority whip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: American military advantage has eroded; ChinaRussia threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-military-advantage-has-eroded-study-says-13390309.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The United States has lost its military edge to a dangerous degree and could potentially lose a war against China or Russia, according to a report released Wednesday by a bipartisan commission that Congress created to evaluate the Trump administration's defense strategy. The National Defense Strategy Commission, comprised of former top Republican and Democratic officials selected by Congress, evaluated the Trump administration's 2018 National Defense Strategy, which ordered a vast reshaping of the U.S. military to compete with Beijing and Moscow in an era of renewed great-power competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitting in embers, residents wonder: Can Paradise be rebuilt?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-paradise/sitting-in-the-embers-californians-wonder-can-paradise-be-rebuilt-idUSKCN1NI2UK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lovingly placed statues of a family of deer still mark the entrance to Mare Reas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Jesus' face' uncovered at ancient church in Israeli desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/jesus-face-uncovered-at-ancient-church-in-the-israeli-desert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A previously-unknown 1,500-year-old painting of Christ’s face has been uncovered at a Byzantine church in Israel’s Negev desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNLUCKY IN LOVE?  IT'S ALL YOUR MOTHER'S FAULT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6385855/Your-mothers-love-life-determines-romantic-partners-have.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say the findings, based on data of mothers and children in the US since 1979, show mothers pass relationship skills to their kids, which influence how they interact with everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Lady's Office: White House Aide 'No Longer Deserves' to Serve...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-aide-ricardel-no-longer-deserves-serve-first-194655656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. first lady Melania Trump has asked that the White House sever ties with deputy national security adviser Mira Ricardel, a spokeswoman for the first lady's office said on Tuesday. "It is the position of the Office of the First Lady that she [Ricardel] no longer deserves the honor of serving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY'S BREXIT D-DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4179680916a64b08a3afa24ea50785a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Theresa May will try to persuade her divided Cabinet on Wednesday that they have a choice between backing a draft Brexit deal with the European Union or plunging the U.K. into political and economic uncertainty. May called a special Cabinet meeting after negotiators from Britain and the EU broke a months-long logjam and reached agreement on divorce terms, including a plan to keep the border between Ireland and Northern Ireland open after Brexit. May was meeting with ministers one-on-one Wednesday morning ahead of the Cabinet meeting at 2 p.m. (1400 GMT) in a bid to build agreement and stave off potential resignations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfire death toll rises as search for missing continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2144d7d18c2144d09ce31eec69515441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — A message board at a shelter for the many people who fled California's deadliest wildfire is filled with photos of the missing, as well as pleas for any information about relatives and friends. "I hope you are okay," reads one hand written note on the board filled with white and yellow sheets of notebook paper. Another had a picture of a missing man: "If seen, please have him call." Authorities on Tuesday reported six more fatalities from the Northern California blaze, bringing the total number of dead so far to 48. They haven't disclosed the total number still missing, but earlier in the week that figure was more than 200.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
