<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign turns Iran attack into massive FACEBOOK ad blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-campaign-turns-Iran-attack-into-massive-14960107.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days after President Donald Trump ordered a drone strike that killed a top Iranian general, the commander in chief's 2020 campaign turned the attack into a political pitch, purchasing roughly 1,000 ads on Facebook that touted his military credentials - and sought to raise money for his reelection push.  The online advertising blitz began late Monday as Trump's team sought to defend the killing of Qasem Soleimani, a major general in Iran's Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps. Many of the ads solicited personal information from voters that could be useful as the campaign seeks to mobilize voters on Election Day.  The digital strategy mirrors Trump's previous social media campaigns concerning impeachment, immigration and other signature issues, relying on a mix of narrowly targeted messages - along with headline-grabbing tweets seen by millions - to command the political conversation, mobilize his base and advance his policy agenda with an eye on the election. Trump's campaign also alerted supporters with a series of similar text messages highlighting Soleimani's death.  "From a campaign perspective, any time the president accomplishes something - and fighting terrorism is among his biggest campaign promises, keeping our country safe - that is grounds for making the argument that he should be reelected," said Matt Braynard, the data director for Trump's 2016 campaign who says he is not involved in his reelection effort.  But some experts bristled at Trump's tactics in the context of national security, stressing that the stakes are higher than usual: Every ad, tweet and social media statement from Trump carries significant weight in a rapidly developing conflict, they said.  "Growing campaign email lists based on fear and online fundraising for political gain should hardly be a priority of the commander in chief during a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber Says He Has Lyme...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/01/08/not-so-yummy-justin-bieber-says-he-has-lyme-disease-and-chronic-mono</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber is responding to TMZ and other reports that he looks bad, etc. He says on Instagram that he has Lyme disease and chronic mono.  He should know that the Global Lyme Alliance in New Yor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who impersonated missing boy after watching '20/20' gets 2 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/crime/ny-man-who-impersonated-missing-boy-gets-two-years-in-prison-20200108-2vgxgk3zwnhnxhquithh2ljp4u-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ohio man who claimed to be a long-missing child last year, sparking nationwide attention and raising false hopes for the family, was sentenced to two years in prison Wednesday after admitting the story was a hoax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS BRING RECORD CABLE NEWS RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/tucker-carlson-scores-highest-ratings-ever-at-8-p-m-during-coverage-of-iran-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breaking Iran news sent viewers scrambling to their sets on Tuesday nights — leading to massive across the board numbers for the big three cable news networks. Fox News had its biggest night since</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNER BROS. Using AI to Pick Movie Scripts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/warner-bros-signs-deal-ai-driven-film-management-system-1268036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The studio has made a pact with Cinelytic to use its project management system that was launched last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senator Rages at 'Insulting' Military Briefing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/477424-rand-paul-mike-lee-rip-administration-over-insulting-and-demeaning-iran</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP Sens. Mike Lee (Utah) and Rand Paul (Ky.) ripped the administration over a closed-door briefing on Iran on Wednesday, announcing they will now support a resolution reining in President Trump's military powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE COMMONERS:  Meghan and Harry quit as senior members of royal family...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/08/prince-harry-and-meghan-markle-are-hypocrites-abdicate-or-stay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How’s this for quitting your job: Abandon every aspect you hate, while continuing to reap all the benefits you love. This, in effect, is what Prince Harry and Meghan Markle have done. In a statemen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STANDING DOWN'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/stampede-iran-generals-funeral-leaves-over-30-dead-111350204.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump pulled back from the brink of war with Iran on Wednesday, saying that Tehran appeared to be "standing down" after firing missiles -- without causing casualties -- at US troops based in Iraq. In a televised address to the nation from the White House, Trump emphasized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katzenberg unveils new mobile format: 'Turnstyle'... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/quibi-hopes-quick-bite-tv-smartphones-wins-viewers-215314674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New streaming service Quibi on Wednesday provided a glimpse into its bid to win over smartphone users, vowing to shake up the industry with original programs lasting less than 10 minutes. Quibi founder Jeffrey Katzenberg said it was designed for young lifestyles, offering episodes to be viewed while</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACK FROM THE BRINK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d40501d9b0a712d02e2a6626f607ead2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. and Iran stepped back from the brink of possible war on Wednesday as President Donald Trump signaled he would not retaliate militarily for Iran's missile strikes on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACE RACE:  VIRGIN GALACTIC reaches milestone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ba8750d5c7ba862a457c972034b8432b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Virgin Galactic's next passenger spaceship has reached a major construction milestone, the company said Wednesday. All major structural elements have been assembled and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay for video bites?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/717e7a42efea81f22afd2e3ab40d1d6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — A startup heavily backed by Hollywood is wagering that you're ready to set aside YouTube and TikTok to watch star-studded short videos on your phone — for a price. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg says she's cancer-free...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/08/ruth-bader-ginsburg-health-096302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 86-year-old Supreme Court justice made the declaration after a series of health issues in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDI B 'Filing for Nigerian Citizenship' Amid Growing U.S. Tension with Iran...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/music/cardi-b-filing-for-nigerian-citizenship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week, President Donald Trump ordered an airstrike that killed Iran's top military official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New plan keeps autonomous vehicle standards voluntary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d38d6dc3c126baed6d2da3f925dab884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Wednesday unveiled its most recent round of guidelines for autonomous vehicle makers that rely on voluntary standards despite calls for specific...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders GOOGLE to turn over Jussie Smollett's emails, data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/69832caded917d8c8643fbc69ab7eb2e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ÇHICAGO (AP) — A judge has ordered Google to turn over a year's worth of Jussie Smollett's emails, private messages, photographs and location data to a special prosecutor who is looking into why...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein lawyers want judge off rape case over texting jabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/harvey-weinstein-s-lawyers-want-judge-rape-case-over-texting-n1112591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weinstein’s lawyers sent a letter to Judge James Burke saying his comments Tuesday raised questions about his impartiality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu Season May Yet Turn Ugly, CDC Warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-flu-season-may-yet-turn-ugly-cdc-warns/ar-BBYKhAd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senator Rages at 'Insulting' Military Briefing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/gop-sen-mike-lee-rages-at-insulting-military-briefing-on-iran-crisis-probably-the-worst-ive-ever-seen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of Congress were briefed today on Iran, and Senator Mike Lee (R- UT) wanted to make it clear to reporters afterwards that he was pissed off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krugman Says Hacker Downloaded 'Child Porn' Using His IP Address...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/nyts-paul-krugman-says-hacker-downloaded-child-pornography-using-his-ip-address/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Someone compromised my IP address and is using it to download child pornography."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Did TWITTER Diplomacy Stop War?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/donald-trump-iran-twitter-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tweets from US president Donald Trump and Iranian foreign minister Javad Zarif Tuesday offered a fascinating glimpse at how world leaders can communicate more quickly and directly than ever in times of crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House to vote Thursday to curb President's war powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/08/democrats-trump-iran-war-power-096193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats remain frustrated that the administration hasn't provided much information about the killing of a top Iranian general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The medications that change who we are...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200108-the-medications-that-change-who-we-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’ve been linked to road rage, pathological gambling, and complicated acts of fraud. It turns out many ordinary medications don’t just affect our bodies – they affect our brains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>93-Year-Old Tenant Opens Fire On Apt Manager Over Water Issue...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2020/01/08/watch-93-year-old-man-opens-fire-on-apartment-manager-over-water-issue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 93-year-old man upset about water damage at his Las Vegas apartment was caught on camera shooting the manager of his residential complex, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel unveils 'laser-sword' to ward off threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Israels-Defense-Ministry-announces-breakthrough-in-laser-technology-613568</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology expected to take down a variety of aerial threats including rockets, drones, anti-tank missiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS Won't Have Host -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/the-oscar-telecast-2020-no-ho-abcst-second-straight-year-tca-1202824503/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s official — the 2020 Academy Awards will have no host. Karey Burke, entertainment president for ABC, the network that carries the Oscars, confirmed the decision during her executive…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retiree saves CA's oldest weekly newspaper from closure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ca7bf4db2302609e21fcb9003de931a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOWNIEVILLE, Calif. (AP) — A retiree has canceled an around-the-world trip to save California's oldest weekly newspaper, which was set to shut down when its editor retires this month. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell says 'no haggling' as impeachment standoff deepens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/698067e211b6d0f61d98c2277e459c57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Wednesday there will be “no haggling” over the process for President Donald Trump's impeachment trial in a deepening standoff with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving to North America, palace confirms...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10700782/prince-harry-meghan-markle-moving-canada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Harry and Meghan Markle are moving out of the UK in a “step back” from royal duties and plan to pay for themselves, Buckingham Palace confirmed today. The pair are set to quit as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian journals retract 800 papers after 'bombshell' investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/01/russian-journals-retract-more-800-papers-after-bombshell-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Academy commission's probe of domestic journals causes "conflict and tension"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan and Harry quit as senior members of royal family...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-meghan-markle-harry-announce-21241726</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke and Duchess have tonight revealed the news in a statement on their Instagram page - saying they plan to make a move to North America this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTOLOGY Argues Actor's Stalking Lawsuit Must Go to 'Religious Arbitration'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/church-scientology-says-danny-masterson-stalking-suit-go-religious-arbitration-1268021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New court papers argue that four suing women consented to "ecclesiastical rule" and forever relinquished their right to sue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Reviving 'THIRTYSOMETHING,' 'WHO WANTS TO BE MILLIONAIRE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/jimmy-kimmel-host-celebrity-driven-who-wants-be-a-millionaire-abc-1268004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special run of episodes will premiere April 8 and feature an interactive component.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Calls for Plastic Bag Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/biden-calls-plastic-bag-ban-we-should-not-be-allowing-plastic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden said he “100 percent” supports a national ban on plastic bags.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Here’s the key exchange:&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Voter at town hall: “When I go back to Kenya, we don’t even use plastic bags or plastic papers. It’s not allowed, because we are trying to clean the ocean. And I think here in America, we are not trying to do that, to support the environment. And so, what’s your view? I mean, what’s your focus? Because in Kenya, we are trying to clean the environment. No plastic bags, you go with your own bags.”&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Biden: “Well I agree with you 100 percent. We should not be allowing plastic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't bite!' quips pope as he kisses nun...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dont-bite-quips-pope-kisses-nun-172059958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beard Bravado: 75% Of Men Feel More Confident With Facial Hair...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/beard-bravado-75-of-men-feel-more-confident-with-facial-hair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial hair is so important to modern men that one in five say they would give up sex for a full year if it meant they could grow the "perfect beard."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge accused of courthouse threesome is suspended...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/kentucky-judge-accused-courthouse-threesome-suspended-n1112296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Dawn Gentry, who is facing nine counts of misconduct, denies engaging in sexual activity at the courthouse with two employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man breaks into TACO BELL to cook his own meal...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/georgia-police-man-cooks-food-takes-nap-during-taco-bell-break-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gwinnett County police need help identifying a man accused of breaking into a fast-food restaurant, preparing food, then taking a nap on Christmas morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katzenberg unveils new mobile video format: 'Turnstyle'... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/quibi-unveils-turnstyle-its-flagship-mobile-video-format-03a19028-0a7e-4d1a-8173-211cd979ee71.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new video service hopes its vertical-to-horizontal trick will lure subscribers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury selection process continues in Weinstein rape trial...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-gloria-allred-ban-attempt-day-3-jury-selection-1202824473/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mother of one of Harvey Weinstein’s former attorneys and one of America’s most well-known lawyers was the object of the Oscar-winning producer’s legal derision on the third day of his rape tria…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq Fears Turning Into a Warzone Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/iraq-fears-turning-into-a-warzone-again/ar-BBYKfIZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite image reveals damage to US airbase after strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/satellite-image-shows-airbase-hit-21240678</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran launched missiles at the American Ain al-Assad airbase in retaliation over the US assassination of the Iranian general Qassam Soleimani</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STANDING DOWN'</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-to-make-statement-on-iranian-missile-strikes-assures-nation-all-is-well</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump declared Wednesday that Iran “appears to be standing down,” in the wake of missile strikes on American bases in Iraq that he said resulted in “no casualties.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine plane crashes in Iran, killing all 176 on board...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/08/boeing-737-passenger-plane-crashes-in-iran-state-news-agencies-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Boeing 737 passenger plane operated by a Ukrainian airline crashed minutes after takeoff from Tehran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ERS Players Destress -- Thanks To NFL's First Emotional Support Dog!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/01/07/49ers-frenchie-nfls-first-emotional-support-dog-assists-players-and-staff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zoe is the NFL’s first emotional support dog. The smallest 49er offers a big assist to players and staff alike at Levi's Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUR MISSILES BIGGER</title>
      <link>https://grabien.com/story.php?id=267683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The fact that we have this great military and equipment, however, does not mean we have to use it’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  LET'S MAKE A DEAL</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/us-iran-news-01-08-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran attacked two Iraqi military bases housing US troops with more than a dozen ballistic missiles, in retaliation for the US killing of Iranian commander Qasem Soleimani. Follow here for the latest updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMY WARNS OF DRAFT HOAX</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108160518-cycqb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/USA-DRAFT:No draft, and definitely no draft by text message: U.S. Army warns of hoax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two quakes strike near nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/08/middleeast/iran-earthquakes-nuclear-plant-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two earthquakes struck near a nuclear power plant in southwestern Iran on Wednesday morning, just over a week after another quake hit the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ SETS NEW RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/08/stock-markets-today-us-futures-fall-following-attack-in-iraq.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investor sentiment was boosted as oil prices retreated from their highs. There were also no reports of casualties so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUPAUL: Wouldn't mind if never did drag again...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rupaul-on-new-netflix-show-aj-and-the-queen-why-he-wouldnt-mind-never-doing-drag-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RuPaul has had many titles, including drag queen, TV host, author and businessman – but there's another one he wants people to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEFACEBOOK Make Rare Appearance to Brag About 'Privacy'...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/01/apple-facebook-exec-discuss-data-privacy-ces-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Apple’s first official appearance at CES in 27 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SLAP'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7116313efdb56f4e928289faa1ad8cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran struck back at the United States early Wednesday for killing its most powerful military commander, firing a barrage of ballistic missiles at two Iraqi military bases that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army debunks fake texts telling people they've been drafted...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article239073053.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S WAR!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7865171/Trump-address-world-Iran-Ayatollah-calls-missile-attack-not-revenge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-stakes address comes just hours after Iran launched what it promised would be a 'crushing revenge' strike over the death of General Qassem Soleimani but only damaged two airbases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500 quakes have rattled in 10 days. May be more to come...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/08/us/puerto-rico-region-hundreds-of-earthquakes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 6.4 magnitude earthquake that killed one person in Puerto Rico on Tuesday is one of hundreds of tremors that have rattled the island for more than a week. And experts say the shaking is not over yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY: I STILL HAVE MORE TO PROVE...</title>
      <link>https://weei.radio.com/blogs/ryan-hannable/tom-brady-thanks-patriots-fans-in-instagram-post</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weei.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady reflected on the season, future via Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabbings, shootings, assaults weigh on US Jewish youth...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cce65f400c17b004d4ec7d5ff5a0ff8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — When a man spewed anti-Semitic slurs and spat on her face, Shoshana Blum remembered her ancestors who survived the Holocaust, and instead of looking down - she defiantly stared at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech plane joins search for mysterious drones in Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/high-tech-plane-joins-search-mysterious-drones-colorado/story?id=68128257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plane, intended for use in wildfires, carries sophisticated cameras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA had advance warning of attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2020/01/08/us-officials-warned-missile-launch-iraq-bases-troops/2842200001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials had advance warning of Iran's missile assault that damaged two Iraqi bases housing U.S. and coalition forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to address nation 11 a.m. ET...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/01/08/donald-trump-address-nation-iran-attacks/2842056001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were no casualties in the missile barrage that Iran described as retaliation for last week's U.S. attack that killed a top Iranian general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shot down?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10694922/iran-plane-crash-ukrainian-airline-black-box/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN has refused to hand over the black box of a plane that crashed killing 176 people to international investigators. The Kiev-bound Ukraine International Airlines jet came down shortly after taki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot lab producing 'human replicas' laid bare in video tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-lab-producing-human-21239270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: RealDoll guided viewers through its groundbreaking lab producing AI-powered dolls. It is currently testing models with futuristic AI vision and touch sensors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Fewer Than Third of American Voters Can Point to Iran on Map...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2020/01/08/can-you-locate-iran-few-voters-can/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As tensions between the United States and Iran rise in the aftermath of the American drone strike that killed the country’s most powerful commander, Gen. Qassem Soleimani, a new Morning Consult/Politico survey finds fewer than 3 in 10 registered voters can identify the Islamic republic on an unlabeled map.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What next?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/what-next-awaiting-trumps-response-to-iranian-missile-attack-on-us-bases-in-iraq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL IS WELL: Once it seemed clear there were no U.S. casualties from Iran’s missile strike on two U.S. bases in Iraq, the White House called off plans for President Trump to address the nation, and instead Trump went to bed after sending a single tweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Survey of Media Executives Shows Dire Views About Industry's Future...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/digital/news/media-and-entertainment-exec-survey-business-model-ey-1203456357/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With media and entertainment sectors continuing to be whipped by winds of digital disruption, many industry execs believe they need to change the ways they’ve done business — or see the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China facial-recognition case puts Big Brother on trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-facial-recognition-case-puts-big-brother-trial-045846432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial-recognition technology has become embedded in China, from airports to hotels, e-commerce sites and even public toilets, but a law professor had enough when asked to scan his face at a safari park. Guo Bing took the wildlife park to court, raising the temperature in a growing debate about privacy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child found dead in plane's landing gear at Paris airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10696574/child-found-dead-in-planes-landing-gear-at-paris-airport-on-flight-from-ivory-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHILD has been found dead in the landing gear of a plane at a Paris airport. The Air France flight was travelling to Paris-Charles de Gaulle airport in the French capital from Abidjan in Ivory Co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left launches pre-Iowa assault on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/08/progressives-pre-iowa-assault-biden-095934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many activist groups expected the former veep to crumble by now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will not give black box to BOEING...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Iran-civil-aviation-org-says-will-not-give-black-box-to-Boeing-613548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Ricans sleep outside, wait for power after 'devastating' quake...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108102705-whjbu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a week of tremors, many fear their homes will crumble if there's another earthquake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombian drug lord El Tio arrested after son tips off police because dad had affair with his wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10694600/drug-lord-arrested-affair-sons-wife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of the world’s most wanted drug lords has been arrested, reportedly after a tip-off by his son. At one stage, Colombian Luis del Rio — known as El Tio — was trafficking at least ten tons of coc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red devil horns appear over Persian Gulf during eclipse...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10694515/red-devil-horns-sunrise-photos-captured-rare-solar-eclipse-mirage/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE incredible images appear to show giant devil horns rising over the Persian Gulf during a solar eclipse. A photographer waited in just the right place to snap the rare spectacle as the sun was…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're going to war, bro': Fort Bragg's 82nd Airborne deploys to Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iraq-security-usa-fort-bragg/were-going-to-war-bro-fort-braggs-82nd-airborne-deploys-to-the-middle-east-idUSKBN1Z616W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many of the soldiers, it would be their first mission. They packed up ammuni...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran leader tweets flag -- like Trump did...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article239060528.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg to appear in FOXNEWS town hall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/477158-pete-buttigieg-to-appear-in-fox-news-town-hall  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News will host a town hall with former South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg on Jan. 26 from Des Moines, Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi tells colleagues to 'pray'... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/ill-call-him-back-pelosi-puts-house-business-first-as-pence-calls-about-missile-attack-on-iraq-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi was huddling with Democratic colleagues when she was alerted of the missile attack on an Iraqi base that hosts U.S. troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas facing 10,000 potential cybersecurity attacks from Iran per minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/article239042893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security upped in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattlepi.com/news/article/Security-upped-in-D-C-region-after-threats-by-14957314.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattlepi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Authorities across the Washington, District of Columbia, region are boosting security at military bases, Arlington Cemetery and at sites along the National Mall following threats by Iran to retaliate against the United States for the killing of Maj. Gen. Qasem Soleimani.  In some cases, entry gates at military facilities have been closed, and officials are carrying out more thorough identity checks. A spokesman for the U.S. Park Police said the agency's uniformed officers will have a more visible presence because of the tensions with Iran.  "There's no specific threats," said Sgt. Eduardo Delgado, spokesman for the U.S. Park Police. "It's just an abundance of precaution."  But the rollout of the enhanced security has not been smooth in every case, leaving some people facing a chaotic return to work at the beginning of the new year. The Navy command that runs Walter Reed National Military Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, modified some of its new precautions and issued a lighthearted mea culpa on its Facebook page Monday evening after the security changescaused monstrous traffic in the area that morning.  "Today's traffic was awful. It was horrible," the post read. "It looked at normal D.C. Monday traffic and said, 'Hey, watch this!' "  Nevertheless, officials wrote that the enhanced security was necessary to keep people safe.  Last week, President Donald Trump ordered the drone strike that killed Soleimani, Iran's most important military commander. Iran's leaders quickly promised to take revenge. And an Iranian official said Tuesday that the country was considering 13 scenarios for retaliation and had American bases in the Middle East under surveillance.  Over the weekend, the Department of Homeland Security issued a bulletin warning that Iran and its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN settles lawsuit with Covington Catholic student...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/cnn-settles-lawsuit-with-covington-catholic-student-nick-sandmann/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN, on Tuesday, settled a lawsuit with Covington Catholic student Nick Sandmann — who alleged that the network made "vicious" and "direct attacks" against him following a viral co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm sorry, I have a sick child,' Philly robber writes in demand note...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/robber-claims-he-has-a-sick-child-during-philly-robbery-20200107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case eerily echoes a similar robbery last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSILES FIRED AT BASES</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/missile-attacks-target-us-forces-in-iraq-senior-military-source-says-iran-suspected</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missiles were fired early Wednesday in multiple locations across Iraq, a senior U.S. military source in the country told Fox News, describing it as a series of attacks on U.S. forces from Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S WAR!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7862453/Multiple-rockets-hit-Taji-military-base-Iraq-American-British-troops-based.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tehran has tonight launched missile attack on two US bases in Iraq housing US and coalition troops, defense sources have revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL UP 4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/07/oil-prices-surge-4percent-following-attack-on-iraq-airbase.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices surged in early trading on Tuesday night following attacks on bases in Western Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA GETS RAVES AT CES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/digital/news/ivanka-trump-ces-keynote-tech-jobs-impeachment-1203459163/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump talked about the current and future state of the U.S. workforce at CES — an appearance that was met with a fair amount of enthusiasm among the tech-industry attendees. In a keyno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOLLYWOOD,' '1917' boosted by producer, director nods...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/once-upon-time-1917-boosted-producer-director-nods-190416514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino's "Once Upon a Time... in Hollywood" and Sam Mendes's "1917" boosted their awards charges Tuesday, collecting key nominations from Hollywood's producing and directing guilds just days after bagging the top Golden Globes prizes. Tarantino's homage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack came in three waves just after midnight...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-launches-missiles-iraq-housing-us-troops-state-003842838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran on Wednesday launched a missile attack on an Iraqi airbase where US forces are based, threatening "more crushing responses" if Washington carried out further strikes, Iranian state media said. It said the missiles were in response to a US strike last week that killed Iranian general Qasem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell to begin impeachment trial with no deal on witnesses... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4b1b786420b4468dbe5da3b334e037db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Tuesday he has the votes to start President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial as soon as House Speaker Nancy Pelosi releases the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author Wurtzel dies at 52...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3bc202902e8baa8b479d39acbee38102</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Elizabeth Wurtzel, whose blunt and painful confessions of her struggles with addiction and depression in the best-selling “Prozac Nation” made her a voice and a target for an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URGENT MEETING AT WHITE HOUSE...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108002323-ne7v3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/ATTACK-WHITEHOUSE (URGENT):Pompeo, Esper arrive at White House after Iran attack on Iraqi base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone's scared'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108000251-zv8o8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUERTORICO-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 12, PIX, TV):UPDATE 12-'Everyone's scared' - Puerto Rico declares emergency after earthquakes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation 'Martyr Soleimani'... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200107234619-cb330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/ATTACK-PENTAGON (URGENT):Iran launches large attack on U.S.-led forces in Iraq, Pentagon says</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
