<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trans woman fatally shot weeks after viral assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Transgender-Woman-Whose-Assault-Was-Captured-on-Video-Fatally-Shot-Saturday-510143521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcdfw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transgender woman whose April assault in a Dallas parking lot was captured on video and went viral, was shot and killed Saturday morning, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diocese raid inspires Catholics to close ranks or lose faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/dallas/2019/05/19/raid-dallas-diocese-inspires-catholics-close-ranks-lose-faith-enough-enough</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholics across the area wrestled with sadness, disappointment and outright anger after last week's raid on the Dallas diocese, which police say...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yosemite looks like snow globe with summer just around corner...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/yosemite-snow-summer-winter-weather-conditions-13851359.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a time when Yosemite National Park is typically preparing for the summer season, the mountains and granite monoliths surrounding the majestic valley are coated in fresh white powder. If you were standing atop Half Dome today, you might feel as if you were in the center of a snow globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GAME OF THRONES' Finale End of TV As We Know It?</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/entertainment/article/3010652/how-netflixs-rise-and-game-thrones-finale-mark-end-tv-we</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix ushered in the era of binge watching by releasing the entire TV series on the same day. The weekly episodes of Game of Thrones, and the office conversations around them and other series, could soon be a thing of the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SIMMERS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/444483-trump-hits-fox-for-wasting-airtime-on-coverage-of-pete-buttigieg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Sunday criticized Fox News, accusing the network of "wasting airtime" over its coverage of South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg and other Democratic 2020 contenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket almost hits US Embassy in Baghdad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9110117/donald-trump-threat-official-end-iran-baghdad-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump threatened Iran with destruction today as tensions flared after a rocket almost hit the US Embassy in Baghdad. The US President tweeted: “If Iran wants to fight, that will be the offic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAYOR PETE STANDING OVATION FOXNEWS TOWNHALL</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/pete-buttigieg-gets-standing-ovation-at-end-of-fox-news-town-hall-surprising-chris-wallace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg received a standing ovation from the crowd at the end of his Fox News town hall in Claremont, New Hampshire Sunday night. The South Bend, Indiana Mayor and 2020 presidential candidate drew raucous applause throughout his town hall with Fox News anchor Chris Wallace, particularly when he dismissed President Donald Trump's tweets: "I don't care," Buttigieg remarked when asked how he felt about the missives. At the end of the town hall, Wallace gave him time for a closing statement: Look, what we're trying to do here is different. Because the moment that we're in is different. I get that a millennial, midwestern mayor is not what leaps to mind when you think about a prototypical candidate for president. But I also think we're living -- if it's hard to figure out what's going on right now, it's because we are living on one of those blank pages in between chapters of American history. And what comes next could be ugly or it could be amazing. And I believe running for office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady stabs straphanger accused of fondling self on NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/19/man-accused-of-pleasuring-himself-on-subway-gets-stabbed-moments-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A straphanger was stabbed after a woman accused him of fondling himself on the subway in Manhattan, cops said Sunday. The 29-year-old was riding the southbound 5 line on the East Side around 8:30 p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS DIG DEUTSCHE BANK...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-deutsche-bank/bank-staff-flagged-trump-kushner-transactions-for-watchdog-nytimes-idUSKCN1SP0PB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-money laundering specialists at Deutsche Bank AG recommended in 2016 and 20...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vintage planes fly USA to Normandy for 'last large' D-Day commemoration...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/news/connecticut/hc-news-dday-75th-anniversary-squadron-trip-oxford-20190518-k535nyev55edna3rjgjhrzt6wy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vintage warplanes bearing the black and white stripes of Operation Overlord are set to take off from Connecticut on Sunday for a return trip to Europe, 75 years after dropping airborne troops into Nazi-occupied France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commencment speaker stuns grads with pledge to pay their loans...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/just-morehouse-commencement-speaker-pay-off-class-2019-student-loans/XvMHlS1SVyJiG3mRp1WOWL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Morehouse graduation, philanthropist Robert F. Smith has big surprise announcement. His his family is providing a grant to eliminate the student loans of the entire Class of 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge porn protected by Constitution? States might say yes...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Is-revenge-porn-protected-by-the-constitution-13857363.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bethany Austin learned her fiance had been unfaithful in late-May 2016.  After sharing a home with him for seven years, Matthew Rychlik was having an affair with a neighbor. The relationship was unsalvageable according to court documents; they even argued over how to call off the wedding - Rychlik wanted to tell family and friends it was mutual, Austin wanted to tell them the truth, that Rychlik was cheating on her.  But the situation escalated, and Rychlik told the world in his own way, from his own point of view. According to court documents, he spread rumors about his "crazy" fiancee and announced he was "sleeping at another girl's house" because Austin "never cooks or does house chores," NPR reported.  Then, Bethany Austin admits she sent friends and family a four-page letter that contained text messages between Rychlik and the neighbor, Elizabeth Dreher, including nude photos of Dreher. Austin had access to all of their conversations and photos because she shared an iCloud account with Rychlik, court documents show. Because of that, she received all of his conversations with the neighbor on her own phone. Rychlik and Dreher acknowledged they knew this.  Austin was arrested and charged with a felony: "nonconsensual dissemination of private sexual images," otherwise known as revenge porn.  In a motion filed in March at the Supreme Court of Illinois, Austin challenged the revenge-porn law itself, calling it unconstitutional. Yes, she was a scorned woman. But according to court documents, Austin argued she was exercising "her freedom of speech."  Appeals courts are beginning to take up cases involving the constitutionality of "revenge porn" statutes. Legislation criminalizing these actions has gained traction in most of America. Forty five states, including Illinois, have revenge-porn laws in place. The U.S. Supreme...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risks credibility with policy that veers between threats and inaction... </title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/05/17/analysis-trump-risks-credibility-with-his-policy-gyrations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has said there is no inconsistency in his administration’s messaging but that the image of incoherence can be useful. “At least Iran doesn’t know what to think, which at thi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrence Malick Film Panned at Cannes: 'Mystifying 3-Hour Indulgence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/a-hidden-life-review-1212083 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Premiering in competition, Terrence Malick's latest film tells the true story of Franz Jagerstatter, an Austrian conscientious objector during World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to focus on investment in Middle East as part of peace proposal...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/19/politics/white-house-middle-east-peace-proposal/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House announced Sunday afternoon the first part of its Middle East peace proposal, what officials are calling an economic "workshop" to encourage investing capital in the West Bank, Gaza, and the region, a senior administration official tells CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business forum set for Bahrain...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/trump-admin-kicks-off-plan-to-foster-israeli-palestinian-peace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has started to implement its multi-faceted plan to foster peace between Israel and the Palestinians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JARED SHOWS SOME CARDS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b640fd5dd77e4a1ba18a758a48c5b6c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration will unveil the first phase of its long-awaited blueprint for Mideast peace next month at a conference in the region designed to highlight economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudis say they don't want war, but will defend themselves...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aecc99fa337e4b419d457d935a0cbb32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Saudi Arabia does not want war but will not hesitate to defend itself against Iran, a top Saudi diplomat said Sunday, after the kingdom's energy sector was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM:  Vast gasoline lines form in oil-rich Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d179369e9e04ab693886bab1e47dab6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARACAIBO, Venezuela (AP) — U.S. sanctions on oil-rich Venezuela appear to be taking hold, resulting in mile-long lines for fuel in the South American nation's second-largest city,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman's false rape claim led to innocent man's death...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/false-report-largo-386952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 19--The false report of a brutal sexual assault set off a bizarre chain of events that ended last week with the self-defense killing of a Florida man, according to police. The fatal set of circu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO THE MIDDLE</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/05/joe-biden-rally-trump-philadelphia/589780/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In many ways, he’s running the same kind of campaign he would have in a pre-Trump, pre-Sanders era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami flying car port almost ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article230533194.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland votes to tighten gun control...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2019/05/18/are-switzerland-s-gun-laws-about-to-change-euronews-answers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland — one of the most heavily armed countries in Europe — voted to comply with stricter European Union gun laws in a referendum Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol flies migrants--to California!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/19/border-patrol-flies-migrants-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Border Patrol said it would fly hundreds of migrant families from south Texas to San Diego for processing and that it was considering flights to Detroit, Miami and Buffalo, New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Peculiar Blindness of Experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/06/how-to-predict-the-future/588040/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credentialed authorities are comically bad at predicting the future. But reliable forecasting is possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President May Pardon Servicemen Convicted of War Crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-shows-signs-he-will-pardon-servicemen-accused-or-convicted-of-war-crimes/ar-AABytFb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi calls urgent summit with Arab leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190519-saudi-arabia-calls-urgent-summit-gulf-arab-league-leaders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has called for urgent meetings of the regional Gulf Cooperation Council and the Arab League to discuss escalating tensions in the region, the kingdom’s official news agency said on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder-for-hire plot rocks NYPD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/18/the-twisted-motive-behind-the-alleged-murder-for-hire-plot-thats-rocked-the-nypd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The feds allege that Valerie Cincinelli, who is accused of plotting with her boyfriend John DiRubba to kill her estranged husband, also wanted DiRubba's 15-year-old daughter killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants exceptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/05/19/donald-trump-comments-on-abortion-laws/3731000002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets Saturday, Trump seemed to suggest the Alabma law might have gone too far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR driver throws punches after All-Star Race...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/19/nascar-driver-throws-punches-after-end-of-all-star-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, N.C. — Clint Bowyer had a lot more to say to Ryan Newman after the checkered flag flew at the NASCAR All-Star Race. He made sure his fists sent that message. Bowyer rushed Newman’s c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotels roll out automation; Workers worry...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/as-seattles-new-hotels-roll-out-automation-to-serve-guests-workers-worry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From automated check-in to droids that carry bags to rooms, artificial-intelligence technology is transforming the hospitality industry worldwide. As a result, hotel workers around the nation are seeking a say in the introduction of devices that could threaten their jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian govt collapses as far right leader caught in video sting...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-austria-politics-freedom-party/austrian-government-collapses-as-far-right-leader-caught-in-video-sting-idUSKCN1SN2RA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria raced on Saturday toward a snap election as Chancellor Sebastian Kurz pu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blame Bieber: Iceland canyon too popular...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/blame-it-bieber-iceland-canyon-too-popular-visitors-n1007446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Icelandic environmental officials have had to close off the Fjadrárgljúfur canyon to protect it from the hordes of Justin Bieber fans who are determined to visit the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riderless colt races to Preakness finish...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/sports/2019/05/19/horsing-around-riderless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore • Unencumbered by a jockey and suddenly free to run wherever he darn pleased, Bodexpress decided to take a shot at winning the Preakness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state braces for eco-friendly 'human composting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/washington-state-braces-for-eco-friendly-human-composting/ar-AABzXSk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
