<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Saudi prince vows 'totally different' country in five years...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saudi-prince-vows-totally-different-country-five-years-182620616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia's powerful crown prince said Wednesday his country would be "totally different" within five years, vowing to pursue sweeping reforms to diversify its economy away from oil. "I believe the new Europe is the Middle East," Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman told a major</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Falsely Claims He Got One...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/clintons-obama-suspicious-packages/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Secret Service says "potential explosive devices" were sent to the homes of Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama. Another was found at the Time Warner Center in New York. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-teen girls planned to kill 15 students with knives...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxla.com/news/local-news/bartow-pd-girls-planned-to-attack-and-kill-at-least-15-students</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say they stopped two students from carrying out a plot to go on a stabbing spree at Bartow Middle School Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police Investigating One Addressed to Maxine Waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/10/24/capitol-police-probing-suspicious-package-intercepted-at-md-facility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Capitol Police on Wednesday is investigating at least one suspicious package intercepted at a Maryland mail sorting facility, according to ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns of new 'arms race'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/putin-warns-arms-race-175531139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow (AFP) - President Vladimir Putin warned Wednesday of a new arms race if America pulls out of weapons treaties, and said Russia would respond "in kind" to any new US missiles placed on European soil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant wife saves husband's life, delivers baby...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox9.com/news/pregnant-wife-saves-husband-s-life-delivers-baby-days-later</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A birth story out of St. Paul is almost too remarkable to believe. A pregnant wife saved her husband’s life with CPR, just days before giving birth to their healthy baby boy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across Michigan: Look like cops, but they're not...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/investigations/2018/10/24/mcoles-michigan-reserve-cops/1353397002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;3,000 civilian officers operate with no state oversight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee sees rare hope...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab5d6ef8782c4eee85c5342c54962cd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — Tennessee Democrats know something about disappointment. The last time voters chose a governor, the party pinned its hopes on a longshot punchline named Charlie Brown, who was trounced by 30 percentage points. Two years before that, the Democrat who unexpectedly bested a weak primary field for a U.S. Senate seat was promptly disavowed by party leaders for his anti-gay views. Republican Bob Corker won re-election in a blowout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police investigate mail at Congressional sorting facility...</title>
      <link>http://www.wbal.com/article/342756/2/explosive-devices-sent-to-obama-clintons-cnn-evacuated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WBAL Radio 1090 AM - U.S. Capitol Police are investigating at least one suspicious package intercepted at a congressional mail sorting facility in Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/york-gov-andrew-cuomo-says-manhattan-office-received-170759608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo says his Manhattan office also received a suspicious device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Doctors Prescribing Time Outdoors...</title>
      <link>https://www.ecowatch.com/natural-medicine-doctors-prescribing-outdoors-2614316041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ecowatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Shetland doctors are only the latest in a growing number of healthcare providers incorporating nature into their treatment plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Holder Delivery Returned to Sender...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/politics/bill-clinton-hillary-clinton-chappaqua/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities have intercepted suspicious devices intended for former President Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton, and the Florida office of Democratic Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz was evacuated Wednesday after a suspicious package was mailed there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Eric Holder Delivery Intercepted...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/mitchellreports/status/1055135848767864833</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“.@PeteWilliamsNBC reports another suspicious package addressed to former AG Eric Holder was intercepted not sure if similar or copycat @MSNBC #AMR”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY WORLD's Big Secret: Favorite Spot to Scatter Family Ashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/disney-worlds-big-secret-its-a-favorite-spot-to-scatter-family-ashes-1540390229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans say treating the parks as a final resting place is the ultimate tribute, assuming they can sneak the remains past security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Says John Brennan Was Target...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cnn-reports-suspicious-package-was-addressed-to-msnbc-contributor-john-brennan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspicious package that forced an evacuation of CNN's New York headquarters was addressed to former CIA John Brennan, a frequent Trump critic and MSNBC contributor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN DIEGO UNION-TRIBUNE evacuated...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/sd-me-suspicious-package-ut-20181024-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A downtown San Diego street was cordoned off Wednesday morning after a stack of supicious looking packages were spotted in front of the building that houses the San Diego Union-Tribune, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angst grips Brazil as election ramps up...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/angst-grips-brazil-election-ramps-151605054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilians, or at least those who can afford it, were already keen believers in psychoanalysis. Admar Horn, a Rio psychoanalyst and member of the Brazilian Society of Psychoanalysis, said 80 percent of his patients expressed problems linked to the election. The country's polarization -- between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious package found at Debbie Wasserman Schultz office...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article220542845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspicious package has been found at U.S. Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz’ office in Sunrise, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince first speech since Khashoggi murder...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181024151807-7qivr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-KHASHOGGI/ (UPDATE 3, PIX,TV):UPDATE 3-Saudi crown prince says justice will prevail in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data breach warning for CATHAY PACIFIC passengers after 10 million have details stolen...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/7573094/cathay-pacific-passengers-data-breach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CATHAY Pacific has revealed that the information of 9.4m of its passengers had been accessed in a huge data breach. The airline said that the matter has already been reported to the Hong Kong polic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL 4 Explosive Devices Linked...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/investigations/Bomb-Hillary-Clinton-House-Chappaqua-New-York-George-Soros-498411611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All four 'potential explosive devices' sent to Hillary Clinton, former President Obama, billionaire philanthropist George Soros and CNN at Manhattan's Time Warner Center are thought to be linked, law enforcement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMBS SENT TO CLINTON, OBAMA</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/suspicious-package-found-clintons-home-north-york-city/story?id=58713254</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this week a pipe bomb was put in George Soros' mailbox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN EVACUATED</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-cnns-new-york-headquarters-evacuated-after-suspicious-package-found/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipe Bomb at Soros Home Was 'Hand-Delivered'...</title>
      <link>https://www.knoe.com/content/news/Pipe-bomb-hand-delivered-to-George-Soros-mailbox-authorities-say-498363381.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.knoe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is trying to determine who left a pipe bomb for George Soros.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto yard signs set on fire outside Dallas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2018-elections/2018/10/23/campaign-signs-beto-orourke-colin-allred-set-ablaze-richardson-yards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five yard signs for Democratic candidates were set on fire in a Richardson neighborhood Monday night, officials said. Police received three calls...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMBS SENT TO CLINTON, OBAMA</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/24/feds-investigating-suspicious-package-near-clintons-new-york-home-nbc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The packages were reportedly similar to an explosive device sent to billionaire George Soros, a frequent target of the right. A top White House official says President Trump is taking the situation "extremely seriously."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Sends Officers To Media Outlets Across City...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/10/24/clintons-suspicious-package/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secret Service said its members intercepted the package addressed to former First Lady Hillary Clinton late Tuesday and then another one addressed to former President Barack Obama early Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  No suspicious package addressed to White House...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181024144501-jed6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-POLITICIANS/PACKAGE-WHITEHOUSE (URGENT):No suspicious package addressed to White House -source</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New home sales drop; Near two-year low</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/24/new-home-sales-september.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of new U.S. single-family homes fell to a near two-year low in September and data for the prior three months was revised lower, the latest indications that rising mortgage rates and higher prices were undercutting the housing market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly Makes Tearful On-Air Apology for Blackface Comments...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2018/10/24/emotional-megyn-kelly-apologizes-again-for-blackface-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I was wrong and I am sorry," the "Megyn Kelly Today" host stated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION: Biden thinks he's in Miami -- he's in Tampa...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/confusion-joe-biden-thinks-hes-in-miami-when-hes-in-tampa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes politicians just show up to the next microphone without knowing where they really are. That seemed to be the case yesterday, when 75-year-old former Vice President Joe Biden thought he was in Miami when he was really in Tampa — about 281 miles away. “Well, I can say, it’s great to be with you …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jesus becomes 'organ donor' on crucifix in shock ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/738382/Jesus-news-Australian-ad-sparks-fury-Jesus-organ-donor-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK 'could collapse' if election scandals keep coming, author warns...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/10/24/facebook-could-collapse-if-election-scandals-keep-coming-author-warns-8069938/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something to look forward to?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: VIRUS KILLS 7 KIDS AT FACILITY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/NJ-Viral-Outbreak-7-Kids-Dead-498407531.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seventh child who was treated at a long-term care medical facility in New Jersey has died after a “severe outbreak” of adenovirus, a family of viruses that can otherwise cause mild illness, according to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran SMALLEST home hits market for $650,000! 460 sq ft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6309839/PICTURED-San-Franciscos-smallest-home-just-460sq-ft-costing-mammoth-650-000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A quaint 480-square-foot cottage in Visitavion Valley, San Francisco, is selling for just $650,000 - making it both the smallest and cheapest home in the country's most expensive city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Twisted' fiber optic light breakthrough could make internet 100 times faster...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/oct/24/twisted-fibre-optic-light-breakthrough-could-make-internet-100-times-faster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say they have developed tiny readers that can detect information in light spirals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homelessness Exploding On Coasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/more-than-half-a-million-people-americas-homelessness-crisis-is-rapidly-exploding-on-both-coasts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, most of our politicians are all talk and no action, and the homelessness crisis is likely to get a whole lot worse as the U.S. economy continues to deteriorate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the grave: What's next for the horror reboot?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/oct/23/halloween-horror-reboots-upcoming-pet-sematary-it </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Halloween’s record-breaking haul, Hollywood is set to look to the past to bring back horror’s most feared villains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Dem win Kansas gov race?</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Could-a-Democrat-win-the-Kansas-governor-s-race-13332002.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kansas is a state entirely controlled by Republicans now and one that voted for President Donald Trump in 2016 by 20 points. And yet in a couple of weeks, voters there could elect a Democrat to be their governor for the first time in eight years - just in time to have a hand in the upcoming redistricting battle that could shape control of the state for the next decade. That there is such a tight race is more a reflection of Republican control of the state for the past eight years than any major shift in conservative Kansas to the left. Kansas has been struggling for years with massive budget shortfalls. Those have cut deep into budgets for roads, schools and hospitals in a way that's hard for the average Kansan to miss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens when they arrive?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/24/trump-administration-has-not-settled-on-a-plan-for-what-to-do-if-the-migrant-caravan-arrives-at-the-us-border.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has not settled on a plan for what to do if a migrant caravan arrives at the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dogs now have cameras, too...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9ec0ccc37af3477c9c6f2e0577484f34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILWAUKEE (AP) — Police dogs have always helped their human counterparts through their eyes and nose, and now some of the dogs are getting their own backup — cameras that transmit live video. The devices generally attach to dogs' backs on a vest and transmit video to a handler watching from a screen, possibly on their wrist or around their necks. It's so the officers can better assess what they are up against before they go into a situation. "If we have a really close encounter with armed people it doesn't work out well for anyone," said Shawn Gore, Portland, Oregon, police K-9 officer. "If we can gain distance it gives us lots of options to negotiate and de-escalate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradise lost: Tourist spots in danger of being loved to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181024-paradise-lost-tourist-spots-danger-being-loved-death </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince first speech since Khashoggi murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/saudi-crown-prince-make-first-speech-khashoggi-murder-doc-1a943n1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger may help...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/americans-anger-may-help-democrats-november-6-vote-101320273.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Chico, 67, a Republican in California, says his annoyance with Democrats morphed into full-blown outrage when he heard they might try to impeach President Donald Trump after the Nov. 6 elections. Eden Stramer, 23, a North Dakota Democrat, says the possibility of abortions becoming illegal again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever auction of AI-created artwork set for Christie's gavel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6310909/First-auction-painting-created-AI-artist-opens-Christies-New-York.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artwork - which is up for auction in New York - is one of a group of portraits of the fictional Belamy family created by a Paris-based trio of 25-year-olds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China's internment camps: tear gas, Tasers and textbooks...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/717/inside-chinas-internment-camps-tear-gas-tasers-and-textbooks-doc-1a73p63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Class Flying More Luxurious Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/first-class-flying-is-back-and-it-s-more-luxurious-than-ever#gs.MHyve5I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carriers are adding routes and amping up the amenity quotient of their premium cabins.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicides Surge in Hopeless Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/suicides-surge-in-a-hopeless-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicides Surge in a Hopeless Venezuela</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota at Crossroads of Divided America...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/-ground-zero-for-house-control-puts-trump-s-appeal-to-the-test#gs.uWH4n8w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;`Ground Zero' for House Control Puts Trump's Appeal to the Test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Weighs Teaching Arabic In School...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/france-weighs-teaching-arabic-in-schools-to-keep-lessons-secular-1540373401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Macron’s government is considering giving parents a secular alternative to intertwined Arabic and Islamic instruction in mosques by prodding more public schools to offer Arabic lessons—without religious content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cook blistering attack on 'data industrial complex'...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/10/24/apples-tim-cook-makes-blistering-attack-on-the-data-industrial-complex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple’s CEO Tim Cook has joined the chorus of voices warning that data itself is being weaponized again people and societies — arguing that the trade in digital data has exploded into a “data industrial complex”. Cook did not namecheck the adtech elephants in the room: Googl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even 10-Min Walk Good for Brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/24/well/move/exercise-brain-memory-fitness-cognitive.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten minutes of mild exercise can immediately alter how certain parts of the brain communicate and coordinate with one another and improve memory function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SCARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/24/dow-poised-for-triple-digit-losses-at-the-open-after-tuesdays-500-point-recovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures indicated a weak start to the trading day, as investors look ahead to a raft of economic data and third-quarter corporate earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record numbers of West Nile cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/24/record-numbers-of-west-nile-virus-cases-reported-in-parts-of-us </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warming temperatures and flooding driven by climate change is heightening the risk of contracting the disease, experts warn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials prepare for potential false claims of election interference...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/412863-officials-prepare-for-potential-false-claims-of-election-interference</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State and federal officials say they are well prepared for the possibility of a cyberattack on American election systems Nov. 6, but experts warn that even a false claim of interference by foreign actors on Election Day could undermine the public’s faith in the voting process.Officials prepare for potential false claims of election interference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese Tells Pope: 'World Marked by Evil'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/10/23/watch-martin-scorsese-tells-pope-the-world-is-marked-by-evil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film director Martin Scorsese told pope Francis Tuesday that the world is “marked by evil” and asked how to “strengthen and guide the young.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate slipping away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d97c666cf6fa4a42a7cadc9b9ac742de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — In the closing stretch of the 2018 campaign, the question is no longer the size of the Democratic wave. It's whether there will be a wave at all. Top operatives in both political parties concede that Democrats' narrow path to the Senate majority has essentially disappeared, a casualty of surging Republican enthusiasm across GOP strongholds. At the same time, leading Democrats now fear the battle for the House majority will be decided by just a handful of seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants split over corporate tax to help homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-tech-giants-split-over-corporate-tax-help-015821021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taxing San Francisco's wealthiest companies to rein in the city's homelessness problem makes sense to local campaigners -- but the local tech giants aren't all so sure. On November 6, voters in the city that is the home base of Twitter, Uber and Airbnb will decide the fate of "Proposition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'all Trump, all the time' help in midterms?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-time-help-gop-midterms-204647756--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is betting that his ubiquitous role in the midterm elections — all Trump, all the time — will pay off for Republicans trying to hang onto their perilous majorities in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gays, blacks still voting for Brazil's Bolsonaro despite rhetoric...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/gays-blacks-still-voting-brazils-bolsonaro-despite-rhetoric-015504908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right-wing Brazilian presidential candidate Jair Bolsonaro once said he'd rather have a dead son than one who came out of the closet, but that isn't stopping conservative gay voters from backing him in Sunday's decisive election run-off. For these voters, Bolsonaro is tough on crime and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador no longer to intervene with UK for Assange... </title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/exclusive-ecuador-no-longer-intervene-uk-wikileaks-assange-003907346.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign Minister José Valencia said in an interview with Reuters that Ecuador's only responsibility was looking after Assange's wellbeing, after the Australian national sued the country over new conditions placed on his asylum in the London embassy. "Ecuador has no responsibility to take</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SCARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/10/23/stocks-drop-after-caterpillar-3-m-issue-disappointing-forecasts/1737169002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks sold off again Tuesday after Caterpillar and 3M issued outlooks that worried investors. Stocks later recovered part of those losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHODUNNIT MYSTERY IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/23/british-metoo-scandal-cannot-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leading businessman has been granted an injunction against The Telegraph to prevent this newspaper revealing alleged sexual harassment and racial abuse of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAT:  Candidates clash at Georgia gov debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/stacey-abrams-brian-kemp-debate-tonight/h5hAHuiFtUPlEOR66cK0HN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire alarm was a surprise, but otherwise Tuesday’s debate between Georgia gubernatorial ca...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How it became so big and why it continues to grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/How-the-migrant-caravan-became-so-big-and-why-13331175.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUIXTLA, Mexico - Edith Cruz was sitting at home in central Honduras, scanning Facebook on her phone, when she saw the post about the caravan on a community news page. It was Oct. 12. She and her cousin had just opened a small business selling tortillas when they were confronted by a gang, threatened with death if they didn't hand over half of their profits. She looked at the Facebook post: "An avalanche of Hondurans is preparing to leave in a caravan to the United States. Share this!" Within three hours, her bags were packed. The question of how the migrant caravan began has wound its way to the American midterm elections. President Donald Trump and other Republicans have suggested that Democrats paid migrants to begin the journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Could Hold Back Wave? Economy, Confidence, Independence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/what-could-hold-back-a-democratic-wave-economy-confidence-independence/ar-BBOM067</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS AT CBSNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/23/60-minutes-correspondents-threaten-to-quit-over-potential-new-boss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman from “48 Hours” running “60 Minutes”? You must be joking. Snooty correspondents at CBS’ “60 Minutes” are apoplectic over the idea that Susan Zirinsky — the longtime boss of the network’s cr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRTY TRICKS:  Racist robocalls in campaign for Florida governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article220490950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An out-of-state website is once again making robocalls to Florida voters with a racist message intended to malign Democrat Andrew Gillum, who would be the state’s first black governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal families set record for year...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/oct/23/illegal-immigrant-families-set-record-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigration by families surged this summer after the collapse of President Trump’s zero-tolerance border policy, reaching record levels and leaving the Trump administration frustrated over the lack of easy solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane season most powerful on record...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/10/23/hurricane-season-most-active-record-atlantic-pacific-combined/1741226002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When all the hurricanes and tropical storms in the Atlantic and Pacific are added together, the 2018 hurricane season is the most active season ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAPCHAT helped 400,000+ register...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/snapchat-helped-over-400000-people-register-to-vote-says-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popular app got even more people to register than Taylor Swift did, says The New York Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON execs already donating for 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/amazon-ceo-jeff-bezos-backs-senator-cory-gardner-for-re-election---in-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Sen. Cory Gardner's campaign saw a boost from Amazon executives in the third quarter, including CEO Jeff Bezos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARSCALE: Big Tech Meddling with Free Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/10/23/exclusive-brad-parscale-big-tech-is-meddling-with-free-speech-and-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest of the Big Tech companies are quickly positioning themselves as the internet’s thought police, threatening to stamp out one of America’s most cherished freedoms — the right to free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARAVAN SWELLS TO 14,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/10/23/mexican-news-outlet-officials-say-14000-honduran-migrants-heading-to-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican El Universal news outlet is reporting that more than 14,000 Hondurans are heading to the United States border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto superhero mural pops up in Austin...</title>
      <link>http://spectrumlocalnews.com/tx/austin/news/2018/10/23/mural-of-beto-as-a-superhero-pops-up-in-east-austin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectrumlocalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artist goal to show “out of the darkness comes the light.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors brace for surge of polio-like disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-investigating-more-cases-polio-syndrome-n923041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors are bracing for an upsurge in cases this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas county adopts rules to preempt sexbot brothels...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/politics/houston/article/Harris-County-adopts-new-rules-to-pre-empt-robot-13329896.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris County Commissioners Court on Tuesday unanimously adopted new rules regulating sexually oriented business to prevent so-called "robot brothels" from opening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Steps Up Attacks on Fed Chairman...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-steps-up-attacks-on-fed-chairman-jerome-powell-1540338090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump escalated his attacks on Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, saying the head of the nation’s central bank threaten U.S. economic growth and appeared to enjoy raising interest rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armies of lawyers mobilize...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/midterms/article220481405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Americans go to the polls for midterm elections, political parties and interest groups are deploying thousands of lawyers nationwide to guard against voting problems or challenge results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Uses Gillum Soundbite for Network Promo...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/10/23/cnn-andrew-gillum-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facts First?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pets -- can tell time...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2018/10/23/Your-pets-know-what-time-it-is-study-shows/9121540315010/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research suggests animals have a relatively accurate sense of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll worker error means vote re-do...</title>
      <link>https://www.greensboro.com/ap/north_carolina/poll-worker-s-error-means-vote-re-do-for-legislative/article_5f59cf9c-6798-5490-b742-05e68d176c83.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greensboro.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOLIVIA, N.C. (AP) — Nearly 150 North Carolina voters will be invited to cast their ballots a second time after a poll worker's mistake meant they were given the wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA founder lays off all journalists from new media website...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/10/23/18015174/wikipedia-founder-jimmy-wales-wikitribune-journalist-lay-off-community-focus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WikiTribune is shifting to a community-focused operation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Brain Trust Sees 2020 Successor: Deval Patrick...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/darrensands/deval-patrick-2020-president-campaign-barack-obama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The perils of the road to the presidency — and a life and business he loves — may ultimately keep Deval Patrick away from the Democratic primary. It’s just that he’s running into an awful lot of reaso</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot survives as plane crashes, burns on CA freeway...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/traffic/small-plane-reportedly-down-on-101-freeway-in-agoura-hills/4543306/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small plane crashed on the westbound 101 in Agoura Hills on Tuesday, and the fiery wreck shut down both sides of the freeway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer falls to death from airplane in failed music video stunt...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/canadian-rapper-dies-after-falling-off-airplane-wing-in-failed-stunt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jon James McMurray died Saturday filming a project he had been working on for months, a statement said. He trained ‘intensively’ for the stunt, it said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,100 mostly unarmed Guard troops on border...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2018/10/23/2000-unarmed-guard-troops-on-border-as-trump-vows-to-send-more-to-stop-migrant-caravan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Guard could send 2,000 more troops to border, if governors OK the deployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple narrowly escape death after beaver topples 65-ft tree onto yacht!</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/germany-beaver-couple-tree-yacht-muritz-elde-a8597841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodent causes thousands of euros in damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Speeding escalator at metro goes haywire, piles dozens on floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/rome-subway-escalator-out-of-control-video-2018-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An escalator malfunctioned at a Rome metro station and injured at least 10 people. A video of the event shows people being spit out onto the floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy expert quits GOOGLE-backed 'smart city'...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/privacy-expert-resigns-from-alphabet-backed-smart-city-1829934748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A privacy expert tasked with helping a new smart city development protect the data privacy of residents has resigned over concerns that her guidelines would be largely ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City bans clowns on Halloween...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksat.com/news/no-clowns-allowed-michigan-city-bans-clowns-on-halloween</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you plan to attend the Boo Bash in the Detroit suburb of Oak Park on Halloween, you can be a ghost, goblin, zombie, vampire or any other character that you wish, but you can't be a clown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON futuristic cashierless convenience store coming to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/amazon-go-cashierless-store-reportedly-opening-in-new-york-city.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Go stores use "Just Walk Out" technology so shoppers can skip the wait to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM HOT IN FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-23/florida-governor-election-2018-andrew-gillum-leads-desantis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto bets big on FACEBOOK ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-23/facebook-ad-report-puts-o-rourke-as-top-spender-after-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP 6</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/florida/release-detail?ReleaseID=2582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gillum Leads In Tight Florida Governor's Race, Quinnipiac University Poll Finds; Dem Boosted By Independents, Women, Non-White Voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000 MILES AWAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/honduran-migrant-caravan-resumes-march-mexico-us-142832691.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of mainly Honduran migrants heading to the United States -- a caravan President Donald Trump has called an "assault on our country" -- stopped to rest Tuesday after walking for two days into Mexican territory. "They're exhausted," said migrant rights activist Rodrigo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS KILLS 6 KIDS AT FACILITY</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/adenovirus-wanaque-center-for-nursing-and-rehabilitation-new-jersey-outbreak-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strain of adenovirus is affecting "medically fragile children with severely compromised immune systems," health officials say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ILLEGALS TO VOTE IN SAN FRAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-allow-noncitizens-vote-school-board-184120600--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco will become the largest city in the United States and one of only a handful nationwide to allow noncitizens, including people in the country illegally, to vote in a local election in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gillum ahead by 6 points in Florida gov's race...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2018/10/23/poll-andrew-gillum-leads-ron-desantis-by-6-in-florida-governors-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most recent governor's race poll shows what every independent general election survey has shown: Andrew Gillum is winning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEOs give employees time off to vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/ceos-give-employees-time-off-to-vote-in-hotly-contested-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEOs Give Employees Time Off to Vote in Hotly Contested Midterms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service cancels controlled burn near Earth's largest tree...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-prescribed-fire-sequoias-20181023-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Park Service plan to set fire to an ancient sequoia grove in the western Sierra Nevada has been canceled for the second time this year, further delaying a delicate forestry operation aimed at triggering new growth near the world’s largest tree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE:  Nuke Weapons in Space Possible...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Pence-leaves-open-the-possibility-of-nuclear-13330288.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Vice President Mike Pence on Tuesday declined to rule out the idea of deploying nuclear weapons in space, saying the current ban on their use is "in the interest of every nation" but the issue should be decided on "the principle that peace comes through strength." "What we need to do is make sure that we provide for the common defense of the people of the United States of America and that's the president's determination here," Pence said in an interview with The Washington Post, when asked if nuclear weapons should be banned from orbit. Pence added, "What we want to do is continue to advance the principle that peace comes through strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper whose lyrics reflected Baltimore's pain fatally shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rapper-whose-lyrics-reflected-baltimores-pain-fatally-shot-151532492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — A rising Baltimore rapper who advocated for nonviolence and whose lyrics often reflected the city's trauma has been shot and killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein, Accusers in Early Talks to Settle Civil Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/harvey-weinstein-accusers-insurers-in-early-talks-to-settle-civil-claims-1540319930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Harvey Weinstein and women who have accused him of sexual misconduct are working with insurance companies and the New York attorney general’s office in an attempt to reach a sweeping settlement of all civil suits pending against the disgraced producer and his former film studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams's Burning of Georgia Flag Surfaces on Eve of Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/abrams-role-in-burning-georgia-flag-is-revealed/17938592/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — At a protest on the steps of the Georgia Capitol in 1992, Stacey Abrams, now the Democratic candidate for governor, joined in the burning of the state flag, which at the time incorporated the Confederate battle flag design and was viewed by many as a lingering symbol of white supremacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS KILLS 6 KIDS</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/health/6-kids-dead-12-sick-in-viral-outbreak-at-nj-rehab-center/4542019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state Department of Health on Tuesday confirmed 18 cases of adenovirus at the Wanaque Center for Nursing and Rehabilitation in Haskell, Passaic County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stealth bomber makes emergency landing in CO...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-stealth-bomber-lands-colorado-emergency-152740438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLORADO SPRINGS, Colo. (AP) — The Air Force says a Missouri-based B2 stealth bomber landed in Colorado Springs after an unspecified emergency, but neither of the pilots was injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Support Claims Rep. Married Her Brother...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/davidsteinberg/official-school-records-support-claims-that-rep-ilhan-omar-d-mn-married-her-brother/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She is implicated in multiple felonies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
