<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>150 rockets fired at Israel after IDF assassinates Gaza terror leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/idf-orders-schools-businesses-shot-from-gaza-to-tel-aviv-for-1st-time-since-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sirens wail in Tel Aviv; IDF orders schools shut from Gaza to Tel Aviv for 1st time since 2014; army says it's prepared for several days of fighting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Threatened From NY to Texas With Blast of Arctic Air...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2019-11-08-arctic-cold-outbreak-mid-november-record-midwest-south-east?cm_ven=hp-slot-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent cold fronts have been notable, but this week's plunge will be the coldest so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX HOST:  WHY IS DRUDGE COVERING NEWS?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jesse-watters-accuses-drudge-of-being-anti-trump-thats-what-you-log-on-to-cnn-com-for/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Jesse Watters went after The Drudge Report editor Matt Drudge arguing his site is turning against President Donald Trump because it has posted negative headlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TILLERSON DENIES TRUMP SABOTAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/11/11/rex-tillerson-said-he-resisted-trumps-decisions-or-else-people-would-die-nikki-haley-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – Former Secretary of State Rex Tillerson is disputing a claim by Nikki Haley, the former U.S. ambassador to the United Nations, that he sought...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://video.foxnews.com/v/6102221338001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;video.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the internet's top websites has shifted to negative Trump headlines and pro-Buttigieg coverage. Fox News media analyst Howard Kurtz reacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump's Stock Market Record Stacks Up...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-stock-market-record-stacks-193002360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- It’s been three years now since Donald Trump was elected president, which means it’s been three years of listening to Donald Trump bragging about how great the stock market is doing. Contrary to one now-infamous pre-election prediction, it has done quite well.The Dow Jones Industrial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon official testifies freeze on aid to Ukraine came from Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fded1157e52341338fd3f7086a0eb28d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The view among the national security officials was unanimous: Military aid to Ukraine should not be stopped. But President Donald Trump's acting chief of staff thought...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuel-theft rings fill South Florida roads with 'moving bombs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/crime/fl-ne-fuel-theft-south-florida-credit-card-fraud-20191111-iyhiq7hyf5fabpvj3hc2jo2jce-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These criminals lug huge amounts of stolen gasoline across South Florida’s roadways, hiding hundreds of gallons in modified trucks and SUVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-month-old to be taken off life support against mom's wishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article237224574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House at war with itself even as it fights  inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/white-house-at-war-with-itself-even-as-it-fights-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The White House's bifurcated and disjointed response to Democrats' impeachment inquiry has been fueled by a fierce West Wing battle between two of President Donald Trump's top advisers, and the outcome of the messy skirmish could be on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDOLEEZZA RICE:  The call is murky, it is really murky...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment-condoleezza/former-u-s-top-diplomat-rice-concerned-by-shadow-diplomacy-on-ukraine-idUSKBN1XL2A7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Condoleezza Rice, a secretary of state under Republican President George W. Bush...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. 'Dreamers' may come down to Chief Justice Roberts...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-11/supreme-court-case-about-dreamers-may-come-down-to-chief-justice-roberts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dreamers' best hope for victory at the Supreme Court almost surely depends on Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco's New DA: Public Urination 'Will Not Be Prosecuted'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/11/san-francisco-chesa-boudin-public-urination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chesa Boudin, the urine-and-feces-plagued city's incoming district attorney, pledged during the campaign not to prosecute public urination and other quality-of-life crimes if he was elected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast, cable news networks to preempt regular programming...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/15e3ce69ef7b49219ff3855fb75be96f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Impeachable or not? Both Democrats and Republicans see the televised impeachment hearings starting this week as their first and best opportunity to shape public opinion...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi promo video labels feminism, atheism, homosexuality as extremist ideas...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191111183240-ipalt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homosexuality and atheism have long been illegal and punishable by death in the absolute monarchy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia's Most Populous State Prepares for Extreme Fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/news/education/article/Australia-s-most-populous-state-prepares-for-14826772.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Hundreds of schools remained closed across Australia's most populous state on Tuesday, and residents were urged to evacuate woodlands for the relative safety of city centers as authorities braced for extreme fire danger. New South Wales on Monday declared a weeklong state of emergency in preparation for Tuesday's hot, dry and windy conditions. The declaration gives the Rural Fire Service sweeping powers to control resources and direct other government agencies. Rural Fire Service Commissioner Shane Fitzsimmons said 3,000 firefighters were available to fight more than 50 fires blazing across the state. The fires are expected to worsen as winds are forecast to gust at between 70 kmh (43 mph) and 90 kmh (56 mph) later Tuesday. The worst fires are expected in the state's northeast, where three people have died and more than 150 homes have been destroyed since Friday, as well as around Sydney. "Now is the time to exercise those decisions to leave, leave early and go to safer locations, safer towns and villages or safer places in your local community, such as the shopping centers," Fitzsimmons told reporters. "We plan for these sorts of days. But we always hope they never come," he added. More than 600 schools and technical colleges across the state are closed on Tuesday because they are close to woodlands at risk of fire. The annual Australian fire season, which peaks during the Southern Hemisphere summer, has started early after an unusually warm and dry winter. More than 1 million hectares (3,800 square miles) of forest and farmland had already burned across the state this fire season, more than three times the 280,000 hectares (1,080 square miles) that burned during the entire last season, Fitzsimmons said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deval Patrick Mulls Last-Minute Entry Into Presidential Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.necn.com/news/new-england/Former-Mass-Gov-Deval-Patrick-Presidential-Run-Report-564768242.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.necn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick is exploring a late run for president, according to people with knowledge of Patrick's deliberations, who spoke on condition of anonymity because they were not authorized...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera, tripwire device found near Charlottesville Confederate monument...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/11/stonewall-jackson-confederate-monument-camera-trip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have removed an unauthorized camera and apparent tripwire device from the vicinity of a Confederate monument in Charlottesville, Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top US general says 500 American troops to stay in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2019/11/10/top-us-general-says-500-600-american-troops-to-stay-in-syria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff says about 500 or 600 U.S. troops will remain in Syria to counter Islamic State fighters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Hockey Host Fired After Calling Immigrants 'You People'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/don-cherry-fired</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cherry, 85, had singled out new immigrants for not honouring Canada’s veterans and dead soldiers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Doctors Remove 8-Inch Screwdriver From Mentally Ill Man's Rectum...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/11/doctors-remove-8-inch-screwdriver-from-mans-rectum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 46-year-old man had a screwdriver pulled out of his rectum after he apparently pushed it inside himself and leaving it there for a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoping for Tears...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/pbs-correspondent-dems-hoping-witness-will-cry-during-impeachment-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PBS White House correspondent Yamiche Alcindor said congressional Democrats are looking for emotional witnesses to get viewers invested in impeachment proceedings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton Rejects Legal Alliance With Mulvaney...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/11/11/bolton-rejects-legal-alliance-with-mulvaney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A long-simmering feud within the White House broke into the open on Monday as a lawyer for John</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's tiniest twin boys defy odds after being born at 23 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10318673/worlds-tiniest-twin-boys-23-weeks-one-pound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUM Talia Keates cradles her “little miracles” — the world’s tiniest twin boys. Ashley and Joe each weighed less than 1lb when born at 23 weeks. The Brit mum says the boys are her “one in a million…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Can Marriage Counseling Save America?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/12/better-angels-can-this-union-be-saved/600775/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Borrowing techniques from couples therapy to bring liberals and conservatives back together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy launching -- podcast?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/11/politics/rudy-giuliani-impeachment-podcast/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani is considering re-entering the impeachment fray by launching a podcast to provide impeachment analysis of the public hearings in the House of Representatives scheduled for later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor arrested for performing procedures on patients without consent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/11/health/virginia-doctor-hysterectomies-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Virginia doctor has been arrested after he was accused of performing hysterectomies and other unnecessary medical procedures on patients without their consent, according to a federal affidavit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can't sue NY to stop release of tax returns, judge says...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/judge-dismisses-trump-lawsuit-ny-officials-house-committee/story?id=66918561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Monday issued another blow to President Donald Trump and his ongoing effort to avoid having his tax records turned over to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pub crawl in NKorea? Tour offers St Patrick's Day party like no other...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/pub-crawl-north-korea-tour-172859249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cities dye their rivers green (looking at you, Chicago), others light up the sky with emerald fireworks, but across the globe, St Patrick’s Day is universally celebrated with a drink or two. And it seems in North Korea it is no different. Although the Foreign Office advises against visiting North</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMON, IS THAT YOU?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-7672837/Simon-Cowell-looks-slimmer-steps-London.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The X Factor head judge revealed a noticeably slender physique while greeting onlookers ahead of his appearance at Heart Radio studios in Leicester Square.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense firms on track to make killer bots reality...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1746154/lacking-regulation-firms-on-track-to-make-killer-robots-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such weapons “violate fundamental legal and ethical principles and would destabilize international peace and security,” says a Dutch NGO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students turn against free speech amid 'culture of conformity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7672091/Fewer-HALF-UK-students-support-freedom-speech-polls-finds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey by think tank The Policy Exchange shows youngsters whose views don't conform with the majority of students, such as those who support Brexit, feel silenced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO REPLACE IPHONES WITH GLASSES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/11/smart-glasses-that-replace-phones-may-be-the-next-hottest-tech-trend.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft, Snap, Facebook, Google, Apple and Amazon are all racing to replace our phones with glasses we wear everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. abandons book event after being drowned out  by hecklers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/11/donald-trump-jr-walks-out-of-triggered-book-launch-after-heckling-from-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Event at University of California is cut short amid anger at his refusal to take questions from the audience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Happiness Most Dominant Human Expression...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/reason-to-smile-happiness-most-dominant-human-expression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the thousands of possibilities, there are but 35 universally accepted facial expressions. Yet perhaps most remarkable is roughly half of these are expressions of happiness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the President's Yes Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-road-to-impeachment-paved-by-all-the-presidents-yes-men/ar-BBWAnPf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Threatens to Sue Hillary Over 'Defamatory' Russia Comment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/tulsi-gabbard-demands-hillary-clinton-retract-russia-comments-your-statement-is-defamatory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 presidential candidate Tulsi Gabbard has sent a letter to Hillary Clinton demanding the 2016 presidential candidate retract her statements on Gabbard and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPEYE'S worker brutally attacks woman seeking refund...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/popeyes-worker-accused-of-attacking-customer-seeking-refund</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Popeyes worker recorded throwing a woman onto the pavement outside a restaurant in Tennessee has been charged with felony aggravated assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB rental turns out to be NYC public housing apartment...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/airbnb-rental-turns-out-to-be-public-housing-apartment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tourist discovered her Airbnb rental was actually in a public housing complex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/politics/elections/ct-iowa-joe-biden-pete-buttigieg-2020-presidential-race-moderates-20191107-qdqrz2fb3fd55o4xlkaq2ogzye-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Iowa, Pete Buttigieg has emerged as the major alternative to Joe Biden among moderate voters the former vice president has counted on as the bedrock of his campaign in the first-in-the-nation caucus state. The Midwestern mayor not only has caught Biden in the polls, but his campaign is better funded, has drawn larger and louder crowds at events, and has shown signs of a more effective ground operation in a state where the former vice president is making his third bid for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake Booed Offstage, Stormy Daniels Raps at Bizarre L.A. Concert...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/drake-booed-off-stage-stormy-daniels-donald-trump-camp-flog-gnaw-watch-1203400388/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyler, The Creator’s Camp Flog Gnaw Carnival is always entertaining — last year featured Kanye West and Kid Cudi performing inside a giant glass box. But it inadvertently outdid itself this year wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDBERG:  Worst thing about Trump's 'fake news' warning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/469408-the-worst-thing-about-trumps-fake-news-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even if there were proof that Trump tries to discredit journalists so he won't look bad, his fans wouldn't care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napoleon expert confesses to chopping up lover...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russias-napoleon-expert-confesses-chopping-lover-114345339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prominent Saint Petersburg-based Napoleon expert has confessed to murdering his young lover and former student and dismembering her body in a grisly crime that sent shock waves across Russia. Oleg Sokolov, a 63-year-old history lecturer who received France's Legion d'Honneur from Jacques Chirac</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capsule living: 'Cheap' option for young people flocking to LA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/capsule-living-cheap-option-young-people-flocking-la-161917564.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kay Wilson packed up her life in a hurry and moved to Los Angeles... only to find that what she paid in Pennsylvania for a nice studio apartment would only get her a 2.9-square-meter box in California. Wilson arrived a month ago at UP(st)ART, a community for young people with artistic aspirations in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still teaching at 95, Jimmy Carter draws devotees to church...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0fb39dc916d48c1a8fa5bf72f5deb32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLAINS, Ga. (AP) — The pilgrims arrive early and from all over, gathering hours before daybreak in an old pecan grove that surrounds a country church. They come, they say, for a dose of simple...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napolitano emerges as Trump critic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/52b6a16fa159457b907cc90c4846d6a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — More than two decades into his career as a commentator at Fox News Channel, Andrew Napolitano reached a milestone of sorts when he was called a "fool" on his own network. Not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain sees widening political divide as nationalism rises...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ef48230926d485faeb551ef17e91127</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain looked set Monday to endure many more months of political uncertainty after the country's fourth election in as many years reflected a widening political chasm between parties...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL WARMING ON HOLD:  WINTER COMES EARLY TO WINDY CITY...</title>
      <link>https://accuweather.com/en/weather-news/snow-arctic-cold-to-blast-the-northeast-us-in-the-coming-days/622226 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hundreds of records could fall in cold snap...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/11/veterans-day-weather-snow-record-breaking-cold-sweep-nation/2560318001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wintry weather pattern was rolling across a wide swath of the nation, threatening to break hundreds of records and a freeze as far south as Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACH SIGNS HANG OVER TRUMP VETERAN'S DAY SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/ABC/status/1193919259510001664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Signs spelling out "Impeach" adorn windows of a building overlooking Pres. Trump's speech at New York City's Veterans Day Parade. https://t.co/qUl8R8XHCY”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. abandons book event after being drowned out -- by angry supporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/lions-den-don-trump-jr-abandons-book-event-after-being-drowned-out-by-angry-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump, Jr. ended a book event after his own supporters heckled him for not taking questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly Internet Comeback Fizzles...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/11/megyn-kelly-internet-comeback-fizzles-with-only-six-thousand-instagram-subscribers-22k-on-youtube</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly’s big comeback on You Tube and Instagram has fizzled. She’s scratched up just 22,000 followers on the latter, and a mere 6 subscribers on the former. For her big interview w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo cartel puts on show of strength with armored convoy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/el-chapos-cartel-puts-show-20860240</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vehicles were seen barreling into the village filled with armed cartel members</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Starts Sending Captured Foreign Fighters Home From Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-50372155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey says one US jihadist has been expelled, and several Europeans will follow shortly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews Egged in Brooklyn...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/11/10/hate-crime-anti-semitism-boro-park-jews-egged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another hate crime investigation is underway in Brooklyn. Once again, community leaders say Jewish people are being targeted in Borough Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Of Needles Wash Ashore Along Venice Beach...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/10/large-amount-of-needles-other-medical-supplies-appear-along-venice-beach-shoreline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities cordoned off an area of Venice Beach Sunday after a large amount of medical supplies appeared on the sand, including needles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER CEO comment about murdered journalist sparks backlash...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uber-ceo-dara-khosrowshahi-murdered-journalist-jamal-khashoggi-serious-mistake-boycott-uber-142945393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hashtag #BoycottUber began trending on Twitter (TWTR) Monday morning after CEO Dara Khosrowshahi called the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi “a serious mistake” during an interview with Axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland Criticizes NETFLIX After 'Terrible Mistake' on Holocaust...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-netflix-poland/poland-asks-netflix-to-make-changes-to-documentary-about-nazi-death-camp-guard-idUSKBN1XL1PI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish Prime Minister Mateusz Morawiecki has pressed Netflix, the U.S. streaming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast, cable news networks to preempt regular programming...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/469846-broadcast-cable-news-networks-to-preempt-regular-programming-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC, CBS, NBC and PBS on Wednesday will preempt their regularly scheduled programming for live coverage of the House Intelligence Committee's open impeachment hearings of President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment week: Probe hits crucial point...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/469822-impeachment-week-trump-probe-hits-crucial-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It all comes down to this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American robots lose jobs to Asian robots as ADIDAS shifts manufacturing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/11/american-robots-lose-jobs-to-asian-robots-as-adidas-shifts-manufacturing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adidas plans to close high-tech “robot” factories in Germany and the United States it launched to bring production closer to customers, saying on Monday deploying some of the technology in Asia wou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FARAGE STANDS DOWN; LIFTS BORIS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uks-farage-withdraws-brexit-threat-pm-johnson-135343952.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Populist Brexit Party leader Nigel Farage on Monday withdrew his threat to challenge the governing Conservatives at every seat in next month's election, in a boost for Prime Minister Boris Johnson. Farage, a leading force behind the 2016 referendum vote to leave the European Union, had faced criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Millions, It Feels Like Economic Depression...</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/for-millions-of-americans-in-the-middle-of-the-country-it-feels-like-an-economic-depression-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you do when you have lost all hope that things will ever turn around?  It may still feel like "the economy is booming" for those at the top end of the economic food</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tiger next door: America's backyard big cats...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global/2019/nov/10/the-tiger-next-door-americas-backyard-big-cats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more tigers in American gardens than there are left in the wild. Alex Hannaford meets the owners who live cheek by jowl with their pets, and also those ensuring the big cats are treated without cruelty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The West's left-right battle lines run through Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-West-s-left-right-battle-lines-run-through-14825130.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They did not jail a man," declared the released prisoner. "They tried to kill an idea, and ideas don't disappear."  The freed man was Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, the former left-wing Brazilian president who was jailed last year on corruption charges that his supporters believe were politically motivated. Lula left office in 2010 with a staggering 80 percent approval rating and was favored to be on course to return to power in 2018; his imprisonment paved the path to the presidency for far-right firebrand Jair Bolsonaro, who, both on the campaign trail and now in office, has loudly banged the drum against perceived perfidy and tyranny of leftist dogma.  But last week, Brazil's Supreme Court ruled that Lula, as well dozens of others ensnared in a rolling corruption probe that reshaped Brazilian politics, had been unjustly jailed without receiving due process - that is, they had been denied the ability to exhaust their right to appeal their sentences before imprisonment. On Friday, Lula walked out of jail and was greeted by a throng of supporters from his left-leaning Workers' Party.  "You have no idea of the meaning of me being here with you," he said soon after his release in the southern city of Curitiba. "I, who have been speaking to the Brazilian people through all my life, did not think that I would be able to speak today . . . Every day you were the democracy's fuel I needed to exist."  From thousands of miles to the north came a striking message of support. Democratic presidential candidate Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., tweeted his admiration for Lula's socially minded policies and decried his imprisonment. "I am delighted that he has been released from jail, something that never should have happened in the first place," Sanders said. Lula thanked the U.S. candidate for his "solidarity," and expressed his "hope"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigar-shaped UFO now over Kansas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/cigar-shaped-ufo-appears-plane-20847849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some believed the UFO was following the plane and the shape of the "craft" mirrored others that have been spotted above the US this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOPPING: Bezos buying NFL team?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/amazon-founder-jeff-bezos-interested-in-owning-nfl-team-has-strong-support-among-current-owners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of Amazon and the Washington Post could be the next person to join the NFL's ownership ranks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a sin': Cambodia's brutal and shadowy dog meat trade...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sin-cambodias-brutal-shadowy-dog-meat-trade-065939849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cambodian dog meat traders drown, strangle and stab thousands of canines a day in a shadowy but sprawling business that traumatises workers and exposes them to deadly health risks like rabies. Khieu Chan bursts into tears when describing a job that haunts him as he goes to sleep: he kills up to six</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After push from Perry, backers got huge gas deal in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d8ae551fb884371a2a592ed85a74426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Two political supporters of U.S. Energy Secretary Rick Perry secured a potentially lucrative oil and gas exploration deal from the Ukrainian government soon after Perry...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
