<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Al Capone's granddaughters selling his possessions, fearing wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/mobster-al-capone-s-granddaughters-are-selling-his-possessions-partly-out-of-fear-of-wildfires/ar-AANKihu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The women feared that a wildfire could threaten their Northern California homes and destroy the 174 family photographs and knickknacks they say show a warmer side to the infamous mob boss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bennett-Biden meeting delayed due to Kabul attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/kabul-bombing-currently-not-affecting-bennett-biden-meeting-report-677799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennett is in Washington on his first visit since becoming prime minister in June and was expected to meet Biden this afternoon at 6 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,811 recovered Israeli patients got reinfected...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/4811-recovered-israeli-covid-patients-got-reinfected-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women warned to stay home...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3545871/taliban-tell-women-to-stay-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Taliban has warned women not to go out to work as militants now ruling the streets need “equality training” to know how to speak to them. The jihadi militants have already promised …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters cover Buckingham Palace fountain in BLOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3545151/extinction-rebellion-activists-cover-buckingham-palace-fountain-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACTIVISTS linked to Extinction Rebellion have covered a Buckingham Palace fountain in fake blood in a protest against the Queen and the royal family. Shameless eco-warriors clutching signs reading …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Diana biopic drops trailer......</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3539354/spencer-movie-trailer-kristen-stewart-princess-diana-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KRISTEN Stewart’s fans are blown away by the stunning new teaser trailer and poster for the actress’ upcoming Princess Diana movie, Spencer. The 31-year-old transformed into the late royal in the n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Mad-Dough: Is MSNBC Host Worth $30 Million Year Without Nightly Show?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/rachel-maddow-msnbc-30-million-deal-worth-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry insiders say MSNBC is taking a "gamble," but agree the star primetime host is worth the network's money</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TASTY BONE AT CITY'S POPULAR DOG PARK WAS HUMAN, COPS SAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article253756298.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They didn’t say if a dog found it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Cook Poised to Get $750 Million Payout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/apple-ceo-poised-to-get-24750-million-final-payout-from-award/ar-AANLP9h?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Cook, Apple Inc.’s chief executive officer, will this week collect the 10th and final tranche of the pay deal he received a decade ago after he took over the top job from co-founder Steve Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who was hospitalized with virus comes home to find infected husband dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/florida-woman-hospitalized-with-covid-19-comes-home-to-find-husband-dead-of-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Central Florida woman fought for her life in the hospital, survived, and thought she'd seen the worst of COVID -- until she went home and made a shocking discovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Natural immunity superior to Covid vaccine?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/bombshell-study-finds-natural-immunity-superior-to-vaccination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major study conducted by Israeli researchers into natural immunity has found that immunity acquired via infection from Covid-19 is superior to immunity from the Pfizer vaccine. Researchers at Maccabi Healthcare and Tel Aviv University compared the outcomes of over 76,000 Israelis in three groups: the doubly vaccinated (with the Pfizer vaccine), the previously infected [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder Rise Has Own Party Uneasy...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/larry-elders-california-recall-rise-has-even-republicans-uneasy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODELS..</title>
      <link>https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/storminfo/09L_tracks_latest.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tropicaltidbits.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/refresh/AL092021_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/144701_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Major hurricane threat developing for US Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/major-hurricane-ida-threat-gulf-coast-louisiana-alabama-texas-mississippi/1006485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters say the likelihood is increasing that a storm -- still only a depression as of Thursday morning -- could rapidly develop into a Category 3 hurricane and threaten the U.S. in a matter of days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN:  APPLE PRIVACY DISASTER...</title>
      <link>https://edwardsnowden.substack.com/p/all-seeing-i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edwardsnowden.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Under His Eye,” she says. The right farewell. “Under His Eye,” I reply, and she gives a little nod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW SULLIVAN</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To see what is in front of one's nose needs a constant struggle," - Orwell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Storm Threatens to Roil Gulf, Hit Texas or Louisiana...</title>
      <link>https://www.kxan.com/weather/weather-blog/first-warning-tropical-system-may-develop-in-gulf-of-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it develops into a tropical storm, it would be named Ida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder Rise Has Own Party Uneasy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-26/larry-elder-s-california-recall-rise-has-even-republicans-uneasy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular conservative radio talk show host’s entry into California’s gubernatorial recall race has upended predictions for the outcome as both Democrats and some Republicans now work to defeat him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows militants taking joyride in Black Hawk helicopter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/26/taliban-appear-to-take-joyride-in-us-made-helicopter-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It remains unclear exactly how many former Afghan military aircraft are under Taliban control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Nearly Collides With Plane At Logan Airport...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/08/25/iteam-drone-plane-near-collision-nahant-beach-logan-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A near-collision between a plane and drone near Logan Airport put the Massachusetts State Police Air Wing on alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery jellyfish-shaped object filmed entering atmosphere...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3544462/mystery-jellyfish-shaped-object-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS “jellyfish-shaped object” which suddenly appeared in the Earth’s atmosphere has stunned local Russians.   Residents in the Amur Oblast region spotted the glowing object flying overhead…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Cook Poised to Get $750 Million Payout...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/apple-ceo-poised-to-get-750-million-final-payout-from-big-award</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook will this week collect the 10th and final tranche of the pay deal he received a decade ago after he took over from Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unbearable Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/08/summer-2021-climate-change-records/619887/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disastrous environmental events are converging like never before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXEL SPRINGER to buy POLITICO in deal reportedly worth $1 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/26/axel-springer-to-buy-politico.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acquisition grows the publishing group's portfolio further, adding to its ownership of Insider and Morning Brew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Hospitalizations Pass 100,000 First Time Since Jan...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/569493-us-breaks-100k-covid-19-hospitalizations-threshold-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States now has more than 100,000 people hospitalized with coronavirus across the country for the first time since January, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bennett meets Biden as tensions grow...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-israel-iran-nuclear-55aa75ef1b43ec09165391c533f5b5f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden and Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett are set to hold their first face-to-face meeting Thursday, and Israel's new leader intends to press Biden to give up pursuit of reviving the Iran nuclear deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny says he is forced to watch eight hours of state TV a day...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/26/alexei-navalny-russia-prison-state-tv-china-labour-camp-psychological-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian opposition leader tells of brainwashing and propaganda in jail but remains optimistic Putin regime will end ‘sooner or later’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland gunfight fuels alarm over growing use of weapons at rallies...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/26/portland-proud-boys-rally-gunfight-protest-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right Proud Boys regularly carry handguns and other groups have adopted less lethal weapons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Results could ripple across nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/stakes-are-extremely-high-results-of-gavin-newsom-recall-could-ripple-across-nation/ar-AANJU67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – California voters are deciding now if Gov. Gavin Newsom gets to keep his job. Their verdict could reverberate far beyond the state. Top officials from both parties are preparing to parse the results of next month’s unexpectedly competitive recall election for what it means for next year’s midterm election, control of the U.S. Senate, and a Democratic Party that once thought it had ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Considers Paying Drug Addicts To Stay Sober...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/08/25/ca-pay-drug-addicts-to-be-sober/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustrated by out-of-control increases in drug overdose deaths, California's leaders are trying something radical: They want the state to be the first to pay people to stay sober.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maggie Haberman and the never-ending Trump story...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/media/maggie-haberman-trump/2021/08/25/87374bbe-efbe-11eb-81d2-ffae0f931b8f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How one New York Times reporter found herself turned into a major character in Donald Trump’s political drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror threats hamper evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/26/politics/president-joe-biden-afghan-refugees-donald-trump-immigration/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grave and specific ISIS terror threat is hanging over the frantic endgame of the US withdrawal from Afghanistan with time fast running out to rescue up to 1,500 Americans and the fate of fleeing Afghans looking darker by the hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the turbulent South Sea, US Navy bets on troubled warship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/25/asia/us-navy-littoral-combat-ships-pacific-south-china-sea-intl-hnk-ml-dst/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When US Vice President Kamala Harris stepped aboard the littoral combat ship USS Tulsa in Singapore on Monday, it put a fresh spotlight on arguably one of the most divisive vessels in the US Navy's fleet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC judges express frustration about possible leniency in riot cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dc-judges-express-frustration-about-possible-leniency-in-capitol-riot-cases/ar-AANLvk6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are pressuring defendants to explain their actions and express remorse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel, Germany's 'eternal' chancellor, prepares to leave stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210826-merkel-germany-s-eternal-chancellor-prepares-to-leave-the-stage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel, Germany's 'eternal' chancellor, prepares to leave the stage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could bats hold secret to healthy aging?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210826-could-bats-hold-the-secret-to-healthy-ageing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could bats hold the secret to healthy ageing?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFTs Supplant Rolexes and Lambos as New Digital Savvy 'Flex'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/nfts-supplant-rolexes-and-lambos-as-the-new-digital-savvy-flex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFTs Supplant Rolexes and Lambos as the New Digital Savvy ‘Flex’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deflecting Asteroid Before Hits Earth May Take Multiple Bumps...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/25/deflecting-an-asteroid-before-it-hits-earth-may-take-multiple-bumps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s probably a large space rock out there, somewhere, that has Earth in its cross hairs. Scientists have in fact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 remain as clock ticking... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-evacuations-kabul-f9321f143fd8749c1cc8c460b647fdd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Secretary of State Antony Blinken said as many as 1,500 Americans may be awaiting evacuation from Afghanistan, a figure that suggests the U.S. may accomplish its highest priority for the Kabul airlift — rescuing U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Kilauea volcano set to erupt?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-hawaii-kilauea-science--616e524340569b2d7140d9ec793e622a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — The ground at the summit of Kilauea volcano in Hawaii has been rumbling and swelling in recent days, prompting scientists to warn that the mountain could once again disgorge lava. But there's no indication an eruption is imminent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Chief Chaplain at HARVARD? An Atheist...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/26/the-new-chief-chaplain-at-harvard-an-atheist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Puritan colonists who settled in New England in the 1630s had a nagging concern about the churches they were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Remote American Outpost, Recovery Is Faraway Dream...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/25/in-this-remote-american-outpost-pandemic-recovery-is-a-faraway-dream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMUNING, Guam — Perched steps away from the prismatic seas off Guam’s western shore, a water sports shop sat shuttered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds expand use of facial recognition despite growing concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/federal-government-to-expand-use-of-facial-recognition-despite-growing-concerns/ar-AANKdmh?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten federal agencies, from the departments of Agriculture to Veterans Affairs, said they intended to grow their face-scanning capabilities by 2023. One watchdog official said, “Even with all the privacy issues and accuracy problems, the government is pretty much saying, ‘Damn the torpedoes, full speed ahead.'"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Afghan Christians turned away at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/248773/1200-christians-airlift-afghanistan-taliban-glenn-beck-nazarene-fund</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholicnewsagency.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looming over the deepening humanitarian crisis is a deadline of Friday for civilian evacuation operations at the Kabul airport to give way to the transport of the remaining 5,400 U.S. military personnel in the country in order to meet a target date of Aug. 31, set months ago by the Biden administration, for a complete U.S. withdraw from Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept warns Americans to leave!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/state-department-warns-us-citizens-leave-gates-kabul-airport-immediately-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department warned U.S. citizens at the gates outside of the airport in Kabul to leave "immediately" due to threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU  Reimposing Travel Restrictions on Americans?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsmax.com/finance/streettalk/eu-european-union-european-centre-for-disease-prevention-and-control-covid-19/2021/08/25/id/1033710/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union will discuss on Thursday whether to reintroduce travel restrictions on visitors from the U.S. as new coronavirus cases soar.Slovenia, which holds the rotating presidency of the EU and is currently responsible for triggering an assessment of countries that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Bosses Scale Back Hopes for September Office Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/manhattan-bosses-scale-back-hopes-for-september-office-return/ar-AANKkaK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan bosses have lowered their expectations for a return-to-office next month with cases of Covid-19’s delta variant on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel accelerating plans to take action against Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-news/chief-of-staff-kohavi-idf-accelerating-operational-plans-against-iran-677680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The recently approved budget is earmarked for that," said Kohavi as Israel makes a concerted effort to push Washington to pressure Tehran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britons turn critical of government's pandemic response...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825230102-990e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-POLLS:Britons turn critical of government's pandemic response</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee demands Trump White House records...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825173112-8yk1d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CAPITOL/SECURITY (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. House Jan. 6 committee demands Trump White House records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden receives inconclusive intelligence report on covid origins...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-receives-inconclusive-intelligence-report-on-covid-origins/ar-AANHRNz?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The intelligence community will seek within days to declassify elements of the report for potential public release, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  Vaccine Efficacy Diminishes to 66%...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/vaccine-efficacy-diminished-as-delta-arose-cdc-report-shows/ar-AANGSlO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effectiveness of Covid-19 vaccines among front-line workers declined to 66% after the delta variant became dominant, compared with 91% before it arose, according to a report from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gets jail time for walking on Yellowstone geyser...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article253745818.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s better than spending time in a hospital’s burn unit.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA will charge unvaccinated employees $200 per month...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/25/delta-air-lines-unvaccinated-employees-will-face-200-fees-if-they-dont-get-covid-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta is the latest company to issue new rules for employee vaccinations, but stopped short of an outright mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan withdraws 1.6 mln MODERNA doses over contamination...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210825201352-imk9j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN-MODERNA (PIX):Japan withdraws 1.6 mln Moderna COVID-19 vaccine doses over contamination - Nikkei</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ron Jeremy indicted on more than 30 new charges including rape, sexual battery...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/porn-ron-jeremy-rape-indictment-la-district-attorney-george-gascon-harvey-weinstein-1234822009/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Behind bars for over a year, Ron Jeremy was in court again Wednesday to now face the hard justice of a grand jury. Superseding the previous criminal charges compliant, the former porn star has now …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crews struggle to stop fire bearing down on Lake Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-environment-and-nature-lakes-94f209e734d0e5647189a5b58cfa405b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH LAKE TAHOE, Calif. (AP) — A Northern California fire that gutted hundreds of homes advanced toward Lake Tahoe on Wednesday as thousands of firefighters tried to box in the flames and tourists who hoped to boat or swim were enveloped in a thick yellow haze of the nation's worst air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONES will unveil tour after Charlie Watts' death...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/25/rolling-stones-will-tour-us-next-month-after-charlie-watts-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s only rock ‘n’ roll, so the Rolling Stones will play on without drummer Charlie Watts — and you’ll like it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bennett meets Biden as tensions grow...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-israel-iran-nuclear-caa64123fc7f84bfdc446315fceabdf4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett's meeting with President Joe Biden comes in the midst of heightened tensions with its regional archenemy, Iran, and as Israel grapples with a gradual resurgence of hostilities on its southern border with the Gaza Strip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LED streetlights contribute to insect population declines...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210825-led-streetlights-contribute-to-insect-population-declines-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LED streetlights contribute to insect population declines: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Cholesterol 'Fuels Cancer Growth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/high-cholesterol-fuels-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cancer cells that gobble up cholesterol and live end up with a "superpower" that allows them to withstand stress and spread the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken blames citizens for not leaving earlier...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9926865/Up-1-500-Americans-including-23-California-students-stuck-Afghanistan-State-Dept-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are 1,500 Americans still desperate to leave Afghanistan, the State Department announced after numerous critics demanded the Biden administration make the number public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ron Jeremy indicted on more than 30 new charges including rape, sexual battery...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/ron-jeremy-sexual-assault-charges-los-angeles-county/10975087/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adult film star Ron Jeremy has been indicted on more than 30 sexual assault counts involving 21 victims dating back more than twenty years, the Los Angeles County DA's office announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI raids Detroit city hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2021/08/25/detroit-city-hall-raids-fbi-statement/5589949001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI Detroit Special Agent in Charge Timothy Waters issued statement after raid on Detroit city hall as well as several homes of city council members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA app backtracks Roger Stone ban after 'censorship' accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/08/25/jason-millers-right-wing-gettr-site-backtracks-on-roger-stone-ban-after-accused-of-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Gettr claims to have reversed the ban, a war of words is still raging over in TrumpWorld</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 citizens remain?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/25/politics/blinken-americans-afghanistan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Antony Blinken said Wednesday that there are approximately 1,500 people who may be Americans left in Afghanistan, adding that when evacuation operations began, there was a population of as many as 6,000 American citizens in the country who wanted to leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative hoaxers face $5M fine for election robocalls...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-elections-election-2020-260f8df2ed47fa17bf3e88d0a49e64f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Two conservative hoaxers face a record $5.1 million fine for allegedly making illegal robocalls to wireless phones without the owners' consent in the 2020 election. The Federal Communications Commission said Tuesday that the proposed fine for Jacob Wohl, Jack Burkman and Burkman's lobbying firm would be the largest ever for violating the Telephone Consumer Protection Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected jail inmates given drug that 'can cause serious harm'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ivermeticin-inmates-covid-19-arkansas-fda-warnings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FDA warns that the anti-parasite drug ivermectin shouldn't be used for COVID-19 and can be harmful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo bans woman who said she had 'affair' with chimpanzee...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/belgian-zoo-banned-woman-said-023651564.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Antwerp Zoo said that the interactions between the woman and Chita the chimpanzee resulted in the chimp being ostracized by other primates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy assassin seeks parole -- with no opposition from prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/sirhan-sirhan-convicted-of-robert-f-kennedy-assassination-seeks-parole-with-no-opposition-from-prosecutors/ar-AANJS2S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now 77, the convicted killer of RFK is seeking release on grounds that he is no longer a threat, and that the stature of his victim should not be a consideration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,100 citizens remain?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/afghanistan-news-taliban-refugees-08-25-21/h_15b040da4bb2c75f448fb648b1717867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one week after the Taliban takeover of Kabul, the situation at the capital's airport has become increasingly desperate as thousands still wait to depart the country. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Known Software Can Trigger Revocation of Citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/08/25/atlas-citizenship-denaturalization-homeland-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known as ATLAS, the software mines various federal databases for derogatory information. It runs autonomously on Amazon servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NY gov. adds 12,000 deaths to tally...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/ny-nursing-home-deaths-kathy-hochul-andrew-cuomo-delta-variant/10974447/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York now reports nearly 55,400 people have died of COVID-19 in New York based on death certificate data submitted to the CDC, up from about 43,400 that Gov. Cuomo had reported to the public as of Monday, his last day in office.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
